<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Writers</who><category><shortname>literature-writing</shortname><id>18</id><name>literature/writing</name></category><description>Writers Anonymous is a social writers support group in Boston. It’s been such a rewarding experience. I originally got the idea for this group while I was living in Manhattan. While in NY I hung out with quite a few graduates from NYU, Northeastern, and Columbia who had started a similar writer’s support group, in which they (the original members) all pledged to write something ambitious/monumental and potentially life changing, their first novel. The good news is most did finish.

The main purpose of the NY writers support group wasn’t to have their work critiqued. Instead, it was about keeping each other going/on track holding each other accountable to the writer’s own self-imposed but ambitious goals. Further, it was about being inspired by your peers and about helping to inspire others to find their own voice. It was about connecting with people who have a similar passion in life and who may understand you better because they have the same burning desire inside to tell a story. It was also about forging new friendships and a supportive/encouraging environment during the often lonely and difficult creative writing process. 

Want to write/create something worthwhile?</description><rating>4.88</rating><join_mode>approval</join_mode><created>1229122587000</created><lat>42.3499984741</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>498</id><urlkey>singles</urlkey><name>Singles</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>772</id><urlkey>writers</urlkey><name>Writers</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2767</id><urlkey>bookclub</urlkey><name>Book Club</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4422</id><urlkey>socialnetwork</urlkey><name>Social Networking</name></topics_item></topics><name>Writers Anonymous (Not your typical writers group) Weekly</name><id>1337150</id><members>14</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>8251672</member_id><name>Michael </name></organizer><urlname>Anonymous-Writers-Wanted</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/c/a/600_6726346.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/c/a/highres_6726346.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>6726346</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/c/a/thumb_6726346.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Anonymous-Writers-Wanted/</link><lon>-71.0599975586</lon></item>