<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Paddlers</who><category><shortname>outdoors-adventure</shortname><id>23</id><name>outdoors/adventure</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Meet other local kayakers and those interested in paddling. Beginners welcome, focus is on easier trips - there are many beautiful ponds, lakes and slow rivers in central mass to explore!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***PLEASE NOTE*** The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do ask that everyone wears a PFD at all times on the water, regardless of the time of year.  Also in accordance with local and national boating regulations, whistles are required on all trips and lights (a flashlight is sufficient) are required on late afternoon/evening paddles.  We have on occasion been checked by environmental police at the launch for these items, better to be prepared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is highly recommended that each person participating in an event bring a spare set of clothes in a waterproof bag, as well as water, snack, sunscreen and insect repellent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most trips, on-site rentals are not available. If you need a rental, you can get one at EMS, REI, Great Canadian Canoe or New England Backpacker. They will provide what you need to put the kayak on your car, you do not need a roof rack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trip cancellations will be e-mailed and posting removed at least two hours before trip start time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also ask that you do not bring dogs on group trips unless the trip is designated as a "bring your dog" paddle.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.83</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1179536379000</created><lat>42.3100013733</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>590</id><urlkey>kayaking</urlkey><name>Kayaking</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>726</id><urlkey>paddling</urlkey><name>Paddling</name></topics_item></topics><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name><id>505356</id><members>534</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>4219141</member_id><name>Christine</name></organizer><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/3/8/600_171278712.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/3/8/highres_171278712.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>171278712</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/3/8/thumb_171278712.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Worcester</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/</link><lon>-71.8000030518</lon></item>