<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Singers</who><category><shortname>music</shortname><id>21</id><name>music</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve always wanted to get up and sing in public. But you say, “My voice stinks! I can’t sing! I can’t get up in front of a group and do that!” In Nigeria they say, “If you can talk, you can sing.” Singing in public -- is not about being Sinatra, Streisand, Springsteen, or Stefani. -- is not about “going to Hollywood/Vegas/the next round” so that you can be exploited or disappointed. Singing in public is about letting go and enjoying expressing yourself. SingFree Sessions™ are a path to that growth that will push your envelope in a completely fun way. It is practice and insight on all levels (based on Carolyn Sloan's "Finding Your Voice") that encourage you to shatter the barriers to public self-presentation. We uphold the values of metta (fellowship) and mudita (joy in another's success). No contests! Have fun as you: • Learn to use your breath the right way. • Find, exercise, and use your voice. (Yes, even yours.) • Pick a song to sing. • Sing out and express yourself! There are no pre-requisites, except a desire to sing. Every session is the “first session”. About Scott: • Ed. M., Harvard Graduate School of Education. • Sang 8 years with a prominent Boston chorus, including performances with the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra. • Religious Leader, United Brothers Synagogue, Bristol, RI • Teacher of leaders of Jewish prayer • Ordained Minister, Church of Spiritual Humanism. • Student of karate-do, tai chi chu’an, and Kabbalah. • Taught hundreds of new technology users as a software trainer. • Non-judgmental, supportive, and encouraging instructor and coach. Join the group, and you'll easily find out about upcoming public SingFree Sessions. You can also arrange SingFree Sessions for private groups and corporate events. We look forward to seeing and hearing YOU! SingFree and SingFree Sessions are trademarks of Step 1 Ventures. All content ©2009 Step 1 Ventures&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>5.0</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1250015351000</created><lat>42.4000015259</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1193</id><urlkey>karaoke</urlkey><name>Karaoke</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>8649</id><urlkey>personalgrowth</urlkey><name>Personal Growth</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17301</id><urlkey>singers</urlkey><name>Singers</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>38464</id><urlkey>singing-events</urlkey><name>Singing Events</name></topics_item></topics><name>SingFree™ Sessions</name><id>1504731</id><members>119</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>8548447</member_id><name>Shihan Scott A.</name></organizer><urlname>SingFree-Sessions</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/6/f/4/600_138210452.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/6/f/4/highres_138210452.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>138210452</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/6/f/4/thumb_138210452.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Waltham</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/SingFree-Sessions/</link><lon>-71.2600021362</lon></item>