<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Men</who><category><shortname>health-wellbeing</shortname><id>14</id><name>health/wellbeing</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;To be the man you want to be takes diligence and the support of a community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;It's time to Man Up. Time to get honest with yourself. Time to quit bullshitting your way through the world and start living with some emotional integrity. Time to take a risk and do something good for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are men that share experiences and wisdom to support self-awareness, positive change and transformation. We form a community of peers who take risks to improve our lives and help others. All kinds of men are involved. Non-religious and non-profit. Any man ready to follow some simple ground rules and take responsibility for himself is welcome. This group is facilitated and safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This work can have profound positive impacts on families, friendships and communities. Better health, more happiness, less anger, closer relationships with loved ones! Make the change you've been dreaming of. Become more the man you want to be. Create trusting and open relationships with men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way we see it, the world really needs men who have the strength to get real with one another and work together as brothers. Go-it-alone, dominating, chest pounding, 'tough it up' or 'laugh it off' masculinity is a facade that often covers up the truly effective, powerful, compassionate, nurturing, mature man.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hosted and facilitated by men from the ManKind Project of New England. FIRST and THIRD Wednesday each month. www.openmen.org, www.mankindproject.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.92</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1214509669000</created><lat>42.1199989319</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1544</id><urlkey>peace</urlkey><name>Peace</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3336</id><urlkey>self-improvement</urlkey><name>Self-Improvement</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>8649</id><urlkey>personalgrowth</urlkey><name>Personal Growth</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10261</id><urlkey>men</urlkey><name>Men's Social</name></topics_item></topics><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name><id>1200732</id><members>138</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7527796</member_id><name>Boysen </name></organizer><urlname>openmen</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/e/d/600_4591725.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/e/d/highres_4591725.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>4591725</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/e/d/thumb_4591725.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Springfield</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/</link><lon>-72.5500030518</lon></item>