<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Moms</who><category><shortname>parents-family</shortname><id>25</id><name>parents/family</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;With approximately 200 members, the MetroWest Boston chapter of Mothers &amp;amp; More is one of the largest in the country. Our members come from towns all over MetroWest, including (but not limited to) Framingham, Natick, Ashland, Hopkinton, Southboro, Sudbury, Wayland, and Wellesley. Our children range in age from newborns to teenagers, and we have a good mix of members who are caring for children full time, working full-time for pay, and everywhere in between.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to this large network of mothers, we offer a wide range of activities including monthly discussion meetings, moms&amp;rsquo; nights out, children's activities, a book group, community service projects, playgroups, and much more. There is something for everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mothers &amp;amp; More:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Mothers &amp;amp; More is a national non-profit organization dedicated to improving the lives of mothers through support, education and advocacy. We address mothers&amp;rsquo; needs as individuals and members of society, and promote the value of all the work mothers do. Our mission is based on the following core beliefs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A mother is more than any single role she plays at any given point in her lifetime. She is entitled to fully explore and develop her identity as she chooses: as a woman, a citizen, a parent or an employee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the work mothers do &amp;ndash; whether paid or unpaid - has social and economic value.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All women deserve recognition and support for their right to choose if and how to combine parenting and paid employment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All mothers, all children and all families are unique. We respect the wisdom of each mother to decide how to care for her children, her family and herself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mothers have the right to fulfill their caregiving responsibilities without incurring social and economic penalties. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The transitions women make into and through motherhood are challenging and can be difficult. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Together, mothers are powerful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
Check out our local site for even more information and consider coming to our next scheduled meetup! &lt;a href="http://www.metrowestmothersandmore.org"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.metrowestmothersandmore.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.metrowestmothersandmore.org" title="http://www.metrowestmothersandmore.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrowestmothersandmore.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><rating>4.77</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1221695075000</created><lat>42.3199996948</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>407</id><urlkey>moms</urlkey><name>Moms</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>458</id><urlkey>newparents</urlkey><name>New and Expecting Parents</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1348</id><urlkey>sahm</urlkey><name>Stay At Home Moms</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>9853</id><urlkey>playgroup</urlkey><name>Playgroup</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10232</id><urlkey>women</urlkey><name>Women's Social</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10333</id><urlkey>parents</urlkey><name>Parents</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10555</id><urlkey>workingmoms</urlkey><name>Working Moms</name></topics_item></topics><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name><id>1284421</id><members>659</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>38720692</member_id><name>Gwyneth Landry</name></organizer><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/4/a/600_8459978.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/4/a/highres_8459978.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>8459978</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/4/a/thumb_8459978.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Framingham</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/</link><lon>-71.4300003052</lon></item>