<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Members</who><category><shortname>arts-culture</shortname><id>1</id><name>fine arts/culture</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laughing Matter of Greater Boston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughing Matter is a community service nonprofit organization&amp;nbsp;that brings the therapeutic benefits of laughter and improvisational comedy to&amp;nbsp;individuals in places of care, including hospitals, homeless shelters&amp;nbsp;and senior centers.&amp;nbsp;This Meetup serves as the Auditions Circle for prospective Member Performers of the Greater Boston Chapter of Laughing Matter. Individuals can audition in one of two ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoListParagraphCxSpFirst"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;City-Wide Laughing Matter Audition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast"&gt;&lt;span&gt;City-wide auditions take place once every quarter throughout the year. These auditions, advertised through Meetup.com, posted flyers, and word-of-mouth enable allow interested persons from the general public to audition for membership in a Laughing Matter ensemble through a formalized audition process. &lt;em&gt;Evaluation Criteria&lt;/em&gt;: Invitees are evaluated for qualities which demonstrate commitment to service, satisfy established standards for the learning and practice of improv comedy, and suggest interpersonal fit within an ensemble. Based on the performance of one&amp;rsquo;s audition, the Managing Director and/or Executive Director may either extend an offer of induction, suggest further outside training with an option to re-audition, or decide against induction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;By invitation of a Rostered Performer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you are invited to a rehearsal by a rostered performer, you are eligible to audition for a place on a Laughing Matter ensemble.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Audition Requirements&lt;/em&gt;: Attendance at a minimum of 4 consecutive rehearsals. Absence at more than 2 consecutive rehearsals, since the date of one&amp;rsquo;s first rehearsal, will terminate one&amp;rsquo;s audition.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Evaluation Criteria&lt;/em&gt;: Invitees are evaluated for qualities which demonstrate commitment to service, satisfy established standards for the learning and practice of improv comedy, and suggest interpersonal fit within an ensemble. Upon successful satisfaction of the audition requirements, the Managing Director and/or Executive Director may either extend an offer of induction, suggest further outside training with an option to re-audition, or decide against induction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Further Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast"&gt;Please check back over the next few weeks for more information about the auditions process, as well as scheduled dates for City-Wide Laughing Matter Auditions. For any questions you may have about auditioning, or about Laughing Matter in general, please contact Harish at harish@laughingmatter.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.9</rating><join_mode>closed</join_mode><created>1234931712000</created><lat>42.3499984741</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1001</id><urlkey>comedy</urlkey><name>Comedy</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1459</id><urlkey>theater</urlkey><name>Theater &amp; Performance Art</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>6922</id><urlkey>improvart</urlkey><name>Improv Art</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16645</id><urlkey>volunteering</urlkey><name>Volunteering</name></topics_item></topics><name>Great Boston Chapter of Laughing Matter - Auditions Circle</name><id>1386175</id><members>77</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>8057923</member_id><name>Hari</name></organizer><urlname>laughingmatter</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/0/d/600_35994541.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/0/d/highres_35994541.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>35994541</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/0/d/thumb_35994541.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/laughingmatter/</link><lon>-71.0699996948</lon></item>