<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Writers</who><category><shortname>literature-writing</shortname><id>18</id><name>literature/writing</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;**As of mid-February, 2013, we are closing to new members temporarily. The group has grown exponentially in the last two years and meetups are constantly full, so we're attempting to restructure to make it work better. Please check back if you are interested, and sorry for the inconvenience!**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Love writing? Looking for an opportunity to creep inside your mind, find the little demon inside fast asleep at an old writing desk, and tickle him awake with a quill pen? Or perhaps you think electro shock therapy would work better? Perchance this is the meetup for you! Meet other local writers and let creativity bloom! Come to a Writers' Meetup to review work, trade literary tips, make friends and have fun! All writers are welcome! We meet every week, alternating a workshop meetup with a writing exercise meetup: * All pieces for the workshop meetup will be uploaded under the Files section, so be sure to check them out and be ready to offer constructive criticism (and of course praise) for our writers. * If you are interested in posting something for an upcoming workshop meetup, please send me an email so I can let everyone know what they should be looking for to read. * I am always looking for fun ideas for the writing exercise meetup, so anyone is welcome to bring along ideas or post them on the Message Board!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.43</rating><join_mode>closed</join_mode><created>1223947125000</created><lat>42.3800010681</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>567</id><urlkey>screenwriters</urlkey><name>Screenwriters</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>772</id><urlkey>writers</urlkey><name>Writers</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10352</id><urlkey>wam</urlkey><name>Writers, Artists &amp; Musicians</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Writers' Meetup</name><id>1300976</id><members>418</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7904632</member_id><name>Kate E.</name></organizer><urlname>bostonwriters</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/d/3/600_5878579.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/d/3/highres_5878579.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>5878579</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/d/3/thumb_5878579.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Cambridge</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/bostonwriters/</link><lon>-71.1299972534</lon></item>