<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Patriots</who><category><shortname>government-politics</shortname><id>13</id><name>movements/politics</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in coordinating this event and/or already are coordinating it via another site such as Facebook please contact me and I will make you a MeetUp organizer immediately. Thanks! The Boston Tea Party was an act of direct protest by American Colonists demanding representation in the British Government. They became known as the original patriots. The New Boston Tea Party of 2009 and Tea Parties all across America will reinvigorate that American and Patriotic spirit; one that demands respect for individual rights and property. As the bailouts spiral out of control, we are forced to fund failed banks. With foreclosures on the rise, we are made the collateral of reckless spending. And, when the bills come due, the IRS knocks on the door of “self-responsibility”. ENOUGH! America is the land of opportunity. To succeed AND to Fail. Without consequences, what is our incentive to learn? What is our incentive to produce? On July 4, 2009, those that ask nothing from the government but the protection of our inalienable right to succeed, will gather in many cities across this great nation in an historic act of direct protest.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.58</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1236733029000</created><lat>42.3600006104</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>95</id><urlkey>republican</urlkey><name>Republican Party</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>99</id><urlkey>libertarian</urlkey><name>Libertarian</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4377</id><urlkey>politics</urlkey><name>Politics &amp; Activism</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>8867</id><urlkey>localpolitics</urlkey><name>Local Politics</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Tea Party</name><id>1404985</id><members>571</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>10170370</member_id><name>Christine Morabito</name></organizer><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/b/6/600_135223702.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/b/6/highres_135223702.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>135223702</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/b/6/thumb_135223702.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/</link><lon>-71.0699996948</lon></item>