<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Creative People</who><category><shortname>photography</shortname><id>27</id><name>photography</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Boston Creative People! This group is for painters, photographers, sculptors, horticulturalists, graphic artists and designers of all kinds whose world revolves around their creative passions and are looking to share that passion with other creative people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members are encouraged to upload and share their art, open their studios, minds, and hearts to other members. Meetups are focused around creative activities, such as abstract photo rambles, garden tours, musical jams, museum romps, tactile sculpture excursions, members open houses, demonstrations, portfolio "show and tell" and the like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What people are saying about Creative Peoples.. “Everyone is is friendly and some had brought their work to share, which was great and isn't required. A fun group, I can see this group getting bigger soon!” “Great group of people. I especially enjoyed viewing everyone's work.” “A wonderful group of people - this was my first time at a meetup - and great to compare notes on various artistic endeavors. The event was well-organized. ” “Nice mix of people- everyone was friendly, outgoing and encouraging.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This season's Creative Peoples banner &amp;amp; logo stylized by: Angelina, based on Boston photos by Domenico.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.77</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1199386407000</created><lat>42.3800010681</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>223</id><urlkey>photo</urlkey><name>Photography</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>708</id><urlkey>foundart</urlkey><name>Found Art</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>781</id><urlkey>graphicdesign</urlkey><name>Graphic Design</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>8687</id><urlkey>arttherapy</urlkey><name>Art Therapy</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Creative People</name><id>919281</id><members>397</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>9296355</member_id><name>Domenico</name></organizer><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/3/2/600_238296402.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/3/2/highres_238296402.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>238296402</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/3/2/thumb_238296402.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Cambridge</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/</link><lon>-71.1299972534</lon></item>