<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Magnificent Manifestors</who><category><shortname>new-age-spirituality</shortname><id>22</id><name>new age/spirituality</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;We are a group of individuals who believe and practice the teachings of Abraham and Law of Attraction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you want ---- Abundance, Prosperity, Joy, Peace, Health, Fun, Loving Relationships?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meetup is for like-minded positive individuals practicing and applying principles of The Law of Attraction. We are a suppportive collaboration of amazingly, brilliant, innovative mastermind individuals who desire to share and understand how to manifest and deliberately create anything we want using proven techniques. Lots of info and give-aways!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole is a law of attraction life coach and will guide you through the different easy processes that will help shift your thinking, and empower you to attract and co-create anything you want in your life. The universal law of attraction works with us or against us by default. Once we understand how our thoughts are literally energy and carry a vibration, we will be able to clearly see why we are getting and creating our experiences in our life. We work on attracting to us abundance/prosperity, freedom, health, careers, dreams, relationships, whatever you choose for you. For once and for all, we let go of the past thinking and we stop re-creating it in the moment(our point of attraction). &lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;The understanding of these principles will show you the power you have inside of yourself to take hold of your own thoughts and create a new reality based on joy, love, peace and whatever you desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how to get into the vortex of well-being! We will go over "feeling" our way into the vortex. The discussion will be positive, fun, exciting and healing on many levels. Nicole uses many techniques, stories, experiences, skills, talents and deep inner wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a dream and vision for an amazing future and live it! We will work on Belief. Ask, Believe and Receive! Inspire to see and manifest a delicious and amazingly wonderful life!&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.75</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1257527726000</created><lat>41.6800003052</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>2756</id><urlkey>abrahamhicks</urlkey><name>Abraham Hicks</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3382</id><urlkey>lawofattraction</urlkey><name>Law of Attraction</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10290</id><urlkey>spirituality</urlkey><name>Spirituality</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15942</id><urlkey>abundance-and-prosperity</urlkey><name>Abundance And Prosperity</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17449</id><urlkey>manifestation</urlkey><name>Manifestation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>21136</id><urlkey>spirituality-personal-growth-meditation</urlkey><name>Spirituality, Personal Growth, Meditation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>34042</id><urlkey>in-the-vortex</urlkey><name>In the Vortex</name></topics_item></topics><name>South Shore Law of Attraction  Manifestors</name><id>1552727</id><members>229</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>8953582</member_id><name>Nicole</name></organizer><urlname>South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/d/3/600_19517363.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/d/3/highres_19517363.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>19517363</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/d/3/thumb_19517363.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><timezone>US/Eastern</timezone><city>Fall River</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors/</link><lon>-71.1800003052</lon></item>