<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Pug People</who><category><shortname>pets-animals</shortname><id>26</id><name>pets/animals</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Boston's grand, but let's go south! All those little (and big!) south of Boston Pugs are eager to open their fenced and shaded back yards for Puggie Sunday Socials. WE HAVE VIDEOS! Go to www.youtube.com and type "South of Boston Pug Meetup" into the search field to see them! We're a veritable South Shore (and beyond) melting pot! We have members from Abington, Assonet, Boston, Braintree, Bridgewater, Brockton, Carver, Duxbury, Easton, Halifax, Marion, Marshfield, Middleboro, Needham, New Bedford, North Easton, North Weymouth, Plainville, Pembroke, Plymouth, Portsmouth, South Weymouth, Southbridge, Taunton, Waltham, West Bridgewater, Weymouth, and even from Cranston, Lincoln, Pawtucket, and Tiverton, Rhode Island, and I'm only counting the folks that actually come to the meetups! This is not the time to be shy. Won't you join us? Your Pugs will thank you. Nobody parties like our Puggies! All Pugs are welcome, as are their well behaved non-Puggie canine family members, and of course all human family members are welcome as well. If you are already a member, have a fenced back yard, and want to host one of our Puggie Sunday Socials, just let one of the organizers know!&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.9</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1141585480000</created><lat>42.0800018311</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>591</id><urlkey>pug</urlkey><name>Pug</name></topics_item></topics><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name><id>226623</id><members>276</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>2129718</member_id><name>Charlotte Creeley</name></organizer><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/4/600_227521252.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/4/highres_227521252.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>227521252</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/4/thumb_227521252.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Brockton</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/</link><lon>-71.0</lon></item>