<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Organizers</who><category><shortname>socializing</shortname><id>31</id><name>socializing</name></category><description>Hello fellow Meetup Organizers &amp; Assistant Organizers who run or help run Meetups around the New England Area. I'd like this group be open to all Organizers &amp; Assistant Organizers so we can help each other to become more successful at running all of our Meetup groups. I know we are spread all over but it would nice to meet monthly in some common area like Waltham. 

Also, I encourage people to use the message boards to ask questions and to participate in lively discussions to better help us all! I wanted to thank Adam for saving the group and naming me for the Organizer spot. If you are interested in becoming organizer of this group please let me know! Thanks and enjoy.

New Note: The group is large and growing, but we are spread all over New England to make meeting in one spot practical. I think its best to use the message boards. We are all busy with work and life so lets make the best of what little free time we do have. Please check message boards often and see if you can help others and also post questions to the group too. Thanks</description><rating>4.35</rating><join_mode>approval</join_mode><created>1157755116000</created><lat>42.4000015259</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1044</id><urlkey>eventplanning</urlkey><name>Event Planning</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1787</id><urlkey>meetup</urlkey><name>Meetup</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4422</id><urlkey>socialnetwork</urlkey><name>Social Networking</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10328</id><urlkey>organizer</urlkey><name>Meetup Organizer</name></topics_item></topics><name>New England Meetup Organizers</name><id>321127</id><members>126</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>9052522</member_id><name>Herb Pearce</name></organizer><urlname>NEOrganizers</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/2/f/600_9957647.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/2/f/highres_9957647.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>9957647</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/2/f/thumb_9957647.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Waltham</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/NEOrganizers/</link><lon>-71.2600021362</lon></item>