<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Bostonians</who><category><shortname>education-learning</shortname><id>6</id><name>education/learning</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Come out and explore Boston's history, architecture and culture with a group of knowledgeable and passionate guides.   Boston By Foot is a non-profit organization that promotes the architecture and history of Boston and has been offering guided walking tours of Boston since 1976. Our meetup group is made up of Boston By Foot volunteers, Boston explorers, history buffs, and architecture aficionados who like the "off the beaten trail" walking tours offered by Boston By Foot. Learn more about Boston By Foot at www.bostonbyfoot.org.  Boston By Foot charges a price for their tours to keep the organization going but once in a while we get a freebie. A "card holder" price is also posted which applies to card-carrying Boston By Foot members. Joining this meetup group doesn't make you a Boston By Foot member, you need to do that through the Boston By Foot web site. The membership fees for an individual are about $50 per year (less if you are a student) . If you plan on attending more than a few, the membership is worth it. You can also arrange to sample one and apply your ticket fee to a membership following a tour.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.78</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1215434385000</created><lat>42.3600006104</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>933</id><urlkey>walkers</urlkey><name>Walking</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1737</id><urlkey>architecture</urlkey><name>Architecture</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1793</id><urlkey>amerhistory</urlkey><name>American History</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>7789</id><urlkey>history</urlkey><name>History</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>31254</id><urlkey>boston</urlkey><name>Boston</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name><id>1214263</id><members>858</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7593944</member_id><name>Justin Winsor</name></organizer><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/1/0/600_4708432.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/1/0/highres_4708432.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>4708432</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/1/0/thumb_4708432.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/</link><lon>-71.0699996948</lon></item>