<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>CT</state><who>CardBoard Players</who><category><shortname>games</shortname><id>11</id><name>games</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;My friend Nina created this group on February 23, 2009.  I joined on July 16, 2009, and became the organizer on July 4, 2012, when Nina stepped down due to an upcoming move to Florida.  Nina, we'll forever be in your debt for getting this group off the ground!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the beginning this group has been different than other Meetup Groups I belong to (and have belonged to).  How are we different?  Let me cover a few ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We usually meet in members homes.&lt;/strong&gt; Most Meetup groups that I'm aware of usually have big events in public places where dozens of people can attend.  That's a great way to meet lots of people, but not a great way to get to &lt;strong&gt;know&lt;/strong&gt; and become friends with them.  The Cardboard Players Club of Connecticut, however, encourages all members to consider hosting events in their own homes or apartments, even if space constraints mean only a few people can attend.  There are great games available that can accommodate &lt;strong&gt;any number&lt;/strong&gt; of game players.  If you can only have one other member join you, set up a chess meetup and make a new friend.  If you can have two people, try Settlers of Catan, which is an excellent game for three.  These are just examples, but the point is:  You shouldn't feel as though you can't host a Meetup just because your space is limited!  Meetup allows you to limit the number of attendees, and provides waiting lists and other settings that will allow you to successfully hold even a small Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We're a very friendly group.&lt;/strong&gt; I know, I know... everyone says it.  But if you attend a Meetup or two I think you'll agree:  The Cardboard Players Club of Connecticut is a very friendly, welcoming group.  Of course we regulars all have our friends in the group.  But we're always delighted to meet others who share our interest in games.  New members are the life blood of our group; bringing new games, new perspectives, and new opportunities for friendship.  Seriously, check it out.  And if you find your first meetup anything less than a great experience, please let me know about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we do in this group is limited only by YOUR imagination.&lt;/strong&gt; I don't set the agenda for this group.  All I ask is that events have some connection to either board or card games.  (That doesn't mean you can't have a BBQ and call it a Cardboard Players Club of Connecticut event -- just break out a game or two during the party!)  Aside from that, events can be set up to play anything you want.  &lt;strong&gt;In fact, I want to issue a challenge to all members:&lt;/strong&gt; If you're not currently finding that the Cardboard Players Club is not meeting your needs -- like maybe one of your favorite games isn't getting played -- step up and organize an event.  If you can't do it at your home or apartment, reach out to us and maybe the event can be held somewhere else.  All you have to do is drop me an email and I'll give you all the assistance you need to make it happen.  If you can't hold the event at your home, I'll help you find a different place.  If you want to play a game that you don't own, I'll help you find someone who does.  In short, I promise, you'll have a great time, and you'll be making a big contribution towards making the Cardboard Players Club of Connecticut an even better group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This group sustains itself through donations.&lt;/strong&gt; Some Meetup groups require an annual membership fee.  In this group, we just ask members who can to contribute $1 (this used to be called "Nina bucks"...  I guess in this era, we'll call it "Mitch money" if nobody objects) at each event they attend at a member's home to go toward Meetup fees.  And we ask members who host events in their home to at least mention the donation policy.  However, members should never feel compelled to donate (that's hardly a donation, is it?!).  But members, when they can, should be willing to share the relatively light burden of keeping this awesome group alive.  If you're short a buck one time, put in $2 next time.  Or not.  It's up to you.  The financial situation of the group is always totally transparent, and can be viewed by going to the "Group Tools" menu at the top of our Home page, and then clicking on "Money."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Conclusion,&lt;/strong&gt; I'm delighted to be the Organizer of this group.  I've always loved games, and I have made many great friends through this group.  I think Meetup.com in general, and The Cardboard Players Club of Connecticut in particular, is a great way to help us get off our couches and actually interact with other interesting and dynamic people.  I'm always open to suggestions from anyone who has an interest in making this group better.  Feel free to email or call me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the way, I'm actively interested in discussing sponsorship opportunities with local game stores or game developers.  Feel free to contact me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mitch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;numberslie@yahoo.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;860-372-3707&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.75</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1235413952000</created><lat>41.75</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>255</id><urlkey>cribbage</urlkey><name>Cribbage</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>495</id><urlkey>boardgames</urlkey><name>Boardgames</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>851</id><urlkey>spades</urlkey><name>Spades</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>954</id><urlkey>hearts</urlkey><name>Hearts</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>970</id><urlkey>settlers</urlkey><name>Settlers of Catan</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1373</id><urlkey>trivia</urlkey><name>Trivia</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>9792</id><urlkey>cardgame</urlkey><name>Card Games</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15992</id><urlkey>games</urlkey><name>Games</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16174</id><urlkey>fun-games-night</urlkey><name>Fun &amp; Games Night</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16425</id><urlkey>roleplaying-games-rpgs</urlkey><name>Roleplaying Games (RPGs)</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16814</id><urlkey>Euro-games</urlkey><name>Euro Games</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17785</id><urlkey>strategy-games</urlkey><name>Strategy Games</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>18071</id><urlkey>gaming</urlkey><name>Gaming</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>19585</id><urlkey>board-games</urlkey><name>Board Games</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>26369</id><urlkey>playing-cards-and-board-games</urlkey><name>Playing Cards and Board Games</name></topics_item></topics><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name><id>1390924</id><members>473</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>5111537</member_id><name>Margaret </name></organizer><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/2/c/600_137079212.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/2/c/highres_137079212.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>137079212</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/2/c/thumb_137079212.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Hartford</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/</link><lon>-72.6999969482</lon></item>