<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Members</who><category><shortname>new-age-spirituality</shortname><id>22</id><name>new age/spirituality</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Breathwork clears and purifies your body on a cellular level from past traumas, blocks and damage, declutters your mind, opens your heart, strenghtens your physical and spiritual core, allows you to love yourself and to love others. Breathwork is conductive in healing physical and psychological issues, it's indispensable for permanent healing of anxiety, mood swings and depression. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Breathwork is an excellent adjunct to every holisitc and spiritual practice, and to therapy. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Transformational Breathwork brings about profound and lasting experience of connecting with your own self and with the Source. It takes you on the deep inner journey, beginning with your recent experiences -- to the realms of your higher Self ,&amp;nbsp; from your recent to your more distant past. Breathwork is a conduit that connects you with your essence and life purpose. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Ruach HaKodesh, prana, lifeforce. Every ancient spiritual tradition refers to the healing power of Breath in the highest spiritual terms. Power that heals, force that connects us to our authentic selves and to Creator, conduit, Divine Inspiration that enlivens and envigorates our existence, and gives it meaning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Personally, I know no better way to enhance meditative states, to heighten spiritual experiences and to foster own advancement. Breathwork is essential tool for personal growth and transformation, self-healing, physical and psychological alignment with the higher levels of our soul. As such,  breathwork is immensely potent in changing our lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Breahtwork is conductive in physical, emotional and psychological healing. It renews your body, supports your healthy intentions and life habits, and empowers your life resolutions. It leads you towards completion and fulfillment in your life. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Breathwork liberates you from internal and external dependencies, and sets you free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;__________________________________________________________________________________________________&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Transformational Breathwork, Rebirthing, Conscious breathwork, Connected  breathwork, Energy breathwork all are&amp;nbsp; contemporary names for the  ancient breathing technique&amp;nbsp; -- an amazing gift that humans used  for self-healing, elevation, for achieving expanded states of consciousness and enlightement since times immemoria&lt;/span&gt;l.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.87</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1223769558000</created><lat>42.3699989319</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>243</id><urlkey>alternative</urlkey><name>Alternative Health</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>774</id><urlkey>metaphysics</urlkey><name>Metaphysics</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1322</id><urlkey>meditation</urlkey><name>Meditation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1948</id><urlkey>spiritualism</urlkey><name>Spiritualism</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2030</id><urlkey>energyhealers</urlkey><name>Energy Healers</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3336</id><urlkey>self-improvement</urlkey><name>Self-Improvement</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4417</id><urlkey>consciousness</urlkey><name>Consciousness</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>8702</id><urlkey>lifetransform</urlkey><name>Life Transformation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10290</id><urlkey>spirituality</urlkey><name>Spirituality</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16144</id><urlkey>self-empowerment-exploration</urlkey><name>Self Empowerment &amp; Exploration</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>21136</id><urlkey>spirituality-personal-growth-meditation</urlkey><name>Spirituality, Personal Growth, Meditation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>81130</id><urlkey>breathwork-meditation</urlkey><name>Breathwork Meditation</name></topics_item></topics><name>Breathwork</name><id>1299646</id><members>189</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7891623</member_id><name>Miriam </name></organizer><urlname>Breathwork</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/5/600_18900741.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/5/highres_18900741.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>18900741</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/5/thumb_18900741.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Watertown</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Breathwork/</link><lon>-71.1800003052</lon></item>