<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>trail seekers</who><category><shortname>pets-animals</shortname><id>26</id><name>pets/animals</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for the outdoor enthusiast who is looking for a more adventurous outing with their canine companion(s). We'll be exploring off-beaten paths, hiking trails, and mountains *all* over New England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you like to see an activity that is not posted here?  Have a favorite trail or peak?  Is there somewhere new that you want to explore?  Email the organizer!  This group intends to meet the needs of its members, so speak up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many meet-ups will include vigorous activity, while others will be less strenuous. Barring extreme weather conditions (after all, it is New England) meetups *will* be held rain, snow or shine unless the weather makes the chosen trail or activity treacherous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This group is for ALL dogs, and has now been designated a primarily "off-leash" group.  One leash per dog should always be brought for every outing.   &lt;br /&gt; On-leash dogs are of course more than welcome at all meetups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All activities are at your, and your dog's, own risk. You are responsible for your dog's actions and their well-being, so make it a priority to know if you and your dog's psychological and physical fitness levels are compatible with the chosen activity.  Please don't hesitate to contact the event organizer if you are unsure or need clarification regarding the event you want to attend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.0</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1230916808000</created><lat>42.2400016785</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>638</id><urlkey>hiking</urlkey><name>Hiking</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>9753</id><urlkey>offleash</urlkey><name>Off Leash Dog Recreation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>9772</id><urlkey>activedogs</urlkey><name>Active Dogs</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15046</id><urlkey>outdoors</urlkey><name>Outdoors</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15067</id><urlkey>dogs</urlkey><name>Dogs</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>53052</id><urlkey>pets-animals</urlkey><name>Pets &amp; Animals</name></topics_item></topics><name>New England Trail Dogs</name><id>1347727</id><members>404</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>9867606</member_id><name>Craig</name></organizer><urlname>NE-Trail-Dogs</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/d/c/600_14540188.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/d/c/highres_14540188.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>14540188</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/d/c/thumb_14540188.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Quincy</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/NE-Trail-Dogs/</link><lon>-71.0100021362</lon></item>