<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Very Smart People</who><category><shortname>career-business</shortname><id>2</id><name>career/business</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;The Boston Business Opportunity Group is comprised of a group of visionaries providing a system to help individuals develop economic freedom. Our mission is to create 500 millionaires and to empower individuals to create generational wealth in their families. We believe that time is your most important asset, and the only way get your time back is to get money as an issue out of the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are committed to providing a system and an environment to empower you to achieve all of your goals and dreams. There's nothing like being in an environment with other like minded individuals, who are simply sick and tired of our lives being dictated by how much linear income(trading time for money) we make. Wealthy people live their lifestyles because they generate Passive and Residual incomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to know what others are doing in this area to create passive and residual income, come and join us. Find out how to help yourself as well as your loved ones. This group is open to people looking for an opportunity and also seasoned network marketers who want to work with me directly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have representation in Boston, New York City, Providence RI, Westport CT, Los Angeles and Malibu CA, Austin TX, Miami FL, Cabo San Lucas and Mexico City DF MEX, Melbourne AUS, London and Manchester UK, Canada, Buenos Aires ARG, and Tel Aviv IS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, you won't become wealthy by just joining this group. You need to do something about your situation, and I will give you the vehicle to do that.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>5.0</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1241704782000</created><lat>42.3600006104</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>381</id><urlkey>entrepreneur</urlkey><name>Entrepreneur</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>389</id><urlkey>smallbiz</urlkey><name>Small Business</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>589</id><urlkey>workathome</urlkey><name>Work At Home</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2532</id><urlkey>networkmarket</urlkey><name>Network Marketing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3634</id><urlkey>intlrel</urlkey><name>International Relations</name></topics_item></topics><name>The Boston Business Opportunity Group</name><id>1451981</id><members>170</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>8281457</member_id><name>Dennis Serpone</name></organizer><urlname>BostonBOG</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/9/1/600_43509361.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/9/1/highres_43509361.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>43509361</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/9/1/thumb_43509361.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/BostonBOG/</link><lon>-71.0699996948</lon></item>