<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>RI</state><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><category><shortname>food-drink</shortname><id>10</id><name>food/drink</name></category><description>This is a group that is dedicated to promoting the Vegetarian, Vegan, Raw Food and Organic lifestyles.  We strongly encourage anyone who is interested in pursuing a healthier diet to attend our Meetups.  Even if your goal is just to incorporate one or two healthier meals into your weekly menu, you will find encouragement from our Meetup members!  Take a look at some of the feedback from previous Meetups, and I am sure you will agree.  

Many of us hear about being organic, vegetarian, vegan or raw food enthusiasts, but how does one start?  Where do you begin?  Can one start off slow and gradual?   Besides salad, salad and more salad how do you prepare a variety of tasty organic vegetarian, vegan or raw meals that your non-vegetarian family and friends will not only eat, but actually enjoy?    

There are many of us right here in Rhode Island and in the surrounding area who have a strong desire to change their current lifestyles into a more healthy and active lifestyle.  The problem for so many is that they're too busy, too tired or stuck in their present routines.  Some don't even know a vegetarian, vegan, organic or raw eater and therefore, lack proper role-models, guidance or someone who can help encourage and show you the way to living and eating in a healthier way.   

Come to a local Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group, and learn what it takes to live a healthy, organic, vegetarian, vegan or raw lifestyle.  

Share delicious meal ideas, favorite recipes and healthy information.  You have my guarantee that you will find this Meetup group to be encouraging, and you will find yourself making new friends that you otherwise would probably never have met, even in a state as small as Rhode Island!</description><rating>4.46</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1225638384000</created><lat>41.8199996948</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>309</id><urlkey>vegetarian</urlkey><name>Vegetarian</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>408</id><urlkey>vegan</urlkey><name>Vegan</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1983</id><urlkey>rawfood</urlkey><name>Raw Food</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3714</id><urlkey>organic</urlkey><name>Organic</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10161</id><urlkey>nutrition</urlkey><name>Nutrition</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10306</id><urlkey>wellness</urlkey><name>Wellness</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17440</id><urlkey>living-foods</urlkey><name>Living Foods</name></topics_item></topics><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name><id>1312890</id><members>432</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7947968</member_id><name>Kevin</name></organizer><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/600_12060127.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/highres_12060127.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>12060127</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/thumb_12060127.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Providence</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/</link><lon>-71.4499969482</lon></item>