<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Travelers</who><category><shortname>outdoors-adventure</shortname><id>23</id><name>outdoors/adventure</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Boston Expat and World Travelers meetup group. Do you have a passion for traveling overseas and learning about other cultures? We are a group of friendly travelers and expats who meet monthly for a drink to exchange travel ideas, tips, and stories about exciting places we have traveled to, lived in, or hope to visit soon. We welcome anyone who is interested in world travel, whether you are considering it for the first time or a travel junkie who routinely quits your job in search of your next travel fix, or somewhere in between. Hope to see you at an event soon! Please note, we do not arrange slide shows, organize group trips, or push commercial ventures on you. Unlike some other groups, we're not affiliated with travel companies looking to promote their commercial services. What we do is meet, enjoy each other's company, and remind ourselves why people who travel the world are such good fun to be around. BEWT is a non-commercial social travel group. Active solicitation of members at Meet Ups or via the Message Board by commercial organizations is contrary to the spirit of the group. Commercial Message Board solicitations will be deleted.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.71</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1259124234000</created><lat>42.3400001526</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1998</id><urlkey>travel</urlkey><name>Travel</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4446</id><urlkey>expat</urlkey><name>Expat</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10080</id><urlkey>crosscultural</urlkey><name>Cross Cultural</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10454</id><urlkey>language</urlkey><name>Language &amp; Culture</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15892</id><urlkey>adventure</urlkey><name>Adventure</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16179</id><urlkey>international-travel</urlkey><name>International Travel</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>18988</id><urlkey>backpacking</urlkey><name>Backpacking</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Expat and World Travelers Meetup (BEWT)</name><id>1561742</id><members>1277</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7083634</member_id><name>Teresa</name></organizer><urlname>Boston-Expat-and-World-Travelers</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/c/7/600_11979879.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/c/7/highres_11979879.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>11979879</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/c/7/thumb_11979879.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><timezone>US/Eastern</timezone><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Expat-and-World-Travelers/</link><lon>-71.0999984741</lon></item>