<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Runners</who><category><shortname>fitness</shortname><id>9</id><name>fitness</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a casual group of down to earth runners who enjoy hitting the trails just as much as pounding the pavement? Looking for a competitive group of runners who enjoy running races varying from 5K’s to full marathons? Then look no further than a running group that offers the best of both worlds, Waltham Trail Runners! Whether you’re seeking leisurely runs around the Boston area, or crave a more competitive speed or hill workout, Waltham Trail Runners doles out a little bit of everything!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our weekly run takes place on Tuesday evenings at 6:30 pm where we meet up in front of the Skellig in Waltham. We run between 4 and 6 miles, and finish it all off with beers and munchies at the Skellig post-run. On the weekends, we schedule more trail running opportunities. We also enjoy coordinating group races, and participate in the Race Around Waltham Series (RAW Series)- &lt;a href="http://rawseries.weebly.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://rawseries.weebly.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waltham Trail Runners welcomes runners of all abilities and aspirations. We hope you join us soon! With Waltham Trail Runners, let’s just put it this way, it’s always a wild trail ride!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.86</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1245880077000</created><lat>42.3699989319</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>2516</id><urlkey>running</urlkey><name>Running</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>12711</id><urlkey>jogging</urlkey><name>Jogging</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16301</id><urlkey>trail-running</urlkey><name>Trail Running</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>28238</id><urlkey>trail-races</urlkey><name>Trail Races</name></topics_item></topics><name>Waltham Trail Runners</name><id>1479223</id><members>622</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>4514994</member_id><name>Sue Clever</name></organizer><urlname>Waltham-Trail-Runners</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/6/e/600_238327022.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/6/e/highres_238327022.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>238327022</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/6/e/thumb_238327022.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Waltham</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Waltham-Trail-Runners/</link><lon>-71.2399978638</lon></item>