<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Waterskiers</who><category><shortname>outdoors-adventure</shortname><id>23</id><name>outdoors/adventure</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;What is the purpose of this group?
&lt;br /&gt;The purpose of this group is for greater Boston area people to meet up and waterski for an hour or two or three. We need a minimum of three people to waterski, a waterski boat and of course the waterskis.&amp;nbsp; We encourage you to join even in NH , RI and Western CT and I will help you create&amp;nbsp; Meetups across the region for the most possibilities to waterski close to where you are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who should join? If you have a passion for the water join now! Our members run from Beginners to some of the highest experience levels. Most important, it's a friendly social atmosphere where you can feel comfortable no matter your skill level. We help each other enjoy, learn and get the most out of it. We love people who have have experience waterskiing and/or who can navigate a waterski boat safely and responsibly. It is also great, if you have your waterski boat to add to the group. I expect we will share expenses such as fuel and other incidentals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned to waterski at seven years old. I still love to do it.
&lt;br /&gt;I have a boat and skis.&amp;nbsp; Several other members also have their own boats, so there is variety of boats and favorite waterski locations. Borrowing equipment to learn or try is usual, just let us know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where will we meet and Waterski?
&lt;br /&gt;For freshwater we trailer to nearby Rivers or Lakes such The Merrimac River, Lake Cochiutate, Chebacco Lake.&amp;nbsp; For saltwater, around Boston Harbor or near The Cape, and as far as Newport or Providence RI where the water is warmer. You can review the past meetups for more location details. And keep in mind that we are open to exploring your favorite spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;Let's make the best of the days of summer we have here in Boston. Let's get out and waterski!&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.9</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1251933226000</created><lat>42.3100013733</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>24058</id><urlkey>waterskiing</urlkey><name>Waterskiing</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston WaterSki Enthusiasts</name><id>1517227</id><members>98</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>10327252</member_id><name>Peter D</name></organizer><urlname>BostonWaterSkiEnthusiasts</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/9/d/600_21105981.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/9/d/highres_21105981.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>21105981</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/9/d/thumb_21105981.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Newton Center</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWaterSkiEnthusiasts/</link><lon>-71.1900024414</lon></item>