<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>NH</state><who>Rock Climbers</who><category><shortname>outdoors-adventure</shortname><id>23</id><name>outdoors/adventure</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for people who would like to participate in meeting other local rock climbers to share tips, discuss gear, plan trips, meet partners or learn to climb. All ages, level climbers welcome to the meetups, unless otherwise stated. We meetup at various climbing locations in New England as well as different climbing gyms in the area. &lt;br /&gt;If you are looking for new people to climb with I encourge you to show for the meetups in order to meet eachother, as this sport requires trust in your climbing partners. Once you have met, the message board is a great way to communicate with eachother in order to find climbing partners when the meetups are not happening. &lt;br /&gt;Also if you are climbing, with or without the group, take a few minutes and let us know where you've been! Pic are always great to share with the group as this sports also takes us to amazing places!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are new to the sport and looking for guidance, this meetup is for you also. I am very happy to teach you the fundamentals here at my private non-porfit gym. When the group does meetups at other gyms and outdoors you will have the necessary skills to enjoy the climbing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.87</rating><join_mode>approval</join_mode><created>1208866441000</created><lat>43.2099990845</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>374</id><urlkey>camping</urlkey><name>Camping</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1566</id><urlkey>rockclimbing</urlkey><name>Rock Climbing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15892</id><urlkey>adventure</urlkey><name>Adventure</name></topics_item></topics><name>The NH Rock Climbing Meetup</name><id>1120342</id><members>342</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>6992283</member_id><name>Kellie Barr-Foster</name></organizer><urlname>rockclimbing-134</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/5/5/600_17728757.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/5/5/highres_17728757.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>17728757</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/5/5/thumb_17728757.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Barrington</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/rockclimbing-134/</link><lon>-71.0299987793</lon></item>