<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Procrastinators</who><category><shortname>support</shortname><id>33</id><name>support</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;We meet to help each other overcome procrastination and cluttering. We encourage use of a buddy system where we mostly work with each other one-on-one. Buddies connect by phone or email, and sometimes in person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We seek to reduce procrastination and/or clutter to a maintainable level that no longer impedes us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buddies can help us stay on track and help us make necessary changes in behaviors that we see are not in our best interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us if you find that you are stressed out by the drain in time and energy that procrastination causes and if your clutter has become depressing or overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll help pairs of buddies get started with a few simple guidelines, and our meetings will provide a way to meet new buddies, discuss techniques and resources, exchange success and failure stories, and have a few laughs at what we are finding out about ourselves and each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of us have attention deficit disorder (ADD) - we have trouble getting started and trouble finishing. Our sense of time can be off-kilter. Many of us are easily distracted or get stuck hyper-focussing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of us don't have ADD but have some kind of life stress or event that has caused us to lose control of our environment. Once our sense of order is disrupted, we don't know how to deal with the resulting mess to get back to an orderly life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This group was originally called "The Metrowest Procrastinators Meetup Group". We have added Clutterers to the title because many of us, including the current organizers, have clutter problems that seem to be part of why we procrastinate. And, we procrastinate about dealing with our clutter. Some of the techniques used to declutter can be used to overcome procrastination too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the original group description.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Procrastination is the thief of time.&amp;rdquo; - Edward Young (1683-1765)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Procrastination is only remotely related to time management, (procrastinators often know exactly what they should be doing, even if they cannot do it), which is why very detailed schedules usually are no help."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets work together to understand both the simple and complex issues that underlie procrastination and use this knowledge to help us overcome the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This group will provide a safe and supportive space to talk about our own experiences with procrastination and other unproductive habits, as well as a forum to share techniques that work for us, and lastly an opportunity to review together some of the literature on the subject and discuss it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will also provide a great opportunity to make connections with new friends and support each other as we work to move from procrastination to more productive living!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meetings will include discussion of personal experiences and techniques, discussions of articles and book excerpts relevant to procrastination and productivity, breaking into smaller groups we can stay in contact with throughout the month to help hold us accountable and support us when we stray, and hosting guest speakers who can help or provide insight. We will also entertain ideas from group members as to what they may find helpful or topics they want to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.75</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1231968748000</created><lat>42.3499984741</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1644</id><urlkey>adultadd</urlkey><name>Attention Deficit Disorder</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2794</id><urlkey>procrastinator</urlkey><name>Procrastinators</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3336</id><urlkey>self-improvement</urlkey><name>Self-Improvement</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>6008</id><urlkey>declutter</urlkey><name>Declutter</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>6265</id><urlkey>messies</urlkey><name>Messies</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16435</id><urlkey>midlife-adhd</urlkey><name>Midlife ADHD</name></topics_item></topics><name>Metrowest Procrastinators and Clutterers</name><id>1357989</id><members>119</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7648322</member_id><name>Alice</name></organizer><urlname>Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/d/a/600_6942970.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/d/a/highres_6942970.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>6942970</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/d/a/thumb_6942970.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Marlborough</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers/</link><lon>-71.5500030518</lon></item>