<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><category><shortname>food-drink</shortname><id>10</id><name>food/drink</name></category><description>Do you feel that your "appreciation" of food is never fully "appreciated" by others in your circle of friends?  Do you always insist on providing the food for your dinner parties because you feel that whatever anyone else brings just isn't going to be good enough?  If you're anything like me, you have difficulty finding friends who share your love of food.  Why?  Because you've taken that love of food to a whole new level and have successfully isolated everyone you hold near and dear.  Well you, my friend, are a Food Snob, and you're not alone!  That's why I am calling to arms a meeting of all Food Snobs to Unite.  If you love throwing dinner parties with elaborate 4 course meals, then you are a food snob.  If you take pleasure in regaling everyone with tales of trips to Formaggio Kitchen &amp; Savenor's to your coworker's on Monday morning, then you are a food snob.  If you talk shop about local chefs like Ming Tsai &amp; Frank McClelland like they were baseball legends, then you my friend, are a food snob.  Come out &amp; meet other Food Snobs in a myriad of culinary forums (ie dinner parties, night out at a restaurant, or even a local wine &amp; cheese course).</description><rating>4.73</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1195326373000</created><lat>42.3899993896</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>713</id><urlkey>diningout</urlkey><name>Dining Out</name></topics_item></topics><name>Food Snobs Unite (FSU) - Meetup Group</name><id>824450</id><members>286</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>5109349</member_id><name>Harold</name></organizer><urlname>diningout-625</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/3/f/600_6555935.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/3/f/highres_6555935.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>6555935</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/3/f/thumb_6555935.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Cambridge</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-625/</link><lon>-71.1299972534</lon></item>