<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>CT</state><who>dining companions</who><category><shortname>socializing</shortname><id>31</id><name>socializing</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Meet people that enjoy dining out in your area and who are open to making new friends! We are very easy to be with. Please join us at a Dining Out Meetup to make new friends, begin new relationships and enjoy a good meal and lively conversation. Discover new restaurants, enjoy delicious meals and make satisfying conversation with friendly dinner companions. It's a big dinner table and all are welcome! We are a welcoming group and look forward to meeting you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We try to be punctual for these events. If you happen to be running late please call me on my cell phone at 203-885-6928. This helps us get accurate headcounts to the restaurant staff and makes the whole thing run more smoothly. Also, if you RSVP yes, please make your best effort to show up.&amp;nbsp; If you can't make it for some reason, please change your&amp;nbsp;RSVP at least 24 hours before the event.&amp;nbsp; Unfortunately, because of problems in the past,&amp;nbsp;anyone who doesn't show up to&amp;nbsp;two events they have committed to. will be dropped from the group.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Bottom line: This is about having fun and meeting folks and discovering new dining options, but we make commitments to our restaurant partners and we need to honor them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.69</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1191187714000</created><lat>41.2799987793</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>498</id><urlkey>singles</urlkey><name>Singles</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>713</id><urlkey>diningout</urlkey><name>Dining Out</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3250</id><urlkey>couples</urlkey><name>Couples</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10581</id><urlkey>social</urlkey><name>Social</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17866</id><urlkey>meeting-new-people</urlkey><name>Meeting New People</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>20705</id><urlkey>having-fun</urlkey><name>Having Fun</name></topics_item></topics><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name><id>719640</id><members>554</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>9388041</member_id><name>Chris</name></organizer><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/8/7/600_3095463.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/8/7/highres_3095463.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>3095463</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/8/7/thumb_3095463.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Branford</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/</link><lon>-72.8000030518</lon></item>