<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Game Players</who><category><shortname>games</shortname><id>11</id><name>games</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey All. Like games?  Come play them with us.  We play boards games, some card games, the occasional word game, and sometimes even party games.  We are pretty informal group that meets once a week  (alternating Wednesday and Mondays) at 7:00pm over near Kendall Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We started out with a half-dozen members back in 2007 and now, just over 5 years later, we have over 600 members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The average turnout for a regular meet-up is between 15 and 20 people.  I do not adhere to a strict RSVP policy, so the RSVP list tends to be much lower than the turn-out.  Do not let a small number of yes RSVPs scare you away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are wondering what games we play, I would say we tend to primarily play European strategy games in general, but as I mentioned before, we have also played word games, card games, trivia games, and party games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically we pay the games people bring.  If you have a game you like playing, bring it on down and play with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I only have 2 rules in my group.  1 - No cheating.  It takes away from the fun.  2 - This is not a for-profit group.  Please do not sell your wares in my group.  I do not run this as a business, and do not want others to use it to run their own. I post that there is a suggested $1. donation that goes to fees incurred through Meet-up and any leftovers have gone for refreshments that have been served at group events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occasionally, members have offered to host an event at their homes. In the event that happens, the host may set requirements to attend  (ie:  valid name and picture on profile ) or limit the attendance to the event.  House-hosted events are done at the discretion of the host.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not much else to say.  email me if you have questions.  Otherwise, join and have fun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Becki&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.67</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1181222819000</created><lat>42.3400001526</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>495</id><urlkey>boardgames</urlkey><name>Boardgames</name></topics_item></topics><name>Beantown Gamers</name><id>521103</id><members>850</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>4147212</member_id><name>Becki</name></organizer><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/7/3/600_1509331.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/7/3/highres_1509331.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>1509331</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/7/3/thumb_1509331.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/</link><lon>-71.0899963379</lon></item>