<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>CT</state><who>Cool Singles</who><category><shortname>socializing</shortname><id>31</id><name>socializing</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Please join this Meet Up Group instead of this group, I know it is confusing. I am in the process of fading this group out.  PLEASE JOIN:  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-Iras-Singles-Events/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/The-Iras-Singles-Events/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;All Pictures of past events can be seen at:  &lt;a href="http://www.theirassinglesevents.com/apps/photos/"&gt;http://www.theirassinglesevents.com/apps/photos/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Sorry for the confusion,,,,,, It will get better....... Thank you.  Ira. &lt;a href="mailto:Mistrchrming@aol.com"&gt;Mistrchrming@aol.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab Life for all of its Gusto and Happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a Singles Exclusive Meet Up. I know from personal experience what is like to go to a Meet Up, have 12 people there, and of the 12, there are 5 couples. Yay for a fun on a Saturday Night….. Rest assured, join my group, come to my events, and mingle with all Singles. It is always a challenge to get to more men come to the events. I will work hard to achieve this goal. We all want quality people in our lives. People to enrich our lives in many different ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal is to be the “One Stop Shopping” for all of your Single Events I offer a personal and caring approach. For the past three years, I have presented a variety of Singles Events, for the opportunity to meet that “special person.” Always best to come with the attitude of having a great time no matter what, and if you find that person, all the better. Many nice friendships of the same sex have been made as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At all my events, which I personally host and attend, I strongly believe in giving all who attend, a warm and friendly welcome, name tags, and throughout the evening, introducing all to all. In my heart, I love playing “matchmaker.”My motto “ Come alone, but, never feel alone.’’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About my events: First and foremost- For Singles Only. Sorry, No Couples. The reason for this is that it gives all who attend the assurance that whomever they speak to is Single, and perhaps available for dating. We always need more men at the events, so tell all of your Single Friends about this meet up and my web site for upcoming events. www.theirassinglesevents.com . I am proud of my web site. Please visit my blog for my always-interesting observations of life. I encourage your opinion on all subjects. I pledge to keep it current, so all you have to do is click on the event you are interested in, and all the information will be available for you. Pictures of events are posted within a 24 hour period)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the site for previous The Ira’s Single Events. I am proud of my Testimonial Page and Pictures from previous Events. Countless hours of planning, organizing, creative thought are put into each event. (This is why members are asked to pay $10.00 for yearly due. your membership and the experiences you will enjoy are worth .025 cents per day.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are high quality single events with the purpose of having fun, and interactive communications between all. I dislike loud venues that prevent what I consider so important, speaking and listening to each other. I will do my best to have events where we can hear what the other person is saying. What a novel idea….&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My events will include the traditional Singles Events” Happy Hours, Bus, Trips, Cultural Events/Bushnell/Plays, Day and Overnight Trips, Cooking Clubs, Ping Pong Day, Holiday Parties, Dances, Singles Cruises, Upscale outdoor and indoor Parties. I will be expanding my Single Offerings as well, to include Overnight Trips, Restaurant Single Events/Humanitarian Events to help out those in need/Single Outdoor Activities, and then a little more Creative/Unique Events. Stay tuned. (My exclusive Singles Policy may “waver” a little bit. If we are trying to fill up a bus, and short the number we need to make the trip a go, perhaps, adding some couples may be the way to go. Of course, they will need to ride in the back of the bus. Just Kidding)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ira’s Singles Travel Group will include day and overnight trips. Stay tuned/Start Saving for Overnight Trips to: DC-WASHINGTON,DELAWARE-ULSTER RAILROAD,PA-LANCASTER, PENN DUTCH, MYRTLE BEACH, ME-LOBSTERS &amp;amp; LIGHTHOUSES,, just as an example. Many day trips will be featured as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you say yes to coming to any of the events, You agree  to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : black"&gt;By accepting this entry, I the registrant, legally bind myself, my heirs, administrators, and assigns&lt;/span&gt;  to this agreement. &lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : black"&gt;I waive and release any and all claims I may have against The Ira’s Singles Events, LLC. for any injuries or damages whatsoever&lt;/span&gt;  resulting from attending this event. &lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;3.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : black"&gt;In addition, I represent that I am physically able to participate in said event and do not have any disabilities preventing me from participating in this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : black"&gt;I further release, The Ira’s Singles Events , LLC., from any claims resulting  from my consumption of alcohol  prior to the event, at the event, and following the event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;5.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : black"&gt;Lastly, I grant permission, to The Ira’s Singles Events, LLC.  to use any Film, Video, and or Recordings taken at the&lt;/span&gt;  event, in which I appear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : black"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

All suggestions are welcome as to what type of events you like to see. Please do join today. Share with your Singles Friends/Co-Workers/Neighbors. The more the merrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ira&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.theirassinglesevents.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;mistrchrming@aol.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;860-604-5792&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.78</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1237391751000</created><lat>41.9300003052</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>264</id><urlkey>friends</urlkey><name>Friends</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>498</id><urlkey>singles</urlkey><name>Singles</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>713</id><urlkey>diningout</urlkey><name>Dining Out</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1091</id><urlkey>newlysingle</urlkey><name>Newly Single</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1273</id><urlkey>newintown</urlkey><name>New In Town</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1998</id><urlkey>travel</urlkey><name>Travel</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4392</id><urlkey>nightlife</urlkey><name>Night Life</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15117</id><urlkey>fun-times</urlkey><name>Fun Times</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15892</id><urlkey>adventure</urlkey><name>Adventure</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17866</id><urlkey>meeting-new-people</urlkey><name>Meeting New People</name></topics_item></topics><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name><id>1411725</id><members>203</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>5032313</member_id><name>Ira Wettenstein</name></organizer><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/3/0/600_132876912.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/3/0/highres_132876912.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>132876912</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/3/0/thumb_132876912.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Windsor Locks</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/</link><lon>-72.6399993896</lon></item>