<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Members</who><category><shortname>new-age-spirituality</shortname><id>22</id><name>new age/spirituality</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Kabbalah is the ancient esoteric tradition, Jewish mysticism. Group 'Kabbalah and Meditation' is intended to connect us with the sources of knowledge in the Jewish mystical tradition and thus bring us closer to G-d. Kabbalah literal meaning is 'to receive', which alludes to receiving esoteric influx through learning and practice, with 'mindful heart'.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; Of the three types of Kabbalah: theoretical, meditative and practical, we learn and engage only in 
&lt;em&gt;theoretical and meditative Kabbalah&lt;/em&gt;. We draw exclusively upon Torah-based sources, while making every attempt to identify and connect the dots between kabbalistic notions and our contemporary spiritual experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
      &lt;span style="color: teal;"&gt;Learn and experience&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;OUR STUDY GROUPS.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt; Each group meeting of two hours includes 1 hour of learning and 1 hour of meditation.&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WE LEARN THE BASICS OF KABBALAH FUNDAMENTALS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Structure of creation, Universes and Sefirot&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mystical significance of Hebrew letters (we learn the letters as well) and their permutations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Structure of the soul&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Individual and collective Divine Providence&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Types of reincarnations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seeing and understanding own life purpose from the perspective of higher self&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Developing sensitivity to spiritual communications&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Practices that help us to become closer to G-d&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We base our learning on the works of Ramchal, Rambam, R. Moshe Cordovero, R. Nachman of Breslov, and our contemporaries, R. Aryeh Kaplan, R. Avraham Sutton, R. Avraham Itzik (A. Green). We touch on the texts of Sefer Yetzirah, Zohar and Bahir, but will not expand on them without extensive preparation.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; IN MEDITATION PART, WE LEARN AND PRACTICE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Identifying Sefirot with the parts of the body&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Meditation on Sefirot and meditation on Hebrew letters&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Expanding on importance of breath in attaining meditative states and tuning our connection with the higher levels of our own soul, and with G-d.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We learn and practice breathing techniques and chanting meditations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Exploring and experiencing significance of routine Jewish rituals in drawing down the power of the spiritual realms -- 'elevating the sparks', bringing kochos to the state of tikkun -- clearing and elevating ourselves, and the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span style="color: olive;"&gt;'KABBALAH AT THE SHABBAT TABLE'&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;is another format of our gatherings. Allow learning and experience integrate into your bodies with delicious traditional Shabbat food and fascinating rituals.&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;Everyone is welcome,&lt;/span&gt; whether you want to reconnect with our tradition, or whether your soul is calling you to the Shabbat table, and to learn more about Jewish ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;We meet on Friday nights to experience the beauty of Shabbat, to welcome, to be blessed and to dwell in the glory of the Shabbat Queen, Shechinah, the Divine Presence.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;We perform all Shabbat rituals in the Orthodox tradition, dress in festive way, light candles, sing, enjoy plentiful traditional Shabbat meals, read Torah and discuss how the Torah themes manifest in our lives on spiritual and material levels. We learn the Kabbalistic meaning of Shabbat, rituals and brachot (blessings). If Shabbat falls on Rosh Chodesh or Erev Rosh Chodesh, we bless the new moon and new month. On Shabbat that allows for Kedush Levana, we perform ritual blessings the moon that reaches its fullness. We celebrate all festivals that fall on Shabbat in traditional ways.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.85</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1258388508000</created><lat>42.3699989319</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>2054</id><urlkey>kabbalah</urlkey><name>Kabbalah</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4417</id><urlkey>consciousness</urlkey><name>Consciousness</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10290</id><urlkey>spirituality</urlkey><name>Spirituality</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16144</id><urlkey>self-empowerment-exploration</urlkey><name>Self Empowerment &amp; Exploration</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>18508</id><urlkey>divine-guidance-and-inner-wisdom</urlkey><name>Divine Guidance and Inner Wisdom</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>20588</id><urlkey>god</urlkey><name>God</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>21136</id><urlkey>spirituality-personal-growth-meditation</urlkey><name>Spirituality, Personal Growth, Meditation</name></topics_item></topics><name>Kabbalah and Meditation</name><id>1557684</id><members>79</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>7891623</member_id><name>Miriam </name></organizer><urlname>Kabbalah-and-Meditation</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/c/0/600_18892160.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/c/0/highres_18892160.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>18892160</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/c/0/thumb_18892160.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><timezone>US/Eastern</timezone><city>Watertown</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Kabbalah-and-Meditation/</link><lon>-71.1800003052</lon></item>