<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Will-Be Investors</who><category><shortname>career-business</shortname><id>2</id><name>career/business</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you want to be rich?? Are you tired of renting?? Do you want to know what the rich know?? DO YOU WANT MORE OUT OF LIFE??? Then YOU are the perfect person for this meetup! This meetup exists to teach others about Cashflow101, real estate investing guru Robert Kiyosaki's world-famous board game that teaches the basics of real estate investing and money management. Learn the secrets of what the rich teach their kids about money, and what the middle class doesn't know. Sharpen your money management skills. Laugh and learn from others in a friendly environment that aims to challenge everyone and grow our individual FINANCIAL IQs. We welcome individuals from all backgrounds and all levels of knowledge and experience with money and real estate. Are you a beginner? Do you some day want to own your own home? Or do you already own properties and are reaping the benefits of your hard work and foresight? Join our group, and let's get out of the Rat Race once and for all! JOIN NOW and we'll see you at the next meetup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees at our meetups always talk about how much they learned and how much fun they had! &amp;nbsp;It's a great chance to meet people, play a great game, and really get into some awesome conversations about money, real estate, and investing in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead! &amp;nbsp;Sign up and join us at our next memorable meetup! &amp;nbsp;We're excited to meet you!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.44</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1155332792000</created><lat>42.3899993896</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>495</id><urlkey>boardgames</urlkey><name>Boardgames</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>885</id><urlkey>cashflow</urlkey><name>Cashflow</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1307</id><urlkey>investing</urlkey><name>Investing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2064</id><urlkey>realestate</urlkey><name>Real Estate Buying &amp; Investing</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Cashflow Meetup</name><id>302998</id><members>257</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>3610750</member_id><name>Russ</name></organizer><urlname>BostonCashflowMeetup</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/9/600_35280841.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/9/highres_35280841.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>35280841</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/9/thumb_35280841.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Somerville</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCashflowMeetup/</link><lon>-71.0899963379</lon></item>