<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Runners</who><category><shortname>fitness</shortname><id>9</id><name>fitness</name></category><description>This running group is open to everyone, newbies who have never run before and looking to start, weekend joggers, or seasoned marathoners looking for the renewed inspiration that comes from the companionship of other runners sharing their passion for this sport.  It's all about making friends who run and running with friends we make. We'll share our knowledge on exercise, weight loss, gear, training tips and techniques, racing, injury prevention and recovery, all while sharing a good run.  Distances and pace can be determined with each meet or broken up into separate groups. The members can ultimately decide the group's direction.

BILL IS THE MAIN ORGANIZER OF THIS GROUP, SO PLEASE SEND ALL YOUR INQUIRIES DIRECTLY TO HIM.  JUST CLICK ON HIS NAME UNDER Asst. Organizer AND CLICK ON EMAIL IN HIS PROFILE AND YOUR EMAIL WILL GO TO HIM.

DISCLAIMER: Please remember you must maintain a certain level of fitness to run.  All runs are at your own risk and the group or individuals in the group cannot be held liable for any injury occured during a meet.  Please consult a doctor if there is any question of your fitness to run.</description><rating>4.82</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1257380213000</created><lat>42.2599983215</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>242</id><urlkey>fitness</urlkey><name>Fitness</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2516</id><urlkey>running</urlkey><name>Running</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>12711</id><urlkey>jogging</urlkey><name>Jogging</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15394</id><urlkey>group-fitness-training</urlkey><name>Group Fitness Training</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16301</id><urlkey>trail-running</urlkey><name>Trail Running</name></topics_item></topics><name>Running Hot</name><id>1551891</id><members>170</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>4474200</member_id><name>Pat</name></organizer><urlname>Running-Hot</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/1/6/600_13034870.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/1/6/highres_13034870.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>13034870</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/1/6/thumb_13034870.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><timezone>US/Eastern</timezone><city>Granby</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Running-Hot/</link><lon>-72.5199966431</lon></item>