<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><category><shortname>community-environment</shortname><id>4</id><name>community/environment</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/2/a/event_210761002.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;We hold group hikes and birding events at various locations in and around the vast Myles Standish State Forest in Plymouth and Carver, Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For most of the year, we try to schedule a hike on the first Sunday of the month. Other hikes are offered whenever the mood strikes.&lt;/span&gt; We have a regular group that goes out hiking on Thursday mornings after sharing a hearty breakfast. We also sponsor bird watching and other bird support activities when the birds allow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are approaching our 400th Meetup since our founding in 2009. Clearly, we're having fun and hope you will join us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to signing up here to learn about our hikes and other activities, please consider joining our Friends group. Visit the &lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com/"&gt;Friends of Myles Standish web page&lt;/a&gt; to find out more about us.  Members of the Friends are currently working on various stewardship projects such as &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/photos/15425712/"&gt;monitoring bluebird boxes&lt;/a&gt; or our &lt;a href="http://0195a4f.netsolhost.com/pinebarrenpollinators.html"&gt;Pine Barrens Community Initiative&lt;/a&gt; which raises and sells native plants to raise appreciation of native plants in the unique pine barrens of Southeast Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can find a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/mssf1.pdf"&gt;detailed map of Myles Standish State Forest&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;showing campgrounds, ponds, bike trails and two excellent self-guiding hiking trails on the State's&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/mssf.htm"&gt;Myles Standish State Forest  web page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A 2.5 mile trail starts from the headquarters and goes around the pretty East Head Reservoir. (Follow the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;blue triangle markers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Bentley Loop is 3.7 miles and starts at Parking Lot #2 on Upper College Pond Road. (Follow the signposts and the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;blue blazes painted on trees&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Meetup Group is sponsored by the Friends of Myles Standish State Forest (FMSSF). a volunteer group charity organization.  We are private individuals who want to bring interesting and fun hikes, bird-watching programs and other events for all ages to Myles Standish State Forest, the largest state forest in eastern Massachusetts-- a park as big as many of the towns that surround it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/a/event_116402762.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsoring this group helps the Friends fulfill its mission to encourage a deeper appreciation of Myles Standish State Forest as a wonderful recreational resource, while fostering the understanding that the southeastern Massachusetts' pine barrens are a globally rare habitat and are home to a surprisingly large number of endangered plants and animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are dedicated to promoting responsible use of the forest. We hope that once you see for yourself the incredible plants, animals and special features of the MSSF pine barrens, you will want to become a &lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com/"&gt;member of our Friends group&lt;/a&gt; too!&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/a/c/event_112603692.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/a/2/event_108196802.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We often work closely with the Massachusetts Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR) on clearing trails and many other projects but this group is not sponsored by the DCR or the State of Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All ages are welcome on every hike as long as parents/guardians are with any younger hikers. Friendly leashed dogs are welcome on most hikes--except for bird watching hikes, please.  If you love hiking or birding you will discover that MSSF has some great places to explore. Where else in Massachusetts can you find vistas that make you think you are in the Southwestern U.S.?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, please consider joining our Friends group. Basic membership is only $10 per year.  Visit the &lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com/"&gt;Friends of Myles Standish web page&lt;/a&gt; to find out more about us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.85</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1233246971000</created><lat>41.8400001526</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>374</id><urlkey>camping</urlkey><name>Camping</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>449</id><urlkey>horses</urlkey><name>Horse</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>579</id><urlkey>bike</urlkey><name>Bicycling</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>638</id><urlkey>hiking</urlkey><name>Hiking</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1700</id><urlkey>conservation</urlkey><name>Conservation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2578</id><urlkey>birdwatching</urlkey><name>Birdwatching</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>4239</id><urlkey>hunting</urlkey><name>Hunting</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15046</id><urlkey>outdoors</urlkey><name>Outdoors</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15672</id><urlkey>outdoor-fitness</urlkey><name>Outdoor  Fitness</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15832</id><urlkey>outdoor-recreation</urlkey><name>Outdoor Recreation</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16330</id><urlkey>exercise-and-fun</urlkey><name>Exercise and Fun</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16600</id><urlkey>nature-photography</urlkey><name>Nature Photography</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16871</id><urlkey>staying-active-with-the-kids</urlkey><name>Staying Active with the Kids</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17407</id><urlkey>dog-parks</urlkey><name>Dog Parks</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>19365</id><urlkey>nature-lovers</urlkey><name>nature-lovers</name></topics_item></topics><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name><id>1370268</id><members>639</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>650729</member_id><name>John Bescherer</name></organizer><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/0/c/600_247489932.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/0/c/highres_247489932.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>247489932</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/0/c/thumb_247489932.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>South Carver</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/</link><lon>-70.7399978638</lon></item>