<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>CT</state><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><category><shortname>cars-motorcycles</shortname><id>3</id><name>cars/motorcycles</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;When given the opportunity, Sport bike enthusiasts will ride regardless of most circumstances. But even the most diehard riders admit that riding solo only goes so far. That’s why the West-Conn Sport bike Riders Meet Up group was created, to bring together Sport bike riders of varying experience, riding styles and types of motorcycles to share our passion for the sport.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;The West-Conn Sport Bike Riders meet up group focuses on inviting riders from Connecticut and mid-Hudson Valley, NY areas to participate in some great back road riding. Many of our rides will start in Western CT and venture into Putnam, Dutchess and Ulster Counties, NY. Some of our longer rides will go as far north as upstate NY, NH and VT as two day overnight trips. On occasion, we do team up with other groups like Boston Tier 1 Riders and head into Massachusetts as their members post rides on our website as well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;Sport bikes are the predominant type of motorcycle but hyper-sport touring, sport touring, naked, street fighters and motards will easily fit in. Other types of motorcycles are welcome as well but may find that the associated riding style may not fit in with the riding tempo of the group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;We have a great group of riders from beginners with their first bikes to group leaders that have been riding for many years and know all of the best roads. We are also active in participating in recreational track days with organizations like Penguin Racing and Tony's Track Days which hold their events at New Hampshire Speedway and NJ Motorsports Park.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;All levels of riders are welcome to join and ride! We do encourage safe and responsible riding that strikes a happy medium with twisting the throttle to produce that rush sport bike riders crave. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;However with that said, ALL riders are responsible for riding with in their limits. No rider shall ride in a manner to endanger another fellow sport bike rider. All riders that participate in meet up rides shall wear a helmet and have servicable tires.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; There are enough inherent challenges out there on the road. We want all to come back safe, sound and with a grin on your face.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;We look forward to seeing you in the wind!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;DISCLAIMER: By being a member of this group you hereby agree to assume all risks and liability related to or resulting from any and all group functions. You agree that neither you nor any third party will hold the group's Organizer or any of the group's Assistant organizers liable for any injury, loss, or damage to your own person or property arising directly or as a consequence from a group activity. You also agree that your membership of this group is based on an "at will" basis. See terms of service 6,6.1,6.2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #555555"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/terms/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/terms/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.68</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1254841178000</created><lat>41.6800003052</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>614</id><urlkey>ducati</urlkey><name>Ducati</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>730</id><urlkey>hondabikes</urlkey><name>Honda Motorcycles</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>763</id><urlkey>sportbikes</urlkey><name>Sport Bikes</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>3740</id><urlkey>kawasaki</urlkey><name>Kawasaki</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10315</id><urlkey>motorcycle</urlkey><name>Motorcycle Riders</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15736</id><urlkey>yamaha-motorcycles</urlkey><name>Yamaha Motorcycles</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16310</id><urlkey>motorcycle-touring</urlkey><name>Motorcycle Touring</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>20379</id><urlkey>bikers-that-like-to-ride</urlkey><name>Bikers that like to ride.</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>21882</id><urlkey>sportbike-groups</urlkey><name>Sportbike Groups</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>22410</id><urlkey>motorcycle-riding</urlkey><name>Motorcycle Riding</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>23282</id><urlkey>aprilia</urlkey><name>Aprilia</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>23462</id><urlkey>beginner-motorcycle-riders</urlkey><name>Beginner Motorcycle Riders</name></topics_item></topics><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name><id>1535765</id><members>107</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>14409235</member_id><name>Gp1300</name></organizer><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/5/2/600_71807442.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/5/2/highres_71807442.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>71807442</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/5/2/thumb_71807442.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><timezone>US/Eastern</timezone><city>Bristol</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/</link><lon>-72.9300003052</lon></item>