<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Members</who><category><shortname>language</shortname><id>16</id><name>language/ethnic identity</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Hostelling International Boston and the United Nations Association of Greater Boston at a host of Boston-area restaurants in a celebration of food and culture! Cultural Café, a fun way to explore delicious food and meet new people, holds monthly meetups at restaurants in the Greater Boston area that serve up a variety of tasty cuisines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will enjoy a family-style meal mixing "greatest hits" with some lesser-known gems of that month's cuisine. Each restaurant will provide a cultural presentation or demonstration as part of the experience. Your meal, tip, and nonalcoholic beverages are included in the $25 price; alcoholic drinks must be paid for separately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cultural Café provides an opportunity for community members to experience what students experience in the Cultural Kitchen program. The setting is informal as guests gather to build community, share a delicious meal, learn about another culture, network with like-minded individuals and support a great cause!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we grow, we hope to begin leveraging HI-Boston's new group kitchen and dining room for special cooking demonstrations and in-house cultural dinners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meetup members will need to pay for event tickets in advance. We will have a convenient online payment method or people can contact the group leader, Paul Kuhne at community.boston@hiusa.org or 617-556-5312.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.74</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1257802159000</created><lat>42.3499984741</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>713</id><urlkey>diningout</urlkey><name>Dining Out</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1726</id><urlkey>nonprofit</urlkey><name>Nonprofit</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15210</id><urlkey>ethnic-food</urlkey><name>Ethnic Food</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15892</id><urlkey>adventure</urlkey><name>Adventure</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16179</id><urlkey>international-travel</urlkey><name>International Travel</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>16634</id><urlkey>international-cuisine</urlkey><name>International Cuisine</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17103</id><urlkey>charity-events-and-fundraisers</urlkey><name>Charity Events and Fundraisers</name></topics_item></topics><name>Cultural Café - Dine Out for a Cause</name><id>1554280</id><members>190</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>12811800</member_id><name>Hostelling International Boston</name></organizer><urlname>Culturalcafe</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/c/e/600_11736302.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/c/e/highres_11736302.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>11736302</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/c/e/thumb_11736302.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><timezone>US/Eastern</timezone><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Culturalcafe/</link><lon>-71.0699996948</lon></item>