<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Members</who><category><shortname>career-business</shortname><id>2</id><name>career/business</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Boston Internet Marketing Meetup, (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/#!/BostIMM"&gt;@bostimm&lt;/a&gt;) is a rapidly growing local Internet marketing Meetup focused on the Cambridge and Boston locales. True to a Meetup format, we always have a presentation or learning session and a Q&amp;amp;A which is preceded and followed by general networking opportunities with both experienced and relatively new professionals interested in the Internet and its use in successful marketing programs.&amp;nbsp; We feel peer learning and networking with an educational component is the best way to get introduced to Internet Marketing as well as building your knowledge base and contacts for the experienced online marketer. We like to hang out after a presentation, get some food or a drink, talk internet, answer questions and really get to know all you folks that are both passionate about or just learning of&amp;nbsp; the opportunities online for the first time.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Topics regularly include Websites: buying/selling/optimizing; Search: optimization, tools; Social media: real time, video, tools (twitter/facebook/youtube, etc); Analytics: free and paid programs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our educational series that started in 2011 has been well attended and pulls from our talented membership to create a regular learning track for Internet marketing topics.&amp;nbsp; We also have our eyes open for cool events that may be a little bit different, but hopefully bring a level of take-home value you do not find elsewhere.&amp;nbsp; Our goal with each meetup is to give our attendees at least one thing they can go home with and make a difference in their business, website or internet marketing plan.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We invite anyone interested in these topics to join us anytime. We welcome new members including recent or soon to be college graduates, veteran internet marketers, independent business owners who need a jumpstart, and those folks just venturing into the world of online marketing for the first time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please join us!&lt;br&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.61</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1250339934000</created><lat>42.3499984741</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>381</id><urlkey>entrepreneur</urlkey><name>Entrepreneur</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1330</id><urlkey>ebizowners</urlkey><name>E-Business Owners</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>6761</id><urlkey>seo</urlkey><name>Search Engine Optimization</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>14983</id><urlkey>internet-marketing</urlkey><name>Internet Marketing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>15585</id><urlkey>online-marketing</urlkey><name>Online Marketing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>17742</id><urlkey>social-media-marketing</urlkey><name>Social Media Marketing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>18109</id><urlkey>website-marketing</urlkey><name>Website Marketing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>60929</id><urlkey>small-business-marketing-on-the-internet</urlkey><name>Small Business Marketing On The Internet</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>123277</id><urlkey>local-business-marketing</urlkey><name>Local Business Marketing</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name><id>1506882</id><members>938</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>10673992</member_id><name>lew</name></organizer><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/e/0/600_20145280.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/e/0/highres_20145280.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>20145280</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/e/0/thumb_20145280.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/</link><lon>-71.0400009155</lon></item>