<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>ASL Enthusiasts</who><category><shortname>language</shortname><id>16</id><name>language/ethnic identity</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;We are a group of Deaf, hard of hearing, and hearing people who meet every week to chat in ASL. This group is open to ANYONE with an interest in American Sign Language and Deaf culture, from beginning ASL students to those who are fluent. We especially encourage people to come to our group who want to HAVE FUN while socializing with all sorts of different people! This is not a study group! It's a great group for practicing having real conversations in ASL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We welcome ANYONE with an interest in ASL and Deaf culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a bunch of people who love ASL and Deaf culture, and who want to get better and better at signing. Some of us want to become interpreters or are in interpreting programs. Others work with Deaf people or have Deaf family members. We have beginner ASL students, pros, and everything in between. Some of us are Deaf and just want to hang out with other fun Deaf, hard-of-hearing, or hearing people who sign. Essentially, we are a social group brought together because we love ASL and we want to have a place where we can socialize, get to know one another, and practice our ASL skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Boston ASL welcomes and celebrates diversity in our membership! We do not tolerate audism, racism, sexism, homophobia, or any other type of discriminatory behavior at our meetings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Group rules:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;1. Please treat all members with courtesy and respect--both online and in person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;2. Membership is at the discretion of the organizers, and you can be removed from the group at any time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you at a Meetup soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erika and Sean&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note for absolute beginners: If you want to join our group and haven't taken any ASL classes, or learned the manual alphabet (ABC's), we recommend you take a class with a qualified Deaf ASL teacher. If you can't fit a class in your schedule, we recommend www.westwoodasl.com. This website provides introductory classes in ASL and is run by an excellent Deaf ASL teacher who is fully qualified. Fingerspelling lessons (ABC's) are FREE when you register on his website.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.85</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1223604065000</created><lat>42.3899993896</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>733</id><urlkey>deaf</urlkey><name>Deaf &amp; Hard of Hearing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>844</id><urlkey>asl</urlkey><name>American Sign Language</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>2500</id><urlkey>disability</urlkey><name>Living with Disabilities</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>24321</id><urlkey>deaf-culture-sign-languages</urlkey><name>Deaf Culture Sign Languages</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>25820</id><urlkey>learning-american-sign-language</urlkey><name>Learning American Sign Language</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>36014</id><urlkey>deaf-education</urlkey><name>Deaf Education</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston ASL</name><id>1298565</id><members>594</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>487803</member_id><name>Erika Wentworth</name></organizer><urlname>bostonasl</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/2/6/600_196183302.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/2/6/highres_196183302.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>196183302</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/2/6/thumb_196183302.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Somerville</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/bostonasl/</link><lon>-71.0899963379</lon></item>