<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Singers / Brothers / Friends</who><category><shortname>music</shortname><id>21</id><name>music</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;The Vocal Revolution at vocalrevolution.org (formerly Sounds of Concord) is one of New England's top performing men's a cappella choruses that loves to perform for the love of music. Chartered in the Barbershop Harmony Society (BHS), Vocal Revolution (VR for short) has been entertaining audiences for over 40 years, most recently as one of New England's top-ranked male vocal ensembles, specifically the 2012 Northeastern District (NED) Chorus Champion of the BHS. Our singing is primarily in the barbershop style: four-part close harmony with rich emotional melodies designed to captivate our audiences. Our current repertoire includes gorgeous ballads, toe-tapping swing songs, and vivacious up-tunes geared at energizing our listeners. While we specialize in traditional barbershop tunes, we enjoy all forms of a cappella music from stage and screen, spirituals, folk tunes, and patriotic songs.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 The singers of Vocal Revolution come from all walks of life, joining together to share the&lt;br&gt;

 joy of singing and fellowship. From the risers, you'll find lawyers, software programmers,&lt;br&gt;

 students, salesmen, handymen, retired men, and the list goes on. We join together to create&lt;br&gt;

 music that has the ability to affect people's lives, if only for a moment.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 Our philosophy is that if you want to do something, it's worth doing at the best of your ability!&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 Our culture consists of a diverse group of guys who bond together by one fervent passion: we&lt;br&gt;

 love to sing and we believe that changing lives through music is worth the hard work and&lt;br&gt;

 determination asked of us in Vocal Revolution. We work hard individually outside of rehearsal&lt;br&gt;

 to learn the notes and words to our songs, so that rehearsal time can be spent molding our&lt;br&gt;

 individual abilities into a holistic art form. Our consistent goal is to better ourselves, as well as&lt;br&gt;

 the chorus, as we work together to make our sound a true item of beauty. We hope you will&lt;br&gt;

 love the VR culture of warmth and encouragement; each member has his own unique&lt;br&gt;

 qualities and we love that! We are thrilled to have you experience it for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.94</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1205591261000</created><lat>42.3699989319</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>501</id><urlkey>vocalists</urlkey><name>Singers &amp; Songwriters</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>7112</id><urlkey>barbershop</urlkey><name>Barbershop Quartet</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>10578</id><urlkey>hobbies</urlkey><name>Hobbies</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Area Acapella Barbershop Quartet/Chorus Singing</name><id>1064944</id><members>65</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>34484232</member_id><name>Brandon Youngblood</name></organizer><urlname>VocalRevolution</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/3/0/600_148790992.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/3/0/highres_148790992.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>148790992</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/3/0/thumb_148790992.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Cambridge</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/VocalRevolution/</link><lon>-71.0999984741</lon></item>