<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>RI</state><who>theater lovers</who><category><shortname>arts-culture</shortname><id>1</id><name>fine arts/culture</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;If you love going to the theater, we'd love for you to come with us. Rhode Island has some amazing theater, which you have probably discovered already -- PPAC, Trinity Rep, the Gamm, Brown University, URI, etc. So whatever your passion is -- dramas, musicals, touring Broadway shows, college plays, whatever -- you can probably find a Meetup that interests you.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Ticket purchase details vary by show.  Details will be posted in the event description.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Want to see a show that is not posted as a Meetup?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;

* Post it as an idea in the Suggestions forum on our site&lt;br&gt;

* Send an email to Ron&lt;br&gt;

* Post a note on the message board, asking if anyone else wants to go&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Membership fee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;

There is currently no membership fee for joining the group.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some basics about how the group works:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

* Check our site to find plays that appeal to you.&lt;br&gt;

 * RSVP and pay for your ticket through our site or buy it from the theater.&lt;br&gt;

 * Actually come to the show (this is the important part)!&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

We have Meetups once or twice a month, and we usually go for dinner/drinks/apps before the show, which is the fun part!&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No-Show Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

The week prior to an event to which you have RSVPed "YES", you will receive an e-mail from the organizer reminding you of the event. That e-mail will also include the organizer's cell phone number. If you are unable to attend an event to which you have RSVPed yes, you have three options before the play begins:&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

1) Change your RSVP to "NO" on the site.&lt;br&gt;

2) Call the event organizer.&lt;br&gt;

3) E-mail the event organizer.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

Simply not showing up for an event to which you have RSVPed "YES" without doing one of those three constitutes a "no-show" and warrants removal from the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in the Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group you acknowledge and agree to the following: this group's activities are voluntary; the organizer of this group and the event coordinator(s) of this group's activities are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the group organizer and activity leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.55</rating><join_mode>approval</join_mode><created>1193952548000</created><lat>41.8199996948</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1459</id><urlkey>theater</urlkey><name>Theater &amp; Performance Art</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>1502</id><urlkey>art</urlkey><name>Art</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>6392</id><urlkey>musicals</urlkey><name>Musicals</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>7319</id><urlkey>museum</urlkey><name>Museum</name></topics_item></topics><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name><id>790390</id><members>305</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>8033800</member_id><name>Ron Correia</name></organizer><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/d/5/600_12093749.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/d/5/highres_12093749.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>12093749</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/d/5/thumb_12093749.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Providence</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/</link><lon>-71.4100036621</lon></item>