<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Rock Climbers</who><category><shortname>outdoors-adventure</shortname><id>23</id><name>outdoors/adventure</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Blackstone. In Septermber of 2010, Arleen Virga, the woman who started the Blackstone Rockclimbing meetup back in 2008, has passed away, succumbing to cancer. Through it all, chemo and multiple surgeries, she continued to climb -&amp;nbsp;on rock , plastic, and Ice -&amp;nbsp;as often as she could. I renamed the meetup in honor of her bravery and enthusiasm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to watch the mailing list for outdoor climbing at any of the local (worcester county) crags (Purgatory Chasm, College Rock, Crow Hill, etc) and feel free to join in! There will be trips farther afield as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday Night Training sessions at Central Rock Gym in Worcester have been instituted as regular meetups, be sure to go to the CRG website and check out the video shot there by Big Up Productions, its awesome and inspiring.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ice is here!!!! we are in the midst of the Auburn Ice canyon season, and the lines have come in well and continue to improve. So that's all good, on the other hand, the weekly 10-12 inch snowstorms we've been having weekly mean that the hike in is always a slog, so bring your snowshoes, or follow someone&amp;nbsp;who does!&amp;nbsp;or wear your gaiters and post-hole it&amp;nbsp; all the way. personally, I've done all three so far this season. see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally this meetup is more informal about connecting members with other members for partnering on the rock, or in the gym, or on the ice in winter, and thus, official meetups aren't so frequently listed. So....reiteratively, watch the Email list, and check the message board, and feel free to invite yourself along to anything that seems interesting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;see you on the rock/plastic/ice! Climb ON!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robb&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.41</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1203262333000</created><lat>42.0299987793</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1566</id><urlkey>rockclimbing</urlkey><name>Rock Climbing</name></topics_item></topics><name>The Arleen Virga Blackstone Rock Climbing Meetup</name><id>1017036</id><members>162</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>6588294</member_id><name>Robb</name></organizer><urlname>BlackstoneValley</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/e/8/600_17917608.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/e/8/highres_17917608.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>17917608</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/e/8/thumb_17917608.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Blackstone</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/BlackstoneValley/</link><lon>-71.5299987793</lon></item>