<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Climbers</who><category><shortname>outdoors-adventure</shortname><id>23</id><name>outdoors/adventure</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;Climbing can be a mentally and physically challenging, exhilarating personal adventure, but it can also be about experiencing the awesomeness of community. Come meet other local climbers for outdoor and indoor climbing, and be a part of it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our purpose is provide additional social networking opportunities for Boston-area climbers of all levels, beginner to advanced, to meet, find more climbing partners, and share climbing-related information.  We don't teach novices, or generally offer instructional programs, but we can give advice how and where to get the training and equipment you need.  Once proficient at basic skills, we can all learn further from each other, sharing tips and ideas on advanced skills, techniques, and styles.  The Boston climbing community, including this Meetup group, has cool people from many different backgrounds, and from around the globe, so you can also learn a lot about the world while sharing your passion for the vertical domain!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Seasoned climbers know it well, but to those who are new: Keep it fun by climbing smart and safe. Climbing is inherently dangerous, and any bad fall (rock, ice, or human) can result in serious injury or death. Proper training and good common sense are important to minimize risks. Your participation in any climbing activity (and any activity with this Meetup group) is AT YOUR OWN RISK. Ward Smith summed it up nicely: "If you do get hurt, don't even think about blaming someone else. You made the decision to walk up to the cliff and get on a particular route . . . instead of staying home, watching football, and eating cheese doodles like the rest of the 'free' world. Have fun, but climb safely, and take responsibility for your own actions."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.72</rating><join_mode>open</join_mode><created>1169007687000</created><lat>42.3800010681</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>1566</id><urlkey>rockclimbing</urlkey><name>Rock Climbing</name></topics_item><topics_item><id>24396</id><urlkey>ice-climbing</urlkey><name>Ice Climbing</name></topics_item></topics><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name><id>406080</id><members>1512</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>9443907</member_id><name>Deb</name></organizer><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/5/e/600_120308542.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/5/e/highres_120308542.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>120308542</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/5/e/thumb_120308542.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Cambridge</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/</link><lon>-71.1299972534</lon></item>