<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><state>MA</state><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><category><shortname>language</shortname><id>16</id><name>language/ethnic identity</name></category><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to Boston Japanese and English Language Club!　&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/pages/About_Us_%28%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E%EF%BC%89/"&gt;（日本語はこちら）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We connect language learners with native speakers of Japanese or English. Practice speaking, find out about cultures, styles, history, current events, and meet new friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who want to speak (or hear) Japanese or English can join. It is open to all ages, and all levels of skill. Generally speaking, all people are welcome to join this club, however it is expected that everyone abide by the following basic guidelines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individuals must respect one another.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Let's keep a positive attitude about things!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Let's have a really great time!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike a classroom setting, we meet in a casual environment such as a restaurant, and people just form natural conversations or practice groups. And if you are looking for a language exchange partner, you are likely to find one here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please fill your application/profile as much as possible.&lt;/strong&gt; Because we want to know who you are, what you are looking for in our group. Write up your introduction in several lines. As for language skill set, you could say "English - Native, Japanese - Beginner" or vice versa. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We may decline your application if it doesn't tell much about you&lt;/span&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are not a Dating club.&lt;/strong&gt; A lot of boys and girls come to our event, and we understand you may find someone very attractive. That's okay you get feeling to someone as long as it is appropriate and harmless. But please be careful what you say and what you do. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We do ban people if leadership team decide he/she is not appropriate to be in our club. We mean it&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is no membership cost to join this club.&lt;/strong&gt; However, utilizing meetup website cost us $144/yr. So &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We would appreciate you to make a small donation, if you are attending our events frequently and enjoy being there.&lt;/span&gt; Donation can be made from our home page, under About Us... section on the left. Donation is mainly covered this due. If we meet at a restaurant, people pay individually at the end. Some venues, such as a karaoke club, would have an equally shared cost.&lt;/p&gt;</description><rating>4.64</rating><join_mode>approval</join_mode><created>1042101769000</created><lat>42.3499984741</lat><visibility>public</visibility><topics><topics_item><id>655</id><urlkey>japanese</urlkey><name>Japanese Language and Culture</name></topics_item></topics><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name><id>86694</id><members>1364</members><country>US</country><organizer><member_id>6970020</member_id><name>Mika</name></organizer><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><group_photo><photo_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/7/4/600_23076980.jpeg</photo_link><highres_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/7/4/highres_23076980.jpeg</highres_link><photo_id>23076980</photo_id><thumb_link>http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/7/4/thumb_23076980.jpeg</thumb_link></group_photo><city>Boston</city><link>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/</link><lon>-71.0800018311</lon></item>