<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Hunt Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.836670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1486796</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;4th Annual Brew Fest!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9.23 UPDATE: We will try to meet on the stairs as you are about to head into the front of the building where you would buy your tickets to go on the OGO.  IF we are not there please call the Meetup phone and we will give you the location as to where we are at.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Amesbury Sports Park will be hosting the 4th Annual Brew Fest on Saturday, September 25th (they will be having the event from 12-8pm, but we will be attending at 5:00pm) at its facility at 12 South Hunt Road in Amesbury, MA. The Brew Fest, sponsored by WXGR and Bud Light, will feature up to 100 beers (just $10 for 10 samples), barbecue, OGO (Outdoor Gravity Orb) and summer tubing rides, and music by 6 live bands on an outdoor stage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brew Fest attracted nearly 1,400 people last year, and they are expecting north of 2,000 people to attend the all day event this year. They strive to make the event bigger and better every year, and they've made some changes in the interest of keeping things fresh and fun. There will be a beer garden sponsored by Bud Light, and they've invited their favorite craft brewers to come and talk about their beer to make it more of a personal experience. The Brew Fest will feature such crowd favorites as Sweaty Betty, Lobster Ale, Pig's Ear Brown Ale and Jack's Pumpkin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A note from Amesbury Sports Park:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After being so well received last year, we decided to make Michael Bernier &amp;amp; The Uprising the headlining band this year. Other bands include the Scott Barnett Band, the Dejas, 7 Mile Drive, McAlister Drive, and Beyond Reason.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aside from beer, BBQ and bands, the Brew Fest will feature OGO rides and summer tubing. The OGO (Outdoor Gravity Orb) is an 11 foot inflatable transparent sphere with another inflated sphere suspended inside it. Riders enter the orb and strap themselves into a harness, or enter the H2OGO with up to 3 people and 5 gallons of water and are pushed over the edge of an 800 foot grassy slope!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amesbury Sports Park will be offering up incredible giveaways all day, including Celtics and Bruins tickets, various gift certificates, and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests must be 21 or older unless accompanied by parent or legal guardian. Tickets are available online at &lt;a href="http://www.amesburysp.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amesburysp...&lt;/a&gt;. and at the door the day of the event.&amp;#65279;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Buying ticket(s) for the event:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to the website above and order your ticket(s) on line, or on the day of the event at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Updating the site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to come back and update the site when you have purchased your ticket, so we know exactly who will be coming to the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will update this as the event gets closer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have a pretty big parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that we will only wait 15 minutes to head out to this event (get some beer) if you are running late, get stuck in traffic or get lost, please call the meetup phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weather:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain may cancel this event! Check back before you head out to see if there are any updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the question is who is going to do the OGO and or with water or with out? You can check out what the OGO is all about on their website &lt;a href="http://www.amesburysp.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amesburysp...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will update this as the event gets closer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285506693000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282616152000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4th Annual Brew Fest</name><id>14520142</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285448400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/14520142/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_17433894.jpeg</photo_url></item>