<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 288-1807</phone><name>Unitarian Society of New Haven</name><city>Hamden</city><id>105528</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We had previously announced that American Humanist Ass'n President Dave Niose will be speaking to us on Sunday, August 19, about his soon to be released book, Nonbeliever Nation: The Rise of Secular Americans. In order to encourage our members to read Dave's book, we had originally decided not to schedule a regular book discussion meeting in August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several of our members have expressed an interest in meeting to discuss this book. And, the publisher has sent us a large number of pre-release copies of the book that are available for purchase now at a discounted price of &lt;span style="text-decoration : line-through"&gt;$15.25&lt;/span&gt; (correction: $16.25). So, we have decided to convene the book discussion group to discuss Nonbeliever Nation. We will meet on Sunday, August 12, at 2:00 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ordinarily, we only read books that are widely available at public libraries so that all of our members can participate in our discussions without having to purchase the books. If there is anyone who cannot afford to pay $15.25 for the book, please see June, as she has indicated that we may be able to make a few books available to our members who would otherwise not be able to obtain them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carol Siddall will have the books at the several events that we have scheduled over the next few days (Cider House Rules film screening tonight, Cider House Rules book discussion on Saturday, Monthly meeting on Monday). Please see her if you wish to purchase a book.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Blinn</member_name><member_id>588041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344866091000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342191226000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion: Nonbeliever Nation: The Rise of Secular Americans</name><id>73192122</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344794400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/73192122/</event_url></item>