<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Stony Creek Dock</address_2><address_1>30 Indian Point Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06405</zip><lat>41.264516</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-488-8905</phone><name>Sea Mist Thimble Island Cruises</name><city>Stony Creek</city><id>1001054</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.751869</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;How to find us:&lt;/span&gt; "We will meet at the Stony Creek Dock. I will be holding a Meetup sign."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a summer "must do". This is our third year doing it and it has always been a huge success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us for a relaxing cruise of the lovely Thimble Islands and learn the history and current way of life for the residents of these islands. From there, we will all drive over to "The Place" in Guilford. What a great day...a little relaxation...a great BBQ meal...terrific 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; company. WOW!!! Read on...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, the Cruise...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Captain Mike and the crew of the Sea Mist as you tour the famous Thimble Islands off the coast of Branford, Connecticut. For nearly fifty years, 1000s of seafarers have enjoyed tours and charters of the Long Island Sound with Thimble Island Cruises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sea Mist is a 44 ft. Carmen Boat of Chesepeake Design. This vessel was designed for sightseeing and private cruise with large removable windows and comfortable seating. There are two decks- the lower can be completely enclosed and heated when necessary. The upper deck is for observation under the sun or stars. Both decks have speakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for the only BLACK &amp;amp; WHITE boat with the upper deck, the pirate
 &lt;br /&gt; flag and The "Mermaid Bar " the only bar in town. We offer wine /cold beer and rum punch. We also have bottled water and soda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cruise tour price is $10.00 pp (you will pay at the dock)...Cruise is 45 min.- 1 hr. long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it's raining, give me a call. I'll let you know if we are touring! Or check your email box...I will update the day of the event if weather is threatening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you get there?
 &lt;br /&gt; Exit 56 off I-95 Go South to The Town Dock In Stony Creek&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;** PLEASE NOTE: I WILL BE HAVING 2 BOATS AGAIN THIS YEAR DUE TO THE POPULARITY OF THIS EVENT.&amp;nbsp;A SECOND BOAT HAS BEEN CONFIRMED. IF YOU SIGNED UP ALREADY ON THE WEST HTFD FUN BUNCH, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP AGAIN ON THIS SITE. YOU ARE ALREADY ON A LIST. IF ADDING GUESTS ADD THEM ON THE ORIGINAL SITE YOU SIGNE UP ON. THANKS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; A little about "the Islands".. 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; The inhabited islands bear a total of 81 houses: 14 islands have only one, one (Governor) has 14, one (Money) has 32, and the rest have between two and six. The houses are built in a variety of styles, ranging from a 27-room Tudor mansion, with tennis and basketball courts and a caretaker's residence on 7.75 acres (31,400 m2) on Rogers Island, to small summer cottages built on stilts or small clusters of buildings connected by wooden footbridges. Some of the houses cover a small island completely, while Money Island, 12 acres (49,000 m&amp;sup2;) in size, bears an entire village of 32 houses, a church and post office buildings, concealed among tall trees. Some of the houses were once occupied year-long, but now are only used in the summer. The exposed nature of the houses makes them dangerous during storms; local residents still talk about the hurricane of 1938, which killed seven people. The exclusivity of the houses has made them quite expensive, therefore residents are divided between local families who have owned their homes for generations, and more recent residents who tend to be wealthy. The least expensive houses, on Money Island, are appraised at about $600,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only six islands get electrical power through underwater cables from the shore; the rest utilize some combination of generator, solar power, batteries or kerosene and propane. About half the islands get fresh water through underwater pipes from shore; the rest utilize wells or rainwater, or have containers of water delivered. No sewers serve the islands, requiring the use of septic tanks for all sewage treatment.[5]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current and past well-known residents of the islands range from General Tom Thumb on Cut in Two Island East to Garry Trudeau, Doonesbury cartoonist and Jane Pauley, broadcast journalist. President William Taft established his "Summer White House" on Davis Island for two years. Actor Frank Converse purchased a 2-acre (8,100 m2) Thimble Island in 1975 and showman Billy Rose once owned Tavern Island. [6] Residents of the area tend to protect the privacy of island dwellers, obeying the 5-mile (8.0 km)-an-hour speed limit for motorboats and never landing without an invitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sailing through the islands can be tricky for those unfamiliar with the area, because of the disorientation caused by the myriad of similar islands (particularly at night), the hidden underwater rocks and ledges, and the complex currents caused by the tides acting on the channels between the rocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the warm season, a small ferry, Thimble Island Ferry Service , transports people and goods between the islands and the Stony Creek harbor on the hour from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m. Prior to the advent of telephones, islanders would hang a red flag on the dock to request a ferry visit. An on-call water taxi has recently been added, and three tour boats take passengers on scenic cruises; kayak tours are also available. Many residents have their own boats, and some occasionally arrive by seaplane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OK, so now you have been on the water and YOU ARE HUNGRY. On to "The Place"...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never been to The Place before? Wondering what it's all about? Not sure about the correct Place Ettiquette? Well you've come to the right place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Place is just what the sign out front says: a unique restaurant. Seating is entirely outdoors and the best tasting American cuisine is cooked right in front of you on a huge fire. It is sure to please almost any crowd...just come expecting a good time and great food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the outdoor environment, The Place is open during the warmer months from April to October, 7 days a week. Hours are extended during the summer and for holidays, and closing should only occur in extreme weather. All tables can be covered by retractable tents so the restaurant can remain open on rainy days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Place is as casual as you want it, wear whatever you like. Seat yourself at any available table when you arrive and a waitress will be out to you. You may want to bring along a cushion or two as the only seats in the house are tree stumps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything they serve is on the large menu at the back of the restaurant (see the menu on this web site.Click on the photo to enlarge the menu). Each item is a la carte, so you should order some appetizers with your main course. Normally, serving order is drinks, corn, shrimp, clams/steamers/ 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; mussels, steak/chicken/l 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; obster, dessert; please specify if you prefer otherwise. They DO NOT have hamburgers, hot dogs, or baked potatoes, nor can they cook them for you. However, you are welcome to bring whatever you like with you. Many bring a salad, bread, chips, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BYOB. They have a full line of juices, soda, coffee and tea, but do not serve alcohol. You are welcome to bring whatever you like weather it is a bottle of wine or a keg. Just please be responsible, observe the drinking age, and don't drink and drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Place does not accept credit cards, so please bring cash!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Place is located at 901 Boston Post Road
 &lt;br /&gt; Guilford, CT
 &lt;br /&gt; (203) 453-9276&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SOUND GOOD? Come out and join us. We look forward to it!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REMEMBER to bring your own bottle, if you wish beer or wine. Also, you are encouraged to bring a snack, side dish or dessert to share!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IF YOU NEED TO CONTACT ME...MY CELL IS 203-808-5829&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Terri, or Chuck, or the meetup sign...cell 203-808-5829</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chuck</member_name><member_id>11483387</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312857992000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>93</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307638985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Thimble Island Cruise and BBQ at "The Place"...</name><id>21602261</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312137000000</time><rsvp_limit>96</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/21602261/</event_url></item>