<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Coogan`s - 171 Milk Street - Boston</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coogan`s - 171 Milk Street - Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>247792</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Oct 09 - SpeedImpressions (TM) - Find Out What Kind of First Impression You Make (7:00-9:30pm)  &lt;br /&gt;Coogan`s - 171 Milk Street - Boston Ages:27-45 &lt;br /&gt;PAYMENT POLICY:&lt;br /&gt;$20 if pre-paid&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER AND PAY HERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonsxedsalon.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonsxedsalo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Been interviewing endlessly and can`t seem to find that job?&lt;br /&gt;*Do you go out a lot but have trouble connecting with your peers?&lt;br /&gt;*Wish you could know what the opposite sex is thinking while you`re on a first date or when they first meet you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What if you could get this valuable feedback? Think of how it could improve how you network, socialize and date!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is one part social experiment/one part social mixer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We`ll gather a group of people (singles and non-singles welcome) for what we`re calling ``Speed Impressions.``&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first 30 minutes will be strictly for socializing as a group. There will be someone on hand to make introductions and facilitate the mingling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, we`ll all sit down for a maximum of 7 rounds of ``speed meeting.`` You`ll meet with at least 7 people for 5 minutes each.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of each round, you`ll be asked to fill out an evaluation card after each round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What will you be evaluating/evaluated on?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Demeanor&lt;br /&gt;-Personality&lt;br /&gt;-Communication skills&lt;br /&gt;-Confidence level&lt;br /&gt;-Non-verbal cues (how you say what you say, how you present yourself, body language)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We`ll collect the evalutaion cards, take a few minutes to review them and then give you your sheets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You`ll leave this event empowered and aware! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You`re free to exchange contact information with other participants, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;``But..what if someone says something that hurts my feelings?``&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don`t worry. We will review the sheets before meeting with you and only cover what we feel is pertinent to the purpose of the consultation. It will be made clear, right away, that this is not an opportunity to be intentionally negative. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542103000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>moxiebizsocial</urlname><id>504315</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Social/Singles Networking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189127854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SpeedImpressions (TM) - Find Out What Kind of Impression You Make</name><id>6311905</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191970800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/moxiebizsocial/events/6311905/</event_url></item>