<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Cummings Center, Suite 435-K</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.558906</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 864-7076</phone><name>Eternal Balance</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1226709</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887042</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/event_124504522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The Art of Natural Breathing is a powerful form of breath work, a catalyst for transformation. The spring and summer classes will initiate a physical and spiritual clearing process. Every time you breathe the primitive and limbic part of your brain, as well as the neo cortex will form new connective patterns, allowing you to release what does not serve you any longer. Strengthening these integrative aspects of your brain, will also give your consciousness and soul a chance to fully be expressed through your physicality creating more energy and awareness. Breathing in this connected way will also help you to connect deeper with yourself and those around you. The Art of Natural Breathing is fantastic for your mind, body, relational and spiritual self. I am grateful to be in your breathing presence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dunja Carlson-Moeller Ph.D. has done extensive research and clinical training in medical anthropology. She wrote “Gentle Medicine”, a book on anthroposophical medicine. She has worked at the Center for Psychology and Social Change at Harvard Medical School, where she chaired an academic and interdisciplinary forum addressing healing and social change. Her expertise lies in an integral approach, bridging the world of western medicine and alternative health. She is both a Body Memories and The Art of Natural Breathing Master Practitioner and teacher, is certified in Postural Integration (deep tissue structural bodywork), and graduated from the Lynn Andrews Center for Sacred Arts and Training. Her private practice is located in Billerica, Massachusetts. Breathing fully and sharing it with the world has become a way of life for Dunja.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dunja uses the breath as a tool for healing, stress reduction, and increasing awareness of one’s life. The breath can be used to release and heal emotional traumas. At the time of trauma, the first thing we do is to hold our breath or take short and shallow breaths. By releasing the breath we can open up to more trust and a new perception of ourselves. Breathing exercises form the foundation of many ancient healing practices. They help to connect us to our essential selves; our source, one may say, our own spirit and will power. Deep flowing breath is a good sign of health, balance and fullness of one’s own spirit and life force. Short, weak or shallow breaths indicate stress, confusion and, generally speaking, health problems. Life is being held back. During inhalation, fresh oxygen and energy are brought into the body and organs, nourishing cells and tissues and the body’s natural energy centers. With each exhalation, the body releases carbon dioxide, waste and toxins and all the accumulated stress and anxiety. Participants will learn how their body already knows how to breathe, letting go of incomplete experiences and watching their natural breathing ability return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come find out that breathing is the essence of joy, bliss and laughter and one of the best forms of healing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expanded states of consciousness are profoundly healing. Einstein already said that you cannot fix a problem at the same level it appeared to have been created. We all need to grow and heighten our state of consciousness and breathing in a deep and connected way is a most amazing tool to do this! Experience bliss and your own divine and breathe yourself into this new time of heightened awareness. Use the tools that are available to you. For me one of the most powerful tools remains to be our breath! I look forward to breathing with you in this group setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are already breathing naturally in our sleep at night. Our inhales and exhales are uninterrupted deep and continuous. When we are awake in a conscious state, we disturb this pattern through being stressed. The first thing that we do when under stress is, we hold our breath and at times stop breathing altogether, depriving our system of needed oxygen and life force. The Art of Natural Breathing fills you with an incredible boost of Prana energy (Life Force), travelling on the breath and supplies the much needed oxygen for cellular regeneration to all our inner organs and cellular tissues, healing and rejuvenating them. We will release old emotional patterns through connecting deeply to our inhales and exhales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class is designed to help to support you to create a regular breathing practice in a safe and inspiring group setting. It is a two hour class where you will learn the foundation of breathing in a circular and open manner. Learning to take in deep inhales and relaxing on the exhale mirrors how we receive and let go of anything in our lives. We are filling our circulatory system and our internal organs with more healing power then we can imagine. Our soul and life force respond immediately to conscious breathing and reward us in connecting us to our essence and purpose. Especially during times of transition personal and seasonal our breathing tends to get sluggish. Breathing in a group setting increases the life force energy and reconnects you to a more authentic expression of your life. Give yourself the gift of breathing and the creative force of the universe will permeate and help to recreate yourself from the inside out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olga </member_name><member_id>10158912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339822073000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members with unlimited potential</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club</urlname><id>1467921</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Holistic Lifestyle  Women's Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338336579000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art of Natural Breathing</name><id>66855052</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339714800000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club/events/66855052/</event_url></item>