<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02133</zip><lat>42.335347</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>900281</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.153409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The public nomination hearing before the Mass. Governor's Council of Roderick Ireland to be the new Chief Justice of the Massachusetts Supreme Judicial Court will take place at the State House on Dec. 1, at 10 AM, in the State House Hearing Room B-2.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hearing is extremely important, especially for men and fathers, as the Chief Justice has a direct influence in how the courts are run and whether there will be change for the better in issues affecting fathers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone can speak at the hearing, either in favor or in oppostion to the nomination. The Fatherhood Coalition has sent Judge Ireland a &lt;a href="http://www.fatherhoodcoalition.org/images/Roderick%20Ireland_letter_to.doc" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;letter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href="http://www.fatherhoodcoalition.org/images/Roderick_Ireland_Questionnaire" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;questionnaire&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to which all judicial nominees are expected to respond.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More people are paying attention to the direct affect judges have on everyone's lives. This is the last and only opportunity to speak up about this nomination. In Massachusetts, once a nominee is confirmed it is a lifetime position. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Governor Council is made up of eight members. Lt. Governor Murray is likely&lt;br /&gt;to preside at this hearing making it a body of nine. After introductions, the Lt. Gov. will ask those in favor of the nominee to testify, during which they may be asked questions by the Councilors. Following this, those who oppose the nomination are asked to testify and they also may be questioned by the Councilors.  The nominee is then asked to make a statement. There is no direct questioning of the nominee except by the Councilors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Written testimony and statements may be presented to the Council at any time before the final vote on the nomination which will take place on the following Wed., Dec. 8.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please attend and make your opinion on this nomination known.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info: 857 350-0575&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for directions for the hearing room when you enter the State House.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joseph Ureneck</member_name><member_id>8050884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291220396000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fathers' Rights Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Greater-Boston-Chapter-of-The-Fatherhood-Coalition</urlname><id>1412531</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Chapter of The Fatherhood Coalition</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290521367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nomination of Roderick Ireland to be Chief Justice of MA Supreme Judicial Court</name><id>15535833</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291215600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Chapter-of-The-Fatherhood-Coalition/events/15535833/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/b/global_7743227.jpeg</photo_url></item>