<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Bulls Bridge Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06785</zip><lat>41.677983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Spring Center, Kent School</name><city>South Kent</city><id>1336959</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.474236</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>2010 marks the 15th Anniversary of The Litchfield Jazz Festival. LJF continues the tradition of showcasing jazz legends and fostering up-and-coming talent as we've done since 1996. &amp;quot;Nothing beats the Litchfield Jazz Festival…an ongoing tradition for those in the know.&amp;quot; -- JazzImprov.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a fantastic line up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 7th Gabriel Alegria Afro-Per08-6-uvian Sextet Gerald Clayton Trio Dave Samuels Caribbean Jazz Project Mario Pavone Orange Double Tenor Sextet with support from Chamber Music American and The Doris Duke Charitable Foundation All-Star Cannonball Adderley Tribute featuring Wess Anderson, Terell Stafford, Benny Green, Matt Wilson, and Joanna Pascale Arturo O’Farrill Afro Latin Jazz Orchestra  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Festival Starts on Friday and runs through Sunday.  Besides world renown artist there will be exotic crafts, Fantastic food, and of course wonderful music. Come bring a chair and we will picnic on the lawn so bring a appetizer to share. We can not bring wine but they will sell wine, and beer inside the festival.   All though the festival starts at 12pm.  I thought we could meet at 5pm, I will be there at 12pm but you folks can wonder in and out when ever you like. The last performance will be at 8:45 pm on Saturday evening. To purchase tickets go to  &lt;a href="http://www.litchfieldjazzfest.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.litchfield...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281219022000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280659739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Litchfield Jazz Festival"  You Don't Want To Miss</name><id>14278520</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281214800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/14278520/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/1/global_4236481.jpeg</photo_url></item>