<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Purity is not just about what you put into your body, but also your thoughts, feelings, and actions. In this lecture, Mother Clare Watts, Christian Master Teacher, will introduce you to the subtleties that raise consciousness and increase your awareness for your life. This will awaken you to a new reality that will bring you peace and happiness you have yet to know or experience. Don't wait another minute&amp;hellip; &lt;br /&gt;

 Suggested Donation: $35 - Lunch Included - Bring a Friend for Free! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare Watts is an ordained Priest and Master Teacher in the Order of Christ-Sophia. &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare founded the Boston Center of Light, formerly called the Christ-Sophia Center, &lt;br /&gt;

 where she continued to serve until 2001. At that time she moved to Seattle to begin a new Center of Light. Mother Clare live in Dolores Colorado where she supervise the effort of the Sophia Peace Center. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare worked as a Certified Professional Midwife for 18 years, having her own midwifery practices in Kentucky and Massachusetts. She received her Masters Degree in 1996 in Counseling Psychology. Mother Clare attended three years of postgraduate training in Jungian Analysis at the Boston Jung Institute. She had her own psychotherapy practice alongside her midwifery practice until she ended both in 2001 in order to attend full-time to her work as a Priest and Master Teacher. Mother Clare has four grown children. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare is the author of an autobiographical book chronicling her life of spiritual seeking and the process that led to her being ordained into spiritual Mastery in the Christian mystical tradition. Please visit www.MotherClareWatts.com, to read excerpts and order her book, Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path to Enlightenment. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev Michaela Newheart</member_name><member_id>6251183</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321838892000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319137044000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Purity and the Link to Happiness</name><id>38124102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321714800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/38124102/</event_url></item>