<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This is our 7th monthly video screening in Nashua&lt;/b&gt;. We have screenings every Tuesday somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: &lt;b&gt;1st Tuesday-Nashua&lt;/b&gt;; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesday-North (it looks like this will change location from Plymouth to Bristol). If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, we'll have a special meeting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This month in Nashua we will see &lt;a href="http://fabledenemies.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Fabled Enemies: Extras&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, by Jason Bermas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fabled Enemies&lt;/b&gt; by Jason Bermas is the latest film to question the events of September 11th 2001. Instead of the focus being on physical anomolies surrounding the attacks, it focuses on a vast intelligence network and how they were able to succeed almost 7 years ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Last month we saw the main video&lt;/b&gt; presentation. In this viewing we'll see the extras included in the DVD - extended interviews: Barry Jenning (trapped inside WTC7 - witness to explosions before the collapse of WTC 1&amp;amp;2), among others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After two separate government investigations into 9/11 you would think that the public would be satisfied with their efforts and conclusions. However we show you how both the Congressional Report and the 9/11 Commission Report were a whitewash and a scam to begin with, and how it was used to manipulate the public into believing the issue had been dealt with and thouroghly explained.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Getting to the truth is left to us!&lt;/b&gt; Let's measure up to the task.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;9-11 Cinema Before The Fact!&lt;/b&gt; - After the feature video, we should have time to view the latest edit of &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;9-11 Cinema Before The Fact&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;, a short video presentation of excerpts from 13 feature movies or TV episodes which had references to 9/11 or 9/11-like terror plots - all before 9/11/01! Things that make you go &amp;quot;hmmm&amp;quot;! The filmmaker has been kind enough to share his pre-release edits with our audience for critique. Who knows? - the film-maker may even drop by!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;After the video presentations&lt;/b&gt;, we'll go over the New England 9/11 Truth strategy meeting that was held in Keene a couple of weeks back and how each attender can help implement this strategy, as well as become more involved and spread the workload of running a meetup like this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We'll have free DVD's&lt;/b&gt; and DVD's and books for sale. Everyone should bring their collection for trading, viewing, copying, etc. Bring your favorite books, too. We've developed a collection of books for sale at these various meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donations&lt;/b&gt; - we ask for a donation in the $5 range to help us continue to build our library of books, DVD's and other materials. Please come in any event if you can't afford the $5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at 7:00 PM&lt;/b&gt;, since this meeting is on a tight schedule. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and the video will begin promptly at 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please bring snacks and/or drinks&lt;/b&gt; for sharing, since some may have come to our meeting directly from work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt; is in the lot in front of the building. Please enter the right entry doorway and suite 135 will be directly ahead of you. After entering the office, turn left to go to the video viewing room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpooling&lt;/b&gt; - Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online at &lt;a href="http://mv911t.eRideShare.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mv911t.eRideSh...&lt;/a&gt;. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, &lt;b&gt;donations to the driver&lt;/b&gt; for the ride-sharing are appreciated to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy fixing tea for everyone</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228532792000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226604185000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Fabled Enemies: Extras</name><id>9156452</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228262400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/9156452/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/4/f/global_6058431.jpeg</photo_url></item>