<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1546 Hancock St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.247482</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 770-1546</phone><name>Fuji 1546</name><city>Quincy</city><id>335715</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.001170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Does the quality of your speaking ability effect the quality of your job? Your business?  Your relationships?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course it does!!! The way you talk effects every aspect of your life.  &amp;quot;Communicating Effectively in Business&amp;quot; is the topic of this month's networking event... I have been a member of Toastmasters International for less than 2 years and I have to admit it is the best thing I have done to improve myself and my business.  Many other members would agree.  This month I will have guest speakers of Toastmasters to share their experience and what they have been able to accomplish.  For more information about this world wide organization, please go to www.toastmasters.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Network with like minded individuals and professionals!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's Time to Move Up&amp;quot; is a movement in the real estate industry with a mission of educating the public about anything concerning real estate and home ownership. With all the challenges the community is facing such as defaults and foreclosures, the only way to prevent them from happening in the future is to be more educated.  The commitment to education is communicated via a TV show, streaming video information via websites such as YouTube, home buyer worskshops, blogs, vlogs, and of course in our monthly networking events in which we invite business professionals and anyone interested in networking. Check out the website at &lt;a href="http://www.itstimetomoveup.tv" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.itstimetom...&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Agenda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00pm - 7:00pm -&amp;gt; Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;7:00pm - 7:15pm -&amp;gt; Introduction by Ruben B. Austria&lt;br /&gt;7:15pm - 7:45pm -&amp;gt; &amp;quot;Communicating Effectively in Business&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;7:45pm - 8:00pm -&amp;gt; Q &amp;amp; A Session&lt;br /&gt;8:00pm - 9:00pm -&amp;gt; Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appetizers will be served... Check out the venue website at &lt;a href="http://www.fuji1546.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fuji1546.c...&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event will be sponsored by Maxima Mortgage Solutions, visit at &lt;a href="http://www.maximamortgages.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.maximamort...&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time for a change... It's Time to Move Up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make it a great day,&lt;br /&gt;Ruben&lt;br /&gt;raustria@maximamortgages.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187820130000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>realestateinvestor</urlname><id>596743</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>InvestorsBeat.com - Massachusetts Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185930205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's Time to Move Up! -  "Communicating Effectively"</name><id>6106416</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187647200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestateinvestor/events/6106416/</event_url></item>