<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>83 Exchange Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.660000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207-321-2050</phone><name>O'Naturals</name><city>Portland</city><id>221392</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.260002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This month we're reading:  Gaia's Garden, A guide to home-scale permaculture by Toby Hemenway; More info: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio/1-1890132527-0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please buy locally if you don't have this book!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  Pls feel free to come even if you didn't finish the book!  It's not a novel, after all:)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some *prep questions* to review while reading or before the reading group meetup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[page 18ff] What do you think of his concept of applying &amp;quot;three ecological principles&amp;quot; to backyard gardening (finding a niche, gardening in succession, and backyard biodiversity)?  Do you see these as practical improvements over the way you have done things in the past?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[p45ff] Think about his discussion of using patterns in the landscape.  What are some of the patterns he recommends and what are some other ones you would suggest?  What are the benefits of mimicking natural patterns?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[p71ff] Despite the popularity of sheet mulching and &amp;quot;no till&amp;quot; methods in permaculture, this practice is still viewed very skeptically by mainstream - and even organic - growers and gardeners.  Why do you think that is?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[p81ff] What are some of the most common ways that permaculture incorporates water into the landscape?  Why is this important?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you Tuesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Permaculture Reading Group gets together on the last Tuesday of each month (Jan-Apr and Sept-Nov) for about 1.5 hours to chat about a certain permaculture text or article.  This is envisioned as a smaller, optional group (5-8 people each month) who want to learn more about permaculture through self-study, reading and group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170363881000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1165602367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January Permaculture Reading Group</name><id>5315495</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170190800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/5315495/</event_url></item>