<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>PelletDb: Scalable, Expressive Semantic Reasoning for the Enterprise -&lt;br /&gt;Hector Perez Urbina&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this presentation we will describe use cases and applications of PelletDb -- the first and only OWL 2 reasoner for Oracle Database 11g R2, providing scalable and correct OWL reasoning. Built on Pellet and Oracle Database Semantic Technologies, PelletDb provides an integrated solution for OWL 2 reasoning in the enterprise: more scalable reasoning with world-class information management capabilities and more expressive reasoning with best-of-breed OWL reasoner. The presentation will explain current capabilities of PelletDb 1.0 and future features such as next-generation OWL 2 QL reasoning system and closed-world instance data validation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Integrity constraint semantics for OWL: Using OWL as a data validation language for Linked Data - Evren Sirin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Web Ontology Language (OWL) is a powerful knowledge representation language but, in many real-life applications, developers face problems with OWL because it does not allow Closed World reasoning. Without Closed World assumption, what would trigger a constraint violation in a traditional RDBMS causes an OWL reasoner to compute new inferences. This talk will present a solution to overcome this problem by treating some parts of an OWL ontology (designated by the ontology engineer) as integrity constraints rather than inference rules. This approach enables combining open world reasoning with closed world validation in a principled way and allows one to use OWL ontologies for validating instance data such as the ones published as part of Linked Data.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Making Meaningful Use of Electronic Medical Records at Cleveland Clinic - David Booth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2003 Cleveland Clinic has used semantic web technology to help integrate and analyze data from 200,000 patients with cardiovascular disease in order to measure the effectiveness of different treatments and monitor the quality of patient care in terms of patient outcomes. This data originates in a variety of systems, formats and vocabularies, and must be semantically integrated in order to make meaningful use of it.  This presentation outlines some of the practical issues faced, and describes how some these issues are being addressed and others need more work.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Star Conference Room. 4th Floor, Stata Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marco Neumann</member_name><member_id>2316446</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lee Feigenbaum</member_name><member_id>8546101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274100912000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>18</count></rating><group><who>Semantic Web Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1336198</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge Semantic Web</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>55</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269427370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Cambridge Semantic Web meetup</name><id>gzndnynhbpb</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273615200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group/events/12977043/</event_url></item>