<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02876</zip><lat>41.999748</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Eagle Point</name><city>North Smithfield</city><id>6884352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.580421</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>150.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This workshop must have at least 4 people registered to run.  If it doesn't run due to the number of people registered you will have to register for another date that has at least 4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If inclement weather occurs on the day of a workshop it will be cancelled and you can sign up for a future date listed on this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring your camera with a fully charged battery and the camera's manual.  If you have a tripod please bring it as well.  You may also want to bring a chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also if you are using a GPS to get to this address it sent some people to town hall which is right up the street from the library, so please make sure you are in the library parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 1: Getting to Know Your Digital Camera &lt;br /&gt;

 Understanding your camera controls and functions. The five most valuable features. Features to avoid. Checklist of what your camera can and cannot do. How to get the most out of your digital camera. The biggest advantage of shooting digital: the right way to use your LCD monitor. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment:  Camera Functions Questionnaire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 2: Controlling White Balance and Other Aspects, In-Camera &lt;br /&gt;

 The color of light for the non-physics major. Understanding the white balance options. The easy way to getting the correct white balance. Adjusting the in-camera level for sharpening and color saturation. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: White Balance Before and After; also, Saturation/Sharpness Before and After&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 3: Composition, Tripods and Lens Choice &lt;br /&gt;

 Principles of visual design. Putting the Rule of Thirds to good use. An easy way to understand the Golden Rectangle. Shooting vertical as well as horizontal photos. Understanding lens focal lengths. Wide angle and telephoto options with digital SLR "focal length magnification factors". &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Rule of Thirds/Orientation: Before and After&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson 4: Digital Exposure 101 &lt;br /&gt;

 The primary exposure concepts. Why cameras sometimes make images that are too dark. Using Exposure Compensation, a simple method for perfect exposures. Learn where to meter from and use Exposure Lock. The part ISO plays in exposure. Tip: Use a Semi Automatic mode while maintaining full control. &lt;br /&gt;

 Assignment: Exposure: Over, Under and Just Right&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the back of the North Smithfield Public Library Parking Lot.  Look for my silver van with black cargo top.  Phone # 401-285-1501</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary</member_name><member_id>7489043</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349622112000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1534645</id><group_lat>41.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6600036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341702814000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3 Hour Outdoor Introduction to Digital Photography Workshop</name><id>ddgkwcyqmbnc</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349611200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Photography-Workshops/events/72382632/</event_url></item>