<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We'll be joining in from 8:30 AM to about 1 PM on the trail maintenance project on the Cockaponset Trail in Haddam, CT that the Connecticut Forest and Park Association (CFPA) is hosting and the &amp;quot;Enduro Club&amp;quot; is sponsoring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tools will be provided. Be dressed for outdoor work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NATIONAL TRAILS DAY PROJECT ON THE COCKAPONSET TRAIL&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;CONTEXT...&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;American Hiking Society's National Trails Day&lt;/b&gt;® (NTD), is held the first Saturday of every June and with more than 1000 events hosted by trail and community groups, public agencies, and businesses from coast to coast, is America's largest celebration of trails and the outdoors.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;American Hiking Society&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americanhiking.org/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americanhi...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Cockaponset Trail&lt;/b&gt; This is a Blue-Blazed Hiking Trail (BBHT) in the Cockaponset State Forest. It is is one of over 45 miles of blazed trails in the State Forest and is part of a network of BBHTs and the larger Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) network. This trail is marked with the standard CFPA 2X6&amp;quot; light blue painted blaze. The other CFPA trails use a blue/red blaze. The trail crosses numerous other trails and forest roads. The majority of the Cockaponset Trail was built by the CCC's in the late 1930's and many of their efforts can still be seen in the form of stone staircases and retaining walls. The trail is moderately difficult with no large hills or obstacles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Connecticut Forest and Park Association (CFPA)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctwoodlands.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctwoodland...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PROJECT DETAILS...&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Events Planned:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Trail Maintenance/Construction: 2 mile(s) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pre-Registration:&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 8:30 for sign in and coffee and donuts provided by CFPA. Following a safety lecture we'll go out and work on various projects on the orange and orange/white trails. Projects will include, moving stone for a bridge approach, cutting in side hill on a reroute, water bar construction and cleaning, trimming and other trail maintenace type work. Tools will be provided, but you're welcome to bring your own. Bring bug spray, water, a snack and something for the pot-luck. Please dress appropiately for a day in the woods. High winds or heavy rain cancel. Rain date is June 6. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Sponsored:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enduro club &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Host Organization:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut Forest and Park Association &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Host Contact Phone:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;860-345-8029&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Host Contact Email:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert.Butterworth@arrisi.com &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;AFTER THE WORK IS DONE...&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;After the work join us (the whole group working) for a pot-luck cook out in the forest. Meat will be provided by LCRVHC, so bring a salad or desert to add to the mix.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;GETTING THERE...&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* CT RT9 to Exit 8 Beaver Meadow Rd&lt;br /&gt;* East on Beaver Meadow Rd to first right on to Weiss Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Weiss Rd to end. Turn right on to Filley Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Filley Rd to first right (gravel) on to Jericho Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Jericho Rd approx 1/4 mile to parking in sandpit on the left. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; for meetup location via MapQuest (Intersection of Jericho Rd. with Filley Rd., Haddam, CT -&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Go additional 1/4 mile on Jericho Rd. to park in sandpit on left&lt;/span&gt;):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Haddam&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=299+Filley+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06438-1209&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.445914&amp;amp;longitude=-72.525226&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at event location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275938714000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270426673000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Trail Days Project on Cockaponset Trail, Haddam CT</name><id>13085997</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275741000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13085997/</event_url></item>