<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The day is so nice and sunny after the rains I can't help but hike! Sorry about the late notice but weather and work finally cleared. This is an out-and-back style hike (may loop depending on conditions and temperament) where we'll aim to hike 3 hours max. with turnaround at about 1.5 hrs. out. There is plenty of trail so we'll see how far we can go and explore. I figure 4 - 5 miles of hiking. I'll check signups once at about 12:30 PM today. It might be best to give me a call on my cell if you plan to attend and if you RSVP after 1 PM today, the day of the hike. My cell is in my RSVP. We'll hike mostly on the white blaze trail that runs the spine of the giant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike would start from the trailhead off of the paved parking lot across from Quinnipiac University. The hike would be moderately difficult with a fair amount of up/down on the trail and a respectable length of a hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the parking lot at 2 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be about 46 F with 12 MPH winds for the hike so wear light layers for warmth (avoid cotton material). Might be good to have a daypack to stow layers shed as you warm up. water, snack. Wear boots as it WILL be muddy after the rains! Bring a quart of water and some trail food/lunch for energy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions via MapQuest for parking lot off Mt. Carmel Rd.: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/slaeeping+giant+state+park:Hamden+CT/#a/maps/l:Sleeping+Giant+State+Park:200+Mount+Carmel+Ave:Hamden:CT:06518:US:41.420936:-72.897674:address:/m:hyb:12:41.420935:-72.897674:0::/io:0:::::f:EN:M:/e" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/sleepgiant.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More park information at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325264&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one in Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205777181000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>The rain will be gone, the sky will open to show some sun, Spring is in the air... why not hike!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205582513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Sleeping Giant State Park in Hamden CT</name><id>7537814</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205604000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7537814/</event_url></item>