<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Guest Speaker: Harvey Weinstein / How to Use Your IRA’s to purchase Real Estate&lt;br /&gt;Q &amp;amp; A&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other Topics: By a leading apartment owners/investors…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * 15-Ways to Fill Your Vacancies&lt;br /&gt;    * Avoiding the Eviction Process / 99% Fool Proof Method&lt;br /&gt;    * Buying in “this” market&lt;br /&gt;    * Q &amp;amp; A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What are you waiting for?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How is your IRA account doing? How much did it lose this past year?&lt;br /&gt;Wary of stocks? Bonds? Investors who want to diversify their nest egg are using real estate as another option for their retirement account.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now is the best time to scoop up property at a fraction of true value.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need to pay attention to your iRA or 403b or 401k accounts. Analyze your current retirement investments and ask yourself: What will I do differently next year with my account to grow it faster?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many investors neglect their retirement account, and its left to languish at the hands of the broker, mutual fund or bank-- and don’t grow fast enough to meet your retirement needs. Don’t wait until retirement to calculate what you don’t have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the greatest current boom to buying real estate at depressed prices-- and invest in real estate as part of your retirement accounts. And do it without incurring taxes or penalties in transferring your IRA to real estate investments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investors find it appealing that they can invest in real estate and receive tax-free income and growth on these investments if it is bought inside their retirement accounts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can invest in all types of real estate including foreclosures, pre-foreclosures, probate, and rental property- while owning it from only one day to many years Also, you can invest in tax liens, or become a hard money lender and earn high interest loan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here are some strategies that you can use for both small and large balance accounts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use your IRA as down payment, or partner your IRA with your personal funds, or with relatives, or other investors.&lt;br /&gt;Buy wholesale and sell for higher priceUse creative financing and get owner financing, or use options and “flip” contractsLend money to investors&lt;br /&gt;Use other people’s IRA accounts for YOUR purchases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;But where do you begin and how do you get true investment freedom?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are some IRA custodians who will open a self-directed IRA for real estate purchase but require that you get their prior permission to buy property; wait several days to get checks to buy the property or pay your bills, and pay high custodian fees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Now, there is a better, more powerful way that’s popular with investors:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can structure your self-directed IRA so that you obtain absolute control of the investment decision and operation-- by using checkbook control, with you as the signor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By using a self-directed IRA in a Flex-Pay IRA, you benefit with a quick and convenient way to buying all investments with a check. You can purchase foreclosure and other property and tax liens on the spot by simply writing a check from your IRA. It’s also great to use to run a rental business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you want to avoid lawsuits and protect your other investments? You can create asset protection for all your money by using a special IRA-LLC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;But be careful…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Self-directed IRA can produce great returns, but there are specific guidelines an investor must adhere to. This is why many recommend that people not try to structure these investments themselves without the help of a qualified professional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Learn more…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several ways and techniques to use your IRA. Come to our workshop next month, and learn “The Insider’s Guide to Tax-free Profits in Real Estate”. You’ll learn strategies to make your money work harder. You’ll hear about the opportunities and the tricks to using other people’s money, as well as the IRS traps you must avoid.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232405541000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230530379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Apartment Owners Association of CT Monthly Meeting</name><id>9400427</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232063100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/9400427/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/f/global_6764431.jpeg</photo_url></item>