<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/8/event_54184712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YIN YOGA&lt;/strong&gt; ~ A softer, gentler form of yoga seems to be quietly on the rise. Come enjoy this 75 minute class.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yin Yoga is essentially a stretching practice that focuses on increasing your flexibility, cooling the body and calming the mind. Stretches are held for up to five minutes. By holding a pose and relaxing into it, you'll gently tug at the deep, dense connective tissues of the body: tendons, ligaments and cartilage, which are drier and less elastic than muscles and difficult to keep healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This practice elongates the spine and opens the hips, and is very restorative and rehabilitative for the joints and muscles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yin Yoga is based on traditional Chinese medicine and the theory that our body&amp;rsquo;s network of connective tissue corresponds with the meridians (energy channels) of acupuncture. Therefore, strengthening and stretching connective tissue may be critical for your long-term health by keeping these energy channels - and corresponding organs - functioning optimally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yin yoga is an excellent complement to other styles of yoga and exercise and is especially good at enhancing your performance in sports such as running, cycling, tennis, golf and skiing. Set to relaxing music, most of the poses are seated and held for 3-5 minutes. This practice leaves the yoga practitioner with an overall sense of lightness, spaciousness and relaxation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some benefits include a deeper range of motion, an increased flow of energy, healthier joints, improved health, greater strength, reduced stress levels. Beneficial to all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No Yoga experience needed, all levels welcome &amp;amp; encouraged to attend. Your joints will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please call (857-526-2200) or email me at namaste143@mac.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow the walkway in the back of the house into the studio.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darnell</member_name><member_id>10396246</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369067699000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightenment Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ShantiShala</urlname><id>1534948</id><group_lat>41.9599990845</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8099975586</group_lon><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272803069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yin Yoga with Darnell</name><id>sjtnnyrhbbc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369056600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ShantiShala/events/119326242/</event_url></item>