<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Lunch after the walk for those interested.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors Center Hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maps and Brochures &lt;br /&gt;   Borderland is one of the most historically significant tracts of publicly owned land in the Commonwealth. Created in the early 1900s by artist and suffragist Blanche Ames and her botanist husband Oakes, Borderland offers many of the same pleasures that the Ames family enjoyed: walking and horseback riding on woodland trails, fishing and canoeing in the ponds, or, in winter, ice-skating and sledding. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;approximately three miles from the center of Sharon, Mansfield and North Easton, Massachusetts; the park is twenty miles from Boston and thirty miles from Providence, RI. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From north: Take Rte. 128 south to Rte. 95 south (towards Providence). Take exit 10 (Sharon, Walpole and Coney Street). Take a left at the end of the ramp and follow this road, two or three miles to the traffic lights in Sharon Center. Go straight thru this intersection and immediately bear right onto Pond St. Follow Pond St. for 1-1/2 miles until you come to a traffic rotary. Go half way around the rotary and continue onto Massapoag Ave. for three miles to the park entrance, on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: Take the southeast expressway south to Rte. 128 north and then to Rte. 95 south. Follow directions from above.&lt;br /&gt;From west: Mass Pike to Rte. 495 south to exit 10 (Easton and Rte. 123). Take a left at the end of the ramp and follow Rte. 123 east towards Easton. Rte. 123 will merge with Rte. 106 east. After this merge look for the brown &amp;quot;Borderland&amp;quot; sign, on the left about a half mile from the merge. Take this left onto Poquanticut Ave. After about a mile the road will fork, bear to the left onto Massapoag Ave. and follow the signs to the park, approximately another two miles. Entrance will be on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202227575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199639104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking February Meetup</name><id>7044873</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202054400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/7044873/</event_url></item>