<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;THRIVE is an unconventional documentary that lifts the veil on what's REALLY going on in our world by following the money upstream -- uncovering the global consolidation of power in nearly every aspect of our lives. Weaving together breakthroughs in science, consciousness and activism, THRIVE offers real solutions, empowering us with unprecedented and bold strategies for reclaiming our lives and our future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supporting Thrive: The Movement (www.thrivemovement.com), which is committed to assist humanity in thriving through the evolutionary challenges threatening our survival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It's also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people! These events are free, and if you would like to give a donation, we will send it to an organization that's truly helping the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335718773000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335196547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night - THRIVE: What on Earth Will It Take?</name><id>61764322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335654000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/61764322/</event_url></item>