<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>401 Technology Center Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02072</zip><lat>42.156460</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-297-5110</phone><name>The Olive Garden</name><city>Stoughton</city><id>303903</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064880</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for an Italian luncheon @ The Olive Garden in Stoughton.  They are famous for their salad and Italian dinners.  They also offer other fish, seafood, chicken, beef and pork.  They also offer a great soup and unlimited salad for lunch.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant is large enough to accommodate as many people as are interested in attending, however, they are limited in taking reservations to extremely large parties, so once we have more than twelve or fifteen people attending I will call to see about making some kind of reservation.  The only other option is to arrive really early or to call ahead and hope we don't have to wait too long to be seated.  It will be important for you to update your RSVP if you are no longer able to attend so we will be able to give the restaurant an accurate number of diners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch prices start around $4 for appetizers and salads with entrees starting around $6.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 14th @ 12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;401 Technology Center Drive&lt;br /&gt;Stoughton, MA 02072&lt;br /&gt;781-297-5110&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max:  None.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 4pm on Friday, July 13th (Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer prior to the event.)&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer: Angela&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: Please meet at the hostess station.  If it is a nice day outside then we will probably be outside the front door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash.  You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Rte. 24:  Take Exit 20A on Rt. 139 East towards Randolph.  (Yes, towards Randolph.)  Take a right at the 1st light onto Technology Center Drive.  (The Courtyard Marriott will be straight ahead to your left once you make the turn.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Randolph Center: Follow Rt. 139 towards Rt. 24 and Stoughton. go stright thru the lights in front of the Cinema and take a left at the last set of lights onto Technology Center Drive.  (The Courtyard Marriott will be straight ahead to your left once you make the turn.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Stoughton area: Take Rt. 139 East and follow towards Randolph.  After going over Route 24, take a right at the 1st light onto Technology Center Drive.  (The Courtyard Marriott will be straight ahead to your left once you make the turn.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once on Technology Center Drive: Follow about 1/4-1/2 mile passing the pond/water on your right.  The Olive Garden will be on the right side behind Smokey Bones.  If you pass Kohl's you have gone too far.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184603777000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182096518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Italian Luncheon!</name><id>5901478</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184430600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5901478/</event_url></item>