<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Brattle Theater on the 20th anniversary of &lt;b&gt;Twin Peaks&lt;/b&gt; will be screening on Thursday the first four episodes of the surreal, quirky, and downright weird series by David Lynch that got everybody talking, Twin Peaks. Not sure if our passes for Brattle Members can be used for these. Never heard of the series? Think of it as a weirder grandaddy of Lost, where everybody is a bit off, mysteries aren't always solved, and sometimes, there aren't any answers as Special Agent Dale Cooper -- a loonie, himself -- tries to answer the question... who killed Laura Palmer? At least there is damned good pie! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Brattle Website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/100408.html#e" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tickets $9.75 each screening, or purchase the All Episode Pass for $25/$20 Brattle Members - includes admission to all Twin Peaks screenings April 8–11. This is a Special Event, no other passes or discounts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;2010 marks the 20th anniversary of David Lynch’s legendary TV series, TWIN PEAKS, and to celebrate the Brattle will be presenting the complete series in segments over the course of the year. To kick off this momentous event, we’re screening the complete first season over four days (2 episodes per day) starting on the anniversary of the pilot’s broadcast! Join us in revisiting the quirkiest town in America and one of television’s most engrossing mysteries – the murder of town sweetheart Laura Palmer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Thur 4/8&lt;/u&gt;: Pilot + Episode 2 at 7:00 PM; Episodes 3 + 4 at 9:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Fri 4/9&lt;/u&gt;: Episodes 3 + 4 at 10:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Sat 4/10&lt;/u&gt;: Episodes 5 + 6 at 10:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Sun 4/11&lt;/u&gt;: Episodes 7 + 8 at 10:00 PM&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... The entire first season, the best and most highly rated of the series, was only eight episodes long. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Care to grab a bite to eat? T.J. Maher will be on the lower level food court of &lt;b&gt;The Garage&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-garage-cambridge" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; at 36 JFK Street in Flat Patties next to Subway. He should be getting there at 5:40 pm. Feel free to drop by! We should head to the Brattle and grab seats by 6:40 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, wish short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Twin Peaks, according to Wikipedia:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Twin_Peaks" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Twin Peaks is an American television serial drama created by David Lynch and Mark Frost. The series follows the investigation, headed by Special Agent Dale Cooper (Kyle MacLachlan), of the brutal murder of a popular teenager and homecoming queen, Laura Palmer (Sheryl Lee). Twin Peaks' pilot episode was first broadcast on April 8, 1990 on the ABC Network, which led to another seven episodes being produced, and a second season, which aired until June 10, 1991. The show's name came from its setting, a small fictional Washington town. Exteriors were primarily filmed in Snoqualmie and North Bend; most of the interior scenes were shot on standing sets in a San Fernando Valley warehouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Twin Peaks became one of 1990s' top-rated shows, a critical success both nationally and internationally. Reflecting its devoted cult fan base, the series became a part of popular culture, referenced in other television shows, commercials, comic books, video games, films and song lyrics. Declining viewer ratings led to ABC's insistence that the identity of Laura's murderer be revealed midway through the second season, a ratings ploy which interfered with several other long-running story lines. In 1992, the series spawned a prequel, the film Twin Peaks: Fire Walk with Me, a commercial failure in America. In 2007 Twin Peaks was listed as one of Time magazine's '100 Best TV Shows of All-TIME.'&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Do not watch Twin Peaks: Fire Walk with Me. It will spoil the central mystery of the series if you have not seen it already. It also doesn't really capture the mystique of the show, exactly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Characters:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Twin_Peaks" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Twin Peaks features members of a loose ensemble of Lynch's favorite character actors, including Jack Nance, Kyle MacLachlan, Grace Zabriskie, and Everett McGill. Isabella Rossellini, who had worked with Lynch on Blue Velvet, was originally cast as Giovanna Packard, but she dropped out of the production before shooting began on the pilot episode. The character was then reconceived as Josie Packard, of Chinese ethnicity, and the role given to actress Joan Chen. It is also notable for the casting of several veteran actors who had long been absent from the screen, including 1950s movie stars Richard Beymer, Piper Laurie and Russ Tamblyn, and former The Mod Squad star Peggy Lipton. The main character of the series, Agent Dale Cooper, played by Kyle MacLachlan, would appear in all thirty episodes of Twin Peaks, including the pilot&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions and Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The building is shared with Algiers Cafe, Casablanca Restaurant, and Harvard Square Optical, and the theatre entrance is on the left side of the building—look for our sidewalk poster case and marquee. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;On-Street Parking&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Metered parking spaces are available throughout Harvard Square, however spaces are limited and competition for them can be difficult and time consuming. We recommend use of public transportation when possible, or choose one of the discount parking garages above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Have your parking ticket validated at our box office to receive a discount on parking rates at these participating garages:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Charles Square Garage&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the Charles Hotel, 5 Bennett Street, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Contact the garage at 617 491-0298 for current rates and hours of operation, or visit www.harvardsquareparking.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;University Place Garage&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;124 Mt. Auburn Street, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;$2 Discount with box office validation. Contact the garage at 617 491-0801 for current rates and hours of operation&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271093736000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268170401000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>20th anniversary: Twin Peaks (Pilot, Episode 2, 3, &amp; 4) @ Brattle Theater</name><id>12831734</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270767600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12831734/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/b/global_13562715.jpeg</photo_url></item>