<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>915 Walden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.439850</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Walden Pond State Reservation</name><city>Concord</city><id>669174</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.333939</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Now that the weather is cooling down, its a good time to take a trail run through the woods of concord at Walden Pond. We'll meet in front of the gift shop near the parking lot. We'll follow the pond border trail and then head across the railroad tracks to Lincoln woods and do a loop. Then we'll head back to Walden pond and finish up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optionally, if the conditions permit will take a swim in the pond. The water temperature should be perfect this time of year. Bring a towel and a change of clothes if you plan on swimming. They have changing rooms at the main beach area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, if people are interested we could get a late breakfast in Concord afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A couple of things you should know. Walden Pond is located off of Rt 126 in Concord. It's about a 30-40 minute drive from central Boston. They charge $5 for parking at the pond. The nearest public transportation is at the Concord Commuter Rail station about 2 miles from the pond.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in front of the gift shop at 9:00am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul</member_name><member_id>4878639</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284220952000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283479567000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trail Run at Walden Pond</name><id>14640665</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284210000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/14640665/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/d/global_15812509.jpeg</photo_url></item>