<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Eliot Street, 3rd floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372429</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Humanist Community Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1368565</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121733</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the Harvard Humanists for their annual summer service project this weekend. ... The Humanist Manifesto III affirms our "duty to protect nature's integrity, diversity, and beauty in a secure, sustainable manner." In this vein, the group will be cleaning up a public park in Cambridge. The group will meet at the Chaplaincy office at 1 pm, before traveling together to Christian Herter Park, located near the Harvard athletic complex on the other side of the river. The journey will be made via public transportation, so please bring your Charlie Card or change for the bus. You can also meet at the park if that is more convenient; please email your cell phone number to intern Chelsea Link (chelsea.sky.link@gmail.co&amp;#8203;m) if you plan to do this. All materials (gloves, garbage bags, etc.) will be provided by the Chaplaincy. Be sure to wear sunscreen and bring a water bottle since the work will be outside, and will last about two hours. After the clean-up, there will be an informal gathering at Charlie's Kitchen in Harvard Square -- a chance to relax, socialize, and share experiences from the afternoon. Please RSVP to info@harvardhumanist.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah Chandonnet</member_name><member_id>13068813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312742872000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312483680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Service project with Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard</name><id>28273101</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312736400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/28273101/</event_url></item>