<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>158 Brighton Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.352952</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-779-0140</phone><name>Brighton Music Hall</name><city>Allston</city><id>1478997</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132595</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>World Music/CRASHarts presents Omar Souleyman, performing Tuesday, November 1 at 9pm at Brighton Music Hall, 158 Brighton Ave., Allston, MA. Tickets are $20, general admission, 18+. For tickets and information call World Music/CRASHarts at (617) 876-4275 or buy online at www.WorldMusic.org. Syrian musical legend Omar Souleyman has become a huge crossover sensation, collaborating with Bj&amp;amp;ouml;rk in 2010 and playing major festivals including Bonnaroo this past summer. His fervent music blends classical Arabic vocalization with Syrian folk and party music, mixing Kurdish, Turkish and Iraqi strains for good measure. Then he propels all of it into the 21st century by singing over synthesized keyboards and frenetic percussion. The music is greatly enriched by oud, reeds and a thin-necked lute-like instrument called a baglama saz. The result is an ancient/modern fusion as haunting as it is infectious. Omar Souleyman hails from the small town of Ras Al Ain, located in northeastern Syria near the Iraqi and Turkish borders, in a region called the Jazeera. In the mid-1990s, he began his singing career at the age of 30. Souleyman was encouraged by friends to pursue a musical career after singing at a handful of weddings. He soon began performing at local events backed by traditional instruments such as the ney, violin, hand percussion and saz. In 1996, Souleyman approached a young local musician, Rizan Sa&amp;#146;id. Sa&amp;#146;id, a talented multi-instrumentalist, began playing with Souleyman at a time when a new wave of dabke (the regional folkloric dance and party music) was emerging in the Levant. Armed with Arabic-modified synthesizers, Sa&amp;#146;id lent a distinctive and driving sound by incorporating Syrian, Iraqi, Kurdish and other Arabic styles, resulting in some of the most furious dabke sounds to be heard in the 1990s and 2000s. Souleyman&amp;#146;s first hit in Syria was Jani (1996), which gained cassette-kiosk infamy and brought him recognition throughout the country. Jani became popular via a live wedding concert tape as opposed to a studio recording, as sometimes happens with Syrian dabke tracks. Souleyman and Sa&amp;#146;id have also produced several studio albums in Syria over the years. These have a different sound than the wedding cassettes &amp;#150; cleaner and more calculated &amp;#150; and have also yielded significant dabke hits. Khataba, for instance, was Souleyman&amp;#146;s 2005 studio hit that put him on the pan-Arab map. In 1998, Mark Gergis, a California-based musician, documentarian and frequent collaborator with the Sublime Frequencies label, first heard Omar Souleyman&amp;#146; music blaring from the cassette kiosks of Damascus and began collecting Souleyman tapes on subsequent visits to Syria. In 2006, he set out to meet Souleyman and thus began a friendship and partnership, leading to Souleyman&amp;#146;s first western releases on the label and subsequent international tours. In 2007, Sublime Frequencies released Highway to Hassake, the first compilation of his works to be issued in the West. In 2010, Sublime Frequencies released Jazeera Nights which culls from cassettes recorded between 1995 and 2009; this collection offers a further rare glimpse into Syrian street-level dabke folk-pop. Most recently, on August 30, Sublime Frequencies released the live album, Haflat Gharbia (The Western Concerts), a collection that highlights Souleyman&amp;#146;s live performances in Europe, Australia and the U.S. between 2009 and this year. For More Information visit: &lt;a href="http://worldmusic.org/omar-souleyman-0-898" target="_blank"&gt;http://worldmusic.org...&lt;/a&gt; About World Music/CRASHarts World Music, a non-profit organization established in 1990, is New England&amp;#146;s premier presenter of global culture, featuring music and dance from the far and near corners of the globe. In 2001, World Music launched CRASHarts as a division of World Music dedicated to presenting a contemporary performing arts series in greater Boston. World Music/CRASHarts strives to offer audiences an opportunity to share in many different cultural and artistic expressions and seeks to foster an atmosphere of discovery and exploration. The organization presents approximately 70 concerts and 15 educational programs per year. For more information, call (617) 876-4275 or visit www.WorldMusic.org. World Music/CRASHarts is funded in part by the Massachusetts Cultural Council, a state agency which also receives support from the National Endowment for the Arts.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320200140000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317694278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Omar Souleyman </name><id>36036392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320195600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/36036392/</event_url></item>