<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1800 Asylum Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06117</zip><lat>41.779077</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 987-7888</phone><name>University of Connecticut Greater Hartford Campus</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1216837</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.740173</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join The CT Theatre Group And The Connecticut Guitar Society For A Great Night Of Music And New Friends&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Connecticut Guitar Society will present an evening of music by Thomas Schuttenhelm. With guest artists Dick Provost (guitar), Christopher Ladd (guitar), Anton Miller (violin), Janet Arms (flute), Robert Black (bass), and others from the guitar, strings, and wind departments at the University of Hartford, Hartt School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concert will feature the premiere of 'Symphonia Concertante' for violin and guitar, as well as a new three movement work for guitar quartet. In addition, the CT Guitar Society Guitar Ensemble will give short recital immediately preceding the concert in the Library Auditorium at the &lt;br /&gt;University of Connecticut West Hartford Campus&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit: &lt;a href="http://www.thomasschuttenhelm.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thomasschu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show starts at 8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: There will be a special opening act at 7pm &lt;br /&gt;– The Connecticut Guitar Society Ensemble plays from 7pm to 7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;University of Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;Greater Hartford Campus&lt;br /&gt;1800 Asylum Ave&lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06117&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have 20 tickets available, so get your ticket today before we sell out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info will be emailed to all CT Theatre Group Ticket holders &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pick up your ticket before the show with the CT Theatre Group, or at the will call window &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HAVE A VERY LIMITED NUMBER OF TICKETS IN THE CT THEATRE GROUP SECTION&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT WILL SELL OUT - GET YOUR TICKET NOW&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 43 off of i-84 West or i-84 East, for Park Road (0.5 mi)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn right onto Park Road **Stay in the Middle lane (Trout Brook Dr North ONLY). (75ft)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take immediate Left onto Trout Brook Drive (1.7 mi)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beyond the intersection of Trout Brook Drive and Asylum Ave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a right into Students' and Visitor's Parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Campus is located across the street from Parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show to extend the party  Details will be emailed to all CT Theatre Group Ticket Holders </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Connecticut Theatre Group Events</member_name><member_id>8868299</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272327385000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271105984000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SAT April 24 -Thomas Schuttenhelm Ensemble with CT Guitar Society in W. Hartford</name><id>13162354</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272153600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/13162354/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/0/global_14339232.jpeg</photo_url></item>