<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Suggested donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in?  Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It all starts with a night out at the Foggy Goggle*!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program.  No speaker.  Just arrive and enjoy yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD &amp;amp; DRINK SPECIALS FOR SOJUST MEMBERS:&lt;br /&gt;1/2 PRICE APPETIZERS&lt;br /&gt;$7 PITCHERS OF BEER&lt;br /&gt;$12 FISHBOWLS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At SoJust you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that the people of Socializing for Justice share your vision of building a better world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will NOT be a regular monthly event - so don't miss it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Sorry, this event is 21+.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Socializing for Justice (SoJust) is for feminists, people working against racism, queer pioneers, genderbenders, environmental agitators, class activists, lefty artists and all people across Greater Boston working for justice in our neighborhoods, in our nation and beyond. But it's not work! Instead, we're building a strong cross-issue network through fun social events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Socializing for Justice Meetup Board and you'll gain access to all the events, doings, and social goings-on in the area hosted by those working for a more just society -- and you'll be able to organize your own (please feel free to use the &amp;quot;Socializing for Justice&amp;quot; model when creating events i.e. &amp;quot;Bowling for Justice, Scrabble for Justice, Knitting for Justice, etc.). Isn't it time to put the &amp;quot;social&amp;quot; back in social justice?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.socializingforjustice.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.socializingforjustice.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.socializin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>28</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1161116082000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1156332048000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Putting the SOCIAL back in social justice...</name><id>5092421</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1158793200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5092421/</event_url></item>