<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Inman Square)</address_2><address_1>1418 Cambridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373833</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-960-7766</phone><name>First United Presbyterian Church</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1304901</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101746</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Does the good news about the kingdom of God that Jesus proclaimed have any implications for dealing with the clutter in our lives? Pastor Roger will share some reflections from the perspective of a pastor who has been following Jesus for almost 40 years. Roger, who has battled clutter in his own life, will share some things that he has found helpful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fyi, Father Todd Miller's workshop on spiritual aspects of clutter, hosted by Trinity Episcopal Church in Newton on July 15, 2008 (thanks again to Marilyn Santiesteban for making the arrangements for that!), was one of the most thought-provoking and inspiring workshops in this group that I recall participating in.  Prayers and positive thoughts that this upcoming workshop will serve us so well are welcomed.  -- Judy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 7:30 pm - Socializing (please bring goodies if you want some!). I might bring a digital camera to post a photo of the meeting on our Meetup web site IF participants grant permission (please notify me of any privacy concerns).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 ~ 8:30 pm - &amp;quot;A Christian Perspective of Decluttering&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Pastor Roger Lier of First United Presbyterian Church, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~8:30 - 9:00 pm - As time permits:  Sharing of decluttering successes and inspirations, group problem-solving, buddying up for accountability, input to future Meetups, e.g., group SUCCESSION, future meeting topics (I'm considering devoting the next two meetings to Health and Wealth aspects of decluttering) and schedule, venue (e.g., The Democracy Center near Harvard Square?), speakers, organization (including assistant organizers), activities, resources ... how best to help &lt;i&gt;YOU?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On-street metered parking available near the church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public transportation: Bus lines #69 (from Harvard Square ... or ~15-minute walk from there) and #83 (from Central Square ... or ~15-minute walk from there) pass by Inman Square, Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We might be in the garden out front- otherwise, follow the walkway to the side door at ground level (to lower left of main entrance), then go downstairs inside to the main meeting room at foot of steps.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279040319000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277238834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Christian Perspective on Decluttering</name><id>13878711</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278975600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/13878711/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/1/global_15907729.jpeg</photo_url></item>