<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>44.2178°N, 71.4111°W</address_2><address_1>Route 302 Crawford Notch</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03598</zip><lat>44.206845</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-278-HIKE</phone><name>AMC Highland Center</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>839145</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.403199</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be hiking Mt. Pierce &amp;amp; Mt. Jackson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand &amp;amp; agree to the waiver and liability as outlined on this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must have prior winter hiking experience &amp;amp; be prepared for extreme winter conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting inside the AMC's Highland Center on Route 302.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;starting at Avalon Trailhead (HiCtr) and Mount Willard Trailhead (HiCtr) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.17 mi/6 min/+33 ft on the Avalon Tr to Crawford Path, Rt 302 &lt;br /&gt; From the Avalon trailhead, follow the access road for the Depot to US Route 302. Turn left and follow the highway northerly 0.15 mile where the Crawford path begins on the right at the top of the embankment. &lt;br /&gt; to Crawford Path Trailhead (HiCtr) &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/10 min/+132 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The main parking area at the south end of this trail is now located on the west side of Mt. Clinton Rd. a short distance north of its junction with US 302. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Crawford Connector &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/11 min/+169 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Crawford Path follows the south bank of Gibbs Brook, and a side path leads 40 yd. left to Gibbs Falls. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Gibbs Falls spur &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.30 mi/1 hr 17 min/+1261 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; Soon the trail passes an information sign for the Gibbs Brook Scenic Area, then climbs moderately but steadily. The trail begins to climb away from the brook, angling up the side of the valley. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mizpah Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.20 mi/59 min/+736 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Crawford Path continues to ascend at easy to moderate grades, crossing several small brooks, then reaches its high point on the shoulder of Mt. Pierce and runs almost level, breaking into the open with fine views. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 3.07 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 2 hr 43 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2365 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -35 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2330 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.09 mi/3 min/+56 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; At its junction with the Crawford Path, the Webster Cliff Trail ascends moderately in a southwest direction. It then ascends in the open to the summit of Mt. Pierce. It descends easily through the scrub into a sag. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Pierce &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.80 mi/40 min/-494 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; It then climbs gently to the southwest knob of Mt. Pierce, which affords a view of the summit of Mt. Washington rising over Mt. Pierce. The trail then takes a sharp left turn in a ledgy area and the grade increases. It reaches an open ledge with good views south and west. It then descends a steep, rough section with two ladders, before reaching the hut. &lt;br /&gt; to AMC Mizpah Spring Hut &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.10 mi/3 min/+18 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; Mizpah Spring Hut (where there are also tentsites for backpackers) is reached, and the Mt. Clinton Trail to the Dry River valley diverges left(southeast), headed diagonally down the hut clearing. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mizpah Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.60 mi/57 min/+226 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Webster Cliff Trail ascends gradually to the junction with the Mizpah Cutoff, which leads right(west) to the Crawford Path. The trail continues up and down along the ridge before turning right and dropping into the woods. An overgrown side path leads left 40 yd. to an outlook. The trail then enters and winds through an open alpine meadow before it starts to climb toward the summit of Mt. Jackson. The trail ascends the north end of the cone quickly leaving the scrub and onto the ledges. It follows a line of cairns to the summit of Mt. Jackson where the Jackson Branch of the Webster-Jackson Trail diverges to the right. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Jackson &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 5.66 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 4 hr 26 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3007 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -870 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2137 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 15 min/-1265 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail &lt;br /&gt; From the summit, the trail descends steep ledges and swings to the left. A short distance below the base of the rocky summit cone, it passes Tisdale Spring. It descends steadily, then crosses three branches of Silver Cascade Brook in quick succession. It continues to descend moderately, then gradually to the junction with the Webster branch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 6.86 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 5 hr 41 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3027 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -2155 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +872 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 15 min/+1265 ft on the Webster-Jackson Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Jackson (left) branch ascends gradually until it comes within sight of Silver Cascade Brook, then begins to climb moderately. Above the junction, it crosses three branches of the brook in quick succession. A short distance below the base of the rocky summit cone, it passes Tisdale Spring (unreliable, often scanty and muddy). The trail soon swings right and ascends steep ledges to the open summit. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Jackson &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.60 mi/57 min/-226 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail leaves the summit of Mt. Jackson toward Mt. Pierce, following a line of cairns running north, and descends the ledges at the north end of the cone quite rapidly into the scrub, then the grade eases. The trail enters and winds through open alpine meadows, with views of Mt. Washington and Mt. Jackson, then it turns sharp left and drops into the woods. It continues up and down along the ridge toward Mt. Pierce, then ascends gradually to the junction with the Mizpah Cutoff, which leads left (west) to the Crawford Path. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mizpah Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.60 mi/29 min/-316 ft on the Mizpah Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; The trail starts at Webster Cliff Trail south of Mizpah Spring Hut. It ascends slightly, passes through a fairly level area, and climbs down the ridge at a moderate grade before merging left with the Crawford path. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.30 mi/1 hr 17 min/-1261 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The trail begins to descend towards Gibbs Brook, angling down the side of the valley. The Crawford Path follows the south bank of Gibbs Brook, and a side path leads 40 yd. right  to Gibbs Falls. Soon the trail passes an information sign for the Gibbs Brook Scenic Area, then descends moderately but steadily. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Gibbs Falls spur &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/11 min/-169 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Crawford Path follows the south bank of Gibbs Brook, and a side path leads 40 yd. right to Gibbs Falls. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Crawford Connector &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/10 min/-132 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The main parking area at the south end of this trail is now located on the west side of Mt. Clinton Rd. a short distance north of its junction with US 302. &lt;br /&gt; to Crawford Path Trailhead (HiCtr) &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.17 mi/6 min/-33 ft on the Avalon Tr to Crawford Path, Rt 302 &lt;br /&gt; From the traditional trailhead of the Crawford Path, descend the embankment and turn left along Rt 302. Go southerly 0.15 mile and turn right onto the access road for the Depot. Turn left at the rear of the building to find the trailhead for the Avalon Trail. &lt;br /&gt; to Avalon Trailhead (HiCtr) and Mount Willard Trailhead (HiCtr) &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+12 ft on the Avalon Trail &lt;br /&gt; Just after leaving the information center, the Mt. Willard Trail leaves left, and the Avalon Trail ascends gradually and soon crosses Crawford Brook. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Willard Trail &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 12.23 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 10 hr 10 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +4687 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -4675 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +12 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.10 mi/4 min/-12 ft on the Avalon Trail &lt;br /&gt; After crossing Crawford Brook, the Avalon Trail descends gradually.  The Mt. Willard Trail enters right and the trail terminates at the information center. &lt;br /&gt; to Avalon Trailhead (HiCtr) and Mount Willard Trailhead (HiCtr) &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.17 mi/6 min/+33 ft on the Avalon Tr to Crawford Path, Rt 302 &lt;br /&gt; From the Avalon trailhead, follow the access road for the Depot to US Route 302. Turn left and follow the highway northerly 0.15 mile where the Crawford path begins on the right at the top of the embankment. &lt;br /&gt; to Crawford Path Trailhead (HiCtr) &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/10 min/+132 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The main parking area at the south end of this trail is now located on the west side of Mt. Clinton Rd. a short distance north of its junction with US 302. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Crawford Connector &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/11 min/+169 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Crawford Path follows the south bank of Gibbs Brook, and a side path leads 40 yd. left to Gibbs Falls. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Gibbs Falls spur &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.30 mi/1 hr 17 min/+1261 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; Soon the trail passes an information sign for the Gibbs Brook Scenic Area, then climbs moderately but steadily. The trail begins to climb away from the brook, angling up the side of the valley. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mizpah Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.60 mi/29 min/+316 ft on the Mizpah Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; It diverges right (east) from the Crawford Path from the Mt. Clinton Rd. parking area, climbs the ridge at a moderate grade, passes through a fairly level area, and descends slightly to join the Webster Cliff Trail south of Mizpah Spring Hut. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.60 mi/57 min/+226 ft on the Webster Cliff Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Webster Cliff Trail ascends gradually to the junction with the Mizpah Cutoff, which leads right(west) to the Crawford Path. The trail continues up and down along the ridge before turning right and dropping into the woods. An overgrown side &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet inside the AMC's Highland Center (the room with the fireplace across from the front desk)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268060782000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267119629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT PIERCE &amp; MT JACKSON</name><id>12706483</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267887600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12706483/</event_url></item>