<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>792 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Royal East</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669107</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097340</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Greater Boston Humanists invite all interested persons to join them for their annual Winter Solstice Luncheon; where they'll celebrate the reason for the season (the Earth's tilting axis of rotation!) and the New Year together. This buffet-style luncheon of authentic and delicious Chinese food will take place at 1 pm after a brief reception at 12:30. The meal will be followed by a lecture and discussion by Zach Alexander, titled "'Interfaith' No More: The Virtues and Vices of Secular-Religious Dialogue."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexander, a developer and blogger in the Boston area, will offer a constructive critique of the interfaith work he's been involved in, on and the Harvard Humanist Chaplaincy's charitable work and thinking along these lines, including the dialogue on Chris Stedman's recent book Faitheist. The question at hand is, what language should we use to convey our Humanist and atheist views while working on activities that involve shared values with religionists? Alexander has discussed this topic on his blog (&lt;a href="http://www.zachalexander.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.zachalexander.com&lt;/a&gt;) and before the Harvard LGBT Humanists. This promises to be a very engaging discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Royal East offers a delicious lunch buffet, with vegetarian options, in multiple courses, for $25.00. To attend, you must RSVP by Friday, January 4th, by contacting GBH treasurer Stuart at 617-471-2162. Please leave a message about how many will attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the directions to the restaurant: in Cambridge's Central Square area, turn from Massachusetts Avenue onto Main Street. The Royal East is on your right, a pink building. Remember that you may park free on Sundays in Cambridge both at metered spots on Main Street and 'Resident only' spots on side streets (the MIT Lot on Windsor Street is no longer around, but other street parking is relatively plentiful).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to spread word about this program, a longtime tradition among Humanists in the Greater Boston Area.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359224323000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357246252000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Solstice luncheon &amp; a talk on non-religious involvement in interfaith activities</name><id>97736952</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357493400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/97736952/</event_url></item>