<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374275</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Extension School</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>465494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121765</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registration for the spring semester at the Harvard Extension School ends today, January 22&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;nd&lt;/span&gt;, 2012.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.extension.harvard.edu/"&gt;Harvard Extension School&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this really Harvard?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You bet it is.&amp;nbsp;it&amp;rsquo;s just Harvard in the evening. You have the opportunity to be taught by professors from many of the schools within Harvard University, from the Medical School to Harvard College. Classes held on campus are right in Harvard Square in the same buildings other students use during the day. As a student, you have access to the Grossman Library and more than 3,000 electronic databases and journals through the Harvard Libraries. You can also tap into career or academic counseling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Harvard University&amp;rsquo;s primary resource for continuing education for nearly a century, Harvard Extension School offers an open and comprehensive academic curriculum, with courses and programs to meet the interests and needs of a diverse public. Explore a subject in depth. Gain advanced training for a career change. Earn specialized field credentials. Whether you take a course or work toward a degree or certificate, there is something for you. With more than 600 courses, Harvard Extension School offers a range of possibilities for study, representing more than 65 fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Attend evening classes on campus in Harvard Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Choose from over 100 online courses, including Harvard College lectures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Earn undergraduate or graduate credit, or audit a course. As one of 13 schools at Harvard University, Harvard Extension School has degrees and certificates that will enhance your professional skills, prepare you for a new career, or just satisfy your intellectual curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn from the best, Harvard&amp;rsquo;s World-class faculty.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HES faculty bring scholarly and professional expertise to the classroom. Faculty members hold research appointments and professorships, teach at Harvard College and the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, and hold leadership positions throughout the University. They come to the Extension School for the opportunity to teach experimental courses and interact with a motivated, diverse, and determined student body. Instructors include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Scholars, researchers, and professionals from Harvard University. &amp;bull; Leading faculty from local universities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Experienced professionals from community and business organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join a stimulating academic community.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard University is a place of intellectual stimulation and discovery, where ideas foster change and awareness inspires commitment. Harvard Extension School - a cornerstone of Harvard University for nearly a century - represents the University&amp;rsquo;s dedication to extending its rich academic resources to the public, locally, nationally, and internationally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take advantage of a wealth of resources.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a student, you can take advantage of the extensive resources available through Harvard&amp;rsquo;s libraries, career and academic workshops, and computer facilities. You can attend campus lectures and participate in student organizations. If you graduate from the Extension School, you can join two Harvard alumni organizations. After graduation, not only are you eligible to join the Harvard Extension Alumni Association, you can also join the Harvard Alumni Association, the official alumni association of Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Invest in your future.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard Extension School tuition ranks among the lowest in Boston, offering an educational opportunity that is unmatched. Making Harvard&amp;rsquo;s academic resources available to the wider community is integral to the Extension School&amp;rsquo;s mission. On average, the cost ranges from $800 to $1,975 for undergraduate and graduate 4-credit courses. Charged per course and not per credit, tuition is listed in course descriptions. Financial aid is available to students in degree and certificate programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The above information is from the HES Website. (S.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327245466000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324004618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Continuing Education at Harvard</name><id>44621572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327240800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/44621572/</event_url></item>