<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Constitution Center Parking Lot near Residence Inn</address_2><address_1>1 Warren Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.371909</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Paul Revere Park</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>1269080</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060128</lon></venue><fee><label>Administrative Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This event will take place in and around Paul Revere Park in Charlestown.  This area is rich with photo ops including a great perspective of the Zakim Bridge and various waterfront scenes in and around the park and bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's an added bonus of a walkway along the locks that control the canal between the Charles River and Boston Harbor.  The walkway across the locks gives a unique view of the waterway that leads out to the harbor and the machinery that controls it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  &lt;i&gt;On most days, there is free and open access to the walkway.  However, on occasion, they have been closed from time to time due to high water levels.  I will check in with the officials in the area a day or so before the meetup to find out about access to the walkway.  In any case, there will be no shortage of things to shoot in the area.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 6:00 PM at the park to get some shots of the canal, locks and waterfront.  Then we'll turn our attention to the bridge around sunset and some shooting at twilight into the evening.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/dwiroll/2010_04_zakim?authkey=Gv1sRgCO-LxIjAvqSBDQ#" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Here's a link to some shots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/a&gt;I took a few weeks ago while scouting the area.  They will give you an idea of perspective and what to expect for shooting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Location:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The park is a little tricky to find so the best meeting spot will be in the parking lot near the Residence Inn in Charlestown.  From there, it's a quick walk to the park under the overpass to the other side of the Charlestown Bridge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;To access the public parking lot right next to the hotel, make your way to Chelsea Street in Charlestown.  Turn right onto Warren Street. The Constitution Center Parking Lot is straight ahead where the parking fee is $7.00 for the evening.  (In after 5 p.m., out by 7 a.m.).  There's also street parking in the area and a small lot at the park itself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;PS - Don't forget to bring a tripod for the evening shoot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;RAIN DATE:  Sunday, May 23 - same time and location.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the Residence Inn Parking lot nearest the payment booth for the Constitution Center Parking Lot. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>5274985</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274630169000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273552416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Shoot:  Zakim Bridge at Paul Revere Park</name><id>13446405</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274565600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/13446405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/8/global_14972104.jpeg</photo_url></item>