<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Lynn Fells Parkway </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02176</zip><lat>42.461301</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>JJ Grimsby's</name><city>Stoneham</city><id>1174872</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079239</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;After Zoo Lights let's go to a great restaurant maybe you will be having dinner or just a warm cup of coffee/cocktail to warm you up after a chilly night out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 1985, J.J. Grimsby's has long been the preferred dining destination for families throughout the North Shore of Boston.  We pride ourselves on providing the highest quality foods for the best value in a comfortable English Pub Style atmosphere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are you in the mood for?  Their extensive menu is sure to have just what you're looking for.  From salads to seafood or steak, we use only the best ingredients available.  Check out their menu at &lt;a href="http://jjgrimsbys.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://jjgrimsbys.com...&lt;/a&gt; and hit menu.  You will see that they have a little bit of everything.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: They have a pretty big lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Notes about this event:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please only RSVP if you plan on coming, we will be posting this on all 3 of our groups and we will have a limit to the amount of people that can attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you sign up for this event and you have been a no show in the past we the organizers have the right to remove you, please contact us if you have been a previous no show and want to come to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will NOT be able to do separate check for anyone in the group, unless they put us at separate tables then each table will get a check.  Remember to bring cash and some small bills so when you are paying your portion of the check including tax and tip it is easier for the organizer’s to figure out the money you owe and we ask that you don't leave until the check is figured out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only RSVP if you are definitely attending it wouldn’t be fair to someone else in the group for you to take a spot and not use it. ALSO if you are a member of all 3 of our sites then only RSVP on one of them for this event, again you will be taking a spot that someone else could us, we have the right to remove you from one site if you are a yes on two of them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on the amount of RSVP's and how they set us up, you may be sitting at a table with members that you may not know (yet), if you are uncomfortable then this event may not be for you, please take this into consideration when you respond to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your plans change then please update your reservation as early as you are able to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have already called in the reservation for us, but not sure if we will have to wait for our table(s), if we do PLEASE be patient.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on how many people sign up for this event from this site we may add more people that can attend this event, we will be watching the waiting list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nov/Dec: November 1-Dec 11 Some of our members are already starting to give us their donation(s) for the Lazarus House in Lawrence, thank you! If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event. If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna will have some of the Masspass books on hand so if you are interested in buying a book let her know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s that time of year again that if the weather is bad we may need to cancel this event remember to check back to see if anything has changed, because bad snow will cancel this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always we look forward to seeing you at this event! &lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet inside.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291642008000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290382393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at JJ Grimbsby's</name><id>15520110</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291509000000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15520110/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/global_19794068.jpeg</photo_url></item>