<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>241 Thacher Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02703</zip><lat>41.932072</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Moose Lodge</name><city>Attleboro</city><id>12100692</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.292778</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bagel's and Bones Brunch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; will take place on Sunday April 14. It will be held at the Attleboro Moose Lodge. The event runs from 10:30am-2:00pm and includes omelets made to order and other wonderful brunch delicacies. Mary Ellen Rinaldi will be doing her standup comedy and inspirational messages routine during the latter part of the brunch. From 10:30-12:30 you will also be able to receive amazing personal readings from several well known and gifted psychics, mediums, and animal communicators (Readings are an additional fee of $20 and are not included in the brunch ticket price.  Readings can be booked in advance on the website). There will also be amazing raffles (diamond stud earrings valued at $890, iPad mini valued at $329 donated by Tech Superpowers at Patriot Place, overnight at Foxwoods Casino with dinner credit, Red Sox home game tickets, dinner gift certificates at numerous restaurants, and so much more), door prizes and a 50/50 raffle.  This will obviously be a fun filled brunch that benefits several worthy local animal causes.  So if you enjoy good food, fun, and entertainment and love animals this event is for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets are $25 in advance and $30 at the door.  It is recommended that you purchase your tickets in advance as the event may sell out and you will not have a reservation without having purchased a ticket in advance if it does sell out.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets can be purchased one of two ways in advance;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;On line at-&lt;a href="http://verizonpioneers.org/?page_id=2025" class="linkified"&gt;http://verizonpioneers.org/?page_id=2025&lt;/a&gt; (an additional handling fee of $3.00 is charged on the website)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Or via the mail - call Elaine at 508-488-9111 for further information.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/7/4/event_216614452.jpeg" width="402" height="531" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This event is a fundraiser to benefit;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Attleboro Animal Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was built many years before "no-kill" became an accepted reality. The shelter was originally nothing more than a 588 square foot concrete holding cell where stray dogs would be placed, held for 7 days, and euthanized if not claimed. Fifteen years ago the Attleboro Animal Shelter became a no kill facility (thank god) running strictly on donations and volunteer power alone. The building is out dated and far too small for its current needs. Cat cages are piled one on top of another. There is no quarantine area in which to place sick animals while they get better. This fundraiser will help the shelter raise money to be able to build a new expanded shelter with desperately needed modern facilities. This will provide the environment needed to properly take care of all the animals that arrive while they wait for forever homes! To learn more about the shelter go to; &lt;a href="http://www.faaspets.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.faaspets.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bali is a beautiful Labrador Retriever&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; who was diagnosed with a cancerous tumor in his lung. This is not the first time Bali has known hardship. Bali was abused, starved, and abandoned on a highway before being rescued by his present owner. On December 14th, Bali had lung surgery. Unfortunately, he then had subsequent medical emergencies which included several more hospital admissions and a second emergency lung surgery. While his owner was prepared for his first surgery she was not prepared for these additional emergencies. His medical bills to date have totaled over $17,000. Bali has one more surgical procedure coming up in the near future. The great news is he is now cancer free! This fundraiser will help to raise the much needed funds to help with Bali's medical situation. To see more about Bali go to his Facebook page at; &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/BaliTheLab" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/BaliTheLab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The TelecomPioneers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; have agreed to support the fundraiser. Their organization consists of current employees and retirees of telecommunications companies. The organization is the world's largest industry-related volunteer organization. Local Pioneer chapters facilitate and support numerous animal related projects such as Buddy Dog, NEADS Friends of Greyhounds and much more in the Massachusetts &amp;amp; Rhode Island area. &lt;a href="http://verizonpioneers.org/?page_id=2025" class="linkified"&gt;http://verizonpioneers.org/?page_id=2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a table reserved for our meet-up group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elaine</member_name><member_id>11582321</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366394320000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362552105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bagels &amp; Bones Brunch Charity Event-Brunch,Comedian(Mary Ellen Rinaldi),prizes!</name><id>107867222</id><headcount>120</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365949800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/107867222/</event_url></item>