<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The next workshop Tuesday 11/18, will cover a variety of basic techniques for tone and color mapping in Photoshop, Lightroom, and video editing software. The demonstration will show how digital sensors capture the dynamic range of a scene, and how professionals use post production tools to enhance correctly exposed digital images. Techniques will be drawn from my media production courses on the subject.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The presentation is appropriate for anyone with limited knowledge of Photoshop or video color correction tools, and for film photographers looking to transition to digital.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics include:&lt;br /&gt;- Tonal curves for film, CCDs, monitors, and digital files&lt;br /&gt;- How to interpret an image's histogram&lt;br /&gt;- Dynamic range and clipping in digital images and video&lt;br /&gt;- Enhancing image contrast without losing detail&lt;br /&gt;- Enhancing shadow and highlight detail&lt;br /&gt;- Nondestructive adjustments with levels and curves&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location is on Somerville Ave near Porter Square. On street parking is available, and the office is an easy 5-10 minute walk from the red line T-stop. The 90 minute demonstration will start at 7:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please submit the $20 fee when you RSVP using the Paypal link, or contact the organizer if you prefer to pay by check. If you need to cancel, refunds will be issued up to 5 days before the event if you cancel for any reason. Refunds will be issued after that if the program fills up and someone else takes your spot. All participants will receive a refund if the event is canceled by the organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Computers are not available in the conference room, but all participants will receive a detailed booklet of the information covered, and practice tutorials and files on a CD-R to try at home.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Kelleher</member_name><member_id>1381167</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227227816000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Digital Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-arts</urlname><id>303063</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Digital Arts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224041253000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop Demo: Tone and Color</name><id>8964873</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227054600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-arts/events/8964873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/2/global_2958562.jpeg</photo_url></item>