<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Description: Shenipsit State Forest (a.k.a. Soapstone Mt.), CT covers 6,126 acres in the towns of Ellington, Somers, and Stafford. Hike from the trailhead in Ellington and ending at the observation tower at the top of Soapstone Mt. in Somers. There is a road to and parking at the peak. The hike would be moderately difficult with a fair amount of up/down in a few places. The peak's view is nice to the North. After the hike, those who wish to can meet up at a restaurant for Lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Duration: The hike will be 2.5 hours and will cover about 4.8 miles on the blue blaze trail. A marked map will be posted in the “Saturday, Feb. 25 Hike to Shenipsit State Forest, CT” hike thread in the Message Board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: Meet at the trailhead at 10 AM. The hike will be over at about 12:30 PM. Hikers will be shuttled to vehicles by about 1 PM. Lunch from about 1:30 PM at the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Park Information Online. Trail Map at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/s" target="_blank"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt; tateparks/maps/shenipsitgis.pdf&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool: No official carpooling for this one. Anyone who wishes to carpool or to provide carpool services, please post your request/offer in the hike thread in the Message Board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: Parking will be at the trailhead on Hopkins Rd., Ellington. We will have to have enough transportation parked at the peak on Soapstone Rd., Somers to shuttle people to their vehicles at the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comments/Questions: Please post in the hike thread in the Message Board or e-mail Kevin S, the hike organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General directions from Hartford area:&lt;br /&gt;1. Take I-84 East to Exit 64, CT-83 North/ELLINGTON.&lt;br /&gt;2. Take RIGHT off of Exit and follow CT-83 North to corner with 7-Eleven store (3.4 miles).&lt;br /&gt;3. Take LEFT and continue to follow CT-83 North to CT-140 (3.0 miles).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Trailhead (continuation of general directions):&lt;br /&gt;4a. Take RIGHT onto CT-140 East (1.3 miles).&lt;br /&gt;5a. Take sharp LEFT onto Hopkins Rd. (a dirt road) and trailhead is on RIGHT (about 0.1 mile).&lt;br /&gt;6a. Park on side of road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Peak (continuation of general directions):&lt;br /&gt;4b. Take RIGHT onto CT-140 East (3.7 miles).&lt;br /&gt;5b. Turn LEFT onto Burbank Rd. (1.3 miles).&lt;br /&gt;6b. Burbank Rd. becomes Gulf Rd. (1.2 miles).&lt;br /&gt;7b. Soapstone Rd. and State Forest entrance is on LEFT, drive to peak (about 1.0 mile).&lt;br /&gt;8b. Parking at Soapstone Mt. peak.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1138930060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sat., Feb. 25 - Shenipsit State Forest Hike, Ellington to Somers, CT</name><id>4846394</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1140879600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4846394/</event_url></item>