<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 White Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.388687</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Panera Bread (in Porter Square shopping center)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>11415472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118851</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;ABOUT THE WORKSHOP &lt;br /&gt;

 Now in its ninth year, the weekly Boston Poetry (formerly “Charles River Writers”) has long been a free forum for literary fellowship and discussion. It is entirely free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To participate, please RSVP here, and arrive bearing enough copies of the text you’d like to discuss – whether prose or verse – for each participant to have their own. If you do not have the means to make copies of your writing, send the text by attachment to bostonpoetryunion (at) gmail (dot) com not later than the night before the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occasionally, the moderator will invite a member or guest speaker to open the session with a brief talk on some literary topic. If you’re interested in delivering such a talk, email the organizers and let them know! Likewise let us know if you’d like to suggest a writing exercise or event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT THE MODERATOR &lt;br /&gt;

 Andrew Chenevert is in his final semester as a Creative Writing major at Lesley University. Last month, he signed on with the Boston Poetry Union as a (“meticulous and hardworking”, he writes) intern for the Boston Poetry Union / Pen &amp;amp; Anvil. In view of his experience running his own weekly workshop with a small group of peers, he’s been invited to moderate the newly revived weekly poetry workshop for Boston Poetry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any member of the Meetup group, and their guests, are welcome to join him every Thursday, now through the end of April, at 6 PM, for an open discussion of recent writing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366330480000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366213699000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekly Workshop &amp; Writing Lab</name><id>114799562</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366322400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/114799562/</event_url></item>