<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Having recently learned the philosophical basics of Tibetan Buddhism, we continue our journey by being taught the practice of tantric meditation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description of the event from our teacher and Drikung Meditation Center board member Alexis Tsatpatsaris:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Stuck in the dualism of conceptual thoughts, we are completely unaware of our true nature,  our Buddha-nature. Tantric meditation helps to prepare us to recognize the true nature of our minds.  This session will be an introduction to the tantric path.  There will be an explanation, and then we will do the  meditation together.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Drikung Meditation Center:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The Drikung Meditation Center is a Tibetan Buddhist meditation organization in Arlington, MA, dedicated to the study and practice of the Buddhist teachings as preserved in the Drikung Kagyu lineage from Tibet. We were founded by the Very Venerable Khenchen Konchog Gyaltshen in 1985, and are a 501(C)(3) non-profit educational organization. We meet regularly on Sunday, Tuesdays and Wednesday for teachings and meditation practice. We host a variety of visiting teachers throughout the year to make their teachings available to the community.“&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free event but donations are encouraged (suggested $5 per person) to help support the center.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260144457000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259390179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Tantric Meditation</name><id>11966506</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259971200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/11966506/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/1/b/global_12004379.jpeg</photo_url></item>