<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP early! We will be inviting members of the Boston Investor's Group and IBD will be publicizing the event.  We have a room that holds 150, but we expect it to fill up fast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Scott O'Neil and Daily Graphs Online® (DGO) with the DGO guys&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;W. Scott O'Neil, son of William O'Neil and Portfolio Manager for O'Neil Data Systems will be here to talk stocks - both some of the greats and some current, discuss mistakes he's made and how to avoid them and answer your questions on CANSLIM and how to profit in this volatile market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Inouye and Cornelio Ash gave us a presentation on DGO last year and did wonderful job.   We think they will be heading up the team this year, but we're not sure.  In any case, the DGO guys will review how Daily Graphs Online can support your daily investing routine, demonstrating advanced applications and creative uses of the premium data research tools.  They will also show us some new screens and analyze some of the charts that come up on them with an assist from Scott.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott and the DGO crew will also be presenting at the Fidelity Investor's Summit on June 9 if you have a chance to attend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246572717000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>CANSLIM afficianados</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>IBDBoston</urlname><id>1455959</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Business Daily Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243353993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scott O'Neil and Daily Graphs Online</name><id>10494896</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244674800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/IBDBoston/events/10494896/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/b/global_8623451.jpeg</photo_url></item>