<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Not Just for Skateboarding Dogs Anymore!
 &lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Angela Lussier, 365 Degrees Consulting
 &lt;br /&gt;When: Thursday, September 15, 2011 &amp;ndash; 7:45am &amp;ndash; 9:30am
 &lt;br /&gt;Where: Yankee Pedlar Inn, 1866 Northampton Street, Holyoke, MA
 &lt;br /&gt;Cost: Members- $15 in advance, $18 at the door.&amp;nbsp; Non-members- $20.
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/29734221/"&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;RSVP by September 11, 2011 by registering on our Meetup site
 &lt;br /&gt;or by calling (413) 827-4182.&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Wondering how your business can harness the power of video to bring in new website traffic, introduce your customers to your products or services before they buy, and market yourself in new ways? YouTube is the #2 search engine with millions of people searching for what you have to offer. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this talk that will take your marketing and communications to a whole new level.
 &lt;br /&gt;Learn through case studies of businesses that are capitalizing on this free marketing tool, and what you can do to get started. Find out the top 5 secrets to creating a video that will get people to your website, and buying! Plus, cheap and easy ways to get started today.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Angela Lussier is an award-winning speaker, author of the Seth Godin recommended book &amp;ldquo;The Anti-Resume Revolution&amp;rdquo;, associate director of alumni career programs at the University of Massachusetts Amherst Alumni Association, and&amp;nbsp; career consultant &amp;amp; owner of 365 Degrees Consulting in Springfield, MA. Her advice can be found on Yahoo!, NBC, ABC, The Ladders, and in many career and business books. Speaking engagements and clients include TEDx, Boeing, MassMutual, Comcast, UMass, Westfield State College, and many others. She was once reprimanded for being &amp;ldquo;too creative&amp;rdquo; and is on a mission to help others to stop waiting and start creating their dream job like she did.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;365 Degrees Consulting is all about empowering people to create meaningful careers. From working one-on-one with job seekers and aspiring entrepreneurs to partnering with large corporations and small businesses, my message is always the same: figure out who you are and what you want, and apply this knowledge to your career. This can be conveyed through creating a personal brand, networking with like-minded individuals, creating your own business, networking with your co-workers and getting to know high level executives who can help you get ahead, or finding your next dream position. The world of careers revolves around one central message: stop waiting and start creating. Rather than wait for your career to start tomorrow or when someone notices your talent, why not build what you want today? If not today, when?&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316176037000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315253700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>YouTube Your Business for Added Traffic &amp; Revenue</name><id>32348562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316087100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/32348562/</event_url></item>