<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hunt Room</address_2><address_1>405 Pine St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>42.992096</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-624-6550</phone><name>Manchester City Library</name><city>Manchester</city><id>884929</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.459190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FINDING THE MISSING PEACE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The call of this time is a call for peace. Who is the one who yearns for deep peace and silence?  It is the spiritual self, the soul.  In order to find the missing peace of mind, early in the morning hours, when awaking up and everything and everyone is still asleep, sit quietly, soak into the vibrations of silence and remember that you are a peaceful spiritual being.  At that time when the mind is fresh and rested it is  easy to lay a foundation of peace for the whole day.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is the understanding that, peace is an innate quality of the self, the soul.   When we think of peace being a natural quality within the mind, all mental conflicts come to an end, leading the self into an inner state of stillness and calmness(like an oasis in the desert).  Peace is part of an intrinsic natural tapestry of positive qualities found in each and every individual –soul.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we want to find the missing peace, first we need to teach ourselves to become quiet, and turn inwardly. Secondly, it is necessary to train the intellect to create pure, peaceful and positive thoughts. Thirdly, there is the need to take control of the reins of the mind and bring it to a full stop, before creating new thoughts.  After the mind is centered, then with focused attention re-direct it to the peaceful oasis, existing deep within the self.  Practicing this again and again, will bring the missing peace to where it belongs.  Then there will be the experience to have found a deep sense of inner peace and well-being.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition; wasteful thinking creates heaviness and restlessness in the mind.   For instance the habit of creating too many thoughts, and too many words, just about anything, drains the energy away from the mind and intellect.  But, if we stay connected with our inner self, it is then that we can connect with this stream of divine power, and then, even the sense organs will be very peaceful and ready to serve. When we are in a contemplative mood, the mind can become silent, and introverted reflecting on the innate intrinsic qualities of the soul.  This, new way of thinking exerts peaceful vibrations, and rays of benevolent feelings, like mercy and compassion. Using this method when looking at situations, in the family, at work, at the world, we will see them very different and we will not be affected, but instead we could contribute with pure thoughts and good whishes.  &lt;br /&gt;Finally, when experiencing such a positive state of mind, there will not be any feeling of hate, dislike or frustration, but, the experience will be that, I am my own friend everyone is my friend and I can share a whole of inner wealth of:  peace, love, and happiness.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exerts; dj.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Use Map Quest</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>10101462</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284239756000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Great Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight</urlname><id>1499616</id><group_lat>43.0</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Owning Greatness Through Raja Yoga  Manchester Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281884534000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Finding the Missing Peace</name><id>14427806</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284235200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight/events/14427806/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/c/1/global_16295569.jpeg</photo_url></item>