<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Corner of Main and Hubbard</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.700264</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Glastonbury Green</name><city>Glastonbury</city><id>9137202</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.607925</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Glastonbury Art Guild will present its 50th annual “On the Green” Show on September 8 and 9 on Hubbard Green, at the corner of Main and Hubbard Streets in Glastonbury. I will be there Sunday from 10 to about 11:30. More than 150 exhibitors from around the country are expected to participate in this year’s show, which takes place rain or shine from 10 am to 5 pm both days. Admission is free. &lt;br /&gt;

Exhibitors sell original fine art and hand-made crafts while competing in a juried competition for awards in a variety of categories. The “On the Green” Show is one of the biggest events of the year in Glastonbury, drawing thousands of people from around the region to enjoy a day filled with art and socializing. &lt;br /&gt;

Visit the Glastonbury Art Guild Member’s Tent for an art exhibit by members of the Art Guild and by students who participate in a wide variety of art classes at the Art Guild’s headquarters on Hebron Avenue in Glastonbury. We invite young artists to visit the Eco-Art for Kids Tent to create imaginative sculptures from recyclables. &lt;br /&gt;

We want you to stay to browse and buy, so we’ve invited some popular food vendors to offer up a limited but delicious menu of temptations – burgers, wrap sandwiches, Thai cuisine, pizzas, pop corn, ice cream. You can purchase water from the Art Guild’s busy volunteers, soda from our local Cub Scout troop, and ice cream from the Boy Scouts. Use available trash containers to keep the Green clean. Be good to the environment and use the recycle containers. &lt;br /&gt;

Park for free at Glastonbury High School and take the free shuttle bus for a short ride to and from the show. Free parking is also available at the Soccer Field on Main Street. Glastonbury is located 10 miles southeast of Hartford, Connecticut with easy access from Interstate 91 and Interstate 84. The show is located on Hubbard Green in the heart of Glastonbury’s Historic District at the corner of Main and Hubbard Streets&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the front of the art guild tent between 10 to 10:15. Will be wearing a patriots sweat shirt and charcoal black baseball cap.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim </member_name><member_id>6478306</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347237948000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347059897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>On the Green Fine Art &amp; Craft Show – September 8 &amp; 9, 2012</name><id>81381132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347199200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/81381132/</event_url></item>