<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Elm Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.988503</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Radisson Hotel Manchester</name><city>Manchester</city><id>3288372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464287</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

NEW HAMPSHIRE REPUBLICAN GUBERNATORIAL DEBATE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Granite State Institute of Politics is having a NH Republican Gubernatorial Debate on July 11th, 2012. Debate will be held at The Radisson Hotel Manchester in downtown Manchester, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Candidates Kevin Smith and Ovide Lamontagne will debate the issues facing New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Burt, of NH Politics with John Burt, is hosting the gubernatorial debate which will be moderated by Speaker of the NH House William O’Brien and Alex Talcott who is the communications director of 4RG, a political action committee "for a Republican governor," working to elect the next Republican governor of New Hampshire in 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Doors will open at 5:30pm in the Grand Ball room at The Radisson Hotel Manchester. Debate starts at 7:00pm sharp. There will be a cash bar. Discount parking is also available for those who park in the Radisson parking garage. Make sure you bring your ticket and have it stamped at the will call table. Special room rate is available by calling the Radisson and mention Granite State Institute of Politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The debate will be aired live on pegondemand.tv Members of the media are welcome with prior approval.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Granite State Institute of Politics is dedicated to discussing the issues affecting you and our state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like more information about this event, request a ticket or to request press access, please contact John Burt at 603-289-0792 or e-mail john@burtnh.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are also available at, Kevin Smith for NH Governor at 603-658-2012 and Ovide Lamontagne for NH Governor at 603-668-2012 or e-mailing info@4RG.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cost for the tickets. Granite State Institute of Politics is looking for sponsors for this event. Contact John A. Burt.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342148951000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340767804000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW HAMPSHIRE REPUBLICAN GUBERNATORIAL DEBATE</name><id>70921692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342045800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/70921692/</event_url></item>