<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Market St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02885</zip><lat>41.730804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>40`-247-4200</phone><name>2nd Story Theater</name><city>Warren</city><id>777424</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.281755</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;Update 01/10/12: Please be aware that this play contains three scenes that include male nudity.&amp;nbsp; You may read a review of the play at this link on &lt;a href="http://www.eastbayri.com/news/2012/jan/10/undressed-rehearsal/"&gt;EastBayRI.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;Update 01/11/12: Added dinner option at The Admiral English Pub. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this Meet-up we will return to the 2nd Story Theater in Warren, RI for "Take Me Out." Here is the description of the play from 2nd Story's brochure:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"A home run Broadway hit, Greenberg's witty, passionate, and patriotic look a the great American pastime sneaks a peek into that most exclusive of boys' clubs: the locker room of a major league ball team.&amp;nbsp; When the NY Empire's star player comes out to the press with a closely held secret, assumptions are challenged, tradition is upended, friendships are tested, and the question of what it is to be American is explored in a naked and unflinchingly honest way."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $25.&amp;nbsp; Seating is General Admission. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Each person is responsible for purchasing their own ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For reservations, please call the 2nd Story Theater at 401-247-4200.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note that Friday nights at 2nd Story do sell out early. Please do not wait to order your tickets! I strongly recommend that you order your tickets now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;When you order your ticket, please tell them you are a member of this group.&amp;nbsp; They will then reserve our seats together.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner for those that are interested will be at The Admiral English Pub, 267 Water Street, Warren, RI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is &lt;a href="http://theadmiralenglishpub.com/the-admiral-english-pubs-menu.htm"&gt;their menu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that will be attending dinner, reservations will be made under "Ron Correia" for 6:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost of dinner will be handled as follows:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drinks will be consigned to a separate check from the meal. Each person will add 30% to the price of their drink to cover the 8% RI Tax plus a 20% tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meal will be on one check. A 20% tip will be added to the total and meal check will be divided evenly by the number of people attending the dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will send an e-mail including my cell phone number to all who RSVP "yes". If you will not make it to the restaurant by 6:00 PM please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner is optional and is not included in the price of the ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a fairly large parking lot located next to the theater between Market Street and Route 114 in Warren. A sign for Second Story Theater is on Route 114, although it's somewhat hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are attending dinner, reservations will be under "Ron Correia."&amp;nbsp; Meet at our table by 6:00 PM.&amp;nbsp; If you are not attending dinner, identify yourself as a member of this group when you arrive at the theater and they will show you to our seats.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327118455000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313858845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Take Me Out</name><id>30224821</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327105800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/30224821/</event_url></item>