<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;Notes: This is not a meetup event. Roots and Wings Healing Arts Center and Ann are co-sponsoring this event for all who wish to participate. We're sharing this opportunity and experience with you, as it is always an easy way to align and to feel gooooood; and this is how you allow all that you desire to come to you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our theme this time will be connecting to yourself in new ways and with love and appreciation.&amp;nbsp; Our three meditations will be:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inner Smile: a delightful Taoist meditation to deeply relax and bring healing, smiling energy to your body &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hand meditation:&amp;nbsp; to experience deep presence and self appreciation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sage Advice: to gain access to the wisdom of your old, wise future self &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We invite you to come and immerse yourself in the space of spirit with peace, love and feeling good. Come to relax and align with who you really are and to open yourself to the joy in all that you are. This is always a most wonderful evening!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All you'll have to do is listen to Ann&amp;rsquo;s voice as she guides you through the meditations, each one usually about 15 - 20 minutes long, with discussions in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The intentions for your evening are that you will easily:    &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deeply relax and experience inner peace and harmony &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect to inner resources that you might not tend to normally in your busy mind &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And to create greater possibilities for you by connecting to your greatest self  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join us to experience magnificent feelings of peace, love, happiness and hope- essentially feeling really, really good!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All are welcome. The class is appropriate whether you are a beginner to meditating, or experienced. Please invite others to sign up and join you! Forward this to your friends, family and groups. &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;***If you like, you can bring a mat, blanket, and pillow to fully relax lying down. Or you can use what's available there, too, of course. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please arrive around 7:05 to get settled, so we can start on time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;We have been registered to capacity lately, so either RSVP'ing thru this site, or registration is required. Non- meetup guests should register by sending name, e-mail, and phone number to: annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com. They&amp;rsquo;ll receive confirmation of their registration and a reminder.  &lt;br /&gt;If your plans change, please change your RSVP so we will not be turning away people unnecessarily, as we have done in the past.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Amazing guided meditations! Wow. Ann was incredible! I've been meditating for a few years but have been in a rut. Ann totally got me out of that! Ahhhhhh... &amp;rdquo; Robyn C.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo; It was another great night of meditation with Ann. It's just so relaxing and rejuvenating. If you have never experienced meditation you owe to yourself to give it a try. &amp;rdquo; Rick N.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Warm heart,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Ann &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Wings studio on the first floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299428299000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297002048000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Evening of Guided Meditations for the Community</name><id>16461923</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299370500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/16461923/</event_url></item>