<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:30, so let's meet inside the ticket lobby doors at 7:00. Then we can get snacks and head into the theater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Wednesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is our 100th meetup!! Yay!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810111276/details" target="_blank"&gt;Sex and the City 2&lt;/a&gt; has gotten mixed reviews, honestly, but there's not really a lot playing that are huge draws, and I miss the antics of The Girls, so if you haven't seen the movie yet, let's go together!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fun, the fashion, the friendship: &amp;quot;Sex and the City 2&amp;quot; brings it all back and more as Carrie, Samantha, Charlotte and Miranda take another bite out of The Big Apple--and beyond--carrying on with their busy lives and loves. What happens after you say &amp;quot;I do&amp;quot;? Life is everything the ladies ever wished it to be, but it wouldn't be &amp;quot;Sex and the City&amp;quot; if life didn't hold a few more surprises--this time in the form of a glamorous, sun-drenched adventure that whisks the women away from New York to one of the most luxurious, exotic and vivid places on earth, where the party never ends and there's something mysterious around every corner. It's an escape that comes exactly at the right moment for the four friends, who are finding themselves in--and fighting against--the traditional roles of marriage, motherhood and more. After all, sometimes you just have to get away with the girls. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat). I'll bring the coupons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Sex and the City 2!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277154368000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276107318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sex and the City 2</name><id>13750188</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276729200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/13750188/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>