<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online, Like Webinar</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.358429</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online, Like Webinar</name><city>Boston</city><id>9421862</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059776</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;To Register Click the link below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;December 13, 2012 (Thursday) at 7:00 PM  US/MT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/4213866564997545984" target="_blank"&gt;https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/4213866564997545984&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PSYCH-K® is a fast, efficient spiritually based set of processes that deliver psychological, social, emotional, and spiritual benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PSYCH-K® offers tools that work at the causal level allowing many different kinds of symptoms to be relieved. It is a holistic tool that easily fits with most wellness practices and coaching formats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a world that is rapidly changing, one thing remains constant; the power of the subconscious mind! Everyone has access to this powerful and functional asset, but few know how to efficiently work with it to obtain rapid change and lasting results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;PSYCH-K® works to bring balance and coherency between the two hemispheres of the brain, eliminating hemispheric conflict. This allows the Partner/client to utilize all the resources available to him/her rather than being only “half brained”, accessing half the available resources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may over-identify with one hemisphere more than the other. This over-identifying is what is know as being left brained or right brained. Challenges can arise with this over-identification. If we are very engaged in left brain activity relying only on logic and reasoning to solve an issue, we may totally block creative options which would offer fantastic solutions to the issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The “reality or outward manifestation” of our lives is a result of subconscious programming we have received throughout our lives from many sources! While our current programming may be seen as a blessing or a curse, the fantastic news is that this subconscious programming can easily be re-written.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;We often become stuck when faced with new and different circumstances. If something happened to us in 1960, 1973, etc. our subconscious mind still operates from the old program initiated at that time, thinking it is still current and valid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;How many times have you driven a road and wondered later how you got home? Your subconscious mind was driving the car, not your conscious mind!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learning how to use the basic processes of PSYCH-K takes only a single weekend to learn. More time invested after the class increase one’s skill and dexterity using the processes. PSYCH-K is a tool that can be used every day to create vast and dynamic change for the rest of your life.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ‘secret to life’ is BELIEF. Rather than genes, it is our beliefs that control our lives. PSYCH-K® is a simple, Self-empowering process to change your beliefs and perceptions that impact your life at a cellular level. I have personal &lt;br /&gt;

 experience with PSYCH-K® and I am confident in its integrity, simplicity and effectiveness.” &lt;br /&gt;

 — Bruce Lipton, Ph.D. Cellular Biologist, author of The Biology of Belief&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Join this Free webinar and learn more about this amazing program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register here with GO To Webinar. Click on the registration link below for the date you want to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;December 13, 2012 (Thursday) at 7:00 PM  US/MT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/4213866564997545984" target="_blank"&gt;https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/4213866564997545984&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After registering you will receive a confirmation email containing information about joining the webinar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Karen McKy, MHt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Certified PSYCH-K® Instructor will be joining&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The North-of-Boston Law of Attraction MeetUp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;for a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Two Day PSYCH-K Course on Saturday, March 23-24, 2013&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RELAX!  Participate from the comfort of your own home/office rather than driving to a meeting and dealing with all the traffic!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>9941060</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355462014000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>northofbostonlawofattraction</urlname><id>567480</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The North-of-Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353514239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE PSYCH-K / PER-K Introductory Webinars</name><id>92310302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355450400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/northofbostonlawofattraction/events/92310302/</event_url></item>