<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come join us for a psychic reading party with Terry Kargas!&lt;br /&gt;From 3:00- 7:00pm in Hardwick, Mass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This party is for those who would like to receive a psychic tarot card reading from&lt;br /&gt;Terry for 15 minutes for $15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also be doing a pot-luck supper, and have a pagan discussion group&lt;br /&gt;while others are getting their readings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be doing free animal totem readings, to find your nine animals totems,&lt;br /&gt;and some of our members will be doing free Reiki/ Shamballa healings/ treatments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Terry:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry Kargas is a natural witch whose psychic abilities run in both sides of her family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry been reading tarot cards and studying natal charts since she was 15 years old, and  has been doing psychic readings and parties professionally for over 20 years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She worked at Some Enchanted Evening, for five years, doing psychic &amp;amp; tarot card readings, and educating people about herbs, stones, astrology, auras, dream interpretation, and magick, and has taught several workshops on a variety of subjects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry has also been consulted by the FBI&lt;br /&gt;to provide psychic information on two murder&lt;br /&gt;cases in both Iowa and Florida.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She is also a channeler, and a medium, who&lt;br /&gt;is able to see and speak with spirits, to help &lt;br /&gt;people communicate with  loved ones to resolve unsolved issues or to bring messages from beyond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know, that I can personally vouch for her talent, as can many of those who&lt;br /&gt;she has read for at our gatherings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Please do NOT arrive any earlier than 3pm,&lt;br /&gt;as we may not be there before than...we would rather have you be a little late, than early!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Loose' Schedule of Events are &lt;br /&gt;as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:00- 3:15 Meet &amp;amp; Greet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:15- 3:30  Brief Group Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:30- 5:00 Discussion Group/ Appetizers&lt;br /&gt;Life Death and Re-birth&lt;br /&gt;What do you believe happens when you die?&lt;br /&gt;Do you believe in Reincaration?&lt;br /&gt;(Discussion can carry on through the rest the meet up)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:00- 6:00&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FREE Hands on Healing &lt;br /&gt;FREE Animal Cards Reading (with me!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00- 7:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Homemade Baked Ziti, Sauce &amp;amp; Meatballs&lt;br /&gt;Fresh Homemade Bread&lt;br /&gt;Fresh Garden Salad&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dessert : Cheesecake&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;There will be a donation jar there if anyone would like to contribute a few dollars or even a dollar to pay for the meet-up fees, as it costs me $45 every 3 months to use the meet-up site. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions given on the group only-</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206492696000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><why>Well, first of all, Terry is the very best psychic I have ever known, &amp; we are also having
a wicca discussion, free animal card readings, &amp; hands on healing for anyone who would like one...
Also, there will be great home made food!</why><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196563406000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic Reading Party</name><id>6839494</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200168000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/6839494/</event_url></item>