<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Distance: 9.8 miles (minimum)&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: 3600 ft (minimum)&lt;br /&gt;Book Time: 6 hours and 40 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Baldface Circle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an extremely attractive trail,amonst the most attractive in the Whites with about four miles of open&lt;br /&gt;or semi-open ledge walking between South Badlface and North Baldface.&lt;br /&gt;You will find less solitude here than on most of the other trails&lt;br /&gt;described here, but its remoteness keeps the crowds away. The section&lt;br /&gt;above South Baldface Shelter goes up steep open ledges that are&lt;br /&gt;dangerous when wet or icy, many will want to avoid them at all times.&lt;br /&gt;They can be bypassed using the Slippery Brook and Baldface Knob&lt;br /&gt;trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The shortest way is to do the entire loop on the Baldface Circle&lt;br /&gt;Trail, this loop is 9.8 miles with 3,600 feet of elevation gain, for a&lt;br /&gt;book time of 6:40.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailhead: NH Route 113 about 2.5 miles N of Maine state line at Route&lt;br /&gt;113-B and about 1.8 miles S of Maine state line near Basin Pond,&lt;br /&gt;elevation about 510 feet&lt;br /&gt;44.238°N, 71.016°W (WGS84)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the south, follow Route 113 thirteen miles north from Fryeburg,&lt;br /&gt;ME. The Baldface trailhead is 0.2 miles north of the Cold River AMC&lt;br /&gt;Camp on the west side of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North/West, follow US Route 2 to Route 113 South 11 miles to&lt;br /&gt;the Baldface trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 9.8 Miles&lt;br /&gt;Book Time: 6:40&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an advanced hike with steep sections. Please be prepared to&lt;br /&gt;hike at book time or less. Pace will be 1.5 - 2 MPH. If you have any&lt;br /&gt;doubt please do not sign up. If you are up to it, it will be a great&lt;br /&gt;hike with fantastic views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cross posted with North East Adventures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release, hold&lt;br /&gt;harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group&lt;br /&gt;from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death,&lt;br /&gt;including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. You also&lt;br /&gt;agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know&lt;br /&gt;and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at&lt;br /&gt;www.hikesafe.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279054358000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276617465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baldface Circle</name><id>13807824</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278853200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13807824/</event_url></item>