<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Welles Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06355</zip><lat>41.390931</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-415-4067</phone><name>The Sandbox Indoor Beach Sports</name><city>Mystic</city><id>1430694</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.972161</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New England Social &amp;amp; Sports Adventurers (NESSA) Meetup group is  sponsoring this event. &amp;nbsp;The facility is open to the public so, if you  can, try to get there early to help make sure we all have enough space  to play.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is $10 per person.&amp;nbsp; You may wish to bring an extra beach chair.&amp;nbsp; They have some chairs, but not enough when people are not playing volleyball.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out their website at &lt;a href="http://www.sandboxbeach.com/index.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.sandboxbeach.com/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sandbox has 14,000 square feet of deep, pristine beach sand under  a 35-foot high dome roof. They offer 4 beach courts equipped for  playing volleyball, beach tennis, horseshoes, badminton, or any other  sport or activity you can dream up. The tiki bar and beach lounge offers  food &amp;amp; beverages, cable TV, and a jammin' sound system. For more  information on the facility, check it out at the Sandbox's website&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the party, please bring a dish to share and a cooler with your  own beverages. A grill is available and a table will be set up near one  of the courts for food &amp;amp; drinks. PLEASE NOTE: GLASS CONTAINERS AND  DISHES OF ANY KIND ARE NOT PERMITTED.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant,  intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my  executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights  for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the  New England Social &amp;amp; Sports Adventurers (NESSA) for and related to  the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to  participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant NESSA  permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for  any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tell them you are with meetup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>9267328</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301851280000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>I was there with NESSA a few weeks ago and had a great time!</why><group><who>Exciting People Having Some Fun!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mingle-with-singles</urlname><id>1452082</id><group_lat>41.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Mingle with singles 45+ Socializing and dancing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299879910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Afternoon Beach Party and Volleyball</name><id>16888565</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301846400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mingle-with-singles/events/16888565/</event_url></item>