<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 North Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02113</zip><lat>42.364052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-523-0077</phone><name>Mamma Maria</name><city>Boston</city><id>1029897</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053388</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mamma Maria (&lt;a href="http://www.mammamaria.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mammamaria...&lt;/a&gt;) may well be the most elegant restaurant in the North End. It's located in an 1820 townhouse in North Square, near the Paul Revere House. If you're walking down Hanover St., take a right on Prince St. For this dinner, we have reserved the entire La Terrazza room on the 2nd floor. The cuisine is gourmet and I'm sure the foodies out there will not want to miss it. Since this event will be treated as a banquet, we have had to set a fixed price. The price is $65 and here's what it includes: choice of appetizer, entree and dessert from their Restaurant Week menu. The menu is not out yet because they plan to use the freshest seasonal ingredients available that week, but it will include 3 or 4 choices for each course. Also included is an average of 2 glasses of wine per person with the meal, but you may have more or less as you like. The wine choices will be from the following bottles: Red-'06 Chianti Classico, Gini, Tuscany and White-'06 Chardonnay Rivera, Preludio No. 1, Puglia. Also figured in the price is tax (6.25% as of 8/1) and tip (18% per Mamma Maria). It will be very helpful to collect the prix fixe amount in cash as people arrive. This will allow individuals to leave when they desire. What is not included in the prix fixe is any other beverages other than tap water. Anything ordered during the cocktail hour from 6:00-7:00 is extra, as is coffee or tea with dessert. Valet parking is available for $18. Mamma Maria does not allow shorts, t-shirts, caps or sneakers. Because NEEM has put down a deposit and will be required to spend a minimum amount for food and drink, it is extremely important that all those who RSVP 'Yes' attend or cancel as early as possible in order to allow someone else to take their place. Please e-mail me with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: Please access our 'About' tab for further guidelines. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the NEEM party or the La Terrazza Room (Terrace Room)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim S.</member_name><member_id>4216983</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1251675241000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM</urlname><id>1397251</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>North End Eating Meetup (NEEM)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249508828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mamma Maria-Restaurant Week Banquet</name><id>11044819</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250550000000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM/events/11044819/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/7/a/global_7834474.jpeg</photo_url></item>