<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mountain Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03047</zip><lat>42.907753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Pack Monadnock trailhead - Ted's trail</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>1124741</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.850952</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This loop hike ascends North Pack Monadnock from the NE, using lesser known but prettier trails than the North end of the Wapack Trail. The hike is 5.9 miles and has 1350 feet of elevation gain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted's trail begins on the South side of Old Mountain road and at .5 miles Carolyn's Trail branches to the right. Both trails are blazed with yellow. There are several unblazed cross trails that connect the two trails and hikers should beware lest they find themselves on the other trail by accident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted's trail is steeper and follows a stream that features cascades and waterfalls. Most people prefer to ascend by this trail and descend on the more mellow Carolyn's trail. The trail begins with about a mile of fairly level hiking and then climbs steeply following the brook. The first confusing connector trail bears right at the top of the first waterfall while Ted's Trail turns sharply left. Ledges and views begin at about 2.2 miles. At 2.6 miles Ted's trail turns right while a branch trail leads left .1 mi to the Cliff trail at the south cliff ledges - well worth the detour. Follow Ted's trail right from this junction and note where Carolyn's trail comes in on the right to join Ted's trail - it is easy to miss when you are descending. At about .3 miles from the junction Ted's trail joins the Cliff trail (blue blazes) which leads a short ways to the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North Pack Monadnock has excellent views. When you are ready to descend follow the Cliff trail back to Ted's Trail and at about .1 mi from the top of Ted's trail watch for a small opening to the left with a stone wall. Step over this wall to descend Carolyn's trail. Carolyn's trail is fairly direct with better footing and has a board walk through a marsh as a special feature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Rt. 202 in Peterborough turn east on Sand Hill Road and continue when Sand Hill turns into Old Mountain Road for a total of 5.5 miles. There is a small parking area for about 4 cars on the north side of the road, with the trail departing on the south side.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Rte 31: The trailhead is on Mountain Rd.&amp;nbsp; I usually go Rte 31 to the Yankee Farmer vegetable stand (7 miles north of Wilton)&amp;nbsp; Take the left right after Yankee Farmer on Russell Station Rd, then 1/2 mile to Mountain Rd...parking is a short way on right. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is 5.9 miles and has 1350 feet of elevation gain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304264807000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><why>North Pack Monadnock has excellent views.</why><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303422810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Pack Monadnock - 2278'</name><id>17389674</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304170200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/17389674/</event_url></item>