<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 South School</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02061</zip><lat>42.156588</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-659-8810</phone><name>Norwell High School</name><city>Norwell</city><id>1251516</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.834987</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Boston Internet Marketers ~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two of our meetup members organize Tech Day Camp and they asked if I would present a session on Google Plus.  So please join me for a great day of learning with Reiko &amp;amp; Tom and a whole host of talented presenters this Saturday.  30 Workshops in all !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a special discount code you can use as a member of BIMM. Use the code BOOKNOW and get $40 off!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://techdaycamp.com/registration/"&gt;http://techdaycamp.com/registration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a one day EVENT for those who want to learn and understand more about technology and how to make it work in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Tech Day Camp, no question is “too silly”, and there will be plenty of opportunities to ask.  A minimum of 6 different workshops will be offered each hour, with a couple of breaks to network, ask questions and get refreshed. The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tech Day&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Help Center&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; will be staffed throughout the day by our speakers and other technology pros.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech Day Camp would not be complete without fabulous and fun raffles, prizes and an “afterhours” party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who should attend?&lt;/strong&gt; Technology beginners, intermediates, and even those who think they know it all. .  .the dad, the mom, the grandmother, the business person. . .anyone who would like to better use technology to make  lives easier and cooler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will find:&lt;/strong&gt; The ‘how to’ and why on: Facebook, Twitter, Google, blogging, photo enhancing, “the cloud”, QuickBooks, the web, WordPress, video, the iPad, basic computer classes, self-publishing, and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create your own path through the day choosing workshops to fit your needs including some especially designed for business owners, entrepreneurs and non-profit organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can bring your laptop, your iPad, smartphone, or other electronic gadgets and learn how to maximize their use.  Or just bring yourself and an interest in learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What it’s not:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Expo for businesses to tout their goods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An overnight camp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Just for kids&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t get left behind, hop on the information Highway! We are creating a special day to gather people and businesses interested in sharing, learning and using today’s technology. &lt;a href="http://techdaycamp.com/registration/"&gt;Join us for Tech Day Camp Nov 10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://techdaycamp.com/registration/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://108.167.136.110/%7Etech11/wp-content/uploads/2011/06/register.png" width="179" height="39" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lew</member_name><member_id>10673992</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352584919000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352255649000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Tech Day Camp Invitation to the Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name><id>90307012</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>28800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352556000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/90307012/</event_url></item>