<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Girls Rock!, a documentary by Arne Johnson and Shane King (2007, 90 min), explores a  Rock n Roll Camp where girls from all over the country come to learn Rock-- forming bands, writing songs, and building community.  Laura, an adopted Korean girl, is obsessed with death metal; Misty is emerging from a life of meth-addiction, homelessness, and gang activity; Palace is a sweet-seeming 8 year old with a heavy metal sneer; and Aurelia is writing a fourteen-song cycle about her dog, Poppi.  During one week the girls form bands, write songs, and play a gig, while the rest of the camp engages in an experiment in empowerment that leaves no one unchanged.  As the final performance draws near, the girls are thrown into a paroxysm of excitement and self-discovery, achieving things they never thought possible.  The film uses video diaries, verete footage, interviews and animations.  Seattle Magazine describes Girls Rock as &amp;quot;revolutionary, heartbreaking, and laugh-out-loud funny.  Absolutely not to be missed.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;       After the film we'll be going to a local restaurant for our group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll hold up a Meetup sign in the front of the theater at the end of the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3926531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218559395000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217467000000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Girls Rock</name><id>8445281</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218385800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8445281/</event_url></item>