<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>VA</state><lat>37.431572</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>1180298</id><country>us</country><lon>-78.656891</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Missed the CTREIA Meeting Last Monday? It was Standing Room Only!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over 200 people from all over the region attended to find out how to profit from rehabbing properties.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We were spellbound and totally excited about the opportunity we have RIGHT NOW to buy, renovate, and sell real estate at a profit. Robyn has rehabbed over 290 properties - many of them right here in Connecticut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She developed an EFFICIENT SYSTEM for finding properties, buying correctly, managing contractors tightly, and qualifying buyers - all to MAXIMIZE her PROFITS. More importantly, she has taught thousands of people JUST LIKE YOU to do the same.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you missed Monday's meeting, you have a rare second chance to hear the information that Robyn taught. Because this is her home turf, we were able to twist her arm to conduct a teleseminar this TUESDAY February 2nd at 8:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson will be sharing her strategies on: 1) How to find the profitable homes that need renovation, 2) How to find and control the contractors to get the job done and 3) Selling houses quickly for huge chunks of cash.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register now for this Call at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=r&amp;amp;i=235" target="_blank"&gt;ctreia.com/events.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to check your email after you register. We will email you the number and access pin for this call.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265332018000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265040400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Robyn Thompson Free Teleseminar - How to buy, renovate, and sell properties</name><id>12483395</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265158800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12483395/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/5/global_12369445.jpeg</photo_url></item>