<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>522 Amherst Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.794567</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-882-6026</phone><name>Sky Lounge</name><city>Nashua</city><id>845678</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.526093</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets try out the team trivia at Sky Lounge.  The Team Trivia is held Wednesday nights from 7 PM - 9 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Sky Lounge:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Amherst Street space that now houses Sky Lounge and Bistro has undergone more than a half-million dollars of improvements, creating an elegant nightspot that according to the owners stands as the &amp;quot;premiere social and business gathering locale.&amp;quot; Sky Lounge and Bistro sports two double-door entrances, a mezzanine, comfortable couches, ceramic tile floors, metal stair cases, high ceilings, a modern sound system, and 20-by-20-foot dance floor. Designer lighting fixtures and granite countertops help accent the stylish and contemporary space. Live bands and disc jockey liven up Thursday, Friday, and Saturday nights, while drink specials run throughout the week. For hungry guests, there's a menu with a number of fresh American and Italian-influenced dishes, all reasonably priced. Led by a chef trained at the Culinary Institute of America, the kitchen prepares everything from Mediterranean Vegetable Quesadillas and albacore tuna sandwiches, to pizzas, small plates, and grilled items like sirloin tips and chicken kabobs. Sky Lounge and Bistro is situated near the Nashua campus of the New Hampshire Community Technical College. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rewardsnetwork.com/details.htm?merchantId=86413" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rewardsnet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skyloungenh.com/directions.html/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.skyloungen...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237332948000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234405978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Team Trivia</name><id>9725275</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236811500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9725275/</event_url></item>