<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Lyman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01581</zip><lat>42.281445</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-366-4959</phone><name>Tatnuck Booksellers</name><city>Westborough</city><id>392628</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.608887</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;FREE EVENT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bestselling author, nationally syndicated radio and Fox News television show host Glenn Beck will be signing copies of his latest book “Broke” from noon to 1 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the only Massachusetts stop on his book tour. The Beck event will coincide with the book’s national release just four days earlier. Due to anticipated demand, discounted advance sale books will be available beginning Friday, Oct. 29 from 9 a.m. to 9 p.m. and the day of the event beginning at 9 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Broke” is based on Beck’s assertion that our country is financially broke as a side effect of our broken spirit, our broken faith in government, the broken promises of our leaders, and a broken political system. Beck gives readers his perspective on a journey through 234 years of history. “Broke” contends that when you’re on the wrong path, drastic action is needed to correct the course. His book is full of stories and illustrations in his trademark entertaining style.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beck is the author of six #1 New York Times bestsellers and the publisher of “Fusion” magazine. His quick wit, candid opinions and engaging personality have made “The Glenn Beck Program” the third highest rated radio show in America and “Glenn Beck,” one of the most successful new programs on the Fox News Channel. His unique blend of modern-day storytelling and views on current events enabled him to have #1 New York Times bestsellers in both fiction and non-fiction. Beck also stars in a live stage show. Online, he is the editor of GlennBeck.com and the publisher of TheBlaze.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacki</member_name><member_id>6777705</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288535906000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288132009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Glenn Beck Book Signing</name><id>15239390</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288454400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/15239390/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/c/9/global_19103577.jpeg</photo_url></item>