<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1019 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06405</zip><lat>41.281631</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Branford Green </name><city>Branford</city><id>963428</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.811409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Branford is once again hosting several talented and staged Jazz evenings for the next nine Thursdays&lt;br /&gt;following opening night of Thursday July 1st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music is always good, the weather will change but can be so delicious when you catch one of those perfect balmy summer evenings . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your pic-i-nic basket or grab some take out on the way over,  your cooler ( discreet alcohol consumption is permitted), your chair, a friend or two and lets all laugh and breathe and enjoy . ..despite the stresses of the day . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starts at 6;30pm and does not go very late, but should be very fun and relaxing night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you here!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glennn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info for this weeks scheduled performance ( subject to change)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shilts - Smooth Jazz and Funk - August 19!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even as he's dazzled audiences around the world with his high energy soloing over the funky beats of U.K. jazz groove sensations Down To The Bone, Paul “Shilts” Weimar just wants to be known as “an approachable boy from London who wants to have a laugh…a cheeky cockney chappy.” Part of the fun for the charismatic saxophonist is getting people up and dancing--and if they’re listening to him blow from the car stereo, he hopes as they travel down the open road that they’ll be up for some serious HeadBoppin, the name of his highly anticipated debut on ARTizen Music Group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I’ve always liked to play in the high energy style of the band [Down to the Bone],” Shilts says, “but it’s all groove and style. With my own material, I write for my sax as if it were a vocal instrument. It’s more melody than riff based, and the goal is to create songs that listeners can’t get out of their heads. I want it to reflect the sense of joy I get being around people, getting to know them and having fun.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shilts second solo CD, &amp;quot;Jigsaw Life,&amp;quot; has received heavy airplay on Blue Plate Radio.  Tracks from this CD, his previous solo effort &amp;quot;Headboppin',&amp;quot; and from his Down to the Bone days are sure to make the set list for the second to the last show of the 2010 Branford Jazz on the Green Series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>probably some type of purple balloon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glennn</member_name><member_id>8036405</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282520858000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275506674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday night JAZZ series on the Branford Green</name><id>jnwsnynlbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282256100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/13674440/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>