<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Church St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374382</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-864-6100</phone><name>Border Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669139</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120155</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Aug 15, 1947, The first prime minister of free India Pt Nehru made the following remark in his speech &amp;quot;At the stroke of the midnight hour, when the world sleeps, India will awake to life and freedom&amp;quot;. 62 years have passed since then and awaken to life we certainly did, in a manner that the world is at awe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 28 states, 7 union territories, 22 official languages and more than 7 religions and innumerable national festivals, India is unique in ways more than just being the largest democracy of the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite our differences, our poverty, our laziness, our politicians, grudginly slow judicial process, a cranky administrative sytem, internal and external insurgencies and constant scepticism from the world India has stood and stood tall for last 62 years. And the way I see it, its going to get taller.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time and again we have defied the logicians of the west on how we stay diverse yet united. How, when logic fails, India works :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let us shun our regional, relgious, linguistic, geographic and any other differences and celebrate the birth of such a mystical and spiritual nation, bid adieu to her 62nd year and welcome its journey into her next year of maturity, with our spirited enthusisam and the colorful spirits served at the &amp;quot;Borders Cafe&amp;quot; in Harvard Square on Friday, 14th Aug. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The party begins at around 7:00 PM and goes thru the mid-night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This one is to you. Cheers India.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS: The choice of the place is based on the assumption that Borders serve food / drinks to every one's liking (vegan, non-veg, mocktails, cocktails, beer etc). Should any one have a better suggestion, you are more than welcome to come in the front.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250464321000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249870092000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The birthday party of a 63 year young</name><id>11074066</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250290800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/11074066/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/c/global_10053356.jpeg</photo_url></item>