<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>***Rescheduled for July 24***&lt;br /&gt;Come and join us for a special photography opportunity. On this click and shoot you will be introduced to a family of wolves in the unusual facility that houses them. There is a place in Gardner MA that allows folks to come into their space and learn the mission of preservation of the wolf in the wild through education and exposure to a family of wolves. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you join us for a walk in the woods, we will be accompanied by Denahee, one of their youngest wolves. Yes- you heard me correctly, we'll be walking in the woods with the wolf... There are other &lt;br /&gt;wolves located in the compound and we'll be able to see them and take photos of them as well. Then we can enjoy some quiet time wandering around in the woods - feel free to take pictures, capturing all the other wolves that are housed there and the surroundings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This click and shoot costs $40.00 to participate in and will run from 1PM to 4PM on July 24th, 2010. We will get up to 3 hours for taking photos. This is a private tour just for our group this day. So I hope you can join us. If you would like to...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please follow these instructions to the letter- if you do not you can not join in the fun!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP you must mail a check for &lt;i&gt;$40.00&lt;/i&gt; to the owner of the Wolf Talk Facilities by&lt;b&gt; April 26th&lt;/b&gt;- this check MUST INCLUDE on the Memo Line &lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Worcester Photo Meetup May 8th.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt; The Check should be written out to &amp;quot;Wolf Talk&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address to mail the check to is:&lt;br /&gt;Wolf Talk Educational Programs&lt;br /&gt;Mike LeBlanc&lt;br /&gt;649 West Street&lt;br /&gt;Gardner, MA 01440&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This click and shoot happens rain or shine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email me with questions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the Parking lot at 649 West Street Gardner.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glen</member_name><member_id>4869325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280357682000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270597726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot with Wolves</name><id>13107880</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279990800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13107880/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/b/a/global_14194282.jpeg</photo_url></item>