<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be an informal RECON run for the ride set up for the 24th.  We will be scouting out the area, and fine tuning the route.  This will be an intermediate/advanced ride.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;1st meetup location is at the Dunkin Donuts at 1550 West Main Road, Portsmouth RI 02871-1323 at 0730.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;2nd meetup location&lt;/b&gt;  at 0900&lt;br /&gt;Dunkin Donuts&lt;br /&gt;143 Washington St&lt;br /&gt;Hudson, MA 01749-2763&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a short rest for those coming up from RI, and grab some coffee.  Kickstands up at 0915. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Route&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MA SR-140, to NH SR-123, to NH SR-137, 202, and back south towards the original meetup location .  On the main roads we will be doing close to the posted speed limits.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?msa=0&amp;amp;msid=107726498430591389445.000490f61bca114195ed9&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;doflg=ptm&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.28385,-71.521175&amp;amp;spn=2.068416,4.916382&amp;amp;z=8" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Click here for map of some of the route&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an all day ride, approx 300miles, 6hrs 15min total from the 1st meetup location.&lt;/b&gt;  If you are starting in Franklin, MA its about 4hrs 45min plus any stops.   I am starting early so we can get back home for dinner.  We should be home around 3-4pm at the latest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be plenty of places to join up or split up, just let us know at one of our stops so we are not thinking we lost someone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will stop to re-group at all road changes, with a sweeper in the back so we will not lose anybody. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I always recommend full gear.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no reason to push hard to keep up with anybody. (We much rather wait for you than wait for the paramedics). There should be a least 100ft between bikes at all times, single file, while going through twisty sections. Please take a moment and program ICE (in case of emergency) into your phone, with your emergency point of contact numbers. We are not planning on an emergency, but in case there is one, we want to be able to react quickly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DISCLAIMER:&lt;/b&gt; By being a member of this group you hereby agree to assume all risks and liability related to or resulting from any and all group functions. You agree that neither you nor any third party will hold any of the group's Organizer or Assistant Organizers liable for any injury, loss, or damage to your own person or property arising directly or as a consequence from a group activity. You also agree that your membership of this group is based on an &amp;quot;at will&amp;quot; basis. See terms of service 6,6.1,6.2 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/terms/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please review&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MSF Guide to Group Riding&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.msf-usa.org/downloads/Group_Ride.pdf"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please review&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring water, and a camera.  There should be some good scenery along the way for pictures.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Orange/Black CBR600RR</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Navy CFL</member_name><member_id>8858593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286669344000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><id>1535765</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286300168000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MA/NH Sweepers - The BuRn (Intermediate/Advanced Ride) RECON Run</name><id>15009915</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286623800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/events/15009915/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/0/global_17053792.jpeg</photo_url></item>