<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.363068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Innovation Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>5174212</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083893</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please all sign up for this special event with guest speaker Tom Maloney .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : small"&gt;Are You Clear About What You Want To Attract? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The first step to Manifesting what you desire is to see your self as already there; seeing, feeling, &amp;amp; having that desired Outcome. But what if you are unclear or unsure about your outcome? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Then come to: &lt;br /&gt;

 WELL FORMED OUTCOMES/ ESSENTIAL MIND POWER &lt;br /&gt;

 with Special Guest Speaker: Tom Maloney &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : small"&gt;Outcome thinking is a very powerful approach to achieving what you want. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 By following the steps to setting a well-formed outcome you are modeling the way many successful people think about their outcomes. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : small"&gt;This way of thinking works in all situations and at all levels, from setting an outcome for a five-minute discussion, to establishing a vision for a company. The success comes from ensuring that your vision meets all the conditions for a well-formed outcome, and each element is crucial to the eventual likelihood of success. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Tom will speak about: &lt;br /&gt;

 - Clarifying what it is that you desire &lt;br /&gt;

 - State what you want in a positive sense &lt;br /&gt;

 - Seek the evidence that tells you that you are on the right track &lt;br /&gt;

 - Discover the resources that you need to achieve your desired outcome &lt;br /&gt;

 - Understand your ability to take control &lt;br /&gt;

 - Put you plan into action &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Tom Maloney began his personal journey to success in his teens, when he first studied creative meditation for goal achievement with the Silva Method. Since that time he has, through numerous disciplines, added to his tool kit while assisting others along their path to achieving their dreams. His passion for studies in the field of personal development led him to the achievement of his own personal dream, teaching and empowering others through the Essential Mind Power Program. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;Master Practitioner of NLP and a Certified NLP Coach. Tom has dedicated his life to building viable futures from the inside out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hazel</member_name><member_id>7275959</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334167439000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332882960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Well-formed outcomes/essential mind power (guest speaker Tom Maloney)</name><id>58110632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334094300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/58110632/</event_url></item>