<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I know I'll need to work off some calories after Turkey day... Let's meet for a walk around the trails at Northwood Meadows.  Plan for an hour to an hour and a half walk, easy terrain.  The trails loop around a small pond, so you may want to bring some towels and leave them in your car to dry off any water dogs.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt; We can walk longer if everyone wants to, the trails loop around, so if you need to be back to your car, it's about an hour or so to do the loop, and then you can head back to your car, or keep walking! We'll meet inside the gate, on the trail so we are far enough from Route 4, and as usual, Rosie and Oscar will have their bells on! Please remember to wear bright colors and dress your dog in something bright if you can, as even though there isn't supposed to be hunting in this area, you never can be sure!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep in mind there are usually some people on horseback along the trails.  Just wanted to give you all a heads up!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nalmc.net/uploads/Projects_NALMC_TrailMap061209.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Trail Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is an RSVP limit now for this meetup.  The parking area can get pretty crowded. I'll ask that if you are bringing a guest, please only RSVP for the one Human Driver. :) &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside the gate 30-40 yards. Look for Rosie and Oscar, 2 black doggies, with bells on, and yellow vests.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kaitlyn Nadeau</member_name><member_id>12987531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290958157000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289695850000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turkey Trail Trot at Northwood Meadows </name><id>15438806</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290870000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/15438806/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/4/global_19690740.jpeg</photo_url></item>