<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are there really gender differences? If so, are the differences biologically or socially determined? Find out the latest research and let's examine how men and women tend to communicate differently, how men and women differ emotionally, intellectually, spiritually. Particularly, we'll examine how men and women tend to approach relationship differently and how to bridge differences and the communicate gaps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $20.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00-20, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is vegetarian Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit has been set.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce *****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce taught gender differences courses for 5 years in the past. He has devoted much of his life to study of male-female relationships, personality differences, communication skills and ways to bridge differences and develop the best qualities in all of us. He is a relationship coach and teaches the Enneagram and Myers-Briggs for a living.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com, 781 648 3737, herb@herbpearce.com. He also has a meetup group at www.meetup.com/The-Arlington-Singles-Events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245455937000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Arlington-Singles-Events</urlname><id>1416650</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Arlington Singles Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242302468000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gender Dynamics</name><id>10409950</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244242800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Arlington-Singles-Events/events/10409950/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_8622668.jpeg</photo_url></item>