<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>942 Mail Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767827</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 560-1122 </phone><name>Young Studios</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1285024</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.673032</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per ticket</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ok, it's not MY film, it's a locally-made comedy feature film I'm in, &lt;a href="http://www.burialboys.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;Burial Boys&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; (Disclaimer: I'm only in it for a few minutes.  But it's a very memorable few minutes)  It's being shown in Hartford as part of the &lt;a href="http://www.silkcityflickfest.com" target="_blank"&gt;Silk City Flick Fest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's showing 9:30 at the Young Studios venue.  I'll get there at 9.  It's not a &amp;quot;regular&amp;quot; theater.  Seats only 50.  The Wallingford premiere was in a real cinema with hundreds of seats, and that sold out, so you may want to try to get your tickets as soon as you can.  Buy them &lt;a href="http://www.silkcityflickfest.com/movies.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (look for &amp;quot;Burial Boys&amp;quot;).  Also sold at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My character, Kevin, is a flamboyantly gay perverted makeup artist.  See photo for a look at Kevin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Flick Fest has other films, seminars (some free, some not, some of general interest), &amp;amp; parties going on too.  I may make it to another film before &amp;quot;Burial Boys&amp;quot;, but I won't know that until Sat. afternoon.  Feel free to text me if you want to try to join in if I do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRAILER:&lt;/b&gt; (unrated, NSFW) &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3UUxjr8e0Rc" target="_blank"&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; (the film is rated R)&lt;br /&gt;The film is a low-budget, loose, goofy, over-the-top indie dark comedy.  There's a lot of swearing and crude jokes.  Not much blood.  No nudity (damn).  If you know Neil or Andrea, you can ask them for their review.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOST:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/members/2254163/"&gt;Jason&lt;/a&gt;, cell 203-901-4957 (texting is fine too)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt; The &lt;a href="http://www.hartford.gov/parking/parking/morgan.html"&gt;Morgan Street Garage&lt;/a&gt; is cheap on Sat., and free after 4pm Sat.  Also free street parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SYNOPSIS:&lt;/b&gt;  Royce (Aaron Sandler) is home for the holidays, but while back from College, his Grandma unexpectedly passes away. She leaves behind the family business (a funeral home) to her only grandson. Royce chooses to take on his Grandmother's legacy with the help of his best friend Seppy (Christopher Husta). Things get tough as the two friends try to run things on their own, dealing with some serious debt to the IRS. While running out of options, Royce and Seppy put together a diabolical plan to save the funeral home. MURDER those in town they can't stand - and COLLECT.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text me when you arrive. Also, I'm tall (6'3")</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286678857000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286511104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sat. 10/9 - My film "Burial Boys" at a festival in Hartford</name><id>15042637</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286674200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15042637/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/b/global_17611419.jpeg</photo_url></item>