<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Arrow St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.868.2033</phone><name>Pierre Menard Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>347668</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Free Wine Reading Series presents: Ernest Hilbert and Mark Schorr reading new work on the occasion of the Fall 2009 issue of Sixty-Six&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us on November 12 at the Pierre Menard Gallery in Cambridge for a celebration of the sonnet form. Sonneteers Ernest Hilbert and Mark Schorr will be reading new and collected work, including sonnets appearing in the fall issue of Sixty-Six: The Journal of Sonnet Studies. Please stay after the reading to mingle, imbibe, browse books, and converse with the authors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ernest Hilbert is the editor of the Contemporary Poetry Review. His own poetry has appeared in The New Republic, American Poet, The New Criterion, American Poetry Review, Yale Review, Boston Review, McSweeney’s, The American Scholar, Verse, and other publications. A practiced sonneteer, Hilbert’s first collection Sixty Sonnets, was published by Red Hen Press in 2009. A second sonnet collection, All of You on the Good Earth, is set to be published by Red Hen Press in 2013. Hilbert lives in Philadelphia where he works with Bauman Rare Books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Schorr is the executive director of the Robert Frost Foundation and teaches literature at Cambridge College. He was born in Chicago in 1944 but has lived, worked, and taught in the Merrimack Valley of Massachusetts since 1974. His commentary and poems have appeared in The Charles River Journal, and his collection of poetry Conscious Explanations: Poems for Daniel Dennett was published by Pen &amp;amp; Anvil Press in 2008.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258243777000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257444832000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Wine Reading: Ernest Hilbert and Mark Schorr</name><id>11804036</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258070400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/11804036/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/4/global_8983348.jpeg</photo_url></item>