<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;2020 Women on Boards is a national campaign to increase the percentage of women directors to 20% or greater by the year 2020. The presentation will include information on our latest research: the number of women directors who serve on corporate boards in the Fortune 1000. While several organizations provide this information about Fortune 500 companies, we believe that studying the F1000 provides a better picture about the business community. We will also discuss why this issue should be of interest to corporate stakeholders and give the audience practical ideas of how they can help to influence corporate decision makers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Malli Gero is executive director of 2020 Women on Boards, a national campaign to increase the number of women on corporate boards to 20% or more by the year 2020.&amp;nbsp; She is also principal of Gero Communications, a marketing communications firm.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Prior to starting Gero Communications Ms. Gero served as an account executive for public relations agencies in New York and Boston, working in the fashion and design, health care, B2B, and leisure industries. Her expertise includes developing and managing media and community relations campaigns, producing print and online collateral material, and coordinating special events and product introductions.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ms. Gero is an active community volunteer. She is chairman of the board of More Than Words, an innovative social enterprise, and is past chair and president of the Coolidge Corner Theatre Foundation in Brookline, MA.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;She has also served on the boards of the Brookline Educational Foundation, Ruggles Street Mission Hill Day Care Center, a division of Associated Day Care Services of Greater Boston, and Temple Ohabei Shalom in Brookline. She lives in Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts with her husband, Michael.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327198672000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324315817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 2020 Challenge: 20% Women Directors by 2020</name><id>44913902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326977100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/44913902/</event_url></item>