<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>307 Somerville Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.380328</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 628-7070</phone><name>Machu Picchu</name><city>Somerville</city><id>739181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097356</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.machupicchuboston.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Machu Picchu&lt;/a&gt; is a highly rated Peruvian restaurant in Union with amazing food. The portions are also very good. If you've never had Peruvian this is a good place to try it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip and tax.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations will be under Omni.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Physical Address:&lt;br /&gt;307 Somerville Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Somerville,  Massachusetts 02143 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?ll=42.380277,-71.097235&amp;amp;key=ABQIAAAAxPVBEod5YcXqoVhvJ3S1zxTXP4WedHnr2NccZ_cRUWdHT0FaGRSm6ru1KQyh5rWiO1L0fn2Q715asA" target="_blank"&gt;Get a map &amp;amp; driving directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MBTA.com: Unfortunately Union Square is not a T stop. However, it is accessible by several bus routes: 85, 87, 91, 86. Also, a walkable distance from Inman Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The information below was added by Tonya&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event &lt;br /&gt;and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO in less than twenty-four hours &lt;br /&gt;of the the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list, &lt;br /&gt;to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not able to attend &lt;br /&gt;or are running late, you must contact the organizer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or &lt;br /&gt;less than twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO, is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or &lt;br /&gt;uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An organizer will arrive at least fifteen minutes before the event to confirm seating as well as welcome you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The restaurant is one-room, so it shouldnt be hard.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205251849000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><why>delicious - and Peruvian!</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203620431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peruvian Lunch in Union Square</name><id>7379485</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205078400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7379485/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/c/global_3289324.jpeg</photo_url></item>