<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Difficulty: Easy / flatter than a pancake&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 3-5 miles depending on the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duration: 2hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read the entire write up before signing up for this hike / walk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by signing up for this hike you agree to the terms of the liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will walk at a de-stressing/ strolling pace for about 3-5 miles before sunset. We will start walking South on the path towards Warren and returning to the scenic Barrington Shopping Center where we will see if anyone would like to go for a bite to eat. The East Bay Bike Path is a flat ribbon of former rail tracks that goes from the Providence/ East Providence line down to Bristol. It is about 28 miles round trip. The starting and ending point will be the the Barrington Shopping Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a headlamp or flashlight just in case we run late. If you have a reflective vest bring it. As always bring snacks and water. Make sure you bring a wind layer / fleece for when temps start to drop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Safety First!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liz</member_name><member_id>31266642</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365217488000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365125867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>De-stress from the work week</name><id>112771332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365198300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/112771332/</event_url></item>