<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Main St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03848</zip><lat>42.913366</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Pond</name><city>Kingston</city><id>945472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061631</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Officially cancelled due to forecasted showers this evening.  If the weather breaks, some people may still show up to paddle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday evenings at 5:30 until dark. All are welcome to join. The water is still cold so drysuits and wetsuits are recommended. Tuesday nights are &amp;quot;informal&amp;quot; skills sessions. You can work on whatever you choose. You can ask for help from the experienced paddlers there, or offer something up that we all might learn from....you don't have to be an expert kayaker to share experience. (I actually learned to roll successfully from someone who had only paddled twice, but he could see my problem because he had read some books!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should have at a minimum:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boat&lt;br /&gt;Paddle&lt;br /&gt;PFD (which you must wear and zip when on the water with us)&lt;br /&gt;Paddle float&lt;br /&gt;Pump&lt;br /&gt;Wet or Drysuit (until at least mid-May)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Great Pond:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great Pond is located in Kingston, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We launch at the State Boat Ramp on Main St. in Kingston. (do not park within 15 ft of the fire hydrant..$50 fine that is sometimes enforced)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Main St is located one block off the intersection of Rte 125 and Rte 111 West in Kingston, NH. The boat ramp is about 1/4 mile down Main St on the left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>State Boat Ramp - Main St. Kingston NH   you'll see the cars</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy Foley</member_name><member_id>7753713</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241732644000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241027697000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skills Session - Great Pond, Kingston, NH - Officially cancelled due to rain</name><id>10295315</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241559000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/10295315/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/9/global_8409049.jpeg</photo_url></item>