<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, This Sunday Brunch will be @ 2PM at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sonsie&lt;br /&gt;327 Newbury St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02115&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (617) 351-2500&lt;br /&gt;Price: Very Reasonable&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't been, you'll love Sonsie! At Sonsie, the bartenders and the waiters provide outstanding service and the food is superb.  I think I am going to get there a little earlier and have a Mimosa or a Bloody Mary at the bar!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scene&lt;br /&gt;The people-watching is in its prime, when the front windows are opened up and allow the sun to pour in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Food&lt;br /&gt;Sonsie's kitchen turns out better New American fare than one would find at similarly trendy joints. Starters include steamed mussels in a chili-chipotle broth and a chopped garden salad with sheep's milk Camembert and wood-smoked bacon. Brick-oven pizzas (Nicoise goat cheese, Mexican chicken) prove perfect for sharing at the bar. Entrees span the globe, from Italian (monkfish scaloppini ) to Asian (nori-wrapped salmon with shrimp tempura). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway, hope to see many at Sonsie this week. Just shoot me an email if this interests you. If you decide to join in on the fun, PLEASE... confirm with me your plans so I am able to make the appropriate arraignments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers, &lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS- How did I get the idea for this weekly brunch group here in Boston? Well... here's a little history/background on how it all began. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I belonged to a similar group in Manhattan. In NY what began as weekly brunch quickly grew into monthly movies, five mile Fridays (long runs in Central Park), Sunday afternoons at the local neighborhood pub for a drink or two and even a book club of sorts. I had some of the best times and philosophical conversations that I've ever had with the men and women of that group in NY. It was like college for adults. The group's original members were graduates from all over the map (i.e. Columbia, Brown, NYU, Northeastern, Stanford, Yale; Williams; Penn, Cal; Penn State, Michigan, etc...) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For many of us, it really felt like an extension of college in that we were always surrounded by such a smart, fun, and diverse group of people. The group was about sixty percent women and forty percent men. It also consisted mostly of twenty and thirty somethings. We were all pretty athletic and health conscious, as a result, we were all in good shape. In my opinion, several of the women and men could have modeled in NY successfully but they were all too smart for that. Not only were they attractive, they were all driven in their chosen fields, and everyone of them was extremely down to earth, kind and generous. And, every single one of us went out of our way to make everyone in the group feel welcome. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Further, some of the guys/girls were the funniest people that I ever met. It was always a ton of fun and there was never a dull moment. Instead of brunch, sometimes we'd have a big picnic in the park and hangout playing wiffle ball and touch football all afternoon. A few of us even started a casual book club and would meet out on Saturday afternoons at some low-key cafe or pub in Morningside Heights or in the East Village. When the weather was especially nice, we were always grabbing our books to go read on the steps of the Columbia library or at the Central Park Boathouse or under a tree on Cedar Hill. Other times we'd all head over someone’s apt for wine and cheese and then gather afterwards at our favorite neighborhood hangout. And, sometimes we'd continue the evening at our favorite 24hr diner, talking with Pete, the old man and our friend behind the counter until 4a.m. Pete always remembered our names and what we liked. It was the coolest thing - all of us sitting there together talking with Pete. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Needless to say, I've always preferred to spend my leisure time with friends + people who are kind, generous and down to earth. I've never been able to tolerate snobs of any kind or people who are overly concerned with such shallowness. I know everyone in the group felt the same way and that is why the group was so much fun and successful. People who have to over compensate in such ways are tiring to be around. I guess that's the New Yorker in me. I've just never had the patience for it or for people who approach life in that way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At first, I wasn't sure how well this kind of social group will fly here in Boston? So far so good but it has been more difficult here in Boston for some reason. If there is one big difference between Manhattan and Boston that is the people in Manhattan are attracted to the city for its unique energy, which it gets from its people and its diversity. There is also a lot more people living in Manhattan so there was never a shortage of fun, single, smart, interesting people who enjoyed being social and meeting new people. This is not to suggest, however, that couples are not welcome in the Boston group; of course they are. Some of my best friends were those couples from the NY group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Must RSVP first and then arraignments will be made.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235758582000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224870014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch Anyone? (20 &amp; 30 somethings for wkly brunch, etc... Meetup</name><id>9024903</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225652400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9024903/</event_url></item>