<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>143 First Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.366492</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-492-4646</phone><name>The Helmand Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>930873</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077923</lon></venue><fee><label>reservation fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sorry for the short notice, folks. Life has been beyond hectic for us lately. But we have a reservation for a nice early dinner at Helmand this Saturday and we sure hope some of you will be able to make it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is Jeff Spin's original idea post. It should whet your appetite! &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;PLEASE&lt;/i&gt; take a minute to check out the &lt;a href="http://www.helmandrestaurantcambridge.com" target="_blank"&gt;Helmand web site&lt;/a&gt;  -- and in particular, the menu -- in advance because we will only have the table for 2 hours.&lt;/b&gt; (Sorry, that's what happens when you go out on a Saturday night!) It would be great if we could walk in there with some idea of what we want to eat so as to maximize the amount of time we will have to enjoy it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this is your first meetup with us, please note that you must pay a reservation fee of $3.00 to RSVP. In other words, you gotta commit to some small extent. But don't worry, you get that fee back, in a way. I will figure the bill for the table, put that $3 towards your share of the tax and tip and adjust things accordingly.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff said:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Few cuisines offer better lamb and vegetarian dishes than The Helmand in East Cambridge near Best Buy (the former Lechmere Sales). Truly, the various lamb dishes and eggplant are absolutely delicious.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course, they also have chicken, fish, and beef dishes as well, but their signature dish of Sweet Baby Pumpkin &amp;amp; Savory Beef Sauce is sublime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matching the quality of the good food is the decor, complete with oriental rugs, large modern fireplace, an oven for baking flatbread (delicious bread that comes with 3 tasty sauces), linen tablecloths, and artifacts from Afghanistan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They also feature an imaginative selection of bottles of wine, And, although they don't offer many wine selections by the glass, their house wines are quite good and reasonably priced. In fact, their overall prices are a real deal considering the high quality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is on-street and quite ample. Overall, this is a convenient location to reach.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Convinced? We hope so! See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- iris and bob&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet outside at 4:45 if possible! Reservation is in Bob's name.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob</member_name><member_id>4061181</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271711976000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271291965000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The long-awaited Helmand Meetup, at last!!!</name><id>13186478</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271538000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/13186478/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/4/9/global_14380169.jpeg</photo_url></item>