<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Littleton Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.596606</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 256-0001</phone><name>The Java Room</name><city>Chemsford</city><id>751175</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354094</lon></venue><fee><label>Voluntary donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>At this Linux Meetup, let's discuss the different system administration features of whatever distribution you are running.  I'll bring my laptop and talk about OpenSuSE 10.1 and YaST.  I just found out about profile management in YaST, so I'll share that with anybody who is interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since it is sometimes difficult for a large audience to hear one person speaking at The Java Room, I hope other people will bring their laptops and discuss what they know about the system administration features of their favorite Linux distribution.  You don't have to be an expert, just share what you've learned so far!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anybody with an interest in Linux is welcome to attend!  There is free (as in beer) wireless access for the customers of The Java Room.  Also, if you have a power strip, please bring it.  We'll need 3 or 4 of these to accomodate all of the laptops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please consider making a small ($2-$3) voluntary donation to defray the cost of using Meetup.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm hoping we can get 20 attendees at this meeting......can we do it?  :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to thank The Java Room for hosting the meeting.  The Java Room thanks all of you for your patronage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regarding parking, which can be tight, notice the gas station just past The Java Room.  If the gas station is on your right, turn into the next driveway (notice The Traveling Rhino store).  Stay hard to your right and park along the right side of the parking lot.  There is a set of stairs going up into the parking lot for The Java Room.  It is probably a 1 minute walk from there to The Java Room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy Stewart</member_name><member_id>3117855</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1161385487000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Linux Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>linux-393</urlname><id>304994</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>The Chelmsford Linux Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1159838677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Linux @ The Java Room</name><id>5169025</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1161212400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/linux-393/events/5169025/</event_url></item>