<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members of our MA NE GHOST team recently investigated a gentleman's club at the owner's request. We found so much activity at the location, I asked the owner if I could bring a small group of meetup members for a follow-up investigation, and he graciously agreed. We just have to pay a nominal amount to cover the expense of having the manager open up and monitor the place while we are there ($22/per person).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To protect the owner's privacy, I hav decided not to post the name or exact address of the location. I'll send this info to those whe have registered for the event shortly before the event takes place. It's not a large venue, so I need to limit attendees to 15; however, if folks like it, we will schedule another event there later this year. The MA team collected lots of class A EVPs and even a few interesting photos. They also had some interesting personal experiences. This is a great opportunity for folks who want to experience being on a small, focused paranormal team conducting a scientific investigation of a site. Believe me, it's not like you see on TV :') You can bring cameras and audio equipment, but please, no cell phone apps :')&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've set up the event so that you can pay and register using PayPal to guarantee a spot. If you have questions (other than the location), you can email me and I'll do my best to answer them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy </member_name><member_id>7992934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339808878000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>footsteps-paranormal-meetup</urlname><id>1305459</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0</group_lon><name>Footsteps Paranormal Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336067856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Investigation of a Gentleman's Club</name><id>63277732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338762600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/footsteps-paranormal-meetup/events/63277732/</event_url></item>