<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.384979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Waltham</name><city>Waltham</city><id>561766</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.216743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dr. Brian Clement, author, international lecturer &amp;amp; director of the renowned Hippocrates Health Institute, will speak on &amp;quot;Look and Feel Young by Being Healthy&amp;quot; exploring the institute's fifty years of helping people to heal themselves.  He will also explain quantum health and how individual choices have global impact.  An extensive question and answer period will be offered so that participants will leave with viable, personal roadmaps back to complete health.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;COME AND BE MOTIVATED TO CHANGE YOUR LIFE! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;TUESDAY, SEPTEMBER 8, 2009  5:30 - 9:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;U MA WALTHAM CENTER, 240 BEAVER ST., WALTHAM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 Registration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00- 6:15  Food Demo with samples of delicious Hippocrates Veggie Burgers with ketchup presented by Beth Fishman, personally healed and transformed by the raw and living food life style. Beth is a certified teacher.  See www.RawFoodToTheRescue.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:15 - 7:15   Fantastic raw, organic, unprocessed &amp;quot;living food&amp;quot; buffet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:15   Brian Clement Lecture, Q &amp;amp; A and book-signing  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For a reserved seat (held until 5:45 pm) buy your  $15 ticket by clicking here. First to sign up will have their names on places nearest the stage.  Open seating after 5:45.  Tickets at door are $20.  All proceeds are tax-decuctible and contributed to help nourish children. This is a benefit event.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We encourage everyone to be adventurous and prepare a raw, organic, unprocessed vegan dish for 8 people valued at least for $10.   Please bring labeled utensils and a recipe with your name on it, the source, quantities and instructions, so we can use them in the newsletter and website.  For ideas see Recipes on www.OptimumHealthSolution.org or google YouTube raw recipes. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If it's impossible for you to prepare a dish, please click here to purchase  a $10 meal ticket and I will buy and prepare food for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before coming to the Dinner Speaker Series, please write your recipe with these guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why?      &lt;br /&gt;So many can also make your delicious dish by finding it on the RNEC/OHS Websites&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Title of Dish&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  Your first and last name ie name of person who prepared the dish.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;3.  Source of where the recipe came from in order to give author credit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;4.  Special equipment needed (if any)  dehydratr, food procesor, vitamix, spirooli etc.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;5.  Specific amount of ingredients used.  Many people need to know quantities to replicate the recipe.  Only recipes with specific quantities/measurements will be posted on the web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6.  Circle in red any ingredient that is not organic, not processed, not vegan and not raw.  Many people, especially those with cancer and other diseases will become very ill if they eat food that does not follow these guidelines.  To confirm that produce is organic, it must be marked with a number beginning with 9.  The number on conventional ie produce that has been sprayed or grown in polluted soil, begins with a 4.  The number of genetically modified (GMO) vegetables begins with a 3 (many of these are modified by adding animal products to them and cause extreme allergic reactions).  Cooked produce kills all the enzymes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7.  Write the instructions on how to prepare the recipe.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Posted by Martha Muehe (www.essenic.com)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please ask to be seated with Meetup, introduce yourself to group, and enjoy! :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252786756000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250553385000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS Potluck &amp; Dr. Brian Clement</name><id>11134375</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252445400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/11134375/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/4/global_10258052.jpeg</photo_url></item>