<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mount Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-401-8047</phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>221452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come check out Conspiracy Cafe every Sunday from noon to 8!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Conspiracy Cafe at 45 Mt. Auburn St. in Harvard Sq. is open &lt;b&gt;every&lt;/b&gt; Sunday from 12:00 noon to 8:00 pm. It offers a unique setting for 9/11 Truth activists and those curious to learn more about current events through books, DVDs, film screenings and informal discussions, in a casual cafe environment. The Conspiracy Cafe offers a wide selection of books, cds, &amp;amp; other media. So whether your desires are social, intellectual or oriented toward activism, the Conspiracy Cafe has something for everyone. Hope to see you at the next Conspiracy Cafe! So what are you waiting for? Bring a friend, bring yourself, bring an open mind! Come check out what Conspiracy Cafe is all about!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FILM LINEUP FOR THIS WEEK'S EDITION:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00 Noon - 2:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;9/11: The Great Illusion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George Humphrey provides objective and factual information while asking relevant questions concerning events which took place on September  11. This film gives a clear summary of the occurrences of 9/11 uncovering &amp;quot;The Great Illusion&amp;quot; presented by the predominate media. An invaluable tool to use at a grass roots level. Starting with ourselves, we can restore sanity and justice, one person at a time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:00pm - 3:45pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;The 'New' Clinton Chronicles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can it be when President Clinton asked the question back in 1994: &amp;quot;Where are the charges?&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;Where's the proof?&amp;quot;, he didn't really expect anyone to document the proof and make it available to the public? President Clinton wasn't ready for &amp;quot;The New Clinton Chronicles&amp;quot; video! In fact, President Clinton's personal attorney prompted a gag order on video journalist Pat Matrisciana (producer of the video and author of &amp;quot;The Clinton Chronicles&amp;quot; book) in an attempt to keep the truth about Bill Clinton from becoming more widely known.  This revealing video is an investigation into the Alleged Criminal Activities of Bill Clinton and his Circle of Power. For the first time on video, an in-depth documentary shows you all of the pieces of the Clinton puzzle, and fits them all together to reveal the whole story. You'll hear from and see the faces of the key players who Clinton used to build his Circle of Power...as well as those who got in his way and lost their jobs, reputations, freedoms, virtue, and even their lives! You'll learn everything about Clinton's alleged involvement in Whitewater, The Arkansas Development Finance Authority (ADFA), drug money in the millions smuggled from the airport in Mena, Arkansas, and money laundering with the BCCI. You'll find out the truth behind Gennifer Flowers, Paula Jones, the gangland slaying of private investigator Jerry Parks, and details of the Vince Foster &amp;quot;suicide&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:45pm - 5:55pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Loose Change: Final Cut&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original Loose Change and Loose Change 2nd Edition have been viewed at least 50 million times over the Internet, making it one of the most watched movies in history, but the Final Cut goes above and beyond, making it not simply the third in a trilogy but a completely new film with oodles of unseen footage, commentary, interviews and eyewitness testimony. In an effort to be the catalyst for a new independent investigation of 9/11, the film features new and exclusive interviews with firefighters, EMT's, first responders and other officials who were all eyewitnesses to multiple secondary explosions in the twin towers and around the ground zero area. Alex Jones worked with the trio in an executive producer role on the film and has partly financed it's production and distribution. Other consultants on The Final Cut include Professor David Ray Griffin, author of three widely read studies of the 2001 attacks.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:55pm - 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Police State 2: The Takeover by Alex Jones&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alex Jones exposes the problem-reaction-solution paradigm being used to terrorize the American people into accepting a highly controlled and oppressive society. From children in public schools being trained to turn in their peers and parents, to the National Guard &amp;amp; Army patrolling our country's highways, the takeover reveals the most threatening developments of police state control in our age.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be manning the dvd table &amp; the 10 stack dvd burner!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4883658</member_name><member_id>4883658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204125058000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>We'll be hitting the streets &amp; having a street action as well!  People should not be going through Harvard Square without knowing the truth about 9/11! So if you want to come &amp; participate in street actions &amp; see hard hitting films THIS is your spot!</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203619677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conspiracy Cafe!</name><id>7379384</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203872400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7379384/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/7/global_3289271.jpeg</photo_url></item>