<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>My Personal Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>787702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome BestMatchClub Members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Goal achieved. People will cancel the day of the event because of other priorities.  Please sign up now and be placed on the waiting list, and on the day of the event I will allow men in because of cancellations. I want more high integrity men for the ladies to meet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ladies, you are in automatically, if you attend with a gentleman. Let me know. I will OK you.&lt;br /&gt;You must walk in together, no meeting him at the party. You are a contributor to help other women just like yourself. email me-BestMatchClub@verizon.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite a gentlemen who has the quality and integrity that you possess. I'm assuming birds of a feather flock together. Don't like the quality of men or women then be proactive and raise your standards of who you invite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We achieved our women's quota of gregarious, positive, communicative women. Gentlemen want to meet them? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Has your past and present behavior exemplified integrity? (demonstrate high integrity)?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then you are welcome. Are you kind and considerate of other people. Then you are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I find this informative. Even though I articulate no more women, women are still signing up. They know there will be more women. Why? The responses I'm receiving is that gregarious women are also meeting other gregarious women whom they are developing positive relationships with. This is good. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But, the primary reason singles are coming is to meet a possible life partner of the opposite sex. This is our primary purpose. Please keep that in mind. Let's do both. But not with a skewed ratio men and women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will answer the number one question from a woman. &lt;br /&gt;Yes, we will have  and will continue to strive for a 50-50 ratio of men and women, just like the Sept. 11th party. Ladies this is one of our unique features. That's one reason you should be a loyal member.&lt;br /&gt;Our members are asked to invite gentleman of equal quality and character. Our primary source of membership is referral at this time. Oct 10th I will begin advertising to the general public. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This party is composed of singles. (30-65) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, what ever group I sponsor, the women sign up first, then the men sign up to see the woman's pictures to determine if they want to meet you. Men are visual, that is how we are wired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mission is to have fun, laugh, and meet other single people with common interests. Develop friendships and possibly find a lifetime partner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Values: Be nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and respectful to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite other eligible quality singles that you believe have good character and integrity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Presently-The entry fee is $10.00 plus  food assignment.&lt;br /&gt;I will give food and wine assignments three days prior to party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, loving, supportive and relaxing environment of my home. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dress code - &amp;quot; professional casual.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;First impressions are most meaningful. &lt;br /&gt;7:00PM - 10:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Sat. Sept.11, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maximum attendees 60 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions &lt;br /&gt;My Home &lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road &lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128-Exit 16B/Route 109 toward Westwood&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles  left on Pond Street- just past the middle school on left-if you go by Dunkin Donuts on right you missed it.&lt;br /&gt;Go I mile left on Oak St.&lt;br /&gt;Go 1.5 miles to end-right on Brook St.&lt;br /&gt;100 feet take a  right on Woodridge Road&lt;br /&gt;My home is the 3rd house on the left-cream colored- number 36 Woodridge, Westwood, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Saturday, Sept. 25th at 7:00pm----Invite a gentleman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next Oct. 9th home party- very special day- I will improve and raise my personal professional standards by having our party catered by a quality restaurant in Westwood.  Expect to be Wowed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is right now! &lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285731500000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>57</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281195266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Home Party</name><id>14349175</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285455600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/14349175/</event_url></item>