<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>889 Elm St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.990740</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Veterans Memorial Park</name><city>Manchester</city><id>332819</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463070</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I just noticed that the Summer Concert Series is back at Veterans Park!  Please join me for some excellent music and fantastic company.  Afterward we can go somewhere to have a drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.intownmanchester.com/images/Portrait%20of%20Headliners.jpg"&gt;http://www.intownmanchester.com/images/Portrait%20of%20Headliners.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Band:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mission Hill is an alternative rock band from Boston MA that mixes provoking songwriting, catchy hooks, moody vocals, an energetic live show, and strong musicianship with an unerring commitment to their unique sound. Since forming in late 2007 they have gained a large following through relentless gigging and indie distribution. Their single "Crazy" is receiving airplay all over the country and is steadily rising up the radio charts. The band has received much critical acclaim including recently being awarded an LA Music Award for "Indie Male Vocalist of the Year", being named the "Top Local Band To Watch in 2010" by Boston Music Spotlight, as well as being named to the number one spot on Alternative Addiction's list of "Top Ten Unsigned Bands in the Country".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After bursting onto the scene with their debut EP, "Mission Hill EP", the band has grown into one of the premiere bands on the New England music scene. The bands recent success is apparent with their exciting 2010 that included being selected by Bon Jovi to open for his show at Gillette Stadium, performing at the Kiss 108 Kiss Concert at the Comcast Center, completing a one month residency at the new Hard Rock Cafe in Saigon Vietnam, playing live on FOX Morning News and releasing the critically acclaimed "Beautiful Addiction EP". The band has shared the stage with many national acts including Bon Jovi, Kid Rock, Boys Like Girls, The Script, Candlebox, Tim Reynolds, Ke$ha, Marcy Playground, WAR, Donavan Frankenreiter, Parachute, Blessid Union of Souls, The Gracious Few, and many more. With their new songs and an inspiring live performance, Mission Hill is coming for your audio souls!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vaudandthevillains.com/"&gt;http://www.reverbnation.com/missionhill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; FREE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS TO VETERANS PARK From the South:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the Everett Turnpike or Route 93N to Route 293N. Take Exit 5 (Granite Street). Turn right at bottom of the ramp, cross the bridge and proceed straight through two lights. Look for the Center of NH Parking Garage on your left. Veterans Park will be diagonally across to the left. From the North: Take Route 93S to Route 293S. Take Exit 6 (Amoskeag Bridge). Bear right off of the exit and turn right after the Ramada Inn. Cross the bridge and bear right onto Canal Street. Go through several sets of lights to Granite Street and turn left onto Granite Street. Look for the Center of NH Parking Garage on your left. Veterans Park will be diagonally across to the left. From the East: Take 101 West to 93 South. At the split, follow signs for 293 North. Follow 293 North to Exit 5 (Granite Street). Turn right at the bottom of the ramp, cross the bridge and proceed straight through two lights. Look for the Center of NH Parking Garage on your left. Veterans Park will be diagonally across to the left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a balloon attached to my chair.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345383634000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344718319000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TD Bank Summer Concert Series:  Mission Hill</name><id>77333432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345156200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/77333432/</event_url></item>