<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 32A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01366</zip><lat>42.448673</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 40</name><city>Petersham</city><id>3132431</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.206779</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This hike is maybe 3 miles in each direction. Terrain is wooded and hilly, on a combination of dirt and (very old) paved roads. We will hike from the highway through the woods to the ruins of Dana Common, which was part of the town of Dana before the Quabbin Reservoir was built. After Dana Common, we will continue on another trail to the wreckage of a fighter jet which crashed in the woods in the 1950s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe we'll have time to detour to the shoreline...any questions, Ralph P. is leading the hike!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Reservoir is a state reservation around a water supply. Please *remove all trash* from the premises. Animals are not allowed. Where we are going, there are no facilities except an outhouse at the beginning of the old road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gate 40 is north of the Hardwick/Petersham line, and you have to pass through the center of the small town of Hardwick, and then to a rural stretch again, before you get to Gate 40. Your GPS will be helpful, but I will be there at least 15 minutes before 10am so my white car will be a landmark. It may be hard to see in the shaded parking area, but I'll stand near the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI, Gate 40 is on the *southbound* side of Route 32A, about 1 mile north of Dana Rd. in Petersham, MA. There is no address I can put in that puts the marker in the exact spot. As it is, the marker on Google Maps is somewhat north of where the gate is.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for our cars parked at Gate 40, outside the woods, on the southbound side of Route 32A</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph P</member_name><member_id>4253893</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314193350000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314012995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Dana Common to Jet Wreckage (Quabbin Reservoir)</name><id>30401811</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314108000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/30401811/</event_url></item>