<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Double Indemnity&lt;/b&gt; USA 1941 107 min. Starring Barbara Stanwyck, Fred MacMurray, and Edward G. Robinson. Robinson is the good guy, MacMurray (My Three Sons) is the baddie and Stanwyck is fantastic as the femme fatale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is a weeknight event, please only RSVP Yes if you plan to join us afterward for our post-film discussion. This will make things a lot easier for arranging which restaurant will we go to, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the greatest movies of all time with an electric, snappy, hard-boiled script written by Wilder and Raymond Chandler, based on the novel by James M. Cain. A classic, brooding film noir, told in flashback, about an adulterous, duplicitous couple, a calculating insurance salesman (MacMurray) and a scheming, irresistible, long-legged blonde femme fatale (Stanwyck), who commit the murder of her wealthy husband in a larcenous, fraudulent attempt to collect on an insurance policy that pays double for accidental death. Unfortunately, the double-crossing, cold-hearted protagonists are doggedly and persistently pursued by a suspicious, formidable insurance investigator (Robinson). Academy Award Nominations: 7, including Best Picture, Best Actress--Barbara Stanwyck, Best Director, Best Adapted Screenplay, Best B/W Cinematography. Tim Dirks Top 100 Movies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Double Indemnity&lt;/b&gt; represents the high-water mark of 1940s film noir urban crime dramas  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wilder co-wrote the script with celebrated crime novelist Raymond Chandler and together they cinch this yarn tighter than a hangman's noose. The air positively crackles as Neff (MacMurray) and Phyllis(Stanwyck) are all at once magnetically entwined and totally repelled by one another. Droll lines are delivered like the crack of a whip - and it smarts. &amp;quot;We're both rotten,&amp;quot; declares Phyllis. &amp;quot;Only you're a little more rotten,&amp;quot; answers Neff. If all the sharp edges and stark shadows send a shiver up the spine, Edward G Robinson brings heart as Neff's boss and moral compass. It all makes for a lusciously black brew that renders modern noir pale by comparison.  BBC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should be fun,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be watching my back as I hold a Meet-Up sign near the front row at film's end.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265765989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Billy Wilder's Double Indemnity</name><id>12566404</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268434800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12566404/</event_url></item>