<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Dudley St &amp; W Clifford</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02907</zip><lat>41.810497</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>City Farm</name><city>Providence</city><id>6800362</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.419395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;We've done this event a few times over the years - thank you, Ben!&lt;span&gt;So why not do it again!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Some of you may remember we went to the 4th Annual Urban Agriculture Kickoff and Seed Swap at the Roger Williams Park Botanical Center last March. It was a lot of fun and very inspiring!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;You don't have to be a member to attend SCLT events, but there are a few perks and it only costs a minimum of $35 to join. If you're not a member yet, but have been thinking about it (like me), this is a great time! Through May 19th, your membership will be matched dollar for dollar by the Membership Match Fund donors, so your membership donation will be doubled for SCLT, and you'll get 10% off at the Plant Sale among other perks! Sounds good to me, and I finally joined today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Otherwise, hope to see you there!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/e/2/event_234458882.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;21st Annual Rare and Unusual Plant Sale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, May 18, &amp;amp; Sunday, May 19, 2013&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10am – 2pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special preview hour for members on Saturday, 9 - 10am*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Special Instructions for the special preview hour:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We ask that all SCLT members remember to bring their cards with them to the preview hour! This year, current SCLT members will be given priority admittance. People who plan to sign up or renew their membership at the Plant Sale will be asked to do so before entering the event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://southsideclt.org/visitcityfarm"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to City Farm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://southsideclt.org/membership"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Become a member&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and save 10% on your purchases! Give a &lt;a href="http://southsideclt.org/merchandise#Plant"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plant Sale gift certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to a friend or family member!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;City Farm is home to the Rare and Unusual Plant Sale every year. One weekend in May, hundreds of varieties of annuals, perennials, and fruit and vegetable plant starts are available for purchase. Most of the 18,000 plants were carefully cultivated through the late winter and early spring on-site by the City Farm team, including dozens of volunteers. Hundreds of other perennials and annuals are donated by generous local gardeners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This celebrated event attracts 2,000 gardeners from all levels of experience, from the brand-new community gardener to seasoned home gardening experts. It is a wonderful kick-off to the growing season, featuring live music and several gardening experts on hand to assist gardeners new and old. &lt;strong&gt;As of 2010, the Plant Sale accepts SNAP EBT benefits (food stamps)!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Plant Sale is a community event, and a community effort. All proceeds from the Plant Sale support Southside Community Land Trust's education and community gardening programs, and plant starts that are not sold are donated to over 30 area non-profits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interested in volunteering at the Plant Sale?&lt;/strong&gt; We need talliers (people who count up the items and enter the number on the tallying sheet...no math needed), people who help carry plants to cars, people to check memberships, people to set up tents/tables before the sale and break down the tents/tables after the sale. They will be standing their entire shift. Lunch will be provided! Contact Michelle Walker at michelle@southsideclt.org or 401-273-9419 ext.26&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there early for the Members Preview, wearing a scarf with pink flowers on it, but will hang out for a little while. It's a great event!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368901009000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368224075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI - SCLT 21st Annual Plant Sale!!!!</name><id>118798762</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368885600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/118798762/</event_url></item>