<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you find yourself becoming conscious or "waking up" after your mind has been wandering and imagining things during the day? Daydreams are very similar to night dreams, but are usually not so fantastical. Because we are awake while daydreaming, daydreams are often directed by the conscious mind and are often desirable or pleasant in nature. We are literally awake, but mentally dreaming, being somewhere else than our body is. In the past daydreaming was often considered unproductive, wasteful, sinful, or even dangerous. Now we know that daydreaming is a very healthy, natural activity, and serves many productive functions, including creative problem-solving and future planning. Feel free to bring any daydreams or night dreams to share. Sharing is encouraged but not required. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by parking lot, up stairs, down hall, left through angel doorway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353694277000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352868322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What a Day for a Daydream</name><id>91323262</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353456000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/91323262/</event_url></item>