<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>To friends and group members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has been only half a Year since I took over this group as an organizer, and it has grown well over the 100 mark with high ratings from the participants.  To celebrate this success I invite all of you to come to a free introductory event.  Everyone is welcome, but come especially if you were curious, but never joined us before.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you already made a resolution to make your New Year a year of freedom from trauma, pain and anxiety?  &lt;br /&gt;Whether you have or have not, come and let us ring to Freedom in 2010, meet each other, learn, heal, eat, celebrate!  We are doing a potluck, so bring your favorite snack. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever wanted to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- realize that no matter what your story, healing is possible for all and in a very short      time in a way that is graceful an lasting?&lt;br /&gt;- discover that what is happening to you always has a reason and an explanation;&lt;br /&gt;- learn the new breakthroughs in energy healing based therapies?&lt;br /&gt;- experience a first hand presentation and a demonstration of how these techniques can work for you?&lt;br /&gt;- share understanding and support with other positive folks recovering from trauma/anxiety?&lt;br /&gt;- regain trust in the wisdom and power of the universal laws and principles? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then reserve early, we have a limited space.&lt;br /&gt;Let this be your YEAR OF FREEDOM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;           ****************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Here is My intention for the Next Year:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As I meet a person or talk about someone, I want my first thought be - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;I Remember Something Good About You. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;And being able to do that even if I am in the midst of bouts with upsets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to share with all of you a practice I began recently.  Before I approach a person or think about another person I create a feeling in my mind, heart, my body and my energy field of love, safety and acceptance.  Then I think of something good about this person and shower him/her  (in my thoughts if they are not physically present) with that energy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The results are amazing.&lt;br /&gt;First of all, it takes my &amp;quot;busy&amp;quot; mind away FROM thinking of the next clever thing to say, TO creating a beautiful &amp;quot;white space&amp;quot; of a human connection.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recently I approached a woman in an car in a parking lot asking for directions. As she turned her head it was quite clear she was recovering from some very unpleasant hungover.  She looked disheveled and grumpy.  Yet the wave of positive energy that engulfed her caught her by surprise. She took a couple moments to gather herself back from the state of disorientation, and then proceeded eagerly giving me the most detailed directions i could have received. By the end she looked positively glowing (a new treatment for hangovers??)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My new year challenge is to apply this in situations of personal conflicts.  I am taking a big breath... Being a fiery triple Leo, that could be quite a challenge. Please wish me success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I found this poem to be inspirational. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I KNOW SOMETHING GOOD ABOUT YOU&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't the old world be better&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If folks we meet would say,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I know something good about you&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And then treat us that way?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't it be fine and dandy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If each handclasp warm and true&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carried with it this assurance,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know something good about you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't life be lots more happy,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we praised the good we see?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For there's such a lot of goodness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the world of you and me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't it be great to practice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That fine way of thinking too?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know something good about me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I know something good about you&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Author Unknown-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;I know something good about all of you, even If I do not know you yet. &lt;br /&gt;  Happy 2010 New Year. Yuliya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264890363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262443986000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gift of Freedom New Year celebration - Meet the Group, Learn and Celebrate</name><id>12196804</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262822400000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/12196804/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/6/global_12459558.jpeg</photo_url></item>