<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cambridge</address_2><address_1>738 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 354-2685</phone><name>Cantab Lounge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>274611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105023</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Get ready to get sweaty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's again time to descend upon the Cantab Lounge in Cambridge's Central Square for a night of dancing to The Chicken Slacks.&amp;nbsp; The Chicken Slacks always &lt;strong&gt;bring it&lt;/strong&gt; each and every Thursday night, but a show to kick off the official start of summer is certain to be special.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suspect that a lot of you are taking Friday, 1 July off to begin a four day celebration of the 4th of July, so why not kick it off with a vengeance by joining your fellow Meetup members for a night of R&amp;amp;B and Soul Bacchanalia?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The music starts at 9:30 and continues until 1:30.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The cover charge is $5 at the door.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Cantab is cash only -- no plastic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Cantab is on the small side and can fill up; there are sometimes waiting lines outside....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'll be there sometime after 9.&amp;nbsp; But I also may get some dinner and 'warm up' next door at the Tavern on the Square.&amp;nbsp; (If others are interested in this, I may organize a pre-Meetup meetup.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Cantab is located steps from the Central Square Red Line T station.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some street parking is available near the Cantab.&amp;nbsp; It's generally free after 8, but a couple of small lots are not free until 10.&amp;nbsp; Please be sure to check signs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There's also a taxi stand on the same block on Mass Ave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a joint meetup with the Boston Live Music group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I bear an amazing resemblance to my profile picture and, as an additional aid to those looking for me, I'll force myself to hold a beer.  (cell phone # sent to all attending members at 12:40p, 30 june.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>paul</member_name><member_id>4738108</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309488238000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308928972000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's kick off summer with The Chicken Slacks!</name><id>23377501</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309483800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/23377501/</event_url></item>