<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>21 Garden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01985</zip><lat>42.809288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurel Grange </name><city>West Newbury</city><id>13083772</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.944702</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Laurel Grange is partnering with New Harmony Farm to host a screening of the award winning documentary &lt;strong&gt;THE REAL DIRT ON FARMER JOHN&lt;/strong&gt; followed by a meet your local farmer discussion with Lisa Colby and Erin Stack. The screening is a fundraiser to support the &lt;em&gt;Remineralize the Earth&lt;/em&gt; project at New Harmony Farm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE REAL DIRT ON FARMER JOHN&lt;/strong&gt; is an epic tale of a maverick Midwestern farmer. An outcast in his community, Farmer John bravely stands amidst a failing economy, vicious rumors, and violence. By melding the traditions of family farming with the power of art and free expression, this powerful story of transformation and renewal heralds a resurrection of farming in America. Through highly personal interviews and 50 years of beautifully textured footage, filmmaker Taggart Siegel shares Farmer John's haunting and humorous odyssey, capturing what it means to be wildly different in a rural community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Remineralize the Earth&lt;/em&gt; is partnering with New Harmony Farm to conduct research on the use of ground rock dust, compost and a type of charcoal known as ‘biochar’ to improve the quality and amount of topsoil. Designed by Dr. Thomas Goreau, the scientific study currently underway at New Harmony Farm aims to quantify nutrients in soil and plant matter, monitor growth rates of crop plants, soil carbon storage, and quantitatively measure greenhouse admissions from soil. The findings of this research will point the way to increasing crop yieldsand their nutritional value. The New Harmony Farm study is cutting-edge in its scope and has important implications for global climate, agriculture and the environment. This project has gone forward in the first year without funding. It has progressed only due to in-kind donations of materials and time by unpaid volunteers. While Remineralize The Earth is actively pursuing larger funding to cover a three year period, in the interim donations are needed to cover the costs of soil and plant testing (an amount of roughly $3,000) associated with this work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: Suggested donation is $10 (more would be most welcome). &lt;br /&gt;

 If you have any questions or want to make reservations contact Erin at 978-807-6315&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erin Stack</member_name><member_id>10226383</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367633862000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367012466000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Real Dirt on Farmer John</name><id>116373642</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367622000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/116373642/</event_url></item>