<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Crown St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304432</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 777-3116</phone><name>116 Crown St</name><city>New Haven</city><id>704500</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.926163</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>On July 22, our group will be hosting two special guests for our members to network with - representatives Kathleen Krolak and CEO Michele Whelley of the Economic Development Corporation of New Haven. EDC New Haven is a group focused on retaining and building business in New Haven, by connecting local businesses with available resources. If you are a Freelancer or Business conducting business in or near New Haven, the EDC may be able to help you take advantage of grants, tax deductions, or other resources that your business may be eligible for, but not aware of. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Wednesday, July 22, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Location: 116 Crown St.&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:00-8:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $3 online / $5 door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT THE EDC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who We Are&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Economic Development Corporation of New Haven is a private not-for-profit corporation focused exclusively on economic development in New Haven, Connecticut.  We look forward to working with you to help your business grow and prosper in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our Mission&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We work in collaboration with our partners – the City of New Haven, Yale University and other institutions and the business community – to create a vibrant business environment in New Haven. We serve as a catalyst for attracting human and capital investment to the City and its neighborhoods by retaining and attracting businesses and fostering a positive economic climate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about the EDC, please visit their website: &lt;a href="http://www.edcnewhaven.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.edcnewhaven.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the front bar or in back. Please ask an employee if you cannot find the group.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250116801000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246556080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Network with Representatives from EDC New Haven</name><id>10789581</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248300000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/10789581/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/c/global_701868.jpeg</photo_url></item>