<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Broad st</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04217</zip><lat>44.400806</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bethel Inn</name><city>Bethel</city><id>830512</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.788117</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/f/5/0/event_65292112.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;You can still come!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Friday - Sunday, December 23 - 25 &lt;br /&gt;

The 18th Annual Bethel Inn Winter Weekend&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Trip's Leaders&lt;/strong&gt;: Barry Polsky&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;and Sara Secunda&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVENT:&lt;/strong&gt; Join us for a Mosaic of Mass tradition &amp;ndash; our annual winter weekend trip to the Bethel Inn in Bethel, ME. (When we are there, it turns into Beth El!). Enjoy the comforts of a first class inn for two nights, two sumptuous buffet breakfasts, a Saturday night 3-course gourmet dinner, a swim in an outdoor heated pool, and a workout room all at an unbelievably reasonable price. Nearby is Sunday River (info at&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.sundayriver.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.sundayriver.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;), a world class downhill ski resort renowned for its snow conditions even this early in the ski season. For those of you who prefer cross-country skiing or snowshoeing, there are 30 km of groomed and marked trails right out the back door of the inn. Ski and snowshoe rentals are available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Even if you are neither a downhill nor a cross country skier, you can have an enjoyable relaxing weekend at the inn swimming in the heated pool, exercising in their workout room, or walking the picturesque streets of the town of Bethel. After your daytime activities&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;and dinner on Saturday evening, relax by the fireplace and enjoy games and good conversation. You can read more about the Bethel Inn at &lt;a href="http://www.bethelinn.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.bethelinn.com/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span&gt;This year, we are pleased to be holding the weekend on Xmas weekend so that it may be more feasible to stay over one or two extra days for some of you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;MEET:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;A list of members will be made available for the purpose of facilitating ride sharing to the inn on Friday evening (about a 3 &amp;frac12; hour drive from Boston). The inn is located at 21 Broad St., Bethel, Maine. To contact the inn call: 800-654-0125 or 207-824-2175.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;RSVP:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Is still open you can contact me for more details and to make connections with the Trip's 2 leaders&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mail your check, made out to MOMC of MA, to Sara Secunda, 272 Main St, #B2, Acton, MA 01720.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Please include:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(1)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Your name and your town&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(2)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Your email address&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(3)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Your phone number(s),&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(4)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;whether you would like a lift ticket for Sunday River and for when&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(5)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;who you would like as a roommate if you have a preference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(6)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;whether you want to be on a list for carpooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(7)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;whether you have any objections to being on a list of participants (names and email addresses)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Absolutely no reservations will be taken after &lt;strong&gt;December 16&lt;/strong&gt; subject to availability. First come, first serve with respect to rooms - most of our rooms will be in the main inn but later registrants will be given rooms in the Oaks or Pines, a short walk from the main building. The latest registrants will be offered rooms in outlying buildings about a 10-minute walk from the main inn - you will be informed beforehand if this is your only choice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; Includes two nights lodging, two buffet breakfasts, and one 3-course gourmet dinner. Regular rate is an amazing $199. Early bird rate is an even more amazing $189 if we get your check by November 15th. The late rate is $209 if we get your check after November 22. Late checks will be accepted only as availability allows.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are a very limited number of single rooms available &amp;ndash;add $53 to the rate if you want a regular single room. There are larger deluxe rooms available for an extra $83 per person for a deluxe double room or an extra $160 per person for a deluxe single room. Reserving one of these rooms guarantees that you will be in the main inn. There is an option to arrive earlier than Friday for $102 per night ppdo in regular rooms or stay later than Sunday for an additional $144 per night ppdo in a deluxe room. You can call the inn directly to make these arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;LIFT TICKETS:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;We will be ordering our lift tickets directly through the Bethel Inn. When you RSVP, please indicate whether you would like a lift-ticket. If so, how many days do will you be skiing? Also, are you or anyone in your party a Senior (over 65), Young Adult (13-18), or Junior (6-12)? We must have your request for lift tickets by December 17. You will pick up your lift-ticket when you check in and the cost will be charged&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;to your room account. More info will be forthcoming as to lift ticket prices but they will be less than the prices on the mountain. How much less depends on how many people order lift tickets..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be waiting at the Inn when you check in</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324951063000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319165567000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 18th Annual Bethel Inn Winter Weekend</name><id>38177342</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324681200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/38177342/</event_url></item>