<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Holy huge crowd, Batman! Maybe everyone's just trying to get in from the heat this week or maybe everyone loves a mindbender, but I always say, &amp;quot;The more, the merrier!&amp;quot; Please try to keep your RSVP up to date, as it helps me know who to wait for. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:05, so let's meet at 6:30 right inside the ticket lobby. At 6:45 SHARP, I'll buy us all our tickets ($8 per), then we can get concessions and take our seats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie (running time: 2 hrs, 22 minutes), those of us who'd like to go out can head to Uno's to chat and have a bite or a drink to eat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call me if you're going to be late but are definitely coming. (508/308-4897)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on Thursday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810099246/info" target="_blank"&gt;Inception&lt;/a&gt; looks like The Matrix for a new decade. But with Leo, which is hardly ever bad. ;-) Take a break from the heat and hang out with us for a mind-boggling adventure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dom Cobb is a skilled thief, the absolute best in the dangerous art of extraction, stealing valuable secrets from deep within the subconscious during the dream state when the mind is at its most vulnerable. Cobb's rare ability has made him a coveted player in this treacherous new world of corporate espionage, but it has also made him an international fugitive and cost him everything he has ever loved. Now Cobb is being offered a chance at redemption. One last job could give him his life back but only if he can accomplish the impossible -- inception. Instead of the perfect heist, Cobb and his team of specialists have to pull off the reverse: their task is not to steal an idea but to plant one. If they succeed, it could be the perfect crime. But no amount of careful planning or expertise can prepare the team for the dangerous enemy that seems to predict their every move. An enemy that only Cobb could have seen coming. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Inception!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282010353000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278966769000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inception</name><id>14080685</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281652200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/14080685/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>