<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Intersection of Spruce &amp; Charter Oak Streets</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.763653</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>East Coast Greenway, Manchester portion</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1339117</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.516000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Some day the East Coast Greenway (ECG) will go all the way from Florida to Maine, and vice versa! But right now, parts of it are open and ready to walk, roll, skate, and push a baby stroller along. So come explore the Greenway! &lt;br /&gt;Start at the ECG kiosk at Manchester's Charter Oak Park.&lt;br /&gt;Two options on this walk -- a longer and shorter one. Both are moderately paced and not too hilly. The terrain is mostly pavement - a wide bike path, although we will be crossing one street.&lt;br /&gt;We will walk east on the Greenway for a mile or so, then return to the park. Option two -- we will then walk west toward the Cheney Historic District, and return to the park, about four miles all together. But participants can decide to skip the second half of the walk. Another option is to come early, 12:45, for a talk at the kiosk in the park dedicated to raising awareness of kidney transplantation and disease, as well as a talk by a member of the East Coast Greenway organization, that is creating this accessible trail, a part of which we are fortunate to host here in Manchester. Directions: The entrance to Charter Oak Park is south of the intersection of Spruce and Charter Oak Streets in Manchester. Drive into the park, and make a sharp right at the bottom of the hill into the parking lot near the playground. The kiosk is just south of the parking area. No rain date, but we will go out if mild sprinkles. No dogs, please. &lt;br /&gt;Please note that the general public is also invited to this walk, so if you prefer to walk with only Meetup members, you may want to skip this one. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue backpack</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan B</member_name><member_id>7644854</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283132477000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280865517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Aug. 28 East Coast Greenway Walks, Manchester CT</name><id>14307716</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283014800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/14307716/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/global_16938147.jpeg</photo_url></item>