<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gilford</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03246</zip><lat>43.579052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Belknap Carriage Road</name><city>03246</city><id>13613372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.474998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for hikers aged 50-70+ (most of us are 55-65) who haven't given up on their love of hiking and being in nature despite their age or level of physical conditioning. We hike at a pace 50% slower than the AMC Trailguide book time.Hike ratings: easy, moderate, strenuous,very strenuous.We start as a group,we hike as a group and we end as a group. There are three other hiking Meetup groups if you want a faster pace or more challenging hikes (The New England Hiking Meetup, 4 Seasons Hiking Group, New England Over 40 Hiking Group). The hiking Meetup group,(Fellowship of the Tortoise) does easier,slower paced hikes than this group. Our goal is to stay fit while enjoying the camaraderie of hikers who have similar skills and goals. This is a dog free hiking group.Everybody must join the group and have a picture to be on a hike.If you are camera shy,print out a picture of yourself,and give it to me at the trailhead.The picture is to show Fish and Game if you get separated from the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead: Take I93 north to exit 20,make a left onto US3 north towards Laconia for 6.7 miles, stay with US3 on the Laconia/Gilford Bypass for 3.5 miles, take the exit for Gilford Avenue (NH11A), make a right at the bottom of the exit ramp for 2.4 miles to the flashing yellow light,  make a right onto Belknap Mountain Road for 2.6 miles, make a left onto Belknap Carriage Road for 1.6 miles to the trailhead at the end of the road. We will hike the RED Trail to the summit of Belknap Mountain(2,382'), the Blue,Saddle and Brook Trails to the summit of Gunstock Mountain(2,250'). 3.8 mile round trip, 960' elevation gain,AMC book time 3.0 hours, 4.5 hours estimated time for our group.Views of the Belknap Mountain Range on both summits.----Steve----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look forBlue/Gray Chevy pick up truck NH2646423</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve A</member_name><member_id>6009756</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369612634000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1413769</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>New England Over 50 Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369409212000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EASY / MODERATE  HIKE--BELKNAP AND GUNSTOCK MOUNTAINS</name><id>121033372</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369576800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group/events/121033372/</event_url></item>