<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Longfellow Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375848</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Friends Meeting House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>918727</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.127358</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Winter Tree ID has practical uses, such as finding the trees that have: &lt;br /&gt;

 sap for making syrup or fermented drinks (not only maple) &lt;br /&gt;

 edible buds &lt;br /&gt;

 twigs for flavoring tea &lt;br /&gt;

 bark with medicinal properties &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

It can also help you better observe, appreciate and feel closer to the nature around you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This class will focus on how to distinguish trees primarily by their twigs and buds.  I will give some information on dietary, medicinal and practical uses of different trees.  There will be handouts with pictures, charts, and diagrams.  We’ll have samples twigs of 25-30 of the most common trees in the area.  You’ll learn a lot of new vocabulary.  There will be exercises to help you see things you may not have paid attention to before.  In addition to classroom instruction, there will be outdoor practice with trees in a nearby park. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The introductory class will be 4 hours.  Bring a bag lunch and clothes suitable for walking around outside in winter. Tuition will be $40.  If you can’t afford the tuition, you can contact me to find out if you are eligible for a partial scholarship.  Contact me about this by Saturday, January 26, 12 noon at 617-492-2340.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The classroom accommodates 12 people.  If you want to guarantee a seat, you have to pay in advance by January 31 by Paypal or mailing a check.  Contact me at 617-492-2340 or ejkobek@gmail.com for the account number or mailing address. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This is an introductory class.  To feel confident in identifying trees requires practice.  If there is interest in continued, supervised study, I would be available for additional classes and field trips. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Jules Kobek is co-founder of DIO (Do-It-Ourselves) Skillshare, which teaches skills on urban homesteading and sustainability.  Jules has taught or co-taught classes on sprouting and microgreens, foraging, making cordage from found plants, and vegetable gardening through the Boston Skillshare, Cambridge Center for Adult Education, and the Urban Homesteaders League.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Basement, Room 3.  Call 617-492-2340 for more information</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>HJ</member_name><member_id>13327790</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359999297000</updated><rating><average>3.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357321352000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Tree Identification for Urban Foragers</name><id>97895242</id><headcount>12</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359817200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/97895242/</event_url></item>