<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51, Room 315</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>836742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084771</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Boston Investors Business Daily Group Main Meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;Map of MIT campus&lt;/a&gt;, Building E51, we meet in Room 315&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DAVID WEIS ON THE MARKET, MIKE KINKEAD CONTINUES HIS SERIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; Market Talk by David Weis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Market Talk is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker - usually for the next month and sometimes including longer range predictions. The speaker then makes a short case for defense of the prediction - usually taking about 10 minutes.  The audience is expected to probe or support the speaker's ideas. In general the audience participation portion of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. Historically this market discussion is lively and insights come from all around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;CAN SLIM™ Investing in a Severe Bear Market Rally: Is It Possible to Win?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Note that Mike has updated this description due to the very interesting results he has uncovered in his research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Kinkead continues his series on investing the IBD way using William J. O’Neil’s CAN SLIM® approach. Unfortunately, some of the IBD investing rules do not work during a rally in a severe bear market.  Worse, some of the CAN SLIM® rules are very different than the traditional IBD approach!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Using actual stock and Industry Group performance data during the 12.2.08 to 1.12.09 rally, the February talk will focus on these revised rules and how to play rallies in today’s severe and volatile bear market. The talk will address the following questions:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What are the characteristics of the winner stocks that gained 20% or more during the latest rally? Are they traditional CAN SLIM® stocks? Would we have found these stocks for our Watch List as of 12.2.08, the follow-through day and beginning of the rally?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How do IBD’s 20 Rules for Investment Success change based on the winner stocks during the latest rally?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How do we use the Screens of the Day on investors.com in today’s market?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What types of chart patterns work now?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What Industry Groups and stocks are growing now? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Based on what we have learned above, what are some good candidates for our Watch List going forward?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the fifth in a series of interactive talks with Mike at the Wednesday Boston IBD Meetup. Everyone is encouraged to contribute his or her experience and expertise to the discussion.   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING of the Tiger Financial Network starts at 5:30 PM.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; See &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;the announcement here&lt;/a&gt;. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers by Bob Podd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Doug&lt;br /&gt;7:15 Market Talk by David Weis&lt;br /&gt;7:45 Stockpicks&lt;br /&gt;8:15 Break&lt;br /&gt;8:25 Feature Talk by Mike Kinkead&lt;br /&gt;We will stick to this schedule. Please do not ask to change the time limits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to join our online discussion!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are open to the public, there is no admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236035325000</updated><rating><average>4.07999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232553709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors February Main Meeting</name><id>9570228</id><headcount>66</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235606400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9570228/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>