<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>96 Winthrop street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372280</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tommy Doyles</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1114814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a Boston Skeptics event, for which we will be tagging along. Jonathan McDowell is also a member of this group and is an Astrophysicist at Harvard. He has collected a rare library of space flight documents/books/periodicals dating more than four decades, and has been interviewed many times by news agencies (NPR, BBC, et. al.) concerning astronomical and space stories of public interest. He has also been gregarious enough to host several astronomical observatory meetups at Harvard for BA in the past. As a conduit of public understanding of science, Jonathan is truly one of our treasured members&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jonathan's title and abstract:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Elegy For A Spaceplane: 30 Years of Space Shuttles&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;NASA&amp;rsquo;s Space Shuttle is being retired this month after three decades of ups and downs both literal and metaphorical. I&amp;rsquo;ll take a trip down memory lane and review what the Shuttles did and didn&amp;rsquo;t do, and discuss other spaceplanes past and present. Finally, I&amp;rsquo;ll speculate about what&amp;rsquo;s next for the US human spaceflight program.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Jonathan is a long-time member of the Boston Skeptics, an astronomer, and expert on space travel. He writes a monthly column for Sky and Telescope and maintains the Jonathan&amp;rsquo;s Space Report web site. He previously spoke to us about the history of the Moon Race, in a very interesting, informative and popular talk, especially about the little-known Soviet moon program. Be sure to arrive early so you can get a seat in front!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is the Tommy Doyles just off Harvard Square T stop.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>4427039</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311716807000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309399575000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skeptics in the Pub: Jonathan McDowell  "Elegy For A Spaceplane"</name><id>24048631</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311634800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/24048631/</event_url></item>