<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting Fee </label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>After a 2 month hiatus the Afterwork Mixer returns, this time we are kicking off the summer on the Provincetown Pier ship as we set sail along the Boston harbor. The ship will be located at 200 Seaport Blvd along the commonwealth pier. We will board at 7pm and the cruise goes until 11pm. This will be a great opportunity to meet other members of the group and also expand your network as there will be hundreds of Boston's young professionals on board. Last year over 800 people experienced this cruise!! We expect this years attendence to exceed last years total!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Please be  sure to join us for the preparty  mix and mingle at Seaport Bar and Grille  (6:30)  prior to boarding.   Afterwards there is a complimentary after party for those still interested in continuing the nite. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy 3 floors of entertainment , the first floor will have a few rooms for mixing and mingling with other young professionals,   and a  Sinatra themed  lounge on the 2nd floor. The third floor will have a Dj spinning great top 40 dance music on the  mega  sized dance floor. All floor will have a cash bar. This will surely be one of the major events of the summer! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Cost: Boston Nightlife group  members will receive a special 2 for 1 deal.We need to keep track on how many of  our  members will be attending this event   If you are interested please contact the &lt;b&gt;Assistant Organizer Steve&lt;/b&gt; by email or call 617-671-5310 for information on  how to order tickets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be an exciting event, remember we will be meeting at the Seaport Bar and Grille 150 Northern Ave at 6:30,   please go online for directions.We will meet at the bar please take down my phone number listed above for reference.  I look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transportation Options: By  MBTA: Silver Line SL1 towards Logan Airport get off at World Trade Center. &lt;br /&gt;                                                        5 minute walk to the Seaport Grille and the Ship. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                       By Car:  There will be parking lots around the seaport area the avg rate is &lt;br /&gt;                                                      $8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                       By Cab: If you are located within the Boston area the Seaport district is less than   &lt;br /&gt;                                                     a ten minute ride. I highly recommend this option.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: A ticket is required for entry into the cruise, plaease contact Assistant Organizer Steve for details.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the Seaport Bar and Grille,  which will be great for members to mix and mingle before the ship boards at 7pm. I HIGHLY recommend meeting the group here because after we all board it will be extremely hard to find the group.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214088107000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This is going to be a great event and opportunity to meet some new and excting people and better yet set sail on the Boston Harbor for which should be a wonderful Thurs evening!!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212634810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>**Special Event** Afterwork Mixer Sunset Party Cruise along the Boston Harbor!!!</name><id>8082252</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213914600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8082252/</event_url></item>