<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Trinity St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.766235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BUSHNELL PARK</name><city>Hartford</city><id>664313</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.679720</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Enjoy the evening with these talented artist, picnic in the park with friends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hartford Jazz Society's Monday Night Jazz&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;at the Pavilion in Bushnell Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brandee Younger Trio&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     A versatile musician who has been proven to defy genres and labels, this young harpist has created a unique niche in both traditional and non-traditional harp arenas. Performing mainly on a concert grand classical harp, Ms. Younger is often heard performing jazz, classical and hip-hop in a seemingly effortless manner.&lt;br /&gt;     Best-known for her limitless drive, Ms. Younger remains in high demand and attracts the attention of today’s most well-known artists, producers and groups. As a classical harpist, she has performed with an array of orchestras including the Eastern Connecticut Symphony, Soulful Symphony, Ensemble Du Monde, Camerata New York and the Red Bull Artsehcro, a “non-conformist” orchestra.&lt;br /&gt;     She has worked &amp;amp; recorded with a number of jazz luminaries including Nat Reeves, Ravi Coltrane, Charlie Haden, Reggie Workman, Kenny Garrett, Rashied Ali, Jeff “Tain” Watts and Steve Wilson, as well as with a host of New York City’s top, young jazz musicians.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://brandeeyounger.com/about/biography/" target="_blank"&gt;http://brandeeyounger...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carolyn Leonhart - Wayne Escoffery Quintet&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.carolynleonhart.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.carolynleo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.escofferymusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.escofferym...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wayne Escoffery:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Since moving to New York City in 2000, tenor saxophonist Wayne Escoffery has become one of the Jazz world's most talented rising stars and in-demand sidemen. At only 35 he has recorded seven CDs as a leader and been on numerous recordings as a sideman. Wayne began his professional New York career touring and recording with The Eric Reed Septet. In 2001 he became a steady member of the Mingus Big Band/Orchestra/Dynasty, The Lonnie Plaxico Group, and Abdulah Ibrahim's Akaya. Then in 2004 Grammy award winning producer, arranger and trumpeter Don Sickler asked Wayne to be a part of Ben Riley's Monk legacy Septet (an innovative piano-less group dedicated to carrying on the legacy of jazz great Thelonious Monk).&lt;br /&gt;     At this time Wayne was also touring with Jazz At Lincoln Center's Music of the Masters consisting of two groups of musicians hand picked by Wynton Marsalis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carolyn Leonhart&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Since 2000 she has been performing regularly with her jazz group and started the Sunday Vocalists Series at New York City's Smoke Jazz Club. She has been a guest vocalist on several instrumentalists' albums, a featured guest with the house rhythm sections at Steamers and The Vic in California, as well as clubs in New York City and across the East Coast. The past few years have allowed her to develop her own group sound. In 2003, Carolyn was featured on the cover of Jazziz's women's issue, which spotlighted notable up-and-coming singers.&lt;br /&gt;     On her newest release, New 8th Day, Carolyn returns with a working band - tenor saxophonist Wayne Escoffery, pianist Rick Germanson, bassist Hans Glawischnig and drummers Donald Edwards and Jason Brown - who honed the material in front of live audiences. The album presents Carolyn's intimate and soulful voice and broad tonal palette in songs filled with rich textures. &amp;quot;The title of the CD is a lyric in one of my original songs on the album, called 'Noneday.' I feel like the whole album represents a new beginning. I'm finally starting to bring all of my musical experiences together to create music that is wholly representative of me. This album is very meaningful to me because it marks the next stage of my career.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where is the rain venue?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Asylum Hill Congregational Church (Drew Hall)&lt;br /&gt;814 Asylum Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metered parking on the street.&lt;br /&gt;Also: Goodwin Square Garage&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;City Place Garage&lt;br /&gt;Asylum Lot&lt;br /&gt;all within close proximity to the park&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will fly the BW Piano Key Scarf on a tall stake, check out attending pictures to connect.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280253589000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274201098000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hartford Jazz Society's Monday Night Jazz </name><id>13520079</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280180700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13520079/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/3/5/global_15131685.jpeg</photo_url></item>