<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>PLEASE NOTE: The December 3rd event is currently sold out. If you were unable to register in time, Mr. Agassi will also be speaking at a public event at Harvard's Kennedy School at 6:30pm on Thursday (December 4th), and space is still available for that event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mintz Levin and the Consulate General of Israel to New England are pleased to invite you to spend an evening with Shai Agassi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shai Agassi, founder and chief executive of Better Place, will describe his mission to take on one of the greatest challenges of our time: ending the world’s addiction to oil. Named one of Time magazine’s “Heroes of the Environment 2008,” Agassi will explain how Better Place’s revolutionary model for scalable, electrified personal transportation will liberate cars from oil, reduce carbon emissions, and facilitate an era of sustainable mobility. Through partnerships with government leaders, auto manufacturers, energy companies, and other key parties, Better Place is building the world’s first zero-emission transportation infrastructure. Israel, Denmark, and Australia are the first countries to embrace the Better Place model, with many others soon to follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us at the Museum of Science in Boston to learn more about Mr. Agassi’s bold initiative on the evening of December 3rd. His presentation will be followed by a reception with light refreshments and exhibit-viewing in the Blue Wing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Co-sponsored by Combined Jewish Philanthropies, Jewish Community Relations Council, the Consulate General of France in Boston, WorldBoston, Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance and the New England-Israel Business Council.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229363174000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227045815000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shai Agassi's Electric Car Revolution</name><id>9187947</id><headcount>300</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228346100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/9187947/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/8/global_6363800.jpeg</photo_url></item>