<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This meetup's topic is &amp;quot;Managing Database State Changes&amp;quot; by Jacob Nikom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like the software applications that use them, databases evolve over time to reflect&lt;br /&gt;the changes in the business requirements. However, while contemporary software&lt;br /&gt;applications have well developed tools and methodology to handle those changes&lt;br /&gt;(every developer uses Subversion, CVS, SourceSafe, ClearCase or other configuration&lt;br /&gt;management system or CMS), for databases those methods and tools are not standardized&lt;br /&gt;in such a degree.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Modern CMS manages source code changes based on file names by storing the&lt;br /&gt;differences (so called deltas) between subsequent changes in the code for each source&lt;br /&gt;file. Many database change management (DCM) tools work differently. They go directly&lt;br /&gt;to schema and show the differences in data for particular tables. In case of large tables it&lt;br /&gt;is difficult to observe and understand those differences. For example, just looking at the&lt;br /&gt;data in a server tables it is not always obvious whether that server has all necessary data&lt;br /&gt;to run particular application successfully.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, instead of comparing the data directly, it could be beneficial to compare&lt;br /&gt;references to those data. Those references are the names of the SQL scripts which were&lt;br /&gt;used to create and fill out the database. If there is a list of such files and if all the database&lt;br /&gt;changes happened only as a result of application of those SQL scripts, the state of the&lt;br /&gt;database uniquely identified by the scripts names and their order.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on those ideas we created a program - CatalogVersion - which implements the&lt;br /&gt;DCM functionality by tracking the names of the applied SQL scripts used to create or&lt;br /&gt;upgrade our servers. It was successfully used by all our software developers and QA&lt;br /&gt;testers for creating new servers, upgrading the existing ones to particular version. It also&lt;br /&gt;allows using traditional CSM tools for managing SQL scripts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This talk discusses the DCM principles and their implementation by CatalogVersion&lt;br /&gt;program. It also shares author experience and tips for other DBAs when they perform this&lt;br /&gt;type of work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;Logistics&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's map with the building (E51) highlighted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's map with the Kendall square T stop highlighted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=L5&amp;amp;Landmarks=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(the stop is in red on that map, and you can see E51 in the bottom right)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's maps with parking lot information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P4&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P5&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that MIT lots are free to park in after 3 pm or so, even if it says &amp;quot;reserved for faculty&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free pizza and soda will be served, so please RSVP accurately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To RSVP anonymously, please login to the Meetup site with the e-mail address &amp;quot;admin at sheeri dot com&amp;quot; and the password &amp;quot;guest&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/calendar/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the third floor, make a right, and walk until you find room 372.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheeri Kritzer Cabral</member_name><member_id>2380684</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289317602000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Boston-Metro MySQL Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mysqlbos</urlname><id>212864</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278935593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>lqzznynpblb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289260800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/events/14926554/</event_url></item>