<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>393 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06062</zip><lat>41.690453</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>793-8809</phone><name>Confetti's Restaurant</name><city>Plainville</city><id>450781</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.850190</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>24.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Save the date, Wednesday, November 30, to learn about an opportunity for the ICC to have its own website.&lt;/strong&gt; Beth Messina from Artbox.com will join us to show us how her company can create and host an ICC-branded website. While we have long talked about having a website for the ICC and its members, the amount of work and costs have always seemed to be more than any of us have been able to take on. Now, with Artbox.com, we have an opportunity to create an ICC website that would feature each of our members and serve as a "go-to" resource for both members and potential clients. To see an example of what Artbox.com could do for the ICC, please visit the site they created for the Farmington Valley Arts Center at &lt;a href="http://www.artistsfvac.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artistsfva...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reserve your place and pay&lt;/strong&gt; using the Paypal link, $24 per person. Please be sure to add your meal choice in the "Instructions to Merchant" section of the Paypal transaction: Potato-Crusted Basa Sole; Chicken Picatta; or Cortecce Pasta with Butternut Squash and Sage Butter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reservation Deadline is Friday, November 25, by end of day.&lt;/strong&gt; To cancel, you must do so by this time or your payment will be forfeited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our mission&lt;/strong&gt; is to share ideas in a relaxed casual forum. Network and make new friends, treat yourself to a nice meal and enjoy the presentation. We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Kolk</member_name><member_id>6023842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322756686000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Network Marketers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>networkmarket-792</urlname><id>818489</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4400024414</group_lon><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319146356000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ICC Members Website Opportunity</name><id>38148112</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322694000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/networkmarket-792/events/38148112/</event_url></item>