<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;USING your FLASH WORKSHOP (ON and OFF CAMERA)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Understanding how to use flash and how to incorporate it into your photography skill set is an exciting and easy way to produce some dramatic photography.  This class will cover the basics of flash photography, understanding and controlling flash exposure with advanced off- camera flash techniques.  The use of electronic flash may seem complex and confusing so the goal of this class is to break down the technology into its basic components and then show how each affects your image quality.  The advantages that digital cameras provide make using electronic flash even easier to understand and master.&lt;br /&gt;Electronic flash is hard directional light and we will teach some techniques to modify the quality and the direction of it to add a remarkable visual dimension to your images.  We will explain how to combine flash with daylight/available light a popular technique to improve image quality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TOPICS covered include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FLASH modes and Settings&lt;br /&gt;FLASH EXPOSURE CONTROL&lt;br /&gt;USING MULTIPLE FLASHES&lt;br /&gt;FLASH Modifiers&lt;br /&gt;FLASH TRIGGERING&lt;br /&gt;TYPES of FLASH UNITS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be a combination of class room discussion and hands-on practice exercises.  Please bring your camera and any flash units and triggers you may own.  If you do not own any accessory flash units, this class will still provide you insight in to which products to purchase, and to give you the skills to add this features to your photography. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This class will be held at TEST of TIME PHOTOGRAPHY studio in Nashua, NH on November 22nd, 2009 from 1 to 4 PM&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For directions go to http://testoftimephoto.com/DIRECTIONS.html</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259082609000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255795134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>USING your FLASH WORKSHOP (ON and OFF CAMERA)</name><id>11647979</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258909200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/11647979/</event_url></item>