<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Amity Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06524</zip><lat>41.402840</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Graduate Institute</name><city>Bethany</city><id>1346914</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.002243</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Enlightenment Ain't What It's Cracked Up to Be: A Journey of Discovery, Snow and Jazz in the Soul, By Robert K. C. Forman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Graduate Institute welcomes author Robert Forman for a presentation on his new book Enlightenment Ain’t What It’s Cracked Up To Be: A Journey of Discovery, Snow and Jazz in the Soul, an Award-Winning Finalist in the Spirituality Category of The USA "Best Books 2011" Awards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the back of the book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if you spent years of your life seeking spiritual enlightenment, but were looking in the wrong place over a long time? It’s happening right now to millions of seekers around the world. That’s why Dr. Robert Forman has written his revolutionary book. Told in often poetic prose, it offers new direction for people looking for a sane and healthy spiritual pathway in our increasingly confusing world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack Canfield, author of the Chicken Soup for the Soul series, had this to say about it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This book is more than a memoir of a profoundly revealing spiritual journey. It is a deep invitation to be your authentic self – to fully own, embody and express every aspect of yourself. The honesty, openness and transparency of Robert’s spiritual journey instantly captivated me. I read the book in one long, joyous sitting. I literally could not put the book down. It is illuminating, entertaining and impactful. If you’re looking for guidance as to what is truly spiritual and enlightening, then read this book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Date: July 27, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 7PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: The Graduate Institute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;171 Amity Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bethany, CT 06524&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343557377000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342560249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enlightenment Ain't What It's Cracked Up to Be - Book Signing Event</name><id>73762282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343430000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/73762282/</event_url></item>