<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Upper College Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02881</zip><lat>41.485327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-874-5843</phone><name>University of RI - Fine Arts Concert Hall</name><city>Kingston</city><id>895138</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.525978</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;**Please note: Apparently, this play is NOT general admission, it's reserved seating. So I will buy the tickets so we can all sit together. Please pay in advance using Amazon payments through this site. Thanks!**&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're stepping out of the Providence area and heading south....Last year, we saw &amp;quot;Boy Gets Girl&amp;quot; at &lt;a href="http://www.uri.edu/artsci/the/season2010_11.html" target="_blank"&gt;URI&lt;/a&gt;, which was really intense and amazing. They have a great lineup this season, so look for more Meetups there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's another play that looks pretty intense, &amp;quot;Spinning into Butter.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Gilman's provocative and prize-winning play takes place on a quiet college campus in Vermont. Racist letters found on the door of an African-American student precipitate a turbulent situation that Sarah Daniels, the liberal Dean of Students must investigate. Gilman's play provides insights into contemporary issues of racism and political correctness in a challenging, sometimes comic, and often disturbing way. This production was specifically selected to coincide with the Fall 2010 URI Honors Colloquium on Race. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Tickets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $16 + semi-outrageous handling fees = $18. Surprisingly, it's reserved seating, which is unusual for college productions. Please pay in advance using Amazon Payments through our site, and I will buy tickets so we can all sit together. &lt;b&gt;Please RSVP by 5 pm on Friday, Oct. 8.&lt;/b&gt; The play is at the Fine Arts Center on the URI campus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;When/where to show up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The play starts at 7:30, and we'll meet for dinner before the play at 5:30 pm at &lt;a href="http://www.pinellimarrarestaurants.com/cucina_twist.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Cucina Twist,&lt;/a&gt; which is right around the corner from the university. If you don't want to meet us for dinner, and just want to see the play, please email me so we can make sure we find you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet us for dinner beforehand or email me in advance</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288114605000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284056703000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spinning Into Butter - URI</name><id>14713311</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287869400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/14713311/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/5/global_12093749.jpeg</photo_url></item>