<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will walk around the lake and then over a few blocks to the Great Meadows and back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in the reservoir parking lot at 10:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at Sala Thai&lt;br /&gt;1379 Massachusetts Ave&lt;br /&gt;Arlington, MA 02476&lt;br /&gt;(781) 648-4533&amp;#8206;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arlington Reservoir:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 65 acre Reservoir area (the 'Res') in northwest Arlington Massachusetts on the border with Lexington contains the second largest body of water in the town (28 acres).  It is a man-made pond originally constructed in 1871 by damming Munroe Brook that flows from Lexington.  The dam is an earthen embankment along the southern edge of the Reservoir some 600 yards long and as high as 14 feet (although the water level is much lower).  The Reservoir discharges into Mill Brook that flows through Arlington and empties into the Lower Mystic Lake which then feeds the Mystic River.  The Res was used as a town water supply until Arlington joined the Metropolitan Water District in 1899.&lt;br /&gt;    For years the Reservoir served as a popular summer swimming hole until the water quality started to deteriorate.  In 1981 a separate swimming area was constructed along the northern side of the Reservoir with filtered water and a sandy beach.  The Reservoir is also a popular walking and bird watching spot the year round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great Meadows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arlington's Great Meadows is a 183-acre parcel of land located in east Lexington.   It is the largest piece of undeveloped land in the Arlington/Lexington area.  It is part of the Mystic River watershed.  Once a glacial lake, it is now a wet meadow surrounded by uplands created by glacial outwash.  Great Meadows was purchased by Arlington in 1871 to serve as a supplementary water storage area, but was only briefly used for that purpose.   However, it remains a valuable buffer against flooding in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arlington's Great Meadows has long served as public open space and is a popular recreational spot, particularly since the opening of the Minuteman Bikeway on its southern border.  It also provides a home for local wildlife.  To date, 56 species of birds have been found nesting in Great Meadows, 12 species of amphibians and reptiles live there, and 251 species of plants grow in the wet meadow and uplands.  Last summer's Biodiversity Days survey of the area recorded nearly 400 species of plants and animals in the Great Meadows area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because it is situated between two schools, the Waldorf School of Lexington and Lexington Christian Academy, Arlington's Great Meadows is a valuable resource for teaching children about nature and the environment.  The Citizens for Lexington Conservation organizes annual bird watching and geology walks in the Meadows.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245681156000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245250481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Arlington Reservoir &amp; Great Meadows</name><id>10672012</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245508200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10672012/</event_url></item>