<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.331978</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>11293052</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101646</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>41.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Murder at the Art Museum Scavenger Hunt: &lt;br /&gt;

 A curator has been murdered and left a trail of clues connected with secrets in works of art at the Museum of Fine Arts. As your team gathers answers about the art, you begin to piece together a sordid tale about greed, lust, pride, revenge and treachery, all revolving around the museum’s planned multi-million-dollar purchase of a painting by Leonardo Da Vinci. The murder victim knew too much—and now it’s up to you to learn what he knew and discover what drove one of four suspects to commit murder. To find out, you’ll have to crack a secret code left in the victim’s appointment calendar. Can you figure out who dunnit? Warning: this is our most challenging hunt. We strongly recommend hunting with a team of three or more. If you sign up with fewer than three people, we suggest pairing up with others at the start of the hunt to form a larger team. This hunt was recently revised to include the spectacular new Art of the Americas Wing. All tickets include admission to the museum.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 41.00/person includes Paypal fee of $1.49.</description><how_to_find_us>In lobby. I will send cell phone to attendees</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara</member_name><member_id>6525575</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Rabinovitz</member_name><member_id>8471494</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363481608000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>40-plus</urlname><id>1222683</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2699966431</group_lon><name>40/50 Something Year Olds - Men &amp; Women Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362287105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Who Dunnit at the Museum of Fine Arts</name><id>107321122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363451400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/40-plus/events/107321122/</event_url></item>