<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Powers Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.548981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Outlook at Nashoba Valley</name><city>Westford</city><id>714947</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.437344</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Live Music - TOP BLUES BANDS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00   The Evan Goodrow Band&lt;br /&gt;If James Brown had a white son who cut his teeth playing in Steely Dan along with Prince and Jimi Hendrix?you might get something remotely like Evan Goodrow, a soul-singing, blues guitar playing powerhouse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:00   The Racky Thomas Band&lt;br /&gt;The Racky Thomas Band hails from Boston, but plays the blues as though they came right out of post-war Chicago or the Mississippi delta.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:00   Roomful of Blues&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:30  Jeff Pitchell and Texas Flood&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Pitchell is an internationally acclaimed singer, songwriter, guitarist, and actor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00   The Installers with Jay Geils&lt;br /&gt;The Installers are well known to BluesNBrews Festival fans, having appeared in the lineup more times than any other band in the festival's history! Jay Geils and The Installers will be featuring Jay's CLASSIC blues music... all the good old tunes from waaayyyyy back!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO:&lt;br /&gt;* Dozens of Regional Craft Breweries, PLUS a special booth featuring cask-conditioned ale&lt;br /&gt;* GREAT Food, such as BBQ, grilled chicken, hotdogs/hamburgers, Oktoberfest food, snacks         and ice cream!&lt;br /&gt;* Homebrew Competition awards&lt;br /&gt;* Collectible quality program book featuring bands &amp;amp; breweries&lt;br /&gt;* Raffles, Games, Homebrew Demonstrations, Craft &amp;amp; Vendor Booths, more!&lt;br /&gt;* Beautiful sand beach with lifeguard (weather permitting)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;br /&gt;No Pets&lt;br /&gt;No Coolers&lt;br /&gt;No Readmission&lt;br /&gt;Please take time to read the complete Rules &amp;amp; Regulations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bluesnbrews.com/rulesregs.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bluesnbrew...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blues 'N' Brews is a project of the Westford Rotary Charitable Endowment, Inc. Beneficiaries of the funds raised from this year's festival include the Multiple Sclerosis Society (Blister Buddies), National Guard Family Support Fund, Friends Forever, Habitat for Humanity, the Peru Eyecare Project, and various scholarships and projects supported by Westford Rotary Club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost which includes 10 beverage tickets:  &lt;br /&gt;$28 in advance by calling the number below&lt;br /&gt;BEFORE Friday at 4:30&lt;br /&gt;$35 at the door*&lt;br /&gt;(*walk-in admission is subject to availability)&lt;br /&gt;(Gate opens at 12:30pm) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If YOU WANT A $5.00 DISCOUNT COUPON, GOOD ONLY AT THE GATE SATURDAY PLEASE EMAIL ME DIRECTLY...Sandy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKETS ARE AVAILABLE:&lt;br /&gt;    * BY PHONE - Call 978-692-3033&lt;br /&gt;    * Please note that tickets are NON-REFUNDABLE AND THE EVENT IS HELD RAIN &lt;br /&gt;       OR SHINE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Each beverage ticket can be redeemed for one 3.5 oz. beer tasting or one 2 oz. wine tasting. Canned soda &amp;amp; bottled water are also available and may require multiple beverage tickets. Persons under the age of 21 may not use tickets for alcoholic beverages. Photo ID required for participation in the tasting. Alcoholic beverages are not sold separately from the tasting. Children under 12 admitted free with parent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpools are suggested. They are anticipating over 4500 people this year and this event may sell out.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188253309000</updated><rating><average>3.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185252061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blues N Brews Festival</name><id>6068237</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188059400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/6068237/</event_url></item>