<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a full day trip to hike about 4.7 miles on Overlook Mountain for a breathtaking view in the southeastern portion of the Catskill Mountain Park in southern New York.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pack a hearty trail lunch and a quart of water for this trip. Hiking boots and wool socks are strongly urged as well as warm layered clothing so layers can be removed as you warm up on the hike. A pack is strongly advised to store your lunch and layers removed. Your hands need to be free for the hike. Carpool (limited capacity) from Hartford area leaves 7 AM, group for hike meets at the parking/trailhead at 9:45 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The view is dramatic as we approach in the Hudson River valley. The Catskill Mountains rise quickly to over 3,000 feet in altitude on the west side of the valley. We'll pass through Woodstock, NY and then steeply drive up Overlook Mountain to a monastery at about 1,750 ft. We'll park at the parking lot on the right (east) side and wait for the gathering of hike participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll hike a trail from the parking lot via an old dirt and gravel road. We'll hike first to explore a burnt out shell of an old Inn from the late 1800's and then on to the peak at 3,140 ft. There we'll find the largest firetower in the Catskills for a very dramatic view of the Hudson River Valley and the Catskill Mountains. The gain in altitude is roughly a respectable 1,390 feet in 2.2 miles of hiking. Generous time has been allotted for the ascent (up to 2.25 hours). At the peak we'll enjoy the tower view and eat our packed in lunch. The cab at the top of the firetower isn't open but we can climb the several open flights of stairs for a wonderful full 360 view. We then start our decent after lunch, back the way we came.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are some interesting shops around Woodstock and we'll have about an hour of free time to check them out (see below). I'm not sure what is still open this late in the season though. We plan on going someplace (TBA) to have dinner together (please bring enough cash to facilitate paying the check) before we all head home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you carpool, please chip in a fair share for the ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTES:&lt;br /&gt;+ 1,390 ft total gain in altitude to peek (1,750 ft at start - 3,140 ft at peak).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ I rate the hike to be moderatly difficulty overall, not recommended for those with heart or breathing issues, beginners are fine if reasonably fit/active &amp;amp; PROPERLY dressed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ Must pack for the hike a good trail lunch and 1 qt water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ Have layers of clothing good for cold and windy conditions we may encounter. Layer so that if you are hot you can shed layers to keep cool &amp;amp; dry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ Hiking boots are a must to keep your feet dry &amp;amp; warm. Wool socks are a must to keep your feet warm. I strongly don't advise using sneakers but ask if you must.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ We are late enough in the season that snow is a potential for that altitude. I will track the weather &amp;amp; advise on the conditions for the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Travel/Meet-up--&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 AM Leave with carpool from CT, Hartford area&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 9:45 AM Arrive and park at monastary parking lot. Wait for members to collect&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 10:00 AM Be assembled for hike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Ascent--&lt;br /&gt;* 10:00 AM Start hike up Bear Mtn. via dirt/gravel road trail (alt. 1,750 ft, SLOW 55 min/mi pace)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 11:40 AM Reach burnt out Inn (Overlook Mountain House, c. 1871) &amp;amp; explore (at 1.85 mi, alt. 2,920 ft)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 12:10 PM Continue hike to peak&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 12:30 PM Reach Peak &amp;amp; tower (at 2.35 mi, alt. 3,140 ft)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Lunch &amp;amp; Lookabout--&lt;br /&gt;* 12:30 PM Have packed lunch and climb tower&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 1:30 PM End lunch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Descent--&lt;br /&gt;* 1:30 PM Return by way up Mtn. (at 2.35 mi, alt. 3,140 ft, 30 min/mi pace)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 2:45 PM Back to start in parking lot (at 4.7 mi, alt 1,750 ft)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--To Woodstock--&lt;br /&gt;* 3:00 PM Start travel to Woodstock&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 3:20 PM Arrive in Woodstock and park. Free time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Free Time--&lt;br /&gt;* 3:20 PM Check out small downtown of Woodstock. (approximate SUNSET time 4:25 PM)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 4:30 PM Be assembled for dinner @ (TBA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dinner--&lt;br /&gt;* 4:30 PM Dinner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 6:00 PM Dinner done&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Return Travel--&lt;br /&gt;* 6:00 PM Start travel back to CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 8:45 PM Arrive back at carpool start in CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEETUP LOCATION:&lt;br /&gt;Ktd Monastery parking lot (east side of road)&lt;br /&gt;352 Meads Mountain Rd.&lt;br /&gt;Woodstock, NY 12498-1024&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Can get directions here -NOTE: Mapquest has the road name wrong as Mead instead of Meads -NOTE2: Look at Ariel Photo mode to see monastery [above red star] and the old road trail going to the right with ruins further right):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=352%20Mead%20Mountain%20Rd&amp;amp;city=Woodstock&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;zipcode=12498%2d1024&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;geodiff=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MORE INFO:&lt;br /&gt;Overlook Mountain:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.summitpost.org/mountain/rock/152174/overlook-mountain.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.summitpost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overlook Mountain Fire Tower:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.firetower.org/listings/us224.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.firetower....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Woodstock of legand:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.woodstock69.com/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.woodstock6...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166443255000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1164751206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Overlook Mtn., Catskills, NY</name><id>5295336</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1166270400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5295336/</event_url></item>