<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1612 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.343328</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.730.8002 </phone><name>Tasca Restaurant</name><city>Brighton</city><id>732963</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142873</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Tasca Restaurant, a fantastic tapas place in Brighton, is having a wine dinner next Tuesday evening, for the unbelievable deal of $49.00 (about 60 with tax and tip).  Check out the write up below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Kim (general manager) and Dan (owner) of Tasca will be hosting this five course white table-cloth event. This wine dinner is unlike others in Boston, you will be seated with your reserved party only. We will be personally visiting each table with the wines, rather than lecturing the group. We will be generously pouring the recent vintage releases of some of our favorite Spanish Wines. The dinner will start at 7pm and costs $49 per person. A vegetarian option is also available for each course, upon request.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the price does not include tax and tip so plan on spending about $60 total. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant website is: &lt;a href="http://www.tascarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tascaresta...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is easily accessible by T, using the B line, Washington St. Stop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu for the evening is (food listed above wine): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Selection of savory bites&lt;br /&gt;Cristallino, Brut Rose, N/V&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Pan seared sea scallop over asparagus risotto with white truffle oil&lt;br /&gt;Paso a Paso, Verdejo, La Mancha, 2007&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Roast duck empanada in a sultry orange jus&lt;br /&gt;Bodega Nekeas, Tempranillo Merlot, Navarra, 2006&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Herb and garlic crusted rack of veal served with potato gratin&lt;br /&gt;Vina Mayor, Tempranillo Crianza, Ribera Del Duero, 2002&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Housemade blackberry pie a la mode&lt;br /&gt;Matusalen Pedro Ximinez, Very Rare Solara 1840 Sherry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to table size, am limiting our reservation number to 6.  Please be respectful of your fellow Beantown members and keep your RSVPs accurate to let them fill any unwanted spots.  A final count must be provided the day prior, so RSVPs will be closed on the 13th.  But maybe we'll head there for tapas one night:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As we filled up pretty quickly,  please make a note in your &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP if you'd like join us and will try to get you in if folks change plans, and/or may bump up the number by 1 or 2.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dinner starts at 7 pm but we'll be meeting outside between 6:30-6:45 p.m.  Will send out my cell number to my 'yes' folks the day prior for last minute contacts.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact me directly (doclmeet @yahoo.com) with any vegetarian requests and I'll pass on the word.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet out front prior to heading in for the dinner.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224285992000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223347141000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine Dinner</name><id>8912386</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224024300000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8912386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>