<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The great beings, Jesus and Mary, gave and continue to give an enormous gift to our earth. They took on the karma accumulated by humanity over hundreds of years and paved a path of forgiveness and healing for all of us through love and sacrifice. They taught the Way, through the demonstration of their very lives. Mary transformed everything feminine that had been distorted by humankind's collective unconcious thinking and acting, and Jesus transformed everything masculine. They hold out for us the possibility to truly rise above our past. Why, then is there still so much controversy about why they matter so much and why they matter to you? During this seminar, led by Mother Clare Watts, Christian Master Teacher, author and peace activist, you will come to a new understanding of who Jesus and Mary truly are and why getting to know them will lighten up your life, in a real and meaningful way. Come! Open your heart and mind and be surprised at what you see.&lt;br /&gt;*******************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Mother Clare&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare is a mystic; ordained priest; Master Teacher of Christian mysticism; and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 15 Centers of Light in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she co-directs the effort to develop the Sophia Peace Center. She is the author of &lt;i&gt;Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path To Enlightenment.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238545039000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236360307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Jesus and Mary and You: Why It Matters</name><id>9896737</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237039200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9896737/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/c/1/global_7563777.jpeg</photo_url></item>