<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am inviting the new and old members to come and celebrate the upcoming year of healing you and your connections in life. Lets get together, for a potluck and explore ways of truly healing your connections to your family, friends, partners and, of course, yourself in a way that does not requires painful cutting and disconnection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out exciting and groundbreaking workshop on energy cords scheduled for this coming weekend that comes in half day and a full day option. And let us leave all the non-working connections behind! You can sign up by going now to &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/43982212/"&gt;Healing The Energy Cords, The Ties that Bind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who wonder what we are and what we do, here is a new testimonial from the latest posted meetup group review. This person told me that for a very long time he was reluctant to attend our meetups out of concern of feeling exposed and unsafe, Well, he is a changed man now.&amp;nbsp; Here is what he wrote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Great meetup with Yuliya! What it is not: It's not a meetup where everybody has to share their personal stuff. It's not a "cathartic" experience where you "express your feelings". It is not a "soothing" experience that temporarily soothes you. You don't focus on pain either. What the meetup is is a mini-workshop where Yuliya shares her techniques with you &amp;amp; guides all participants thru what I could only describe as a meditation to reclaim your lost energy from whatever upsetting experience(s) "changed you". For me, each time, it has been surprisingly powerful. And, totally graceful. No need to share what you want to keep private. Yuliya does not make you pretend that it is "a safe place" as a ploy to get you to open up. Just be as you are. The aim is that the experience be effortless. Just come as you are, pay attention, and ask any questions you want to ask, and do the meditation at the end. I'm looking forward to the next one. Definitely try it at least once if you're curious about it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come, bring your favorite food to share and your burning questions. We will provide the refreshments. You're welcome to bring wine too to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn the cutting edge information on how to make the New Year a year of freedom from whatever keeps you down or keeps you back.&amp;nbsp; I am very thankful that I have attracted such wonderful people to join the journey of the effortless healing and transformation in the New Year&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324084552000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323541878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Meet, Eat and Learn how to Heal our Energetic Connections.</name><id>44038282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324080000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/44038282/</event_url></item>