<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>335 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343884</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-975-0075</phone><name>Zaftig's Delicatessen</name><city>Brookline</city><id>669083</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.124153</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update 1/26/2010&lt;/b&gt;: This brunch at Zaftigs is going to be tough. I had been told earlier that yes, they made reservations and Saturday would be fine. Now, they say that they don't take reservations on Saturdays because the rush happens. They suggested I come down 45 minutes beforehand to Zaftigs and put my name in for the large party. Good thing we are meeting at 11 am, eh? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming to see the simulcast of London's National Theatre performance of Terry Pratchett's play &amp;quot;Nation&amp;quot;? &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/12263055/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; This performance may sell out. It might be good to purchase your ticket beforehand online at Coolidge Corner's website at &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Care for brunch beforehand? Let's meet up before 11:00 am at Zaftig Delicatessen down the street. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. T.J. found out last minute they do not take reservations on weekends -- when he was told earlier it was fine. Ah, well. He'll get there early and put his name in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of the accurate headcount is needed, the RSVPs have been set to YES/ NO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Welcome to Zaftigs&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.zaftigs.com/"&gt;http://www.zaftigs.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;And your Jewish mother will kvell over the brisket even if she doesn't take to tray offerings such as pork sausages and smoked ham. Kosher, this is not. In fact, what has made this 'new Jewish'-style restaurant one of the best eating spots in Brookline are the less traditional offerings, including cheddar-apple omelets and banana stuffed French toast. The wild artwork and hip young wait staff seal the deal; this ain't your grandma's deli.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Zaftigs Delicatessen serves breakfast (all day), lunch, and dinner. Located in Coolidge Corner in Brookline, there are public parking lots available and convenient parking available using meters along Harvard Street&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.zaftigs.com/directions.html"&gt;http://www.zaftigs.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;On the T&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Take the &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; branch of the Green line to the Coolidge Corner stop. As you exit the train, turn right onto Harvard Street walking towards the Coolidge Corner cinema. Walk two blocks and Zaftigs will be on your right at 335 Harvard St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;On the Bus&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Take the 66 bus to the corner of Babcock and Harvard St. Walk down Harvard St. heading towards Allston (Coolidge Corner theatre is across the street on your left). Zaftigs is on your right at 335 Harvard St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Parking&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Metered parking available on street. There are parking lots located on Centre St. and Babcock St&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.zaftigs.com/menus.html"&gt;http://www.zaftigs.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With potato pankakes, knishes, BBQ briskets, chopped liver, blintzes, and gefilte fish... and of course bagels and lox ... you know this is a Jewish Deli. [ &lt;b&gt;Adobe Acrobat version&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.zaftigs.com/pdf/zaftigs_menu.pdf"&gt;http://www.zaftigs.co...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265214415000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263834606000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch before Terry Pratchett's play, Nation @ Zaftigs Delicatessen </name><id>12352698</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264867200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12352698/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/8/global_12687848.jpeg</photo_url></item>