<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a work party to clear and maintain trails and conservation land that the not for profit Northern Connecticut Land Trust (NCLT) owns. This event is brought by an alliance between the NCLT and Hartford Area Hiking (HAH).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This weekend is set aside for cleanup, trail maintenance, and other land stewardship projects. Informal hikes will be led throughout the day. Work will be performed on McCann’s and the recently acquired Whitaker property. Refreshments will be available and families are encouraged to participate. Work and fun will start at 9 a.m.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is run by Ginny Patsun  (860) 763-4047 and she is the contact for most questions on this event. &lt;br /&gt;***YOU MUST let her know directly if you will be going so he can plan the workload!***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/Directions are in the event notes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: ***Anyone coming out for the first for a work party with the NCLT will have to sign a liability release form.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation Procedure:  Should it be necessary to postpone or cancel the work party each respondent will be notified by e-mail or a phone call by 8 AM of the work day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: The McCann Family Farm is a hilly 84 acres of farmland and mixed forest. Located on it are two brooks and two vernal pools. It includes extensive hiking trails and the Whit Davis Bird Sanctuary, and is the location of several wildflower and bird watching hikes each year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/Directions:  the McCann Family Farm is Route 190 east of the village. Parking lot is on the south side of 190, about 0.7 miles east of Route 83. Approximate location of the McCann Family Farm given by the URL:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.yahoo.com/maps_result?addr=650%20Main%20Street&amp;amp;csz=Somers%2C+CT&amp;amp;country=us&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;qty=&amp;amp;cat=fin&amp;amp;trf=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.yahoo.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northern Connecticut Land Trust (NCLT)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/Lists/Properties/DispForm.aspx?ID=2" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/Lists/Properties/DispForm.aspx?ID=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1142915527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NCLT Work Party at the McCann Family Farm &amp; Whitaker Property in Somers CT</name><id>4881272</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1145710800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4881272/</event_url></item>