<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The actual time is 4:05 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;My Winnipeg&amp;quot; is a quirky funny look at director Guy Maddin's home town of Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada.  It is somewhat difficult to put into words exactly why it is so hilarious, but it is definitely one of the funniest movies I have ever seen.  It previewed at the Boston Independent Film Festival this year and won the award for the audience's favorite film.  I enjoyed it so much that I wanted to host it for those who didn't get to see it and for those who, like myself, want to see it again.  Maddin approaches the dilemma of  why it is so hard to leave one's home town and move on in life, with both a sentimental and tongue-in-cheek view.  Maddin's previous films, including Brand Upon the Brain! and The Saddest Music in the World, have been considered to be a bit obscure, but in this newest release, Maddin has hit the nail upon the head!  A film that is both personal and universal starring Ann Savage from B-movie fame as his mother (His real-life mom turned down the part).  It has to be seen to be believed.  This docu-fantasia has also received a score of 93% on the tomatometer at rottentomatoes.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we will go to a local restaurant to eat, drink, and discuss.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are two links to reviews for My Winnipeg:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2008/06/13/movies/13winn.html?ref=movies" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.filmcritic.com/misc/emporium.nsf/reviews/My-Winnipeg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.filmcritic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Susan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the front to one side with my MEETUP sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216152853000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213752046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>My Winnipeg</name><id>8162890</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215979200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8162890/</event_url></item>