<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Wedeln Ski House is the former Comstock Inn and is located on the border of North Conway and Bartlett. 4 ski areas are within 20 min drive and all the bars, shops and restaurants of North Conway are only minutes away.  To stay at the house you must be 21+.   I plan to go to Wildcat on both Saturday and Sunday.  Discount lift tickets available from www.liftopia.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Valetines Day weekend and we will attend some open-bar Valentine events (optional).  It looks like it will be a real fun weekend with several entertainment options.  Couples or singles are welcome but please be aware that bedrooms are segregated by sex so if you are looking for a romantic Valentine weekend you may be better off a Bed &amp;amp; Breakfast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will leave from Somerville on Friday night at 6pm.  I can take a couple of extra people.  I plan to meet at the Dunkin Donuts parking lot in Union Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overnight Accommodations: &lt;br /&gt;$20 per night - recommend you stay both Friday and Sat.&lt;br /&gt;There are 21 bedrooms, dorm style and separated by gender. &lt;br /&gt;Most rooms have 2 bunkbeds.&lt;br /&gt;Bring your own sheets, blanket, pillow. A sleeping bag and pillow work well too. &lt;br /&gt;Bring toiletries, towel, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes RSVP's will get directions to the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club and info on payment. This will be a busy weekend so we will need to take advance payment. Maybe RSVP will be allowed for now but will eventually be changed to No.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info about the Wedeln Ski and Outdoor Club please check out: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wedeln.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wedeln.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the bar in the ski house on Friday night at 9pm or in Somerville at 6pm</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235314278000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Snowboarders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>snowboard-46</urlname><id>389975</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Somerville Snowboarding Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233948827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Valetine Weekend at Wedeln Ski House</name><id>9688660</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234573200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/snowboard-46/events/9688660/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_6288127.jpeg</photo_url></item>