<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2401 Commonwealth Avenue (Route 30)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02467</zip><lat>42.337612</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 965-5110</phone><name>Charles River Canoe and Kayak, Newton Boathouse</name><city>Newton</city><id>1001805</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.156990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's Spring Time!  ...and Ingo and I can't wait to get out on the river for some paddling.  I hope you all can come and join us!  Invite your friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Schedule&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9am Meet&lt;br /&gt;We'll first meet at 9am at the Charles River Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak in Newton and rent some kayaks and/or canoes. Depending on whether each of us chooses doubles or quads the hourly price will range between $5 - $9 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:30am - 11:30am Canoeing/Kayaking&lt;br /&gt;We'll take a leisurely paddle down the river toward Waltham's Moody Street and back.  (don't worry if you've never paddled before - it's truly not difficult)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:30am - 1pm Picnic&lt;br /&gt;After we've finished our paddling tour we'll have a picnic lunch at the waterfront area next to the Newton boathouse.  Everyone bring a picnic item to share!  (we love to have fun with gourmet food, so expect some yummy things)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Newton Boat House is located at:&lt;br /&gt;2401 Commonwealth Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Auburndale, MA 02466&lt;br /&gt;(617) 965-5110&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.paddleboston.com/newton/detail.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.paddlebost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunscreen/hat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sneakers or beach shoes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bottled water/drinks for the ride &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Picnic food to share (once we have our list of attendees we'll organize who's bringing what)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Waterproof duffel bags are available for rent at the boathouse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location is easily accessible off of both 90 and 95.  It is also less than a mile from the Riverside T.  If anyone would like to take the train we'll send a car there to pick up any train commuters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions from thier website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking at our Newton Boathouse&lt;br /&gt;The tiny parking lot adjacent to the boathouse is only for handicapped visitors, customers purchasing items at our Paddling Store, and pickup or drop-off of passengers and boats. All other parking, including parking for rentals and classes, is across the river in the Norumbega Road lot, a short 5-minute round trip. From our boathouse parking lot, take every right (onto Rt. 30 West, Rt. 128 Northbound entrance, Norumbega Road, and into the parking lot), then use the stairs at the far end of the lot to return to Rt. 30 and cross the bridge. Thanks very much!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South on Rt. 128&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 24 (Route 30). Turn right onto Rt. 30 (Commonwealth Ave) East. Our brown boathouse is 100 yards down on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North on Rt. 128&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 24 (Route 30). Turn right onto Rt. 30 (Commonwealth Ave) East. Our brown boathouse is 200 yards down on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West&lt;br /&gt;Take the MassPike to Exit 14 (Rt. 128/I-95/Rt. 30). Stay left through the toll (follow signs for I-95 North) and before reaching the highway take Exit 24 for Rt. 30. Turn right onto Rt. 30 (Commonwealth Ave) East. Our brown boathouse is 100 yards down on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East (including Boston)&lt;br /&gt;Take the MassPike to Exit 15 (Rt. 128/I-95/Rt. 30). Stay right through the toll (follow signs for I-95 North) and before reaching the highway take Exit 24 for Rt. 30. Turn right onto Rt. 30 (Commonwealth Ave) East. Our brown boathouse is 100 yards down on the left.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Commuter Rail&lt;br /&gt;Take the MBTA Commuter Rail's Worcester/Framingham Line to Auburndale. Exit toward Auburn Street and turn left onto Auburn St. Follow Auburn until it meets Commonwealth Ave. We are across the street. The distance is approximately 0.5 miles and usually takes about 10 minutes to walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the MBTA Green Line&lt;br /&gt;Take the MBTA Green Line (D train) to Riverside. Cross the parking lot and turn left onto Grove St. Bear left onto Hancock St. Turn left onto Woodland and then turn left onto Auburn St. Follow Auburn until it meets Commonwealth Ave. We are across the street. The distance is approximately 1.2 miles and usually takes about 20 minutes to walk. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacy Goodman</member_name><member_id>3216337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273024498000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270215254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking on the Charles and Spring Picnic</name><id>13067101</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272718800000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/13067101/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/5/global_14078821.jpeg</photo_url></item>