<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>417 Hixbridge rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02790</zip><lat>41.570974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-993-9695.</phone><name>Westport Rivers Vineyard</name><city>Westport</city><id>1044102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060021</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A few friends and I have been doing the Coastal Wine Trail this year, and I thought it would be fun to continue the pattern with a meetup! Our meetup group visited Newport and Greenvale vineyards in October and had a great time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Coastal Wine Trail connects 9 wineries between Cape Cod and Westerly, RI. By visiting each winery, you can earn a stamp on a booklet that you then mail in (or turn in to a winery) to earn a chance to win a cruise, a getaway to the cape, or free wine! &lt;br /&gt;More details here: &lt;a href="http://www.coastalwinetrail.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coastalwin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, we will visit Westport Rivers Vineyard (in Westport, MA) and Sakonnet Vineyards (in Little Compton, RI).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Westport Rivers Vineyard and Winery at 12:45 and take the 1pm tour. We will then do a tasting, which is $7 and includes the glass. Here are more details about Westport Rivers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westportrivers.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westportri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will then drive about 25 min to Sakonnet Vineyards in Little Compton. We will do a tasting and take the tour at 3pm. Here is more information about Sakonnet: &lt;a href="http://www.sakonnetwine.com/index.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sakonnetwi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will finish our day with a late lunch/early dinner at The Four Corners Grille in Tiverton (up the road from Sakonnet, going back towards the highway). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It should be a fun day! Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;This event is cross-listed with WINGS. Please RSVP on just one meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me inside -- tall, shoulder-length brown hair, thick glasses</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trina</member_name><member_id>2292253</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289148255000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288563558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Coast Wine Trail</name><id>15289300</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289061900000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/15289300/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/7/global_6044183.jpeg</photo_url></item>