<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>840 Hillside Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.210617</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Houghton's Pond</name><city>Milton</city><id>5897012</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096237</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join Members and Guests of the South Shore Walkabouts, South Shore Ladies, and Social Fun for a Saturday Morning Walk/Beginner-Friendly Hike!&lt;/strong&gt; It's time to get back outdoors and start our hikes!  We will start off with a Walk/Beginner Friendly Hike at Houghton's Pond @ Blue Hills. This walk/hike is a Green-Dot Trail with some pavement.  We walk/hike 2 looped paths which take about 15-20 minutes each.  It really and truly is a walk and easy hike.  We will walk/hike for about 45 minutes to an hour (or more), depending on the will of the group.  This will cover approximately 1.5-3 miles. We'll meet by the map at Houghton's Pond main parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things to bring: Water, a light snack, sun block, sun glasses, comfortable walking shoes/boots and dress in layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Optional: For those who are interested, we may go to Newcomb Farms on Route 28 in Milton (5 minutes up the road) for an early lunch or late breakfast, whichever suits your fancy.  If you are interested for sure please let us know in the comments section.  Please bring cash as they do not accept credit cards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OUTDOOR Walk/Beginner-Friendly Hike! (Re-Scheduled From 3/23)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, April 13th @ 10-11:30am (at the latest)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Houghton's Pond @ Blue Hills  &lt;br /&gt;

840 Hillside Street  &lt;br /&gt;

Milton, MA  &lt;br /&gt;

Blue Hills Website: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Meet by the map in the main parking lot near the Visitor's Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela &amp;amp;  TBD (An Event Co-Host would be greatly appreciated, preferably someone who has attended at least 3 events.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;span&gt;At least 6 Yes RSVPs (and a co-host, preferably) by 6pm on Wednesday, April 10th. Maximum is 25 for all groups, 12 for SSW and 12 for SF, and 4 for SSL (I'll be a Yes in all groups).  The Wait List is Automatic, you will be moved from the WL to the Yes list in the order in which you RSVP'd.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Welcome!  One adult (21+) per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fees/Costs:&lt;/em&gt; $1/attendee *or* $10 annual donation (as requested after your 3rd event)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Please finalize your RSVP by 8pm on Friday, April 12th.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our No-Show policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Heavy rains will cancel. We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle. Please plan to bring a jacket with a hood just in case. (We will do our best to notify everyone if this event is cancelled by 9am on the day of the walk.)  *Please check back here for an update approximately 24-48 hours prior to the event.*  Any cancellation decisions will be made around the RSVP Deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rain/Snow Date&lt;/em&gt;: TBD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those with a GPS, the address is 840 Hillside Street, Milton, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take &lt;strong&gt;Route 93&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Exit 3&lt;/strong&gt;, Houghton's Pond. Turn right at the end of the exit (from 93SB, left from 93NB). Follow road to the end passing a couple of small parking lots on your right.  At the end of the road (at the stop sign) turn right onto Hillside Street. Houghton's Pond is located approximately 1/4 mile on the right.  (If you go the wrong way off the highway you will know it pretty quickly as it's a dead-end on the other side.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Note: Biagio has asked us to shutoff event reminders.  I have obliged with this request for this event even though this is a strange concept for me.  (Hey, you have to start somewhere.)  That means I'm supposed to send some sort of reminder or something.  I'll most likely post a comment a couple days before the event.  Please put it on your calendar and remember to change your RSVP if you can no longer attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet by the map in the main parking lot near the Visitor's Center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365914617000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363876674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OUTDOOR Walk/Beginner Friendly Hike! (Re-Scheduled From 3/23)</name><id>110343942</id><headcount>15</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365861600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/110343942/</event_url></item>