<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am planning an  Aldrich Astronomical Society indoor talk about the solar system along with outdoor observing if the weather permits on Saturday, January 22 in the Science Building at Anna Maria College in Paxton, MA.  We have control over the lighting, munchies and hot coffee and cocoa. I am opening it to some scouts and some middle school students but want to invite Oxford Astronomy Group members too.  If I plan this one plus will also open up the Science Building on January 29th for another talk and observing session. This way we can have two great chance to learn about our solar system plus get a better shot at night sky viewing through telescopes and binoculars! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The session on January 22, 2011 starts at 7PM - there will be a full PowerPoint presentation with some fun testing about the solar system and plenty of time for questions. Bring telescopes and binoculars if you have them - we will also offer great views through Aldrich Society member scopes if you choose to use one of our scopes.  I will also offer help on collimation and setting up any telescopes that might have been purchased over the holidays. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an indoor program with outdoor viewing if the weather permits so it will occur no matter what New England weather brings unless it brings another 2 feet of snow!! Primary objects for viewing will be M42, the Great Orion Nebula, the double cluster in Perseus, the Hyades and Pleaides star clusters, the Moon, and Jupiter and Uranus. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, NASA has officially designated this as the year of the Solar System - I will explain why in my talks. I'd like to see a good turn out - we have many adults and children attend our events ( last year over 13,000! ) and we have a good track record of providing dynamic and informative talks about astronomy and space exploration. My talks are aimed at helping everyone start checking out the night sky from their own backyard! Once you are shown how to do this backyard observing of the night sky - you are usually hooked for life!  Please try it out - I know you will walk away satisfied! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---Jim J. Zebrowski &lt;br /&gt;    President Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. &lt;br /&gt;    Oxford Astronomy Group Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Drive all the way to the Science Building at the back of the campus - it will have an Aldrich meeting sign out on the steps. Park your car to the right in the Trinity parking lot. If you have a telescope, bring it behind the building to set it up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295802433000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294892108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Tour of the Solar System!</name><id>16031820</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295740800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/16031820/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/global_7975572.jpeg</photo_url></item>