<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Bruegger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>972928</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121038</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For our February Book Club Meeting, we will be reading "A Secret Kept" by Tatiana De Rosnay. The following is the summary from the cover... Antoine Rey thought he had the perfect surprise for his sister Melanie's birthday:a weekend by the sea at Noirmoutier Island, where the pair spent many happy childhood summers playing on the beach. The island's haunting beauty triggers more than happy memories; it reminds Melanie of something unexpected and deeply disturbing about their last summer...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just following up on the question regarding the waitlist and suggestion regarding a change of venue (Thanks for bringing this up). Although participation is limited to 20 people, more often than not, some members are unable to attend. If you are on the wait list and are interested in participating in the discussion, feel free to drop by. Regarding the change in location, this is the first time that I am coordinating the discussion and am not from the area. I would prefer to stay with a space that I am familiar with for now and revisit the idea at a later date. I hope that this is okay. Thanks and see everyone soon! Mary&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary </member_name><member_id>13108187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330294664000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326736373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Brookline Book Club Meetup</name><id>48315702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330290000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/48315702/</event_url></item>