<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>137 Teaticket Hwy</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02536</zip><lat>41.564075</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 548-0073 (directions)</phone><name>Falmouth Cinema Pub</name><city>East Falmouth</city><id>1024794</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.596128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's get together for dinner and a movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be seeing the movie &amp;quot;Hangover&amp;quot;, rated R, 100 minutes. It is a comedy about three guys who put together the mystery what happened during a hard night of Vegas partying the night before one of their weddings. The movie is starring Zach Galifainakis, Bradley Cooper, and Ed Helms. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the Falmouth Cinema Pub, tables of two and four decorate each theater. The swivel chairs are comfy for both dining and movie watching. We will arrive 30 minutes before the movie begins to order food, however, wait staff is available throughout each show to take orders. Twenty minutes before the end of the movie, the check will be handed out. Each woman is responsible for her own movie ticket, food and drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Falmouth Cinema Pub certainly offers something for every movie goers' taste. Popcorn, soda, and candy are all still popular picks, but now there are over 10 other types of food and drinks to choose form. Desserts, appetizers, soup, pizza, salad, burgers, sandwiches, beer, and wine now augment the menu. Appetizers, or &amp;quot;previews&amp;quot; as they are referred to, consist of curly fries ($3.99), mozzarella sticks ($5.99), boneless wings ($7.99), loaded nachos ($7.99), and several others. Clam chowder, lobster bisque, and chili are all each $3.99. Thin crust grilled pizza comes with several different topping combinations and has eight square slices ($6.99 - $8.99). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The real meals are reasonably priced as well. A regular garden salad is just $5.99; add buffalo, plain, or Cajun chicken to it for just $3. Black angus burgers can come with chili, three choices of cheese, bacon, mushrooms, or just plain ($7.99 - $8.99). Various fish, meat, and chicken sandwiches are available ranging from $7.99 to $10.99. All burgers and sandwiches come with a side order of curly fries, chips, coleslaw, three-bean salad, or pasta salad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The drink menu is also fairly extensive. There are several kinds of draft beer than is served by the glass (about $4) or a 60 oz. pitcher (about $14). Bottled beer, non-alcoholic beer, malt drinks are also available (about $4). Over 10 types of wine is sold by the glass ($4.50 - $7.50) or bottle ($18 - $28). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Barbara will meet you in the cinema lobby wearing a Girls Just Wanna Have Fun Pin!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara </member_name><member_id>7313867</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250032263000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248981988000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Falmouth Cinema Pub (dinner and a movie)</name><id>10995507</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249511400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/10995507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>