<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>THE FALL PLEIN AIR CHALLENGE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TODAY'S CHALLENGE: 60 minutes of plein air at 80 degrees or below&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE SCENE: it's one of our all-time favs, even though we haven't painted there this year. It's a grassy penisula that juts into the middle of Duxbury Bay. On one side is beach (swimmable) and on the other side is scenic marsh. In front of us in the distance is a marina and houses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE TO MEET: At the posted time, with 1/2 hour leeway for late-comers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;Route 3 to Exit 10, Duxbury. From memory, get off the exit and continue straight a few miles to a sign at blinking lights that directs you to historic Duxbury. It's another few miles to the Dunkin Donuts. Duxbury is small and if you get into a bind, ask anyone.At the rotary, with DD on your left, go halfway around&lt;br /&gt;(straight if you will). That street goes to the bay&lt;br /&gt;where we were, bare right onto King Cesear Road and&lt;br /&gt;then up about 1/4 of a mile is where we painted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THINGS TO BRING WHICH ARE OFTEN FORGOTTEN: &lt;br /&gt;                        Mosquito repellant,  Paper towels,  Sweater, water, food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAR-POOL: If you need a ride or are willing to drive, say so in your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF LOST: If you become lost getting there, call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LAX: We allow a leisurely 30 minutes for late-ness. If you show up within 30 minutes of the scheduled time you are fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INCLEMENT WEATHER: It is up to you to determine if the weather makes painting untenable. Although, I will try to leave a message on my voice mail if I myself do not intend to be there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Emerald&lt;br /&gt;617/968-0627&lt;br /&gt;westpointusma@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Emerald, CFA</member_name><member_id>3007793</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221502220000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>painter-84</urlname><id>576650</id><group_lat>42.4500007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Plein Air Artists Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220620424000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FALL PLEIN AIR CHALLENGE: Duxbury Bay</name><id>8694531</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221328800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/painter-84/events/8694531/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/c/global_1743932.jpeg</photo_url></item>