<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before signing up for this event, Please read the entire Write Up and understand and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Event Rating: Strenuous&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Distance: 11 Miles&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Time Duration: 4 Hours&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Blaze Orange: NOT REQUIRED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will meet at the parking lot at Lions Memorial Park on Park Road in Mansfield, CT. It is just north of Mansfield Hollow Reservoir, on the left side of Route 89.From the RI/CT border, take Route 6 west for 19 miles, turn right onto Route 198 North. Go 0.6 miles and turn left onto Bedlam Road. Go 1.5 miles and continue onto Atwoodville Road. Go 1.4 miles and turn left&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;onto CT-89 South/​Warrenville Rd. Go 0.6 miles and turn right onto&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Baker Road&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;. Go 400 feet and take a slight right onto&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Park Road&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;. Go 0.6 mile to the last parking lot and look left. We will park there near the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I encourage people to carpool, but since this hike is local for me I won’t be carpooling. Maybe you want to arrange meet at the Ocean State Job Lot on Route 6 in&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Johnston&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;at, say&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;9:15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will hike for 4 hours in a loop of about 11 miles that features three high rocky ledges with views ranging to 20 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/0/4/event_228671012.jpeg" width="457" height="247" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Starting from the Lions memorial park, our path will traverse a series of preserved open spaces owned by the town of Mansfield, Joshua’s Trust, and the State of CT. Along the way we will have views from three named rocky ledges: Coney Rock, Fifty Foot Rock, and Wolf Rock. We will follow sections of Tony’s beloved Nipmuck Trail, as well as other trails along the way. The footpath along many sections of this hike is in good condition, with some sections that feel almost like carpet underfoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/6/0/event_228670592.jpeg" width="464" height="257" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will have walk along two short sections of Route 195, where we will have to be alert for the fast-moving traffic. As usually happens on hikes with vistas, there will be hills. There are two good, steep 200-foot hills and several smaller ones. The climb up to wolf rock along a gas line clearing is one of the steeper hills I’ve seen around here – it will get your ticker up to redline. There are plenty of streams (with bridge crossings – no water hazards on this trip!), forests, meadows, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, a pair of hiking boots is strongly suggested. As always bring sufficient water and snacks along for a 4 hour hike. With the warmer weather, ticks are on the move so bring some tick repellent. Sun screen is also recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterward, some of us will likely have a re-hydration break at a nearby establishment in Willimantic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver:As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.Safety First!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim F</member_name><member_id>13313199</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367161913000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366855323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Three High Rocky Vistas of Mansfield</name><id>116066232</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367071200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/116066232/</event_url></item>