<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Balsam Dr</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04462</zip><lat>45.656982</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(207)723-5140 </phone><name>Baxter State Park</name><city>Millinocket</city><id>686451</id><country>us</country><lon>-68.685407</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mount Katahdin &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Baxter State Park&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to hike the VERY DRAMATIC MOUNT KATAHDIN&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VIDEO FROM LAST YEAR: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4uG_xtu-HDA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See my site for more information: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hvhikers/calendar/12132225/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dates: July 2-5, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;We will be camping in Baxter State park for the three nights, hiking on Saturday and Sunday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 10-12 mile hikes, elevation gain 4000-5000 feet &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrive Campground by 8pm on Friday July 2 &lt;br /&gt;Baxter State Park (Roaring Brook campground, Sites 21 and 22 / 6 people per site) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MAX GROUP SIZE IS 12. &lt;br /&gt;Space is VERY limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be no MAYBE RSVP's (YES means YES) If you RSVP YES that means you are a 100% YES to go. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is $25.00 per person for the three nights' camping and hiking. You can pay me directly with cash (you can also mail a check, or pay with PayPal -- email me for information). NOTE: Your spot is NOT reserved until I have your payment &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Katahdin! The name of perhaps the single most outstanding peak in all the Appalachians is a magic word to Appalachian Trail through hikers who walk for 2,000 miles to reach it, to rock-climbers who challenge its rocky walls, to tourists who gape at its towering form, and to hikers in search of truly rugged mountain majesty. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Katahdin is special due to a variety of factors. It is not a simple mountain, but a broad massif of several peaks, cirques, and ridges, surrounded on almost three sides by a ring of lower summits. This concentrated group of mountains stands utterly alone in the otherwise flat Maine north woods, and the southern face of the main mountain mass rises directly 4,000 feet from the Penobscot River to the highest summit in the entire state. The remote, and, compared to other eastern mountains, almost primeval forest setting of the peak is also very alluring, as is the large area above timberline (about 3800 feet at 46 degrees north). And finally, the spectacular sawtoothed Knife Edge, a serrated crest dropping thousands of feet on both sides, gives Katahdin a special kind of alpine grandeur. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have not chosen the exact hiking routes yet ... but I can tell you this much, we WILL be hiking the Knife Edge!!! -- Chris Baker Hudson Valley Hikers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Interstate 95 to the Millinocket-Mattawamkeag exit about 50 miles north of Bangor, ME. Proceed to Millinocket, following the signs, then turn right where the road &amp;quot;T's&amp;quot; by a high school onto Katahdin Ave. Go a couple blocks and take a left at the sign for Baxter State Park. Follow that about 16 miles to the park. From there, either take the Perimeter Road (to the left) or the Roaring Brook Road (to the right) to the trailhead you desire for your ascent. In accordance with Governor Percival P. Baxter's wishes that the park be kept as wild as possible, the roads are gravel and used to be pretty rough but aren't as bad as they are reputed to be currently (at least the Roaring Brook Road is nicely graded with fresh gravel as of Fall 2002 and still in great shape in Fall 2006). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Baker</member_name><member_id>8452322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278301040000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277753839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baxter State Park / KATAHDIN! 4th of July Weekend Special!</name><id>13938667</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278111600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13938667/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/5/global_11532517.jpeg</photo_url></item>