<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Surf Club Rd, Madison, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06443</zip><lat>41.300000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Madison Surf Club</name><city>Madison</city><id>497624</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.610000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Major update, folks! Everyone's favorite subzero swimmer, our very own Devorah, will be in on the plunge! But CAN she raise the minimum $100 entry pledge by Saturday?!? Will the NHC come through, triumphing over the forces of evil?!? Or shall pricey beer and cheese fries prevail yet again? Find out Saturday - same bat-time, same bat-channel!!&lt;br /&gt;Previously on the NHC:&lt;br /&gt;Come watch people fling themselevs in the freezing ocean for a great cause!&lt;br /&gt;The Connecticut Polar Plunge is raising money to send terminally ill kids to Camp Sunshine in Maine.&lt;br /&gt;Several of my co-workers are participants this year, and they'd be happy to have your support! (Donations optional.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All the details are at: &lt;a href="http://www.freezinforareason.com/connectpp.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.freezinfor...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And below are the basics, with directions. Hope to see a lot of you there!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;645-2008&lt;br /&gt;nkindlon@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camp Sunshine is pleased to have the opportunity to partner with the 2008 Connecticut Polar Plunge. We believe that together we can send many more children with life-threatening illnesses and their families from Connecticut to our one-of-a-kind retreat in Maine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year, the Connecticut Polar Plunge raised almost $10,000 for Camp Sunshine! With the strength of an event such as the Connecticut Polar Plunge and the resources of Camp Sunshine, it is our goal to raise in excess of $25,000 in 2008. That is enough to send more than 16 Connecticut families to Camp Sunshine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why a Connecticut based event for a camp in Maine?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the start of Camp Sunshine in 1984, we have provided a haven for more than 24,000 family members from 46 states and 15 countries. More than 500 of these families have come from Connecticut. In fact, in 2007 alone, 50 Connecticut families applied to participate in our program. Sadly, even with multiple sessions being added annually at Camp Sunshine, there are still many more children from Connecticut being newly diagnosed each year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our program continues to be recommended by the following Connecticut treatment centers: Connecticut Children?s Medical Center and Yale-New Haven Children?s Hospital. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS (from points South):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 North to exit 61. Turn right off the exit onto Route 79 South ( Durham Road). Travel on Route 79 for approximately 0.6 miles. Turn right at the traffic light onto Boston Post Road. Travel on Boston Post Road for approximately 0.5 miles. Turn left onto West Wharf Road. Travel on West Wharf Road for approximately 0.3 miles. Turn right onto Surf Club Road. Travel on Surf Club Road for approximately 0.5 miles to the Surf Club entrance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203463723000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201759932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Devorah Dunk! aka Polar Plunge - charity benefit for terminally ill children</name><id>7232739</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201975200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7232739/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/c/d/global_3106301.jpeg</photo_url></item>