<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Orange Line</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.407211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Outside Stoney Brook T station</name><city>Jamaica Plains</city><id>9529952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.382439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's do the latest Banditos Misteriosos Choose Your Adventure! Please see description below. If you have never participated in a Banditos event before, the exact time and location are announced the day before the event.  We will be assigned a  start time sometime between 1pm - 4pm so please keep your schedules open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will register as a team so that we are all given the same start times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IN ORDER TO JOIN OUR TEAM AND ATTEND THIS EVENT: YOU MUST REGISTER  USING THIS LINK:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;-------&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://www.misteriosos.org/cyoa12/register/?teamcode=1cbbabe0"&gt;http://www.misteriosos.org/cyoa12/register/?teamcode=1cbbabe0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;During registration, I highly recommend that you select "no" when&lt;/span&gt; asked if you'd like notification of new team members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**PLEASE INDICATE WITH YOUR RSVP THAT YOU HAVE REGISTERED WITH THE IM TEAM**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Banditos Misteriosos is excited to announce that this year’s Choose Your Own Adventure will be held on Saturday, September 29th! Our biggest and most unique event of the year is shaping up to be even bigger and uniquer due to a generous grant received from The Awesome Foundation. That means props! Costumes! Maybe even a few expensive surprises! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For those of you joining this event for the first time, our Choose Your Own Adventure is just like one of those books that you (or your parents) read as a child. But instead of boring words on a boring page, your story is played out in front of you by a team of enthusiastic actors spread out across the city. Each of the characters you meet will give you a choice that affects the outcome of your story. You’ll also have fun puzzles to solve and games to play in order to advance the plot. The end result is a truly unique experience dependent on the actions you’ve taken. How your tale ends is up to you! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This year, you’re a student at Mapleridgepark Elementary. You and your classmates in Mrs. Higgins’ 4th grade class will be going on a field trip to the local petting zoo. What happens next is completely up to you! Will it just be another boring day at the petting zoo? Or will it be a THRILLING day at the petting zoo, full of action, intrigue, and the fate of the universe hanging in the balance? The answer may surprise you! So pack your lunches, get a full night’s rest, and make sure you bring your signed permission slip (&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/PzJXnA" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly/PzJXnA&lt;/a&gt;), because this will be the best field trip where-nothing-at-all-unexpected-or-unusual-happens you've ever had! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Finally, if you have any questions about this event please check the list of Frequently Asked Questions: &lt;a href="http://misteriosos.org/#faq" target="_blank"&gt;http://misteriosos.org/#faq&lt;/a&gt; or ask us a question on the Facebook event wall: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/436456659730034" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/436456659730034&lt;/a&gt;/ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We’ll see you in class on September 29th! &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;lt;3 Banditos&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS ON EMAILS FROM BANDITOS.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348964858000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346296782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Banditos Misteriosos - Choose Your Own Adventure 2012!‏</name><id>80030502</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348947000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/80030502/</event_url></item>