<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/c/4/event_222227812.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Difficulty: Easy / flat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 5 miles depending on the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duration: 2hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read the entire write up before signing up for this hike / walk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by signing up for this hike you agree to the terms of the liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending upon the group we will walk  at a brisk pace for about 5--6 miles before sunset. We will start walking North on the path and on the return trip we will try and time it to see the sun set on the water @ Larisa Park or Sabins Point Park. The East Bay Bike Path is a flat ribbon of former rail tracks that goes from the Providence/ East Providence line down to Bristol. It is about 28 miles round trip. We will be starting at the Loof Carousel in Riverside and heading North for a bit before returning to try and catch the sunset on the Narragansett Bay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a headlamp or flashlight just in case we run late. If you have a reflective vest bring it. As always bring snacks and water. I think the forecast is for warmer temps in the daytime. Make sure you bring a wind layer / fleece for when temps start to drop..See you in the parking next to Blount Clam Shack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Safety First!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>parking lot in front of the Blount Clam Shack  next to carousel</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366116558000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365979419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brisk walk on the East Bay Bike Path w/ sunset finish ?</name><id>114345942</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366061400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/114345942/</event_url></item>