<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>bpl.org</phone><name>Rabb Auditorium at Boston Public Library in Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>883985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;massmouth, inc. presents: First Annual Boston Storytelling Festival, April 21st, 2012 at the Boston Public Library&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark your Calendars!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On April 21st&amp;nbsp;at the Boston Public Library, from 10am-4:30pm storytellers from massmouth,inc. will make you laugh, sing and think as they present the art of storytelling through folk and fairy tales, songs, story slams and personal narrative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Storytelling has been entertaining human beings since time immemorial, but the art form hasn&amp;rsquo;t really been getting the kind of attention it deserves. And Boston based &amp;nbsp;massmouth, inc.&amp;nbsp;has been&amp;nbsp;changing that. Since 2008, massmouth,inc., hosts of the first story slam in Boston&amp;nbsp;(at Kennedy's Pub in OCT 2009 ) have held 100s of live events, taught 1000s of people including 1000s of high school students to tell their stories and have hosted a robust online presence that includes audio, video and social media sites.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Storytelling Festival intends to be an annual event and features a variety of storytelling experiences -- from workshops, to traditional and contemporary storytelling, slams: the works &amp;ndash; in an effort to make storytelling truly&amp;nbsp;accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FREE workshops will be held all day&amp;nbsp;on how to tell traditional or personal stories like, &amp;ldquo;From Page to Stage&amp;rdquo; and, &amp;ldquo;How to tell a kick-butt 5 minute story&amp;rdquo; .&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Rabb &amp;nbsp;Lecture Hall will host ongoing concerts throughout the day, that festival- goers will be encouraged to drop in on as they please. And storytellers will be street performers outside at the Copley Sq entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A score of acclaimed storytellers have signed on to perform, including several award-winning storytellers from massmouth slams.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A few of the traditional storytellers include: Judith Black, Doria Hughes, Norah Dooley, Andrea Lovett, Ben Cunningham**, Paula Junn, Jo Radner, Cindy Rivka Marshall, Katie Green and ToRena Webb Thomas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Storytellers &amp;ldquo;for the 21st&amp;nbsp;century&amp;rdquo; include Laura Packer, Scott Schultz, Ben Cunningham**, Robin Maxfield, ToRena Webb Thomas, Norah Dooley, Andrea Lovett, Michael Anderson*, Jackson Anderson, Katie Liesener ***, Farrah Haidar *** will be joined by some of the winners from our season III finale on April 11th 2012&amp;nbsp;at Coolidge Corner Theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/3/0/event_109512592.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Finalist, big mouthoff season 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**1st place award winner, big mouthoff Season 2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*** 2nd place award winner, Season 2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Exclusive performances by our represent&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ative winners of The BigMouthOff, 2012! (Our third season running!&amp;nbsp;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

"Storytelling is our "birthright" art. &amp;nbsp;We aim to reacquaint people with their own creativity and imaginations. In doing so, we bring people together in meaningful and rewarding connection." - Norah Dooley, co-founder and Executive Director &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Best of all?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Honoring our commitment to bring storytelling to the widest audience possible, &amp;nbsp;massmouth,inc. presents this entire event FREE and open to the public.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In order to secure a place in your workshop(s) of choice, pre-registration is strongly recommended but not required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you on the 21st, at what&amp;nbsp;we hope will become an annual celebration of the art of storytelling in its many forms in the city of Boston!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program is sponsored in part by the Boston Cultural Council, a local agency, as administered by the Massachusetts Cultural Council, a state agency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COMING SOON: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://massmouth.eventbrite.com/"&gt;http://massmouth.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for free registration to the workshops, check back in a day or so,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335232075000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>storytellers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>storytelling-28</urlname><id>1247871</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Greater Boston and MA Storytelling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334208741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st Annual Boston Storytelling Festival, 2012</name><id>60253252</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335016800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/storytelling-28/events/60253252/</event_url></item>