<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.sentinelsource.com/articles/2010/02/20/opinion/letters_editor/free/id_390563.txt" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sentinelso...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pictures make clear what really happened&lt;br /&gt;*&lt;br /&gt;Published: Saturday, February 20, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Regarding the article Feb. 11 (“September 11 photos released”), thank you for displaying a picture of the demolition of the World Trade Center building in New York City.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This picture, taken by NYPD photographer Greg Semendinger, from the police helicopter, clearly shows outward explosions, not just plain gravitational collapse from metal fatigue as described by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NIST was a part of the administration’s department of commerce. And ABC News just got these pictures from NIST through the Freedom of Information Act.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greg took hundreds of pictures that day from the helicopter, and another shot shows nearby WTC #7 in fine shape, although that building was pulled down later in the afternoon on the word of owner Larry Silverstein.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That building housed offices of the CIA and the Securities and Exchange Commission, which held the records of the investigations into WorldCom and Enron.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want more information on WTC 9/11 destruction, just Google Greg’s pictures via ABC News.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you want an interesting program for Saturday, Feb 27, besides waiting up for SNL, go to the Keene High School Auditorium at 7 p.m. for “9/11 And Our Future.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featured speaker will be award winning actor Daniel Sunjata of the TV show “Rescue Me.” His talk will be “9/11 Relevance in Age of Obama.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And hear Manny Badillo, 9/11 family member, and Bill Gleason, founder, World Trade Center Rescuers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hear Dr. John Wyndham’s “The Destruction of the Twin Towers – What Does the Evidence Say?”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free admission and music by The Northern Stone Band.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosted by The Monadnock 9/11 Truth Alliance and members of Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267488204000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266966321000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2/27 NH forum 9/11 And Our Future</name><id>12688710</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267315200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/12688710/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/global_12798054.jpeg</photo_url></item>