<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;TC:&lt;/b&gt; Heather - hrport@hotmail.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;EVENT:&lt;/b&gt;  52 minute Documentary (We will go for a bite to eat in Coolidge Corner after the movie) A must see documentary about the years after the Holocaust and leading up to the birth of the modern State of Israel in 1948.  Aliyah Bet (the organization smuggling Jews into pre-1948 British-mandate Palestine) chartered/purchased a number of old American naval ships, and recruited Jewish and non-Jewish crews to pick-up Holocaust survivors in Europe and sail to Palestine in an attempt to break the British blockade, and fulfill the dreams of the passengers to rebuild their lives in a Jewish homeland.  Through archival footage, and modern-day interviews we are able to share in the stories of an extraordinary American crew, the Holocaust survivors bound for pre-1948 Palestine under the British mandate, and British officers carrying out the blockade.  In this, Israel's 60th Anniversary year, this documentary is a pithy and fitting tribute to the heroism, courage, and superhuman endurance of a ships crew and passengers bound for the &lt;br /&gt;Land of Israel.  You've seen the movie &amp;quot;Exodus&amp;quot;; now is your chance to experience some of the stirring real-life stories and history upon which such fictional films were based.  (For more historic information about similar voyages, and descriptions of the film, here are a few links: &lt;a href="http://www.exodus1947.org/eindex.html;" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.exodus1947...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.bjff.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bjff.org...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.jff.org.il/?CategoryID=538&amp;amp;ArticleID=524;" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jff.org.il...&lt;/a&gt;  www.jewishvirtuallibrary.org - keywords: exodus 1947; British Blockade&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEET:&lt;/b&gt; 3:30pm Coolidge Corner Theatre- Brookline  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP:&lt;/b&gt; To Heather by November 10th so that we can have a headcount in order to save seats &lt;br /&gt;(General seating) together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt;  BJFF TICKET INFORMATION:  $12 general admission, $10 BJFF, CCT, ICA, MFA, WGBH members, students, and seniors, Matinees at the CCT: $7 all seats.  Tickets sell-out during BJFF quickly.  For more info and to purchase tickets log on to the BJFF website:  &lt;a href="http://www.bjff.org/festival_tickets.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bjff.org/f...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Contact our Trip Coordinator, Heather for the details</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229740830000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224635985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Jewish Film Festival:  "Waves of Freedom"</name><id>9006792</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226435400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/9006792/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/0/global_1883520.jpeg</photo_url></item>