<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.352823</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 478-3100 </phone><name>Institute of Contemporary Art</name><city>Boston</city><id>731894</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043059</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Adam Rudolph's Moving Pictures&lt;br /&gt;With special guest Hassan Hakmoun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been waiting a long time for these guys to come to Boston. They are the best of the best! An event not to be missed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Institute of Contemporary Art/Boston (ICA) continues its adventurous New Music Now series with Adam Rudolph's Moving Pictures and special guest Hassan Hakmoun on Friday, March 26, 2010 at 7:30 p.m. Tickets can be purchased at www.icaboston.org or by calling (617) 478-3103.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Rudolph's Moving Pictures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Known as an early innovator of world music, Chicago-born Adam Rudolph is a composer and percussionist who has developed a unique approach to hand drums. He was mentored from an early age by Don Cherry, Fred Anderson and Maulawi Nururdin. A student of ethnomusicology, he holds a B.A. from Oberlin and M.F.A. from California Institute of the arts. He traveled to Ghana and met famed West African poet Foday Musa Suso, and in 1978 they formed the Mandingo Griot Society, pioneering a fusion of traditional African music with jazz and R&amp;amp;B. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His travels throughout Europe, Asia and Africa have led to a mastering of a wide range of percussion instruments. He has played with Pharoah Sanders, Herbie Hancock, Bill Laswell, Shadowfax, Yusef Lateef and many others. Rudolph founded Moving Pictures in 1992, and its members have performed with world music ensembles, 20th-century chamber groups, and leading artists in jazz and rhythm and blues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the first time, Rudolph's ensemble will be joined by Marrakesh-born Hassan Hakmoun, a leader in Gnawa music (mixing African, Berber, and Arabic religious songs and rhythms) and master of a three-stringed, long-necked African bass lute called a sinter. He made his U.S. debut in 1987 at Lincoln Center, and he has performed with Peter Gabriel, Don Cherry, Paula Cole, Kronos Quartet and many others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Institute of Contemporary Art/Boston (ICA) continues its adventurous New Music Now series with Adam Rudolph's Moving Pictures and special guest Hassan Hakmoun on Friday, March 26, 2010 at 7:30 p.m. Tickets can be purchased at www.icaboston.org or by calling (617) 478-3103.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.icaboston.org/programs/performance/music/rudolph/" target="_blank"&gt;Adam Rudolph's Moving Pictures  With special guest Hassan Hakmoun&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's contact and message each other to set this up!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269819296000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269124761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adam Rudolph's Moving Pictures  With special guest Hassan Hakmoun</name><id>12942944</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269646200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/12942944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/0/global_13772336.jpeg</photo_url></item>