<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; beginner (flat or gentle hills; but we haven't decided how far we're hiking yet)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many trails at Leominster State Forrest, and maps can be picked up at the gate. We can decide on a trail then if we don't figure that out by Sunday night. Personally, 11am Monday works for me...I don't have to work Monday, and I can sleep in! But if we need to go earlier or later, that's okay, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please use Richard's directions. (I don't know the exact address, so I can't add a location)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Route 2, drive South on 31 until you leave Leominster by 100 yards. Parking is on left. From south, take 31 north until just before Leominster. Parking on right.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you go to the map posted at &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/leominster.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/leominster.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;, the parking area is on the east side of route 31. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are 3 parking areas shown on the east side. It is the middle one.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; If you zoom in, you will also see that this parking area is between the numbers 4 and 5. As an additional landmark, this parking area is paved, there is a porta potty in it and it overlooks ponds. The P for parking appears to be in the middle of a pond, but it isn't!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From Route 2, drive South on 31 out of Leominster by 100 yards. Parking is on left. From south, take 31 north until just before Leominster. Parking on right.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329926205000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329186054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday hikes (Monday Hikes)</name><id>dkfvncyqdbbc</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329753600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/52254662/</event_url></item>