<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We're going to North Cascades National Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am planning on doing a 6 days 5 nights backpacking trip. We willl average about 12 miles a day. This means that perhaps the first day we will do 5 miles and one of the days in between to make up for the distance we might have to do 16 to 20 but most days we will do about 12 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need to at least have gone on one backpacking trip with anyone in your life to join this trip. This is a very tough thing to do if you have never gone backpacking in your life. It is easy to overpack too much food and have 60 lb bag when all you need is a 40lb bag.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am planning on backpacking from Sunday August 15 to Friday August 20th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore I need a few things when you RSVP. First you must be committed to going on this trip. I will need you to book your flight within three weeks of RSPVing. Second thing is that we will be sharing a rental and if you can drive you must be willing to chip in to drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another thing is that my friend's Eric and Alex have kindly agreed to be our hosts on the weekend of the 20th. So we can crash at their apartment! We can do some sightseeing in Seattle and we have planned on visiting Vancouver Island on the 21st and perhaps camping that night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore here is the plan, buy a plane ticket to Seattle arriving on August 14th and either leaving on the 21st if you want. If not you can hang out with me, Anne and Tay until the 23rd!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come next week to Williamsburg if you have not met me yet before you book your ticket. I would like to talk to you before the trip!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Estimate of costs :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Airfare $480 (from Boston)&lt;br /&gt;Hotels (Saturday August 14th and Friday August 20th per person) $50 &lt;br /&gt;Car rental for the week and gas $100 &lt;br /&gt;Food $100&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total cost of trip $730.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, feel free to email me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;metope@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Francisco&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Francisco</member_name><member_id>822470</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281831673000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278549261000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Backpacking Trip to the North Cascades</name><id>14034790</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281826800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14034790/</event_url></item>