<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Mark Duplass is at it again! How does he find the time to direct and act in so many movies?! I first saw him in &lt;em&gt;Humpday&lt;/em&gt;, which was directed by the same person (Lynn Shelton) who directs &lt;em&gt;Your Sister’s Sister&lt;/em&gt;. Last week, I saw him in &lt;em&gt;Safety Not Guaranteed&lt;/em&gt;, a great small-budget movie. Emily Blunt and Rosemarie DeWitt costar with Duplass in &lt;em&gt;Your Sister's Sister&lt;/em&gt;. Reviewers are saying that this movie is amazing considering that it’s just three characters in one setting.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;*****From the theater website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;In the dramatic comedy &lt;em&gt;Your Sister's Sister&lt;/em&gt;, Mark Duplass (co-director of &lt;em&gt;Jeff, Who Lives at Home&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Cyrus&lt;/em&gt;) stars as Jack, a slacker who’s still emotionally unstable a year after his brother Tom’s death. When he makes a scene at a memorial party, Tom’s ex-girlfriend, Iris (Emily Blunt), offers her family cabin on an island in the Pacific Northwest so Jack can seek catharsis in solitude. Once there, however, he runs into Iris’s sister, Hannah (Rosemarie DeWitt), a lesbian reeling from the abrupt end of a seven-year relationship. Hannah finds solace in the affable Tom’s unexpected presence, and the two bond over a long night of drinking. The blurry evening concludes with an awkward sexual incident. Iris's sudden presence at the cabin the next morning sets into motion a twisted tale of ever-complicated relationships. Written and directed by Lynn Shelton (&lt;em&gt;Humpday&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;*****&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;I will purchase my ticket by 6:40 p.m., then wait at the foot of the stairs in the theater lobby. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for me carrying a red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; At 6:55, I will move into the theater auditorium (can’t miss the previews). You can find me there, if you are late. &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The movie starts at 7:10 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;After the movie, I will wait in the theater lobby to gather everyone. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for the red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If we decide to go out after the movie, be prepared to add 25% to the cost of your order for both the tax and the tip. Restaurants in the area add the gratuity to the check automatically. Bring cash to make division of the check easier.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend this event so I know who to look for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Marianne&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the red backpack. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341257651000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340772119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your Sister's Sister</name><id>70929202</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341096300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/70929202/</event_url></item>