<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1600 South East Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06032</zip><lat>41.730000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.674.8110</phone><name>Borders Books</name><city>Farmington</city><id>200171</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.839996</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hail!  I've been hosting a monthly Hartford area &amp;quot;meet and greet&amp;quot; for the Connecticut Wiccan and Pagan Network this past year.  December will be my last such. It will take place at Borders Book Store in Farmington (just 1/4 mile from the Westfarms Mall in West Hartford, easy to get to off I-84).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The theme was already set as &amp;quot;Yule and Community.&amp;quot;  *chuckle*  How heathen can you get?  We can swap bits of lore and ideas about the pre-Christian practices of our ancestors during the &lt;a href="http://www.tworavenskindred.org/bleakmidwinter.html" target="_blank"&gt;bleak midwinter&lt;/a&gt;... as well as share stories of our own Yuletide traditions both old and new.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bordersstores.com/stores/store_pg.jsp?storeID=55" target="_blank"&gt;Info about the Borders store (including directions) here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.witchvox.com/vn/vn_detail/dt_ev.html?a=usct&amp;amp;id=40431" target="_blank"&gt;Info about the December event as originally posted.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway, for those who don't know me, I am a member of the Connecticut-based &lt;a href="http://www.tworavenskindred.org" target="_blank"&gt;Two Ravens Kindred&lt;/a&gt; these past four years.  Currently serving as the Public Relations Officer for &lt;a href="http://www.thetroth.org" target="_blank"&gt;The Troth&lt;/a&gt; and am proposed Troth Steward for Connecticut next year.  I won't call myself a skald, but I do have a lamentable tendency to sing and recite verse in public.  Having just completed a workshop on brewing, I am very excited about making my first batch of mead next month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm taking this opportunity to transition my &amp;quot;second Monday of the month&amp;quot; experience from being one of hanging out with any random pagan that happens to show up -- rarely rewarding -- to one of helping build and strengthen the heathen community in Connecticut.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After December, ongoing meetups can be lore nights, or social gatherings (PubMoot!), or special events.  We'll take the &amp;quot;pulse&amp;quot; of whoever shows up at this first opportunity to get together and see what feels right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My goal is for newcomers to feel every bit as welcome as the veterans.  Knowing the quality of the existing heathen community throughout the Northeast, I have no doubt that those who sincerely wish to find a seat at the table, will have little trouble doing so. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's about it for now.  RSVP, so I know how many to expect and can give Borders a heads up about the impending Viking invasion.  *grin* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yours in frith and honor, &lt;br /&gt;Mike&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hicks</member_name><member_id>3427608</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173634536000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Followers of Asatru</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>asatru-242</urlname><id>369297</id><group_lat>41.8600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut &amp; Western Mass Asatru Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163991557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Asatru December Meetup</name><id>5279699</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165881600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/asatru-242/events/5279699/</event_url></item>