<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street, 2nd Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1065386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183899</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;NEW: I am excited to announce that Ipsalu Tantra Kriya Yoga teacher Bob Johnson will be joining me to co-teach this class!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the interest of members we are offering a basic Introduction to Tantric Practices for the Curious and Open Beginner. An introduction to how couples can begin a more tantric journey together will be included. Thank you to Sukriti for suggesting this MeetUp!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using focused awareness, breath, sound and movement we will explore some of the foundational tenets and practices of Tantra Yoga to energize the body, quiet the mind, activate and transmute sexual energy, and experience Divine Union.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a safe space for exploration, come find out what Tantra is, and what it is not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No partner(ing) necessary. Most of the practices we will be doing are solo practices which can be shared with a partner, but do not require one. If you come as a couple, you may of course work together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your questions, curiosity and open mind!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear comfortable clothing to move in and a water bottle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brynn Bishop&lt;/strong&gt;, is a Tantra Educator and Love and Empowerment Coach with over 25 years experience in the fields of body-mind integration and conscious relating. Her passion is guiding people on the path of intimacy, freedom and fulfillment. Brynn maintains a private practice in Arlington, MA and via phone and Skype. Brynn has been called “Midwife for the Embodied Soul.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bob Johnson&lt;/strong&gt; is a teacher of Ipsalu Tantra Kriya Yoga. He has studied with numerous renowned teachers of many Tantric traditions over the past 25 years. Bob enjoys sharing this path to higher consciousness to enhance one's happiness and fulfillment in life.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob J</member_name><member_id>6123310</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341624379000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>58</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320266414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Tantric Intimacy: For Curious &amp; Open Beginners!</name><id>39705592</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341012600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/39705592/</event_url></item>