<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>OK, this time the military won't be able grag me.  This is the reschedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at my pad to go over some material and at 8pm will be punching out to Mohegan. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I copied their Ad below so you know what to expect. Take heed of the dress code and dress to impress, peacock some to. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should find quality women here, little black dresses, girls on vacation; What are we waiting for!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ultra 88 Nightclub &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the finer side of life with personalized bottle service, dancing and VIP seating in this South Beach-style night club! With over 400 square feet of dance space, your groove is sure to have enough room to move to our 30,000 watt Avalon Series Sound System. Cover charge is $10 on Fridays (free with little black dress before 11pm) and $20 on Saturdays (cover charge and bottle pricing/promotions subject to change on holidays and special events).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our grand VIP Suite offers the ultimate in VIP experience, equipped with its own restroom, wet bar, computer terminal, two LCD screens, private server and security guard. This fabulous one-of-a-kind suite can accommodate up to 18 guests for the perfect party. How about your own private soire? Ultra even has an additional space with its own bar and dance floor, a perfect setting for up to 80 guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cover Charge &lt;br /&gt;$10 on Fridays (free with little black dress before 11:00 pm) and $20 on Saturdays. Cover charge may vary on special occasions. Bottle prices and promotions are subject to change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Age Restrictions: &lt;br /&gt;All patrons must be 21 or older and possess a VALID ID.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress Code &lt;br /&gt;Fashionable and dressy clothing. Guests wearing the following will not be permitted: No athletic wear, sweats or sports jerseys, excessively baggy clothing (tuck-ins are not permitted), sleeveless tee-shirts, plain tee-shirts (short or long sleeve), boots, flip flops, sneakers, headgear, chains, or ripped clothing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249059525000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216251842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Little Black Dress Night at Mohegan</name><id>8354569</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218240000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/8354569/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/4/global_4544868.jpeg</photo_url></item>