<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>By day he works as a programmer analyst for a major food service company doing application development and technical support. By night, he records and analyzes UFO sighting reports, abduction experiences, hauntings and anything else that qualifies as strange/unknown/weird. Chris Augustin has been an Alien/UFO/Paranormal Investigator for 13+ years now. Chris' site, www.aliensthetruth.com, is online for one main reason, the truth. In our community, people who have had UFO sightings, abduction experiences, paranormal encounters, etc; need a place to go. They need a place to share what they have experienced without the fear of ridicule. This is truly an alternate reality for many people. The mainstream media rarely gives our community positive attention, unless it's some major event like the Roswell UFO crash anniversary, or when there's a mass sighting, where hundreds or thousands of people witness the event, like the Phoenix Lights in 1997. The site focuses on some very basic premises, there is life on this planet, which is one out of billions. Therefore, it is mathematically impossible for life not to exist on another. With the vast amount of evidence collected over the years, going back to ancient times, up to today, from reports gathered by MUFON and other organizations; there is no way that we can be alone in the universe. Join us tonight at 9 pm and call in with questions for Chris.&lt;br /&gt;to listen to this episode or to listen to past episodes, visit  &lt;a href="http://www.blogtalkradio.com/isabeauesby" target="_blank"&gt;www.blogtalkradio.com/isabeauesby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258251237000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256352025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intellectual Spirituality Radio Show - Featured Guest Chris Augustin</name><id>11698369</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258077600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/11698369/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/f/global_11311583.jpeg</photo_url></item>