<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our featured speaker will be our own Dr. David Schafer. Since February is Darwin Month, we will once again celebrate the incalculable change wrought by one man in humanity’s understanding of ourselves and our place in the universe. Explaining some of the basic concepts and methods of “Evo-Devo,” (the emerging science of the Evolution of Development, a blend of evolution and embryonic development) illustrated by segments from the December 29 installment of NOVA on PBS, entitled “What Darwin Never Knew,” David will attempt to give an appreciation of the fabulous promise of this research for our future understanding of the detailed panorama of the molecular machinery underlying evolution, something “Darwin Never Knew.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start with a half hour of coffee and conversation at 7:30 PM. The main talk will follow brief announcements at 8:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about this event and others, please read the write-up on &lt;a href="http://www.cthumanist.org/" target="_blank"&gt;our home page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will most probably be in the Social Hall near the main entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Siddall</member_name><member_id>1140632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266453168000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265234239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting - Far Beyond Darwin’s Fondest Dreams</name><id>12511022</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266280200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/12511022/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/global_5196186.jpeg</photo_url></item>