<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>215 Great Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01464</zip><lat>42.578570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-425-4311</phone><name>The Bull Run</name><city>Shirley</city><id>380565</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.642235</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TIME: 6:45 pm ( if you wish to have dinner before the show)&lt;br /&gt;          7:30 pm ( music begins @ 8:00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKET COST:  $15.00 in advance&lt;br /&gt;                        $19.00 day of the show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music begins @ 8pm. &lt;br /&gt;Jody Williams&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp; his All-Star Band&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jody Williams is a Chicago blues guitar-slinger who literally attended the same school as his friend Bo Diddley. You've heard his playing, too, if you've heard &lt;b&gt;Bo Diddley's&lt;/b&gt; &amp;quot;Who Do You Love.? Like Hubert Sumlin, Jody played lead guitar behind the great &lt;b&gt;Howlin' Wolf&lt;/b&gt;. He also invented many riffs you've heard in other songs; often without the proper credit. A contemporary of &lt;b&gt;Magic Sam, Otis Rush and Buddy Guy: &lt;/b&gt; and among the last surviving guitarists from the Chicago blues scene of the 1950s; Williams emerged from retirement in the 1990s and recorded two CDs, Return of a Legend and You Left Me in the Dark.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;He's making a special East Coast tour ( 3 gigs only) with an all-star band. One is @ The Bull Run. don't miss it!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?One of the unsung heroes of the blues guitar? - Bill Dahl, All Music Guide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opener: &lt;b&gt;Brian Templeton - &lt;/b&gt; Maybe you remember him from &lt;b&gt;The Radio Kings&lt;/b&gt;, or his days with &lt;b&gt;Little Milton,&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Monster Mike Welch, &lt;/b&gt;, or &lt;b&gt;Otis Grands,&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Sonny Rhodes.&lt;/b&gt;. Or maybe you just remember that with his powerful voice and commanding stage presence he is easily one of Boston's most dynamic performers&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm sorry, but I am unable to attend this meetup.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209339584000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>The Bull Run is one of 3 only on the East Coast tour for Jody Williams and an all-star band. 
Don't miss it! We had a fantastic night the last time we were here for "Roomful of Blues!"</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205714920000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JODY WILLIAMS @ The Bull Run Concert Series</name><id>7546560</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209166200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7546560/</event_url></item>