<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 New Park Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.747210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 236-6677</phone><name>Cinema City at the Palace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>532404</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.713217</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>PLEASE NOTE:  Cinema City has moved the time back by a half-hour, to start at 6:20pm.&lt;br /&gt;I hope this does not present a problem for anybody who is planning to attend.&lt;br /&gt;==============================================================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've wanted to see this movie since the first time I saw the preview. It's described as &amp;quot;[a] movie spun out of equal parts folk tale, fable and real-life legend about the mysterious, 1930s Tennessee hermit who famously threw his own rollicking funeral party... while he was still alive.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Bowtie Cinemas website: &amp;quot;Felix is a miserable old hermit who has lived in an isolated cabin for the past 38 years. He catches word that an old friend has passed away and hatches a plan to throw himself a &amp;quot;funeral party.&amp;quot; He even wants the townsfolk, who either despise him or fear him, to attend the party and share all the crazy stories they may have heard about creepy old Felix. Is he a fugitive? A murderer? Or something worse?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stars Robert Duvall, Bill Murray, Sissy Spacek, Lucas Black, and Gerald McRaney. &lt;br /&gt;100 minutes. &lt;br /&gt;More information: &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1194263/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show is scheduled to start at 6:50pm, so you have a cushion to arrive; Meetup only schedules on the quarter-hour and I thought that 6:45pm might be a little tight.  Not many people could do the original date I scheduled (Tuesday evening), but a number of persons said they would come if I moved it to the weekend, now that the extended schedule is available.  It's the evening of Labour Day; enough persons told me that they could probably attend that I decided to schedule the meetup.  I did leave the original one in place in case someone can't make this time/date.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the lobby - I'm usually knitting while I wait.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283905249000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283052778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Get Low" @ Cinema City - UPDATED TIME</name><id>14576801</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283810400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/14576801/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>