<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Walnut Grove Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.558052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Veterans Park</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1276910</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.672108</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Come and join us for our 10th annual potluck Memorial Day/Wisteria Festival Picnic. This community event will take place at Veteran's Memorial Field. On this day, we will honor the men and women who served our country in the armed forces and also Wisteria Festival, or Gotan-e in Japanese, that celebrates the birthday and life of Shinran Shonin, the founder and foremost teacher of Shin Buddhism, over 750 years ago in Japan. All members and friends and their guests are invited to attend.&lt;/span&gt; This event is great for families and for those new to Buddhism. There is &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;no Sunday morning gathering at Wesleyan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;LET US KNOW WHAT YOU WILL BE BRINGING. Email &lt;a href="mailto:amida@bffct.net"&gt;amida@bffct.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;What we need?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Plates, napkins, cups, forks, knives, spoons, burgers, hot dogs and veggie burgers, buns. Condiments, salads, desserts, non-alcoholic drinks and other surprises. Also, if you have out door games for adults and kids.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Our Buddhism 101 Winter - Spring class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;will meet at 10:00 a.m. at Veteran's Field. The Community picnic will begin at 12:30 p.m. through 5 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who was Shinran Shonin?&lt;/strong&gt; For followers of Shin Buddhist teaching, this day is very important, as it was Shinran who systematically developed a reformed Pure Land teaching by compiling the commentaries of the seven teachers whom he chose to call the Seven Patriarchs. The essence of the Jodo Shinshu teaching is contained in Shinran’s Kyo-Gyo-Shin-Sho, compiled and written during his last years in the Kanto area, before his return to Kyoto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Shinran Shonin teaches that we are able to attain spiritual liberation or Birth into the Pure Land. Even though Shinran (1173-1263) was born some 800 years ago, the Nembutsu teaching that he developed is still applicable to us in this modern Age of Technology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;What distinguishes his teaching is that it was meant primarily for householders, rather than those who left their homes to enter priesthood and attempt to follow the difficult path of discipline in search of Enlightenment. Without distinguishing between the priesthood and laity, he pointed out that everyone, without distinction of rank or class, would be saved by reciting the Nembutsu – namu amida butsu, with true entrusting in Amida, the Oneness of Immeasurable Life and Light. In Shinran’s teaching, there is no distinction between good and evil. Everyone is equal before the Buddha, and all can be equally liberated by Amida’s Boundless Compassion. This is Shinran Shonin’s true entrusting in working and grace of the the Primal Vow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Our Buddhism 101 Winter - Spring class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;will meet at 10:00 a.m. at Veteran's Field. The Community picnic will begin at 12:30 p.m. through 5 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Visit our main website  at &lt;a href="http://www.bffct.net"&gt;www.bffct.net&lt;/a&gt; for Calendar and more information on our beliefs and practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Hosted by the Buddhist Faith Fellowship. Even though just one or two people from Meetup have RSVPed, you can expect 35 - 45 people in attendance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338147912000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336354136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhist Meetup Group - Memorial Day Sunday Picnic</name><id>dsjphcyqhbkc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338136200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/63708222/</event_url></item>