<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The actual screening time is 1:25. Meetup only allows time posting in 15 minute increments which is why there are two times posted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had the pleasure of seeing this film about six months ago and am looking forward to re-visiting it once more. Admittedly Persepolis was a group event a few weeks ago and the reaction from group members was somewhat mixed ( ahh, the curse of expectations). I found this coming of age tale of an Iranian girl to be not only entertaining but informative and enlightening in its portrayal of one girl's maturation during a cultural period many of us know little about.The hand-drawn animation  may be considered simplistic by some but  it is disarmingly expressive compared to most full-length &amp;quot;cartoon&amp;quot; features.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also a reminder that  detailed voting instructions for our Group Awards is  now available on the Message Board along with a full listing of all the movies we've seen and the nominations that members have suggested so far. Please try to take a few minutes to include your own take on the past year of film- this should be fun, providing an opportunity for everyone  to express their own opinion versus the reductive qualities brought about by the major awards . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Persepolis&lt;/b&gt; Iran/France 95 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A memoir in the form of an animated feature, &amp;quot;Persepolis,&amp;quot; adapted by Marjane Satrapi from her acclaimed graphic novels, is a remembrance told not with anger but disappointment. The film unfolds as a flashback, the quiet color of the uncertain present giving way to the graphic boldness of black-and-white memory. The narrator shares the experience of coming of age in Iran in the wake of the Islamic revolution. At the same time she leads us through her developing perspective as she grows up from little Marji -- a girl who adores Bruce Lee and rocks out to Iron Maiden -- to empowered young woman Marjane (voiced by Chiara Mastroianni). Marjane quickly finds that her artistic ambitions and personal desires are constrained under the oppressive laws of her country. &amp;quot;Persepolis&amp;quot; is an uncompromising look at the culture of Iran as seen by an observant and open-minded child, and a frank exploration of adolescence and identity (not to mention gender) in a culture of intolerance.&lt;br /&gt; Seattle Post-Intelligencer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Satrapi's parents ship her off to a French school in Vienna, but she's rudderless, ungrounded. She's drawn back to a devastated Tehran, where she can't design a life, either. This great film, by Satrapi and Vincent Paronnaud, is that life, designed. It freed her mind; it frees ours.  New York Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.philly.com/philly/entertainment/movies/20080118_An_Iranians_memoir_in_pen_and_ink.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.philly.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meet-up sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201829354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Persepolis Revisted  Starts @ 1:25</name><id>7237312</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203185700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7237312/</event_url></item>