<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.828457</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.272.2116</phone><name>Cafe Noir</name><city>Providence</city><id>1069572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409515</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: XO Cafe (formally Cafe Noir, which WAS XO Steakhouse before that - lol!) Its across from Olives and next to Mills Tavern on N. Main St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So they switched the name two years ago to Cafe Noir from XO Steakhouse, now they've&amp;nbsp; combined the name to XO Cafe. Cafe Noir was a French inspired restaurant with a distinctively cozy and comfortable European feel. I haven't been since they changed the name, but I'm sure its still just as good! The bar is large, and the creative drinks and food are tasty. We haven't been back since January, so, whether you've been there before, or if you'd like to give it a try, or just go again to see if there's been a change, its always a good time and let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.
 &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there around 6:30, but we're hard to miss! I'll be wearing a red flower in my hair in case</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310426119000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310319036000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - XO Cafe</name><id>25227151</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310421600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/25227151/</event_url></item>