<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cambridge Innovation Center (CIC)</address_2><address_1>One Broadway, 4th Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Venture Café</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1369069</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084037</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Django Boston &lt;br /&gt;Thu Dec 9 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6pm-630pm Networking at Venture Café&lt;br /&gt;630pm Introductions&lt;br /&gt;645pm Talks&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Kaplan-Moss, Writing Great Documentation&lt;br /&gt;Paul Bissex, Using Django to Replace Proprietary Database Tools&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Kaplan-Moss&lt;br /&gt;Writing Great Documentation&lt;br /&gt;A look at the structural elements that make documentation useful, including how to break documentation down into component parts, tips on how to get documentation done, and community processes for handling documentation in teams (open or not). We'll also talk about what I'm calling &amp;quot;Documentation Driven Development&amp;quot; (a riff off Test Driven Development) and briefly look at a few Python documentation tools.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Bissex&lt;br /&gt;Using Django to Replace Proprietary Database Tools&lt;br /&gt;Paul will show how he used Django to build a complete solution for live attendance tracking and equipment loan in a career school environment. The system replaced proprietary database systems from two different vendors. It manages all attendance taking and reporting for over 100 class sessions per week. It also tracks equipment lending from a $1 million inventory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Kaplan-Moss will be in Boston for two Django workshops.  Apply &amp;quot;djangoboston&amp;quot; code for 10% discount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Best of the Django Ecosystem (Boston)&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, December 09, 2010 from 9:00 AM - 4:30 PM (ET)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://djangoeco-bos.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://djangoeco-bos....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Django Deployment Workshop (Boston)&lt;br /&gt;Friday, December 10, 2010 from 9:00 AM - 4:30 PM (ET)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://deploydjango-bos.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://deploydjango-b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Venture Café&lt;br /&gt;The Venture Café, currently in its alpha stage, is a resource for the Boston entrepreneurial and innovation communities with the mission of creating fresh and useful conversations. As the Venture Cafe prepares to enter into its permanent home in Kendall Square, the founders project that the marriage of innovation and creativity with a European-style cafe space will facilitate collaboration and build a greater sense of community in Kendall Square. www.venturecafe.net&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact:&lt;br /&gt;Carrie Stalder, Founding Manager for The Venture Café&lt;br /&gt;617-329-1324, carrie@venturecafe.net&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brett Stilwell</member_name><member_id>2081142</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292358045000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Djangonauts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>djangoboston</urlname><id>1289145</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Django Boston Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289149462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Django Boston Dec 2010</name><id>15368391</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291935600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/djangoboston/events/15368391/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/global_12798354.jpeg</photo_url></item>