<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>146 Northern Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.351138</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-357-8000</phone><name>Atlantic Beer Garden</name><city>Boston</city><id>1026662</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043399</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey gang unfortunately a lot of people had scheduling conflicts so going to Providence for the Waterfire had to be postponed.  No big deal, there are a few dates left for that so if people are interested we can re-visit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway, I still figured it would still be cool to get together and hang out for a bit.  I found a really cool place for us to hang out with a few cocktails and relax off the water to come down from a hectic week.  That place is Atlantic Beer Garden off Seaport Blvd. across from the World Trade Center &amp;amp; Seaport Hotel.  They have a large outside deck area overlooking the water which is an awsome sight if it's nice that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is also a great place for an affordable dinner so who ever is interested in meeting up this Friday, August 7th around 6:30 or so please let me know by replying on the site to this event.  By Wednesday or Thursday depending how many we have I will make reservations for dinner.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see as many of you as possible on Friday and here is the direction links to the place.  As far as closest T-stops that would be Courthouse Station off the Silverline.  Silverline can be picked up at Southstation.  I will send an email this week with instructions on where to find each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.atlanticbeergarden.com&lt;br /&gt;146 Northern Ave&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02210-1802&lt;br /&gt;(617) 357-8000&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve rosen</member_name><member_id>3640517</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253572317000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ex-Midwesterners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Midwesterners</urlname><id>545362</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ex-Midwesterners Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249221257000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Drinks at Atlantic Beer Garden</name><id>11013945</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249684200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Midwesterners/events/11013945/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/global_4872018.jpeg</photo_url></item>