<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Change in plans, JediFonger had something come up so I am going to organize (Doreen).

The film starts at 6:50, I will be there at 6:15.    I think we are going to want to go in at 6:30 to ensure we get good seats.   I will be wearing my Boston Movie Group Badge.  I think the show is upstairs, so I will be near the coffee vendor, I will try to get a table.   If, for some reason, the info on the ticket I just bought from Fandango is incorrect, then I will be just inside the ropes in front of the concession stand downstairs.


Runtime: ~2hrs | Rated PG-13 Monster violence+witty dialogue.

Director: Chris Carter

Screenwriter: Chris Carter&amp;Frank Spotnitz

Starring: David Duchovny, Gillian Anderson

Genre: Awesome

Reviews: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;id=11204" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;id=11204&lt;/a&gt;

[b]Trailer#2[/b]
&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/LcuACKXK0FI&amp;hl=en" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

Description:
A group of women are abducted in the wintry hills of rural Virginia, the only clues to their disappearance are the grotesque human remains that begin to turn up in snow banks along the highway. With officials desperate for any lead, a disgraced priest?s questionable ?visions? send local police on a wild goose chase and straight to a bizarre secret medical experiment that may or may not be connected to the women?s disappearance. It?s a case right out of The X-Files. But the FBI closed down its investigations into the paranormal years ago. And the best team for the job is ex-agents Fox Mulder and Dr. Dana Scully, who have no desire to revisit their dark past. Still, the truth of these horrific crimes is out there somewhere?and it will take Mulder and Scully to find it!</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing my  Boston Movie Group Badge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218889275000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>it's the X-Files! and we know you WANT TO BELIEVE IT TOO!</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203947869000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The X-Files: I Want to Believe</name><id>7403311</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217025000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7403311/</event_url></item>