<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Note: Please RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;br /&gt;Since we usually provide refreshments, handouts and set up chairs,  please only RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; if you know you can attend, and are planning on it.  If your plans change, please be considerate and notify us by e-mailing me.  Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*******************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Law of Attraction states, &amp;quot;That which is like unto itself is drawn.&amp;quot;  Hence, when you activate a vibration within you (your thoughts and feelings), the Law of Attraction begins responding to that vibration, matching it - whether it's something wanted or unwanted.  If you are feeling calm, centered, and re-Sourceful, you will attract what you desire.  You are opening the doors to allow those manifestations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How aware are you of when you are aligned and centered, and when you are not?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How flexible are you with being able to re-center yourself when you feel tugged or pushed by life circumstances?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How easily do you maintain your flow state in various circumstances?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In February's meet-up we'll do some simple, playful exercises to help you raise your awareness of when you're out of sync with your greater self-  your Creative Source Energy/Universe/God self.  We'll also practice getting back into a centered, connected, re-Sourceful place.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll begin the evening with a guided meditation to help you access a centered, connected state; and we'll use this in the exercise.  As always, we will also have time for group coaching and support on whatever issues and questions you want to bring to the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in the power of collective energy and learning!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be upstairs.  Go to back of front lobby for stairway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237332310000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232500079000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Meetup: Being open, present, and connected to your center and Source</name><id>9566922</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234915200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/9566922/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/c/global_7047340.jpeg</photo_url></item>