<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Constitution Plaza</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.765655</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Spris </name><city>Hartford</city><id>705675</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.669485</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join social hourz meetup &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Hartford - MAGAZINE'S FAMOUS &amp;quot;THE SOCIAL&amp;quot; 6pm - 10pm Spris Constitution plaza, Hartford CT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yourhartfo.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yourhartfo...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;THE SOCIAL IS YH MAGAZINE'S GIGANTIC FREE BI-MONTHLY UPSCALE SOCIAL EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;The social - YH Magazine's Exclusive Branded BI-Monthly Social Cocktail event, currently held outdoors on Spris Constitution plaza. &lt;br /&gt;What is it all about? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Social&amp;quot; is an upscale cocktail event currently held outdoors on Spris Constitution Plaza during the summer. It is for the &amp;quot;Professional&amp;quot;. It is a social mixer. While outdoors you will enjoy cocktails and taste complimentary Italian Anti-pasto courtesy of Spris Hartford Restaurant. It truly is such a unique and enjoyable experience. It is put together by yours truly YH Magazine. It is easily the biggest social cocktail events ever held in Downtown Hartford. The &amp;quot;Social&amp;quot; is an event from 6PM-10PM and sometimes till 1AM depending on what we have as far as entertainment. Thank you! for the support!&lt;br /&gt;Hundreds of like-minded friendly professionals. &lt;br /&gt;Outdoor on Spris Constitution Plaza. &lt;br /&gt;Complimentary Italian Anti-Pasto Courtesy of Spris Restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;It is an upscale event that anyone can enjoy.&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever had a cocktail outdoors on a gigantic rooftop overlooking downtown in Hartford before?&lt;br /&gt;FREE Admission.&lt;br /&gt;What's the Dress Code? &lt;br /&gt;You can come as you like but keep in mind 99% of the people who come to &amp;quot;The Social&amp;quot; are dressed professionally or stylish.&lt;br /&gt;Is there an entrance fee? &lt;br /&gt;YH Magazine's &amp;quot;The Social&amp;quot; is the only gigantic upscale cocktail event in this region where there is NO entrance fee.&lt;br /&gt;Entertainment at &amp;quot;The Social&amp;quot;? &lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Social&amp;quot; is primarily created as a result of an Art-based ideology. The music will be of two types, a live Jazz band, and a live DJ. Trust us, the music will always be fantastic! The purpose is for people to have fun and socialize. Aside from music we will introduce different art elements like Acrobatics, Belly Dancing etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; organizer is needed&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please join social hourz meetup  - meet by the water fountain</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy</member_name><member_id>4345102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215986528000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215685549000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spris - "The Social"</name><id>8313106</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215813600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8313106/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/9/global_3265913.jpeg</photo_url></item>