<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Man On Wire&lt;br /&gt;Magnolia Pictures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On August 7, 1974 a young Frenchman named Philippe Petit stepped out on a wire illegally rigged between New York's twin towers, then the world's tallest buildings. After nearly an hour dancing on the wire, he was arrested, taken for psychological evaluation and brought to jail. Petit spent eight months in New York planning the execution of the coup. Aided by a team of friends and accomplices, he had to find a way to bypass the WTC's security; smuggle the heavy steel cable and rigging equipment into the towers; pass the wire between the two rooftops; anchor the wire and tension it to withstand the winds and the swaying of the buildings. The rigging was done by night in complete secrecy. At 7:15 AM, Philippe took his first step on the high wire 1,350 feet above the sidewalks of Manhattan. James Marsh's documentary brings Petit's extraordinary adventure to life through the testimony of Philippe himself, and some of the co-conspirators who helped him create the unique and magnificent spectacle that became known as &amp;quot;the artistic crime of the century.&amp;quot; Original music by Michael Nyman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see the &amp;quot;files&amp;quot; section to print out the free admission screening pass.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chelsea</member_name><member_id>3861711</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222684134000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217359357000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Man On Wire Film Screening</name><id>8436297</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217977200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8436297/</event_url></item>