<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10 at the door</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;No Program. No Speaker. No Snow Delay. Show up!&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;**Collection for &lt;a href="http://emafund.org/" target="_blank"&gt;EMA Fund&lt;/a&gt; at the door - bring an extra $1**&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Did you resolve to “do more good” in the world?&lt;/b&gt; Join Socializing for Justice and make your New Year’s resolution count this year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet like-minded progressives and get connected to great social justice organizations in Boston&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Have you been lurking on SoJust?&lt;/i&gt; It’s time to meet the friendly faces of the group that’s grown to almost 1600 members, hosted 85+ events and fostered hundreds of connections since our founding 4 years ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us if you are ready to go BEYOND ALLIES and build a CROSS-ISSUE PROGRESSIVE MOVEMENT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; $2-$10 collected at the door. &lt;i&gt;Newcomers always welcomed!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;THIS IS NOT A MEETING - IT'S A FUN NETWORKING SOCIAL!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Program. No Speaker. Just Us. For Justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;As always we'll help you meet people - so no worries if you're new to SoJust&lt;/b&gt;, plus we'll have &amp;quot;I'M LOOKING FOR&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;ASK ME ABOUT&amp;quot; tags, a CATALYST CORNER staffed by our amazing STARZ (regular attendees), our wildly popular JOBS BOARD and ACTION STATIONS to make it even more likely you'll find the right connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WANT TO CROSS-PROMOTE YOUR EVENTS AND CAMPAIGNS?&lt;/b&gt; Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; Members are all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. Some just moved to Boston and others were born here. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;HEY ORGANIZERS!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers for the free lit table. ACTION STATIONS - if you have an action that can be done in 2 minutes (sign a petition) or within 2 weeks of the event (attend rally, stuff mass mailing) bring it so SoJusters can get connected to you and your work. This is not a typical tabling event, there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network! Email robbie@sojust.org for more information about the Action Stations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The venue is open to anyone over 18 (must be 21+ to enter after 7PM) and is physically accessible - elevator is at the back of the venue. Lir is across from the Hynes Convention Center. Parking near Lir is really hard - you could get lucky or you could drive around for 30 or more minutes. There are parking garages by Back Bay station. Best bet is to take the T to Back Bay or Hynes Convention Center (which is the closest T stop).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HELP SPREAD THE WORD!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Invite your friends to this facebook event: &lt;a href="http://www.fb.me/#!/event.php?eid=180796458603130" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fb.me/#!/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the SoJust Facebook group: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=8770189934" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Twitter? Follow &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/sojust" target="_blank"&gt;@SoJust&lt;/a&gt; and SoJust's Co-Founder &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/robbiesamuels" target="_blank"&gt;@RobbieSamuels&lt;/a&gt; #sojust&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;**Collection for &lt;a href="http://emafund.org/" target="_blank"&gt;EMA Fund&lt;/a&gt; at the door - bring an extra $1**&lt;/b&gt; Since 1999, the Eastern Massachusetts Abortion Fund (the EMA Fund) has helped over 4,000 women and families who couldn’t afford the cost of abortion care. And we have done it all without a single paid staff person, an office, or any corporate sponsorship. Can't attend? &lt;a href="https://www.networkforgood.org/donation/MakeDonation.aspx?ORGID2=043502604&amp;amp;vlrStratCode=ikte7ptBeiZU57MdtOF65oW4Nbryp%2f%2bfMLbBfjs3mgZA7Qdr5aZLlvoGVw%2fMcCSs" target="_blank"&gt;Donate online&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sojust.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SoJust is all about building a cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos. SoJust is NOT a non-profit 501(c)(3), we are a volunteer-run, member-driven, grassroots organization. We may seem like just another liberal social group but get involved to find out what we can create together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison Brill</member_name><member_id>4034719</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297276010000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>94</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292269842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecting for Justice (Open House)</name><id>15722820</id><headcount>112</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296169200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/15722820/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/5/global_18036709.jpeg</photo_url></item>