<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Who is Arlen Faber? He's the man who "redefined spirituality for an entire generation" in his bestselling book, Me and God. Who is he really? No one knows. For 20 years, fans and critics have dissected, adapted, and essentially deified his memoir of holy epiphany––all while hoping that he himself would emerge from obscurity to present himself in the flesh. But with godly credibility comes godly responsibility. Arlen's fans aren't looking for a few pithy sound bites about his creative process; they want the lord's sacred truth from an earthly mouthpiece. They want the answers to the mysteries of life. 

The real Arlen Faber (Jeff Daniels) is no spiritual hologram, but rather a middle-aged man with a sharp tongue and a bad back. The former introduces him to Kris (Lou Taylor Pucci), a young specialty-bookshop manager in the midst of an existential crisis. The latter introduces him to Elizabeth (Lauren Graham), a chiropractor and single mom who is running low on self-confidence. Neither can help but covet a peek at the secrets Arlen's mind might hold––even if he has spent the last 20 years burying them under his own prickly personality.
&lt;xobject width="445" height="364"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/oEGoGl-imw0&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1&amp;color1=0xe1600f&amp;color2=0xfebd01&amp;border=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="445" height="364" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lobby</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243272545000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239629253000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Anwser Man</name><id>10173802</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240681500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/10173802/</event_url></item>