<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Academy Way</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03851</zip><lat>43.442356</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Johnson Theatre in the Paul Creative Arts Center</name><city>Durham</city><id>1581362</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053101</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, Trailblazers!&amp;nbsp; Come enjoy a live show featuring a variety of dance styles.&amp;nbsp; Enjoy this combined childhood favorite and a&amp;nbsp;tribute to Martin Luther King, Jr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From March 30 to April 3, the UNH Dance Company will be performing its annual spring show with a combination of two pieces: an adaptation of "The Wizard of Oz" and "The Wounded Dove". &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These two shows have a cast totaling over 100 members, and each represent different styles of dance. "The Wizard of Oz" portion will feature jazz, tap, aerial, ballet, and modern dance, while "The Wounded Dove" will be primarily a ballet piece.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The Wounded Dove" is a faculty-created piece, featuring compositions by UNH music professor David Ripley, and choreographed by theatre and dance professor, C. Laurence Robertson. The two professors worked together as a part of the "Arts for Life" celebration, which emphasized collaborations between departments as part of the theme. The piece is credited as a tribute to Martin Luther King, Jr, and speaks of the struggle for freedom and identity, transition and rebirth. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The Wounded Dove" contains three separate pieces, titled "Turning Up Stones", "Dance Everlasting", and "Wounded Dove." There will also be an additional ballet piece accompanied on piano by Professors Christopher and Arlene Kies. As the UNH Dance Company dances to these pieces, Ripley will be singing his music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Here is a moment of collaboration that's happening spontaneously in this moment," said Ripley in an interview for the UNH Theatre and Dance podcast series. He and Robertson stressed the importance of the dancers responding to Ripley, and vice-versa, since his live interpretation of the music could possibly differ from the recording the company has been rehearsing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first act of the show will feature the classic tale of "The Wizard of Oz", adapted for the stage by senior, Brad Jensen. Jensen had the idea to tell this story two years ago, and suggested it to professor and choreographer, Gay Nardone, expecting her to scoff at the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Well, here we are!" said Jensen, who plays the Scarecrow. "Sure enough, I get to skip down the Yellow Brick Road my senior year, and I couldn't be happier."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cast members and choreographer Nardone agree that although the show is primarily aimed at children, adult audiences will also take something out of the show. Nardone says that this portion is a great opportunity for parents to bring their children to see live theatre. There is a matinee on April 2 at 2 p.m. for children to come dressed as their favorite character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The children will really appreciate the costumes, sights, and sounds of Oz, while the adults will appreciate the way in which we chose to tell the story," said Jensen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Adults will be brought back to their youth, singing and dancing along to the movie or reading a bedtime story with their parents," said Randy Blake, who plays the Cowardly Lion. "I believe the adults will walk away, hopefully, with a little bit more respect for their children's imagination and remember what it is like to be young and have wild dreams and fantasies once again."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cast of this show has been working for over five months and believes that all should see the show, since it holds something special for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"For the students of UNH, I think people will be surprised how much they enjoy their night in the theatre," said Jensen. "Leave the Keystone, TV, and bars for two hours and sit back and enjoy a live show!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Performances will be in the Johnson Theatre from March 30 to April 2 at 7 p.m. There will be additional matinees at 2 p.m. on April 2 and 3.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Tickets are $12.50, are general admission&amp;nbsp;and can be purchased the day of the show at the&amp;nbsp;Johnson Theatre (opens 1 hour before show) or in advance at the MUB Ticket Office (603-862-2290) Monday to Friday, 10 am to 4 pm, or&amp;nbsp;ordered online at&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.unhmub.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;www.unhmub.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM BOSTON: Take I-95 north from Boston to Exit 4 (N.H. Lakes and Mountain Region, Routes 4 and 16). Continue to Exit 6W and follow Route 4 West. Take 155A Exit. Make a left at the end of the ramp. Travel past Thompson Hall, the Memorial Union Building (MUB), and the bus stop and bear right onto Mill Road. Take your next right on Academic Way. Paul Creative Arts Center is next to the last building on the right.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM PORTLAND: Follow either I-95 or Route 1 south to Portsmouth traffic circle. Take Route 4 west and take Concord-Durham Exit 6W. Directions are then the same as those indicated from the Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM MANCHESTER: Take Route 101 East to Epping, Exit 7, Route 125. Take Route 125 north to the Lee Traffic Circle. Take Route 4 East to Durham and take the Exit 155A. Make a right at the end of the ramp. Directions are then the same as those indicated from the Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM CONCORD: Take Route 4 East to Durham and take the Exit 155A. Make a right at the end of the ramp. Directions are then the same as those indicated from the Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions just give me a call at 603-312-6735.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby of the Paul Creative Arts Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301702848000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's fun!</why><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301264950000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UNH Dance Company Spring Show</name><id>17078306</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301698800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/17078306/</event_url></item>