<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This hike will cover the southern most 14 miles of the Long Trail as well as the Pine Cobble Trail (a short Scenic trail which, together with a short stretch of the Massachusetts AT, provides the most direct access to the southern terminus of the Long Trail).   This trip covers several popular day hikes and traverses some splendid territory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;Totals for the two day trip are:  &lt;br /&gt;Distance: 17.7 miles &lt;br /&gt;Book Time: 11 hours of hiking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tentative plan is to meet at the AT/LT lot at 9:30AM, briefly review gear and plans and then, leaving some cars behind, drive to the Pine Cobble Trail head.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 1&lt;/b&gt;, we will hike 6.1 miles to the Seth Warner Shelter.  While we should not count on staying in the shelter (individuals and people traveling in ones and twos take precedence over larger groups), there is a reliable water source, an out house, and well used tent sites in the immediate vicinity.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book time for this hike is four hours, so we will have a leisurely first day with plenty of time to relax in the shade and sit out the mid-day heat if it turns out to be a hot one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day 2&lt;/b&gt;:    We will plan on a fairly early start (9AM or before, depending on what people want to do). Distance will be 11.6 miles and book time is 7 hours. Depending on conditions, we can stop at Congdon shelter for lunch, before hiking over Harmon Hill and finishing our trip. If time allows and people wish to do so, we could stop for a meal in Bennington, Williamstown or North Adams before going our separate ways.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;Trailhead: The parking area can be found on the north side of Vermont Rte 9 at Appalachian / Long Trail crossing.   The lot is 5.0 miles east from Bennington/Rt. 7,  15.8 miles west from Rt. 100.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NECESSARY GEAR:&lt;/b&gt; If you haven't done much back packing before and/or don't feel confident about your gear list, please send me an email and I'll email you recommended gear list. Also, please consult the Warm Weather Backpacking List (in the list section) and the 10 + 4 essentials list at &lt;a href="http://www.backpacking.net/ten-essl.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.backpackin...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One item I want to stress is something to treat water. Drinking untreated water on most trails carries a risk of infection. Your outfitter will be able to sell you chemicals and filters for water treatment purposes.&lt;br /&gt;If there is a key piece of gear you are lacking, please speak up. Someone might be able to share or lend you an item.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SHARING:&lt;/b&gt;  If people want to coordinate meals, sharing food, food preparation equipment and food chores, please feel free to make that known.   Otherwise, each person should be responsible for their own food. Some gear lends itself to sharing and sharing can reduce your pack weight and save you money (if you don't own it already), for example water filters, stoves, and tents.  Please post your interest if you want to coordinate with someone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CARPOOLING:&lt;/b&gt;   Ride Sharing is encouraged. Please comment if you are in need of a ride, or have a car and are willing to share.   My wife and I (and our dog) will have room for two more people.  We'll be leaving from the Porter/Davis area near the Cambridge Somerville line in Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave's Disclaimer:   Even though I have done a lot of backpacking and have taken friends and family on many backpacking trips, I've never led an organized group on a backpacking trip.  I have no special training or expertise in backpacking safety.  While I may be full of opinions and advice about backpacking, gear and the Long Trail and enjoy sharing ideas (I volunteer as a Long Trail mentor for the GMC), I really only know what works for me.  Your thoughtful independent judgment is the most important piece of equipment you can bring on the trip as I need to be able to trust and rely on your preparation, good sense and ability to take care of yourself on the trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/170/members/4566112/"&gt;QUESTIONS?  CONTACT: David&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers must rsvp. Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that your late or lost. With a small group your response may make or break the event.  Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into groups, or if there is an injury.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that you are qualified to join us on this hike.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for David/PedXing and his wife. They are the organizers of this two day trip. http://hiking.meetup.com/170/members/4566112

Green Mountain National Forest
Southern Vermont
Vermont Route 9, AT/LT Parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214851034000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Vermont's Long Trail is a beautiful trail.  The southern stretch coincides with the Appalachian Trail and is far gentler and much easier than the northern reaches of the trail.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213133441000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Taste Of The Long Trail June 28-29</name><id>8118166</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214661600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8118166/</event_url></item>