<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Building E51, Room 315</address_2><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Sloan School of Management</name><city>Cambridge </city><id>1010762</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event will feature a presentation by Eytan Levy at the MIT Sloan School of Management (E52-175).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Levy is the Co-Founder and CEO of &lt;a href="http://www.emefcy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Emefcy&lt;/a&gt;, an Israel-based startup with a vision of fundamentally changing the energy economics of wastewater treatment. The systems developed by Emefcy produce electricity directly from the treatment of different types of wastewater. This conversion is made possible by use of microbial fuel cell (MFC) technology.  Emefcy raised a first round of financing from &lt;a href="http://www.israelcleantech.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Israel Cleantech Ventures&lt;/a&gt; in 2007. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Levy will share lessons learned from his experience as a serial cleantech entrepreneur.  He will also discuss the process of taking a startup from idea stage to a successful international company.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A campus map of MIT is available at &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is sponsored by the &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/misti/mit-israel/" target="_blank"&gt;MISTI - MIT Israel program&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/sjso/www/" target="_blank"&gt;Sloan Jewish Student Organization (SJSO)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eytan Levy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eytan began his career as a sales manager at Ormat, Israel’s most successful alternative energy company. He continued his work in the power generation sector as Vice President of Infrastructure at Delta, a supplier of capital equipment for the power generation and environmental industries. While at Delta, Eytan worked closely with the Israel Electric Corporation on acquisition and integration of new power generation systems. In 2000 he joined his college classmate Ronen Schechter to found AqWise, leading that company from inception stage to its position as a recognized leader in advanced biological wastewater treatment. While CEO of AqWise, Eytan led the company’s successful entry into the waste water treatment market, building strategic relationships with integrators and key market participants. Eytan is an active Venture Partner at Israel Cleantech Ventures, Israel’s first cleantech focused venture capital fund. Eytan holds a BSc (cum laude) in Chemical Engineering from the Technion – Israel Institute of Technology, and an MBA in International Marketing from Bar-Ilan University.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236896221000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233614992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Water, Energy, and Entrepreneurship: an Israeli Case Study </name><id>9657295</id><headcount>54</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235689200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/9657295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/5/global_7171461.jpeg</photo_url></item>