<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>695 Hillside Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.213108</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-698-1802</phone><name>Blue Hills Reservation</name><city>Milton</city><id>908716</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*****WEATHER LOOKS BAD ON SATURDAY, MOVED TO SUNDAY*****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So we did this back in April and it was a great little hike and I'm ready to do it again! We'll do the skyline loop, which is described as the following from the blue hills website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Skyline Loop 3 miles&lt;br /&gt;(1.5 to 2.5 hours) challenging&lt;br /&gt;Blue Blazes&lt;br /&gt;This popular loop trail crosses several&lt;br /&gt;summits offering panoramic views. The&lt;br /&gt;highlight of the hike is Great Blue Hill, the&lt;br /&gt;highest peak on the Atlantic coast south of&lt;br /&gt;Maine. The North Skyline Trail begins at&lt;br /&gt;Reservation Headquarters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It says challenging, but its all relative. Its definitely hilly terrain but the highest elevation is 635 feet so its not like we're climbing a mountain.  If we feel like it we can take a short detour off the skyline trail that leads to the trailside museum and visit my buddy the river otter. Make sure to bring water and a trail snack with you as we'll be out and about for a couple of hours. Meet at the Reservation Headquarters and look for my bright yellow Ford Escape with RI plates. Note that there are two parking lots right near each other, one for Houghtons pond and one for the headquarters, we'll be at the headquarters.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the bright yellow escape or call my cell 508 414 8544.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258477863000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257818225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills</name><id>11837597</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258300800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/11837597/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>