<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Djleswho, One of our members suggested this event,&lt;br /&gt;It looks pretty good to me..:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anybody is interested there is a Singles Picnic at the First &lt;br /&gt;Church of Christ in Wethersfield, CT 06109 this upcoming &lt;br /&gt;Friday. Aug 24th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm to 10:00pm, be a outside cook out. If rains will be &lt;br /&gt;moved inside (last year it rained and the DJ turned it into a &lt;br /&gt;dance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opened to all faiths and non-faiths, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hot Dogs/Burgers/Beverages included, may bring a side dish to &lt;br /&gt;share - No alcoholic beverages or smoking allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5.00 if bring a side dish, $7.00 if bring none&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There be fellowship, chance to meet new people, there be a DJ &lt;br /&gt;playing music. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adult aged singles, 18 and older, single, divorced, widow. &lt;br /&gt;legally separated,  unmarried couples.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if have no plans come on down, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to First Church of Christ&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;250 Main Street &lt;br /&gt;Wethersfield, Connecticut 06109 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are located in the heart of Old Wethersfield - the large brick church with the tall white spire, just off I-91. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 North:&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 26 off I-91 and turn left at end of exit ramp. Turn left again at stop sign. Pass entrance to highway and turn left at the T-intersection onto Marsh Street. Wind around the cemetery on your right and you'll see First Church. Make a right at the stop sign onto Main Street. Parking lot is just past church on the right. Main entrance to church is in parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 South:&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 26 off I-91 and turn right at end of exit ramp. Make your first left onto Marsh Street. Wind around the cemetery on your right and you'll see First Church. Make a right at the stop sign onto Main Street. Parking lot is just past church on the right. Main entrance to church is in parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 9: &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 to CT-175 EAST (Newington). Stay on 175 for 5.87 miles all the way to the church! (Name changes from Cedar Street in Newington to Wells Road and then Main Street in Wethersfield.) When you cross the Silas Deane Highway (Rt. 99), you'll enter Old Wethersfield. First Church is about 3/4 miles down on the right. Parking lot is just past church on the right. Main entrance to church is in parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention GPS Users&lt;br /&gt;First Church Location is:&lt;br /&gt;Lat: 41.71352 N; Long: 72.65268 W&lt;br /&gt;or just type in the real address for garmins and others...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AL's comment: I have been waiting for a dance..was going to post the In-Famous Gallery..but this looks better ...&lt;br /&gt;maybe the end of summer holiday will be the Gallery for the rest of you...LOl.....&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188167623000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187650939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Picnic and Most Likely Dance, Wethersfield, CT</name><id>6214573</id><headcount>64</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187994600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6214573/</event_url></item>