<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NT Live has added an additional 5th presentation to their inaugural season! LONDON ASSURANCE by Dion Boucicault.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The live simulcast presentation sold out well in advance of performance [trust me -- I found out the hard way].  Tickets still remain for the encore performance, buy yours now to guarantee a seat - there may not be any for walk-up sales!  &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/ntlive" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 general admission/$17 Coolidge members [I bought mine just this afternoon online, so you may still be in luck].&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the play:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sir Harcourt Courtly is lured away from the epicentre of fashionable London by the promise of a rich and beautiful bride, Grace, several decades his junior. Arriving at Oak Hall, Gloucestershire, he marvels at this rural Venus until her charms are eclipsed by her hearty cousin, the foxhunting Lady Gay Spanker. Meanwhile his disguised son turns up in flight from his creditors and falls head over heels for Grace. When Lady Spanker discovers the young couple, she needs little prompting from the visiting chancer Dazzle to lead Sir Harcourt astray.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dion Boucicault, the Irish genius of London theatre in the age of Dickens, wrote the brilliantly funny London Assurance in 1841 and thereby created – in Sir Harcourt and Lady Spanker – two of the great comic roles of the English stage, played at the NT by Simon Russell Beale and Fiona Shaw.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at Panera Bread at 6pm and go to the theater after a quick bite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the Panera Bread across the street from the Coolidge with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278555244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Theatre Live: London Assurance</name><id>14035925</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279144800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14035925/</event_url></item>