<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Redstone Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.801041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rave Motion Pictures Buckland Hills</name><city>Manchester</city><id>664343</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.547752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Is IOUSA a breakthrough movie on the state of our country or a CFR propaganda film? The debate rages and there's only one way to find out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IOUSA will premier across the country at 8PM the 21st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I.O.U.S.A.&amp;quot; examines the rapidly growing national debt and its consequences for the United States and its citizens. As the Baby Boomer generation prepares to retire, will there even be any Social Security benefits left to collect? Burdened with an ever-expanding government and military, increased international competition, overextended entitlement programs, and debts to foreign countries that are becoming impossible to honor, America must mend its spendthrift ways or face an economic disaster of epic proportions. Throughout history, the American government has found it nearly impossible to spend only what has been raised through taxes. Wielding candid interviews with both average American taxpayers and government officials, director Patrick Creadon helps demystify the nation’s financial practices and policies. The film follows U.S. Comptroller General David Walker as he crisscrosses the country explaining America’s unsustainable fiscal policies to its citizens. Creadon interweaves archival footage and economic data to paint a vivid and alarming profile of America’s current economic situation. The ultimate power of &amp;quot;I.O.U.S.A.&amp;quot; is that the film moves beyond doomsday rhetoric to proffer potential financial scenarios and propose solutions about how we can recreate a fiscally sound nation for future generations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.iousathemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.iousathemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.iousathemo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet outside 15 minutes prior. Look for the Ron Paul shirts!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Searles</member_name><member_id>4735307</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219536427000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218137015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IOUSA Premier</name><id>8498441</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219363200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/8498441/</event_url></item>