<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>294 Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.551907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-922-0004</phone><name>Organic Garden Cafe</name><city>Beverly</city><id>598589</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.879082</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Just because it's Raw, Doesn't mean its healthful&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Please show up at 9 AM or so. The speaker will start at 9:30 AM. This event will end by 11 AM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know there are no raw labeling laws?  Many things being sold as “raw” may not be raw, and may not be as healthy as we have been led to believe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· John will share with you his raw food healing journey, how he healed himself of complement immune deficiency (chronically weak immune system)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· John will also share his knowledge on healthful raw food and not-so-healthful raw food ways of eating. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· After attending this talk, you will know how to determine if a “raw” food is healthful or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Learn his secrets on how to obtain the highest level of health and learn how to choose the best foods to eat.  Over the past 15 years John has researched and refined his raw diet to be as healthy as possible and has a deep desire to share his experience and knowledge with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Learn more about how John converted his suburban front lawn to an edible estate and grows the majority of his vegetables year round on only 1/10th of an acre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Kohler has been on the living and raw foods diet since 1995; he turned to living foods for healing from a life threatening-illness (spinal meningitis) and has enjoyed dynamic health ever since. The focus of his research has been in the area of obtaining the highest level of health. One of John’s goals is to educate the world about the power of living and raw foods. He is the founder and creator of the largest living and raw food website on the internet, &lt;a href="http://www.rawfoods.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.RawFoods.com&lt;/a&gt;.  John is also the founder of the Raw Health Expo in California, &lt;a href="http://www.rawhealthexpo.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.RawHealthExpo.com&lt;/a&gt;.  John also owns and manages &lt;a href="http://www.discountjuicers.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.DiscountJuicers.com&lt;/a&gt; and is the number one expert on raw food’s appliances and gadgets in the world. His latest projects are &lt;a href="http://www.growingyourgreens.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.GrowingYourGreens.com&lt;/a&gt; where he teaches people how to grow food in their front yard.  John recently started a new site &lt;a href="http://www.okraw.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.OkRaw.com&lt;/a&gt; where you can learn from his wealth of raw food knowledge.  He is widely sought out and regularly speaks and instructs at many raw food festivals and events. His area of expertise include recipe demos with 5-7 ingredients or less, young coconut recipes, traveling while raw, raw food appliances and successful transition to the raw foods diet. He believes that by using only a few fresh, organic, and whole ingredients simple, healthy, and tasteful recipes can be made.  He is known for his pragmatic approach to raw foods and has coached and helped thousands of people to incorporate more fresh raw fruits and vegetables into their diet. John currently lives in Northern California.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rawbert</member_name><member_id>11144266</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287527207000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286410900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>John Kohler @ Rawbert's Organic Garden (FREE Talk)</name><id>15028341</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287321300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/15028341/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/1/global_18541905.jpeg</photo_url></item>