<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Whipple Dr.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02813</zip><lat>41.436829</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>American Legion Downey-Weaver Post 34</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>13581492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.636703</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/c/event_238924412.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please consider joining Rhode Island Oath Keepers as we show our great appreciation for the sacrifices made to secure our freedoms this Memorial Day May 27. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Rhode Island Oath Keepers outreach float will be part of the Richmond/Carolina Memorial Day parade again this year.  We are looking for a few veterans to ride in a place of honor on the float. (Please contact me ASAP) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be mustering at 08:00  (8 a.m. sharp) at the American Legion " Downey-Weaver Post 34" - 22 Whipple Dr., Charlestown, RI, 02813 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 These parades have turned out to be very rewarding experiences and great outreach opportunities. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The parade will start at the Richmond/Carolina fire Department, 208 Richmond Townhouse Rd, Carolina, RI 02812.  It will proceed south on Route 112 for about a mile and half and consist of two short Memorial Day ceremonies with a 21 gun salute.  (Refreshments to be served afterwards at the American Legion Post) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring lots of Flags, Friends and Family &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Some are asking about a dress code, there is no "absolute" dress code but respectful attire is suggested.  Oath Keeper hats and shirts or just a white shirt) with black pants would be fine. American military uniforms from colonial to present day would be great. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 (National Oath Keepers T-shirts and the new Rhode Island Oath Keepers T-shirts will be available at the start.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Stand up and Sign up Now! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please leave enthusiastic RSVP's, Great testimonials from previous parades or excuses below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Rhode Island Oath Keepers Parade Float...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Swanson</member_name><member_id>9165041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369667661000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers</urlname><id>1425841</id><group_lat>41.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369260235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Oath Keepers at Memorial Day parade</name><id>120738162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369656000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers/events/120738162/</event_url></item>