<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(grey bldg on right at you face high school)</address_2><address_1>345 Ocean House Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04107</zip><lat>43.591783</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207-229-2611 (LisaF's cell phone</phone><name>Cape Elizabeth Community Services Building</name><city>Cape Elizabeth</city><id>1225990</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.226671</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>early bird until Feb 21</description><amount>49.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a repeat of a very successful event we held last year, a local version of the popular MOFGA grafting workshops....&lt;b&gt;Learn fruit tree grafting AND take home ten heirloom fruit trees&lt;/b&gt; from your efforts during the workshop!!! (And compared to the cost of buying 10 trees, this is a really good deal!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://capeelizabethfarms.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Co-sponsored by the Cape Farm Alliance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Learn to propagate and reproduce your favorite fruit tree varieties&lt;/b&gt;. Instructors Jennifer Ries and Bennett Verbeck of Whiffletree Nursery will explain why to graft and demonstrate the techniques for Whip &amp;amp; Tongue and T-Budding (indoors) of new trees as well as Top-working (outdoors) of established trees. This class is hands-on and participants will graft stock to take home and plant. Care for seedlings will be discussed. Also, time permitting, we will look at spring orchard care and basic pruning techniqes. Please bring a sharp &lt;b&gt;grafting knife&lt;/b&gt;*, a bag lunch, and clothing appropriate for potentially wet or cold weather. Course will run from 10-4 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coffee/tea/water will be provided throughout the day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;$49 per person if you register and pay before Feb 21&lt;/b&gt;.  $59 after that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fee includes all supplies&lt;/b&gt; including rootstocks, scionwood, grafting tape, treekote, labels, sharpies, rags, etc.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Grafting knives will be available for sale ($20-25 range) if you do not have one of your own.  Handouts provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Jennifer and Bennett live on a small farm in Brooks, Maine.  They make a living at their Whiffletree Nursery for which they graft trees and propagate fruiting shrubs and ornamentals.  They grow their own food and meat and use a draft horse for farm work. Bennett began grafting over 20 years ago and made his living exclusively from nursery work and homesteading for many years.  Jen began grafting about six years ago.  Besides homesteading and growing trees, Jen works for Fedco Trees and guides wilderness trips.  Bennett works on boats and is preparing to sail around the world.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comments from last year's class:&lt;br /&gt;“ excellent instructors great at answering questions and returning to their 'lecture' well prepared materials enthusiastic and interesting attentive to providing one-on-one instruction during the grafting phase ...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ I thought the tree grafting workshop was great! The instructors were very knowledgeable, the atmosphere of the old barn was fun and it was a a nice group of people.... I learned a lot. ” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ Wonderful experience! Bennett worked with me until he helped me find a way to use a right handed knire left-handedly! It was very exciting to then be able to actually graft apple trees!! ” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ The experts were truly experts - That's very important for me. The materials provided were excellent (wide selection of scions, heatlthy root stock. Can't ask for anything more than this. Thanks to the organizers. ” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ It was excellent! Loved the fact that we had time to practice with the experts. It helped gain confidence in the technique. Might be fun do to a followup with some other techniques.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be upstairs to the left in the "Community Room"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278433538000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265317393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop: Fruit Tree Grafting + 10 Tree "Take Home"</name><id>12520787</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269698400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/12520787/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/3/global_6681155.jpeg</photo_url></item>