<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.368390</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-972-6431</phone><name>Watertown Free Public Library</name><city>Watertown</city><id>669410</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.187158</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Successful Anonymous is looking forward to being a reliant, consistent, useful tool for its members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at 123 Main St. Watertown, MA 02472 at The Watertown Free Library in the Lucia Mastrangelo Meeting Room on the 2nd Floor on Tuesday March 9th, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;7:00pm - 7:30pm --&amp;gt; Networking&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm - 8:00pm --&amp;gt; Introductions&lt;br /&gt;8:00pm - 8:30pm --&amp;gt; Open Forum Discussion&lt;br /&gt;8:45pm - 9:00pm --&amp;gt; Takeaways and Cool Down&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever thought about what makes people successful? How do they make the most of each day and reach their potential? How do they 'take their foot off the brake'? Why do some people acheive their goals while others seem to continue to struggle? Are you looking to surround yourself with people who are motivated, determined, and focused on achieving and exceeding, both personally and professionally?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our mission at 'Successful Anonymous' is to bring together like-minded people from around the Boston area, who share a desire to reach their full potential. The group environment will promote business networking, relationship-building, discussions, open forum, and much more. Business Networking allows individuals to align themselves with people who can help with the growth of their professional network. Often times this may appeal to entrepreneurs, though in reality, we 'Success Addicts' are able to help anyone and everyone work towards accomplishing their goals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been hosting our Meet Ups in Watertown at the Watertown Free Library, though we are open to suggestions for facilities in Cambridge, Newton, Brighton, or Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;S.A. is focused on growth and development via networking, and we are always open to feedback from our members.If you have any feedback, questions, or concerns, do not hesitate to contact us via MeetUp or via e-mail at VandDPartnership@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out our Discussion Board!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/messages/boards/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;^^^ CLICK HERE ^^^ &lt;br /&gt;Post your LinkedIn, Facebook or Twitter HTMLS and discuss topics for our next MeetUp!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Become a Fan on Facebook: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Successful-Anonymous-Networking-Discussions/203818834866?ref=ts#/pages/Successful-Anonymous-Networking-Discussions/203818834866?ref=mf"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>2nd Floor in the meeting room. Any questions, ask the Librarians :o)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dimitry</member_name><member_id>10566344</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270592002000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Success Addicts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>successfulanonymous</urlname><id>1551084</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Successful Anonymous</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266523739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Successful Anonymous: Networking &amp; Discussions - Tuesday March 9th at 7PM </name><id>12640326</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268179200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/events/12640326/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/c/global_11630172.jpeg</photo_url></item>