<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>online</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>online</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12073022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Register - &lt;a href="http://www2.appnovation.com/l/16832/2013-03-03/4tvrq" class="linkified"&gt;http://www2.appnovation.com/l/16832/2013-03-03/4tvrq&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Live Webcast: The Website Redesign Project - 14 Key Concepts to ensure a smooth redesign web development project. &lt;br /&gt;

Working at a company that builds websites we get this question all the time, “When should a business update or redesign it’s website?” Well there are several factors one needs to consider such as: the number of visitors, where they are going when visiting and how long they staying; what kind of conversion rate is the site getting; what kind of functionality is your business getting from the site; is the site integrated with your other marketing activities; and, how does your site compare to competitors (aka, does your site look dated or ugly). During this webcast, we are going to cover the several major concepts that are related to ensuring a smooth redesign project. Some topics include: Technology considerations; Business Analysis and User Experience; Design Trends; Development and Architecture; and, Quality Assurance. Register - &lt;a href="http://www2.appnovation.com/l/16832/2013-03-03/4tvrq" class="linkified"&gt;http://www2.appnovation.com/l/16832/2013-03-03/4tvrq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365627828000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising</urlname><id>984032</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Internet Marketing and Advertising  Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362443361000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Website Redesign Project</name><id>107630222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365616800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising/events/107630222/</event_url></item>