<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Lang Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.899410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>664559</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702910</lon></venue><fee><label>Adult $2 / Child $1</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>FREE PARKING</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is NO LONGER a call for volunteers (although still accepted!), but simply an announcement of an inexpensive, family-friendly &amp;quot;Country Fair&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A one-day afFAIR, THIS SATURDAY, September 29, 10AM to 4PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an old-fashioned Country Fair (hay wagon &amp;amp; pony rides, flower, veggie, art, and baking competitions, box lunch auction, various crafters &amp;amp; demonstrations, w/ lots of food, etc., but it is alcohol-free and there are no noisy amusement park rides.  This is a non-profit fundraiser (all food, etc. proceeds are donated) that exposes this jewel of a nature park to the public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Admission is only $2/Adults and $1/Kids, parking is free, and most activities &amp;amp; competitions are free, or charge a nominal fee to cover expenses.  Whether volunteering or not, feel free to enjoy this very inexpensive, fun, and wholesome event with your kids or grandkids!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of particular interest to young children (pre-K through Grade 8), I Chair the *Kid's Fun &amp;amp; Games* aspect of the Fair:  Pumpkin Carving &amp;amp; Pumpkin Decorating, Bubble Wands, Treasure Hunt in the Hay Stacks, Bead Jewelry making, &amp;quot;Fishing&amp;quot; Pond, Greased (soapy)Pole climb, etc., as well as competitions for pre-K through Middle School: Pie-Eating, Sack Race, 3-Legged Race, Water-Balloon toss, and *Tug-O-War* over Mud Pit!  Following these FREE competitions, I award prizes for ALL participants and extra gifts and ribbons to the top three competitors of each event.  I've organized a great team of Volunteers to ensure these events run safely and smoothly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a BEAUTIFUL day to enjoy with your young children or grand-children... there's pleanty of fun for adults, too - especially if you enjoy Crafters, eating, music, a wholesome ambiance, taking great photos, and 500 acres of hiking trails!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No need to RSVP - just show up!  (Unless volunteering, then email me directly).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmest Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northwest Park is located at 145 Lang Road in Windsor, Connecticut 06095.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northwestpark.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191259958000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189400119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northwest Park Country Fair - WINDSOR</name><id>6328544</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191074400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6328544/</event_url></item>