<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>92 Worcester Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.296471</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-875-3115</phone><name>The Melting Pot</name><city>Framingham</city><id>669195</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.399246</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I know it's short notice but, it's fondue!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is for those who need an excuse to experience the decadent dining experience of fondue at The Melting Pot, as well as for all of us that are constantly craving just such an excuse :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Melting Pot is throwing 3 charitable events in the coming weeks, in which you can get a 4 course meal, including chocolate fondue for dessert for only $50.00.  And what's even sweeter, 15 of those sweet deal bucks can be used towards your tax break charitable contributions.  Nice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week, we'll be helping out the multiple sclerosis foundation and will be heading to The Melting Pot Framingham, a favorite stomping grounds on Rte 9 (look for the Jordan's furniture parking lot as your hint to turn). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details and directions available on their website:&lt;a href="http://www.meltingpot.com/locations.aspx?z=02857&amp;amp;n=423393" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meltingpot...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It also happens to be 80's night, so if you're up for pulling out those legwarmers, you can dress up and vie for the prize of a $50 gift certificate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If folks are interested, and budgets and waistlines allow, we may head to the Providence location for their Alzheimer's charity dinner on Thursday, March 5th.  Please email me directly (doclmeet@yahoo.com)  if you have an interest in attending on the 5th. Will post separately depending on interest.  Details and directions available at their providence website:&lt;a href="http://www.meltingpot.com/locations.aspx?z=02857&amp;amp;n=423393" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meltingpot...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Currently reservations for Framingham are for 6, but depending on interest, this may change.  Based on the short notice, no maybe's will be allowed.   We will be meeting at 7 pm sharp.  I'll be sending my cell phone number to those that reply &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; for last minute updates, but official RSVPs will be closed at 10 pm tomorrow night.  Spontaneous Beantowner's unite!! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email me with any questions or concerns&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see ya there!&lt;br /&gt;  Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be meeting in the bar area, just inside the front door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235933328000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235407840000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Melting Pot Benefit Event for Multiple Sclerosis</name><id>9803573</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235606400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/9803573/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>