<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02148</zip><lat>42.427130</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-322-0474</phone><name>First Parish in Malden, Universalist</name><city>Malden</city><id>803632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076878</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;h2&gt;Come One - Come All! &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be creating sacred space and sharing in the energies of our connection.  Whether you are an experienced drummer or just starting out, there is space for you in our circle.  And what would a circle be without dancers?  So come and join us for this joyous celebration of life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3:00pm Open Drumming &lt;/b&gt; - Bring your drums, rattles, Native American flutes, digeridoos, etc.  We will open up the room and get it rocking with the rhythms.  There will be space made for both heart-pounding beats and softer rhythms with room for voices and instruments.  There will be some instruments available for borrow, but it would be best in the beginning if everyone brings what they have so we are certain to have enough to go around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;4:00pm Mid-Circle Break&lt;/b&gt; - We'll take a break at roughly the half-way mark to allow people to introduce themselves and say what they bring to the container.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;5:00pm - Closing Circle&lt;/b&gt; - We'll close the space as we opened it with a circling up of the participants and a closing of the energy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost: &lt;/b&gt; Suggested Donation is $7, but give what you can.  Donations will go to cover the costs of maintaining this Meetup group, obtaining and repairing instruments, and the costs of electricity and heat for the church.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have instruments to share, please bring them!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've gotten a lot of new people involved in drumming and not many of them have their own drums yet.  So if you have extra drums, rattles and the like that you're willing to share, please bring them with you to the circle.  Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The First Parish in Malden, a Unitarian Universalist congregation, is located three blocks west of the Malden Center T station at 2 Elm Street (intersection with Pleasant Street), just off Route 60. Convenient, free parking is available between the church and the Beebe Elementary School. Visit MaldenUUA.org for directions and map. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We run this event once each month on the third Sunday of the month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelle Sparta</member_name><member_id>1953058</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287452517000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Rhythm Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-drum-circle</urlname><id>617617</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285596400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Drum and Dance Monthly Meetup</name><id>14909537</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287342000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-drum-circle/events/14909537/</event_url></item>