<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;Yipes 62 people have already signed up through the Boston Sci Fi/Fantasy Group! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don't miss out come to an awesome Halloween Party in Davis Square!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you like dressing up and acting silly around Halloween? Did you hear about or go to the party last year?  It was awesome!  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/d/6/event_165857622.jpeg" width="276" height="233" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My boyfriend talked me into dressing up like Bugs Bunny.  He dressed up like Elmer Fudd and kept telling me it was Wabbit Season and pointing a plastic gun at me.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won't tell you what we are doing this year...you will have to come and see in person...but I guarantee that it will be silly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come with your fellow nerds and members of the Boston Sci-Fi &amp;amp; Fantasy Group to this year's party on October 27th!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #c76924 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note it is $25 and you must prepay for yourself and any pluses you are bringing in order to be on the guest list.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Party Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food: &lt;/strong&gt; Food is being catered by Putterham Grille and Catering. We'll have a spread of appetizers including Cheese, Fruit, Veggies and Dip, and Chips and Salsa. The dinner menu will consist of a choice of four hot Italian entrees (Cheese Lasagna w/Meat Sauce, Vegetarian Lasagna, and Chicken with Mushroom and Alfredo Sauce (Gluten-Free)), served buffet style with Garden Salad and Hot Rolls. Oh, of course, we'll have desserts and Halloween Candy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drinks:&lt;/strong&gt; A full cash bar will be on site, and their drinks are cheap! Pricing last year was $2.00 for water/soda/juice, $3.75 for most domestic beers and wine, $4.25 to $4.75 for single liquor drinks and imported beers, $5.50 for two liquor drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costume contest:&lt;/strong&gt; First place is $100, second place is $75, third place is $50, so come in costume and be prepared to compete! There is no "theme" for the party or the contest, so let your imagination run wild.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; The Dilboy VFW is located a short walking distance from the Davis Square T stop, but it also has a private parking lot that we will be able to use (it is surrounded by a chain-link fence, is well lit, and there are clear signs to lead you to it). Please note that the front entrance to the VFW will not be accessible for this event, so you must enter at the back (where the parking lot is). We'll have signs outside in case you get lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do I Have to Prepay:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #c76924"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Since I know people will ask if it is possible to not pre-pay and pay in person on the night of the party, the answer is no, unless we have not sold out, and we'll announce that change if it happens before the event.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see a lot of you there...let's show them how creative Nerds can be about costumes! &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter the back door of the building go up the stairs and follow the signs and noise to the party.  :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1351468353000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349437714000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nerd Fun &amp; Boston Sci-Fi &amp; Fantasy Group Halloween Party and Costume Contest</name><id>85629422</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351378800000</time><rsvp_limit>32</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/85629422/</event_url></item>