<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 William T Morrissey Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.316437</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Boston Circle Lawn</name><city>Boston</city><id>5706192</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.039902</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2 day, 39-mile Avon Breast Cancer Walk in Boston:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday May 19th &amp;amp; Sunday May 20th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.avonwalk.org/boston/"&gt;www.avonwalk.org/boston/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.avonwalk.org/boston/event-information.html"&gt;www.avonwalk.org/boston/event-information.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winding through Boston’s charming streets is a perfect way to experience the city’s epic history. Take in beautiful views from the shores of Boston’s famous harbor and enjoy its lovely neighborhoods, like Back Bay. You’ll experience Boston Common and stroll along the shores of the Charles River. On Day 1 we'll walk 26.2 miles, followed by 13.1 miles on Day 2. The walk begins at the University of Massachusetts, goes to the Reebok World Headquarters and returns back to the University. The walk route to and from UMass Boston and the Wellness Village will consist mostly of sidewalks and city streets. There may be occasions where the route will take us through some of Boston’s beloved parks and bike paths. The route itself will be clearly marked with directional signage and other markings. There is also a route support team called ‘the Sweep Team,’ who are available to help you while you are on the road between Quick Stops and Rest Stops. Overall, the route will give you a look at some historical, commercial, and residential neighborhoods, and is designed to be safe, fun and interesting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337568028000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329335559000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>39-mile Breast Cancer Walk in Boston</name><id>52481342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337425200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/52481342/</event_url></item>