<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Spotted Cow is a locally brewed WI ale, and has a beautiful smooth taste. When I was in Milwaukee, I was introduced to this by the locals and somehow I was hooked to it so much. From my last trip to Milwaukee I have some 20bottles of this beer with me and who else to share this with, other than beer lovers from this group!! This is a special beer and not available in New England area for sure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is an Brazilian restaurant downstairs, which can supply food for the night. Mostly sandwiches, pizza etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll also throw in a &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bollywood movie/songs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; to lighten up the evening, if some people prefer to watch a new genre of movie. I have a bunch of them, so may be we can decide on this one that night, what the group will be interested to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; Drinks and Movie is no cost to you, of course. No obligation to drink beer, I can get wine, other beers on request, there is a liquor store downstairs ;). Also some non-alcoholic beverages will also be there to choose from. Only food cost is shared!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;VENUE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;379 Broadway Apt 10&lt;br /&gt;Somerville MA 02145&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to reach there: Either take orange line to &lt;b&gt;Sullivan&lt;/b&gt; or Red Line to &lt;b&gt;Davis Sq&lt;/b&gt;. Take bus &lt;b&gt;89&lt;/b&gt;, this bus runs from Sullivan to Davis Sq stn. Get down at the &lt;b&gt;'Main St'&lt;/b&gt; bus stop and the apartment is right on the Broadway and Main St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tapas</member_name><member_id>9229009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1254096580000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253621450000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spotted Cow Night- (Special Wisconsin Beer)</name><id>11435338</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253835000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/11435338/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/c/global_10847980.jpeg</photo_url></item>