<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Update: we will be hiking Mt Garfield, roughly 10 miles with one of the most spectacular views of the Pemi wilderness at the top and a nice even grade most of the way. We will be meeting at the western entrance to the Gale River Road (which I'm seeing listed as the Gale River Trail on google maps). Basically you will want to take 93 until you get past Franconia notch, then take the exit onto Rt 3 and the Gale River rd/trail is the first real road on your right. It should take about 2 and a half hours to get there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So when I posted the Blueberry stumble ( &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/18970991/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/18970991/&lt;/a&gt;) a couple of my friends saw it and said "hey I want to go on a hike like that one!", so that's what this is... except without the blueberries, because those aren't in season yet. Ice cream can be negotiated...&amp;nbsp;silliness&amp;nbsp;is not optional!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No prior hiking experience is required, but if not you must be in good shape, this isn't going to be a kiddy hike, you have to be in shape to hike and laugh at the same time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not make plans to be in town that evening, sometimes the group doesn't move quickly and I can't promise we will be down at any particular time... and really, why would you want to rush the hike? so the fun ends earlier?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm not putting a list of things to bring because I'm lazy and I'm going to assume you already know (even though I know better), please contact me if you have any questions about what to bring.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pete</member_name><member_id>4010848</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>10</waitlist_count><updated>1308798542000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307050003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stumble light (sans blueberries) - Beginner/Intermediate</name><id>20735781</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308402000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/20735781/</event_url></item>