<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>289 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-788-9988</phone><name>Back Pages Bookstore Gallery (2nd Floor)</name><city>Waltham</city><id>801617</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236929</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Noam Chomsky has been very hostile to anyone that asks a question regarding the unresolved questions about 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We suggest you show up with a video camera and a great question and put it on the web.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google &amp;quot;Chomsky 9/11&amp;quot; or anything like that to find his dismal responses to the questions we are all asking about 9/11. Who knows you may even get your footage in an upcoming wearechange.org movie if it is good enough. do you have what it takes to get the job done?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noam Chomsky discusses his book &lt;b&gt;Inventions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Editorial Reviews&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From &lt;b&gt;Publishers Weekly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though sometimes distracted by topics like Hurricane Katrina or South America, the essays in Chomsky's latest, written for the New York Times Syndicate between September 2002 and July '06, are largely concerned with Iraq, seen through the combative, populist (though by no means popular) convictions that the linguist and activist has become known for. His long-standing criticism of Israel makes it the next-most discussed topic; he accuses Israel of kidnapping and killing civilians and wonders why no has yet called for a Desert Storm-style invasion of the Jewish state. Though he clearly represents a voice unfettered by elitist concerns, tainted money or fear of reprisal, what comes through most strongly-indeed, what drives his arguments-isn't special insight into the issues at hand, but simple disgust with American imperialism and hypocrisy. Many pieces have been rendered irrelevant by events (though Chomsky offers footnoted updates), and he's no prose stylist. Few newspaper or magazines print Chomsky's work; given his views and his gloom-and-doom style, it's understandable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright © Reed Business Information, a division of Reed Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From &lt;b&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviewed by Jonathan Rauch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For all his celebrity on the academic and activist left, Noam Chomsky, the linguist turned gadfly, goes all but unnoticed inside the Capital Beltway. And this neglect, according to Chomsky's new collection of op-ed articles, Interventions, is not benign. &amp;quot;Chomsky's op-eds have been picked up widely by the international press,&amp;quot; according to an editor's note, but American &amp;quot;'newspapers of record' have declined to publish them.&amp;quot; When I picked up the new Chomsky collection, my first reaction was to be glad that City Lights Books -- &amp;quot;published at the City Lights Bookstore,&amp;quot;in San Francisco -- had brought out what promised to be a refreshing, if sometimes infuriating, challenge to conventional smugness. No such luck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chomsky's 44 brief essays, along with some supplementary notes added for republication, come to just over 200 loosely set pages. Yet this short book proves a chore to get through. To be sure, Chomsky's trademark barbs and provocations are here, but so are his flights to a separate reality. In Chomsky's universe, the 2001 U.S. attack on Afghanistan's Taliban &amp;quot;was undertaken with the expectation that it might drive several million people over the edge of starvation.&amp;quot; And North Korea's counterfeiting racket may actually be a CIA operation. And the Clinton administration intervened militarily in Kosovo not in order to prevent ethnic cleansing but to impose Washington's neoliberal economic agenda. And President Bush -- the first and only U.S. president to declare formal American support for a Palestinian state -- is the obstacle to a two-state solution that Hezbollah, Hamas and Iran are all prepared to accept. (I am not making that up.) This kind of tendentious whimsy is more peculiar than interesting; as the pages turn, one becomes inured to it and begins to yawn. Also working against readability is that some columns ramble, some repeat, and some are compilations of news clippings. None of those flaws, however, would condemn Chomsky's collection to instant forgettability if it offered fresh analysis or supple argument. Instead the reader gets the sneaking suspicion that the author has not felt the need to adjust an opinion in 30 or so years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As all who have read Chomsky know, he believes that &amp;quot;every form of authority and domination bears a severe burden of proof.&amp;quot; The United States is the world's mightiest power, and its survival instinct, like that of all great powers, is the &amp;quot;imperial mentality&amp;quot; of domination and control. America, for Chomsky, has long been a major perpetrator of state terror; but now, with the advent of the Bush administration, &amp;quot;The most powerful state in history has proclaimed that it intends to control the world by force.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.....&lt;br /&gt;more info on the book here&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Interventions-City-Lights-Open-Media/dp/0872864839%3FSubscriptionId%3D13DX9SSZNT4MP1351CR2%26tag%3Dbook0052-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D0872864839" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/290/calendar/9362373/"&gt;http://9-11.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232490929000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229666579000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Noam Chomsky - booksigning - chance to redeem his dismal stance on 9/11.......</name><id>9362459</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232143200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/9362459/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/e/global_6679262.jpeg</photo_url></item>