<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8129392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120926</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come celebrate H. P. Lovecraft's 122st birthday with a weekend long tribute of H.P Lovecraft inspired movies at the Brattle Theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They're showing HPL movies Friday, Saturday, and Sunday, but Friday looks like the one to go to, so that's what we're doing. It's a double (and a half) feature;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:00 Whisperer in the Darkness/Call of Cthulhu &lt;br /&gt;

11:30 From Beyond&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Double feature ticket price is $12 for both features. (Whisperer/Call count as one, Beyond counts as the other)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In THE WHISPERER IN DARKNESS, folklore professor Albert Wilmarth investigates legends of strange creatures in the most remote hills of Vermont. His inquiry reveals a terrifying glimpse of the truth that lurks behind the legends. H.P. Lovecraft’s classic tale of suspense and alien horrors is brought to life in the style of the classic horror films of the 1930s. Using a mix of modern and vintage techniques, the H.P. Lovecraft Historical Society has strived to create the most authentic and faithful screen adaptation of a Lovecraft story yet attempted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Screens with&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Call of Cthulhu &lt;br /&gt;

(2005) dir Andrew Leman [47 min] &lt;br /&gt;

THE CALL OF CTHULHU is H.P. Lovecraft’s most famous story – and the only one to feature the celebrated monster Cthulhu. In it, a man inherits his grandfather’s papers and becomes obsessed with investigating the mysterious and dangerous Cthulhu Cult. The famed story is brought richly to life in the style of a classic 1920s silent movie, with a haunting and original symphonic score.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on Lovecraft’s story of the same name, FROM BEYOND features Jeffrey Combs as a scientist who is involved in an experiment to stimulate the human pineal gland opening us up to higher dimensions. Unfortunately, those dimensions are extremely hostile and filled with horror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(from brattlefilm.org)&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345333357000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344650598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>H. P. Lovecraft birthday tribute @ the Brattle</name><id>77259812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345250700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/77259812/</event_url></item>