<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm starting a series of game nights at my place on the 2nd and 4th Monday of each month. They'll all start at 7:00. BYOB, BYOS(nacks).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to, bring $1 to contribute towards our Meetup fees.  It's much appreciated, but absolutely not required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll play a variety of games, but they'll mostly be Euros or strategy games rather than party games, mainly due to space issues.  (But also because I have an unmet craving for these types of games!)  Suggestions will certainly be accepted for future events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The attendee limit at each of these events will be determined by the maximum number of players the game can accommodate, so it will vary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests aren't allowed at these events for three reasons:  1)  A very limited number of spots are available due to the nature of the games we'll be playing.  2)  It's easy enough for someone to join our group if they want to come.  If you have a "guest" you wish you could bring, just have them join the group and sign up.  3)  If you sign up with a guest and then bail at the last minute, chances are your guest won't come either, so we're down two players from what we expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a waiting list available.  Please, if you sign up, be considerate of others and change your RSVP as soon as possible if you find you can't come.  No shows will be publicly derided.  If you're on the waiting list and get moved up on the day of the event, I'll try to contact you to make sure you're aware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing (and competing with!) you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;This time: &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bang!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/e/6/event_141770662.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;"The Outlaws hunt the Sheriff. The Sheriff hunts the Outlaws. The Renegade plots secretly, ready to take one side or the other. Bullets fly. Who among the gunmen is a Deputy, ready to sacrifice himself for the Sheriff? And who is a merciless Outlaw, willing to kill him? If you want to find out, just draw (your cards)!"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;This a great game of the old west.  In the beginning, only the Sheriff is known.  Everybody else reveals their character only through their actions.  You shoot your enemies and protect your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;You'll get to upgrade to a better weapon so you can shoot clear across the table, find a barrel to hide behind when someone's shooting at you, drink beer to restore your health, and dodge live dynamite, all in this terrific, fast-paced card game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Note:  As this game requires 4 people to play, the Meetup will be cancelled if we don't get 4 RSVPs by the day before the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send parking instructions and further info to "yes" RSVPs a few days before the event.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1346121851000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343012720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bang! @ Mitch's  (2nd and 4th Monday Game Series)</name><id>74484272</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346108400000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/74484272/</event_url></item>