<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>770 Boston Post Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06437</zip><lat>41.288795</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comfort Keepers</name><city>Guilford</city><id>1845621</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.675476</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Come for networking at 8:30 and stay for our panel of three dynamic local women who do "all" and do it well. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Each will offer her unique perspective on balancing your business and personal lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Cindy Cartier: A shoreline woman entrepreneur that makes us say "How does she do it all?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Cindy is a practicing lawyer, a Selectman on Guilford's Board of Selectman, a certified fitness and yoga instructor, and co-owner, with her husband, of New England Car Wash in Branford. Cindy is the mom of two young children and despite being busy in business, she has found time to run for political office and even makes time to coach the GHS debate team! Cindy will share her best tips for balancing work/family, keeping focus, charting schedules and making lists!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Lisa Lelas: A professional speaker/author on the subject of Organizing Time, Space and Goals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Lisa will share her best tips from her popular seminar, "How Valuable is Your Time?" Learn to streamline your schedule and create more time in your every day to accomplish all your goals. Work smarter, not harder! A busy mom of two teenagers, Lisa is also a successful entrepreneur in a variety of roles: newspaper columnist, magazine editor, book author, goal setting "bucket list coach", professional organizer/speaker...and drama &amp;amp; presentation coach!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yvette McIntire: A Master Life Coach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Yvette  “preaches” self-love and acceptance as a fast-track path to life fulfillment.  She also knows a thing or two about driving yourself into the ground with stress. After a “spiritual awakening” accompanied by panic attacks and pure exhaustion, she loved her way back to emotional, spiritual and physical health by throwing away her To Do list and learning to feel what wants to happen each day rather than effort-ing her way though life. Yvette now enjoys sharing her discoveries along this journey with others who want to experience life differently.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also have several other coaches and organizers among our ranks.  This is sure to be a content rich meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cheryl Roby</member_name><member_id>10682494</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368840394000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Association-of-Women-Business-leaders</urlname><id>1543671</id><group_lat>41.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>AWBL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363799954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Time Management Panel--Three experts talk about how they "do it all"</name><id>drqmcfyrhbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368793800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Association-of-Women-Business-leaders/events/110195082/</event_url></item>