<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>799 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363407</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-8356</phone><name>Bertucci's </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>754675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097389</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you put things off, like cleaning or putting things &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;away&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;?&amp;nbsp;  Do you find yourself procrastinating on almost everything?&amp;nbsp; Have you  had to live with this for most of your life?&amp;nbsp; Come- let's explore the  why's and some solutions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"If you don't understand why you're putting things off, then all the  practical suggestions in the world aren't likely to help because you  won't let yourself use them. Yet, even if you've searched your soul and  believe you thoroughly understand your reasons for procrastinating, you  still won't get anywhere unless you do something to overcome it."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"procrastination ... serves a protective function for people."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"There are plenty of times when it's in your best interest to put something aside and not attend to it."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Procrastination&lt;/em&gt; by Jane B. Burka, Ph.D., and Lenora M. Yuen, Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's have a discussion and discovery about this.  &lt;strong&gt;Often when we look at something from a different point of view, we see things we had not noticed before&lt;/strong&gt;. The same is true of cluttering - be that physical (manifestation of our thoughts) or metaphysical (our thoughts). &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kevin Martin&lt;/strong&gt;,  a practicing certified hypnotherapist and neurolinguistic programming  (NLP) Master Practitioner, is back to offer more pointers and frameworks  for QUICKLY (on a scale of MINUTES- NOT months or years...so,  practically magic: like a "Gestalt switch") "reprogram" our lives to  surmount cluttered thinking for more successful, satisfying living-  particularly regarding procrastination this evening. As organizer of  several Boston-area NLP Meetups, Kevin originally envisioned his groups  to help people learn self-help tools. He often looks for resources,  tools, and groups outside the fields of hypnosis and NLP to mesh with  that vision -and fortunately, our group does! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(&lt;em&gt;If you plan to eat, please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt; to order; otherwise, by 7 pm will be fine.   There is no specified  purchase minimum for refreshments, but participants are encouraged to  order something to support the business in appreciation of Management's  permission to meet in their space.   PLEASE BE ADVISED: Commercial  eating establishments generally do not permit on-site consumption of  refreshments brought from elsewhere, due to liability concerns.) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt; (Approximate) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6:30 pm- Order dinner/refreshment if you plan to eat: $2.45 (for a soda) and upward &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm- Intro to neurolinguistic programming (NLP) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7:15 pm- Roots of clutter/Procrastination:  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7:30 pm&amp;ndash; NLP technique(s) described &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7:45 pm - Demonstration &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;8:30 pm- Q&amp;amp;A &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;8:45 pm- Wrap-up &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Notepad &amp;amp; pen or other note-taking device, calendar to schedule  Action Items (next steps). Dress in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in case  the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer) and comfortably, as Kevin  sometimes has us do NLP/EFT physical exercises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PREVIEWS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Bandler: NLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S. Andreas: Compulsion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: EFT/procrastination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: Tapping&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Procrastination&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; by Jane B. Burka, Ph.D., and Lenora M. Yuen, Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; by Richard Bandler&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation&lt;/em&gt; - EXCERPTS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...there is a magic moment when it all comes together, without effort."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...if you learned to do something one way, you can learn how to do   it totally different and better. Learning is the way to personal   freedom. Hypnosis and NLP are tools to make this easy and fun."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...when we know how something is done, it becomes easy to change.   We're highly programmable beings ... we can program ourselves to change.   That's not being a robot; that's becoming a free spirit."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...three steps to making enduring change:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. People must become so sick of having the problem that they decide they really want to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. They have to somehow see their problem from a new perspective or in a new light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. New and appealing options must be found or created, and pursued.&lt;em&gt;"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...since time distortion is a characteristic of the phenomenon we   call "trance," just as it is of dreaming, we can lead people through   choices very rapidly. The learning tool of altered states permits us to   familiarize the subject with a new experience in a fraction of the time   it would take for them in an ordinary waking state."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I noticed that when they made the change, they switched to &lt;em&gt;watching&lt;/em&gt; themselves doing the behavior. ...they'd discovered how to disassociate from the problem experience."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...I had some people...apply what I had learned. I had them "step   out" of their bodies.... And it worked. They got rid of their [problems]   really quickly. Their brains simply shifted the way they perceived   their situation, and their problems went away."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Suddenly, without actually realizing it, something happened that switched off the problem and turned on the solution."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Each of us creates a representation of the world in which we   live--that is, we create a map or model which we use to generate our   behavior. Our representation of the world determines to a large degree   what our experience of the world will be, how we will perceive the   world, what choices we will see available to us as we live in the   world."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"it's often much more productive - and a lot easier - to change the   map someone has been using rather than the territory in which the person   is functioning."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If we build feed-forward loops so we're moving toward pleasure   rather than away from pain, we're walking toward something we want, and   we know in which direction we're going."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If we have only one response, we're stuck. If we have two, we can   oscillate backward and forward. If we have three or more, it starts to   feel a lot better."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The pattern is simple: white out the image you don't want, and then immediately replace it with something you prefer."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I work by accentuating people's desires, hopes, and dreams, and making them absolutely irresistible."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I've told people not just to listen to what their clients are   saying, but also to notice what they're not talking about, because   what's &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; there is what they need."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I'm always looking for the shortest route to get people where they   want to be, comfortably and with the greatest degree of enjoyment...."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"the right mental strategy ... means that it works and you enjoy it, and therefore you'll practice it more and more...."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...recognize the value of simplicity."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"if you give yourself bad commands, bad things happen."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"procrastination is not a psychological problem; it's just a matter of mental organization."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"there's nothing wrong with easy."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Repeat this thought and action several times, making it faster each   time, until you feel yourself being pulled to your feet by the  vividness  of your image."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I consider the model of submodalities to be probably the most   significant thing I've done so far. It allows us to create maps that   show with tremendous precision how consciousness functions to produce   wanted and unwanted results. The strategy model shows us how to work   sequentially; the model of submodalities explains how things work   simultaneously."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"find out what they're certain about and start to give them doubt   about their limitations and certainty about the things they want."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Often, one or two submodality changes precipitate a systemwide shift."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"how quickly the brain learns if we learn to communicate with it in a language we understand."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In a third column, write down in some detail how your life would be better for making these changes."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I said, 'Maybe you guys should have seven hundred people in the   audience and then it would be a lot easier, because if people are   scared, they retreat into deep trances.'"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The other important thing you need to remember when making this sort   of change is speed. The brain learns quickly; ...if the information is   presented too slowly, the brain won't learn because it can't detect a   pattern."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...'entrainment.' There are certain distinct signs of developing   trance that people unconsciously pick up on and follow, until they, too,   go into trance."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...keep your eye on what you want to achieve, which is to put people   into wonderful, relaxed states, and then have them face their problems   with all the resources they didn't know they had.&amp;nbsp; Then, ... the  waking  state will never be the same... that's called learning."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Success Is An Altered State"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLARIFICATION FROM KEVIN--&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Misconceptions&amp;nbsp;about hypnosis&amp;nbsp;abound- formed through TV, movies, and   staged entertainment. The most prevalent misconception is that hypnosis   is a form of mind control - that a hypnotist can make someone rob a  bank  or do terrible or absurd things. This is absolutely false! A  hypnotist  cannot make anyone do anything against their values. No one  will do  anything they would not normally do or that they have not  wanted to do.  Onstage, a hypnotist provides a 'safe' atmosphere for  people to have fun  and act on things they may not normally do socially;  however, if they  have never wanted to do some particular thing, they  will not do so under  hypnosis. In a clinical offfice session, people  under hypnosis do only  what they feel safe doing, and no more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hypnotist is only a guide; the person under hypnosis is actually   doing the work by following suggestions. That is why we say that all   hypnosis is self-hypnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another general misconception is that someone under hypnosis is   sleeping. This is far from true: Most people are totally aware of what   is happening around them, and can remember everything.   Most&amp;nbsp;hypnosis&amp;nbsp;sessions are experienced as deep relaxation -   approximating the state of awakening in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;The  $10-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal, preferably, or in cash to Judy Stitt at event &lt;em&gt;before presentation&lt;/em&gt;,  please) helps to compensate (1) the presenter for his  time, training,  and specialized knowledge so generously shared with us,  and (2) the  organizer(s) for time spent planning, administering, and coordinating   events - also to defray Meetup.com's charge assessed organizers for this  Web site and other resources to  serve our group.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk about this Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Kevin and the Meetup sign -place is not so big</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308264097000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307165254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PROCRASTINATION: Why We Do It, &amp; Doing Something About It</name><id>20918881</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308090600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/20918881/</event_url></item>