<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please read the full description from top to bottom, before you RSVP Yes.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The goal of this hike is watch sunset from the summit (8:28 PM) then hike out under a nearly full moon (99% full) which rises at 7:59 PM. We should finish around 11 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be doing a loop hike around Jobildunk and Gorge Brook Ravines starting and ending from The Ravine Lodge. We will ascend by Asquam Ridge passing near Mt. Waternomee, Mt. Jim, and Mt. Blue before reaching the summit of Mooslauke. We will then descend by the Carriage Road which has good footing and a clear path. A side trip to South Peak is also a possibility.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hope is for clear sky and moonlight, but headlamps may be needed. Everyone should have headlamps and spare batteries. The summit and surrounding area is exposed. We will be standing around for a while on the summit as the sun sets and temperatures drop. Plenty of warm clothing will be needed. Hat,  gloves, extra layers, jacket. A down jacket would not be uncalled for. Temps will likely be in the 40s or maybe even 30s without windchill. Be prepared for it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is very weather dependent. It may be shifted a day earlier or a day later if weather is not ideal. The start time may be changed slightly also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GPS coordinates&lt;/b&gt;: 43.99333, -71.81583 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/?q=43.99333,-71.81583" target="_blank"&gt;Map of 43.99333, -71.81583&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance&lt;/b&gt;: 10.55 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;: 2999 ft  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time&lt;/b&gt;: 6 hours and 50 minutes  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails&lt;/b&gt;: Asquam Ridge Tr, Beaver Brook Tr, Carriage Road, Hurricane Tr &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.8 miles and 2671 ft elevation gain to summit. 4:15 book time&lt;br /&gt;4.75 miles and 328 elevation gain on descent, 2:35 book time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that you're late or lost.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244492547000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243377629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moosilauke by Moonlight</name><id>10498505</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244319300000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10498505/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/e/f/global_8849103.jpeg</photo_url></item>