<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>148 John St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02865</zip><lat>41.906918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blackstone River Bikeway - John Street Parking Area</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>1013991</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.402805</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;**New Details: additional parking if needed -- this is a larger group than normal, so if you arrive at the John Street parking lot and can't find a spot, try the parking OPPOSITE of 1 Mendon Rd., Cumberland RI. (NOTE: this is literally up the street from the John St. lot). The bike trail runs next to the Dollar Store which is on the FAR left of Stop &amp;amp; Shop. There should be lots of room to park but you might want to remove your bike rack from the car. If you end up parking here, simply ride down the bike path to the LEFT (~1/8 mile) and meet the group. (Thanks David!!)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ask and you shall receive...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A late April ride on the &lt;a href="http://www.blackstoneriverbikeway.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Blackstone River Bikeway&lt;/a&gt; :-) This is an out-and-back ride so your ability level isn't an issue. You want to sprint the entire route? You'll just be responsible for letting us know and we'll see you back at the parking lot. You want a simple leisure ride and stop at the numerous photo op spots? Enjoy, just let us know you're bringing up the rear!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.blackstoneriverbikeway.com/ri_map.php" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for map of route&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the John Street Parking lot, here are directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John St. Parking&lt;br /&gt;From Route 146&lt;br /&gt;Take exit for Route 123 Breakneck Hill Road&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 123. It will become Great Road, then Front St. and eventually John St.&lt;br /&gt;Parking is north of MM7.5 on the bikeway&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is limited parking at this location but we've never had an issue before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last time we went on this ride we ended up riding through Woonsocket to a small pavilion with restrooms and a snack bar (water refills!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on the group and interest level, afterward we can go grab some 'grub' at a nearby restaurant that serves Italian food (and awesome homemade dough for their pizzas and calzones!)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bethany</member_name><member_id>10111481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272389932000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Grinders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group</urlname><id>1500421</id><group_lat>42.0600013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Foxboro Grind &amp; Grub Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270734950000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blackstone River Bikepath</name><id>13123852</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272126600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group/events/13123852/</event_url></item>