<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 101</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01440</zip><lat>42.579849</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dunn Park</name><city>Gardner</city><id>827146</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.986281</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Anyone up for a few jaunts around this very nice trail into the wooded areas and around the pond? With hunting season still on until the end of the year, this is a safe alternative to some of our more wooded trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This is a dog friendly hike. Bags are generally available to pick up after your pet but please bring one just in case there are none available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We'll be meeting inside the visitor's center to stay warm. BTW, there are no parking fees in effect this time of year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Dunn State Park Fishing at Dunn Pond Dunn State Park 289 Pearl St. Gardner 01440 978 632-7897 This 130-acre park features a 20 acre pond, walking trails, swimming, fishing, picnicking, public programs, and play equipment. Private canoes and non-motorized boats are allowed on the pond. In the winter the trails are open for cross country skiing, ice skating is allowed on the pond and often there is a fire blazing in the visitors centers fireplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; All activities offered by the park are accessible to people with disabilities. Parking Fees Parking fees are in effect at Dunn State Park from Memorial weekend through Labor Day. Car - $5 Annual Pass - $35 Massachusetts Resident / $45 Out of State Vehicles bearing a HP or Veterans license plate or placard as well as Massachusetts seniors who are 62 years of age or more and have a Mass. Senior Citizen Pass from the DCR are allowed in free of charge as long as space is available. Trail Map Download printable version (pdf)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Park Directions The park is located in north central Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; From the East/Northeast/Southeast Take I-495 to exit 29, Rt. 2 west. Drive 23.5 miles on Rt. 2 west to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. At the bottom of the exit ramp, merge onto Rt. 140 north. Drive 2.7 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left on to Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Park entrance is on left. OR Take 1-90 west (MA PIKE) to exit 10, I-290 north. Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north. Drive 18.75 miles on I-190 north and merge onto Rt. 2 west. Drive 12 miles on Rt. 2 west to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. At the bottom of the exit ramp, merge onto Rt. 140 north. Drive 2.7 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left onto Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Park entrance is on left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; From the West Take Rt. 2 east to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. At the bottom of the exit ramp, take a left on to Rt. 140 north. Drive 2.8 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left on to Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Park entrance is on left. From Southwest/Northwest Take I-91 to Exit 27, Rt. 2 east. Drive 29 miles on Rt. 2 east to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. At the bottom of the exit ramp take a left on to Rt. 140 north. Drive 2.8 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a right on to Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. Park entrance is on left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325171896000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324698012000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dunn Park Hike</name><id>45365792</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325084400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/45365792/</event_url></item>