<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>hammond pond parkway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02467</zip><lat>42.322247</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>hammond pond reservation</name><city>Newton</city><id>887977</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.172646</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The largest conservation area in Newton is wooded, with noted rock outcroppings of Roxbury Puddingstone, brooks, ponds, wetlands, fields, and an historic woodland garden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Activities to enjoy here are walking, jogging, nature study, geology study, birding, rock climbing, and cross-country skiing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gooch's Caves - These are Roxbury Conglomerate fissure caves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandstone Ledges - These thick ledges alternate with Roxbury Conglomerate rock. They are sandstone formations that may have been river deposits. You can see the evidence of ripple marks, such as are made by water. Note the very long, almost vertical joints toward the westerly end of the ledges. The ledges are located west of Hammond Pond Parkway and north of the MBTA track, off the southbound lane of the Parkway. Enter the pathway about 600' south of Beacon Street and see the ledges to the right of the path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deer Park - Mrs. Webster brought a couple of dozen deer into the area many years ago. Today, only several occupy an enclosed area of six acres.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hammond Woods and Pond - The trails and cliffs attract hikers and rock climbers. The pond, as a "great pond" (any pond larger that 10 acres) is state-owned, operated by the DCR. Its average depth is just four feet. Access is from the gravel beach on the west side of the pond, near the Chestnut Hill Shopping Center parking lot. The pond and its adjoining marshes and woodlands provide valuable habitats for a diversity of wildlife, aquatic species, and native plants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Houghton Garden - This section of the park is described on a separate page of this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Houghton Garden:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here in Newton is a wild garden that's listed on the National Register of Historic Places. Its gracious paths, overhung by azalea and rhododendron, wind around a stream and lagoon-like pond. Water features were designed by Warren Manning, who formerly worked for the Olmsted studio. Uncommon migrating birds are seen here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The alpine rock garden on a ledge overlooking Houghton Pond was one of the first of its kind. Especially lovel are the climbing hydrangea, the naturalized lilly of the valley (in actuality--a horribly invasive woodland weed), the wood hyacinth, the umbrella pine, and other exotic evergreens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MBTA: Green Line (D) to Chestnut Hills Station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Car:Take Route 9 east or west to the Hammond Pond Parkway Exit. Just north of the Parkway is the reservation parking lot on the left as one enters the Chestnut Hill Shopping Center. Lost Pond is south off Hammond Pond Parkway. Reservation can be accessed through Newton Conservation Land off Dudley Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/c/f/event_4268911.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the dcr parking lot near the trail head.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6025746</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349549675000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Subnats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>science-88</urlname><id>1005141</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Suburban Naturalists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349228748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fourteen Ferns of Hammond Pond (and the wild garden) with Don Lubin</name><id>85226702</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349535600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/science-88/events/85226702/</event_url></item>