<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Third Floor</address_2><address_1>890 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.350904</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.353.0909/800.909.9287</phone><name>WBUR Offices</name><city>Boston</city><id>1287500</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114992</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Event: &lt;br /&gt;Getting together &amp;quot;as quiet listeners&amp;quot; at WBUR Executive Council Meeting on June 10 Thursday at 890 Commonwealth Avenue, across the street from BU's Athletic Center. &lt;br /&gt;If you are planning to join us and represent the &amp;quot;P&amp;quot; in NPR, please call WBUR's&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WBUR's receptionist @ 617.353.0909/800.909.9287 to confirm that you will be there so that they can make a name badge (optional) for you.  You can call the front desk a few days before the event or even on the day of the event. &lt;br /&gt;890 Commonwealth Avenue, then Stairs or Elevator... go to the third floor, get your badge or sign your name in and welcome to the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The Meeting: &lt;br /&gt;This is usually an semi-annual educational meeting under the leadership of Gen. Mngr Paul A. La Camera (very nice guy) and top managers of the station giving State of WBUR to the Council Members (some big donors) and answer questions about operations. &lt;br /&gt;The members start coming in at 4:30 and the official start time is 5:00 pm.  There will be plenty of catered (donated) healthy food and drinks.  Bon-a-petit. &lt;br /&gt;Some of the council members will seated with their backs turned to the few listeners who are &amp;quot;the public&amp;quot; - Rude!!!  &lt;br /&gt;We will be reminded that we are just listeners, our voice or opinion is not sought - Rude!!! &lt;br /&gt;There is usually a brief chat/networking around the food table after the meeting, but some of the Council Members and WBUR Managers leave in a hurry. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We want:  &lt;br /&gt;More representation of the public in programming, coverage of &amp;quot;taboo&amp;quot; subjects, ie. Hardcore Peace, bold anti-war Movement and Serious 9/11 Truth.  We want elimination of &amp;quot;monitoring/deletion&amp;quot; service from their OnPoint's Message Board (waste of time/money, censorship).  We want interactive and editorial dialog between the management and The Public (mini-ombudsman functionality through an intern, at least) about the subjects that are covered and the Guests that are invited.  Enough of Retired Generals, Tea-Bag Party, Think-Tanks, Talking Points, Money Guys, AEI, and people who make money from wars and destruction of our country.   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Why you should show up: &lt;br /&gt;NPR Ombudsman's Office in Washington (Alicia Shepard) does not have any direct influence in Member Stations.  WBUR is the biggest NPR Station and also is the home of the second most popular talk show after Talk of the Nation.  The more people we have as members of the Public, they will listen to us more.  This Executive Council Meeting may even be an ideal venue and forum to influence the Producers right there during the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Caution: &lt;br /&gt;Please be discrete when you are signing up.  Usually the attendance of public/listener members is not more than 5-6 people; we don't want to alert anybody so that they may take a defensive attitude.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Travis  McGee</member_name><member_id>451265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276383353000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275450836000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WBUR Executive Council Meeting - as Listeners</name><id>13667349</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276204500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/13667349/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/global_12798054.jpeg</photo_url></item>