<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sunstein Kann Murphy &amp; Timbers LLP</name><city>Boston</city><id>5951112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Note: the Libertarian Association of Massachusetts does not support or endorse candidates for President before the national nominating convention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Known as "Governor Veto", former Governor of New Mexico Gary Johnson is visiting Massachusetts for a fund raiser for his Libertarian campaign for President on Super Tuesday, March 6! Johnson will be on Fox News with Neil Cavuto during the 6 o'clock hour, so the fundraiser will start as soon as he can make it to the site from the TV studio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Johnson is currently polling at 7-9% in the latest PPP three way poll against Romney and Obama. With a Ron Paul upset win unlikely for the GOP nomination, the liberty movement in Massachusetts needs to come together to support a strong Libertarian candidate. Let's carry the message of liberty forward!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal is to raise at least $3000 dollars from Massachusetts in order to be one of the qualifying states for presidential matching funds. The &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;suggested&lt;/span&gt; donation for this event is $100 per person, but &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;any donation will be accepted&lt;/span&gt;!&amp;nbsp; Bring your friends, too. Double your investment in the message of liberty: any donation from $1 to $250 will be doubled!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intimate Fund Raising Dinner: ** There are a limited number of seats for a private dinner with Johnson following the reception. Contact blau.liberty@gmail.com by Sunday, March 4 if you are interested in attending. The price per person is $500. **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/385347434827395/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook event link: http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave</member_name><member_id>4297517</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331083797000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-349</urlname><id>593245</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Libertarian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330568180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fundraising event with Gary Johnson</name><id>54437512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331078400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-349/events/54437512/</event_url></item>