<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>264 Tower Hill Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03034</zip><lat>43.033783</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>3rd Gate Past the NH 101 Underpass Just Before</name><city>Candia</city><id>12590012</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.357230</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will do an easy 3 mile hike around Tower Hill Pond.  Any one feeling particularly frisky could do an additional 2 mile loop around Clark Pond as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Even though I let my dog go in the water be aware that if a warden catches your dog doing that you could be given a fine so do so at your own risk.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Per club policy, no adult guests. Please have your adult guests &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/4-Seasons-Hiking-Group/events/101673392/"&gt;join&lt;/a&gt; the club. A minor would need a waiver signed by a parent or guardian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;agree&lt;/a&gt; the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;property damage&lt;/a&gt;, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;property damage&lt;/a&gt;, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Turn off of Candia Road/ Old Candia Road onto Tower Hill Road in Auburn. Proceed 0.3 miles going under the underpass for NH 101 to the 3rd Gate.  Park on the side of the road.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365967294000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364869195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tower Hill Pond Loop - 3 Mile Hike</name><id>112194512</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365861600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/112194512/</event_url></item>