<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am currently in beautiful Indianapolis, Indiana at GenCon the best 4 days in gaming. Where games of all kinds are on display. The convention runs 4 days and I have been gathering some great games to share with people when I return home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would love to meetup and play some of these games with the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting once again at Jumpgate in Portsmouth and should have enough space for 8 gamers if we can rustle them up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by Wednesday evening at 5PM EST. I will then send out an email if we don't have enough gamers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minimum is 3 Max is 8-10. Bring a friend if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there are any specific types of games people want me to check out please let me know as there are still 2 days left of the convention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow my adventures on The Sages of RPG Twitter page. &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/srpgtwitter" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.Twitter.com/SagesOfRPG" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Twitter.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; you do NOT have to sign up for twitter to read updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone has any questions please let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description of GenCon from &lt;a href="http://www.gencon.com" target="_blank"&gt;GenCon's Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Gen Con Indy is the original, longest running, best attended, gaming convention in the world. For over 40 years, Gen Con Indy has been setting the trend and breaking records. Last year, more than 28,000 unique attendees experienced Gen Con Indy. The biggest complaint we hear is that there is simply too much to do, see, and experience. Get lost in a phantasm of art exhibits. Stare at jaw-dropping costumes, or better yet, wear one of your own. Meet the movers and the shakers in the gaming industry. Check out the newest games and get a sneak peek at the latest editions.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Wayne. Tan Ball Cap.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wayne</member_name><member_id>1411667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1251928421000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>sagesofrpg</urlname><id>747276</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth, NH / Seacoast Boardgames Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250337813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join us for all the Newest Games from GenCon!</name><id>11116880</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250803800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sagesofrpg/events/11116880/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/1/global_2300225.jpeg</photo_url></item>