<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Revere Beach Pkwy</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02151</zip><lat>42.400932</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Revere Beach, William G. Reinstein Bandstand</name><city>Revere</city><id>701555</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.997554</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Sand Sculpting Festival is back in Revere this week and I'll be there again this year to see these transient works of art come into being.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festival runs from July 15-18th, and we're headed there on Saturday, to get a sense of the almost completed projects, while still getting a chance to see the sculptors at work. Check out the website at:  &lt;a href="http://reverebeachpartnership.com/?p=24" target="_blank"&gt;http://reverebeachpar...&lt;/a&gt; or: &lt;a href="http://www.celebrateboston.com/events/revere-beach-sand-sculpting-festival.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.celebrateb...&lt;/a&gt; for an idea of what you're going to see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revere Beach is easily accessible by T, and that's probably your best bet due to the nightmare parking can provide. Revere Beach is on the blue line, and you can either get off at the Revere Beach or Wonderland Station. Parking spots are available at the Wonderland station if ya wanna risk it. The sand castle competition is slightly closer to the Revere Beach Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The competition is based at the William G. Reinstein Bandstand (gazebo looking thing...photo available at &lt;a href="http://www.beautyinre..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beautyinre...&lt;/a&gt;) and it might be a mobscene, but I'll be hovering around on the street side of this landmark around noon. Will be sending my cell number to my yes's and maybe's on friday night in case you don't recognize me from my photos, but it'll only be out and receiving calls from about 11:30 am - 12:30 and then I make no guarantees that I'll hear it ring :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will likely plan on grabbing some lunch there, walking around the sculptures, and maybe hanging on the beach a bit if folks are interested.  I have to depart at 3 pm to make an overnight shift at work, but folks are more than welcome to make a beach day of this.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring funds for food, and, if ya want some beach time, a bathing suit, beach towel, sunscreen (probably a good idea regardless) etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check back for details regarding rain changes, though currently it looks to be mostly sunny.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is cross posted with the Social Fun group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, contact Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279680321000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278806668000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revere Beach Sand Sculpting Festival</name><id>14063634</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279382400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/14063634/</event_url></item>