<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE THAT DUE TO VISA ISSUES,  THE DIRECTOR WILL NOT BE PRESENT AT THIS SCREENING. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Mahamat-Saleh Haroun is one of the leading African filmakers, &lt;b&gt;Dry-Season&lt;/b&gt; is his third feature film. His previous film Our Father (Abouna) had a short run at Kendall a few years which I was lucky enough to catch and I've been eagerly awaiting Haroun's next film. Little did I imagine  I would also have the opportunity to listen to the director speak when his next film  screens in the Boston area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; As I hope most of you are aware, The Harvard Film Archive  has been presenting some of the world's  top directors to discuss their work in person over the past year  and our group has had the pleasure of attending many of these events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Movie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dry Season&lt;/b&gt; Chad 96 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;THIS IS A FILM THAT ASKS: WHAT IS COURAGE?&amp;quot;  BBC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the announcement that the Chadian government has issued an amnesty for war criminals following decades of civil war, teenage orphan Atim is handed a revolver by his elderly grandfather and given a mission of vengeance: the boy must travel from his tiny rural village to the capital city and kill the man who many years earlier murdered his father. His target, however, turns out to be not a bloodthirsty monster but a devoutly religious Muslim baker who gruffly takes the young would-be assassin under his wing as an apprentice. The elliptical story, graced with notes of humor and expressive silences, unfolds with some surprising twists before ultimately resolving into a quietly wrenching drama of personal accountability and moral choice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dry Season&lt;/b&gt; has scored the rare 100% rating on Rotten Tomatoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An intimate parable of truth and reconciliation.   TimeOut &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gently and quietly told, Daratt (Dry Season) is an unassumingly political work that unfolds with the simplicity of a parable and the gravity of a Bible story  NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.eyeforfilm.co.uk/reviews.php?film_id=12543" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eyeforfilm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll go to a local restaurant afterward to  further discuss this film. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the theater a little on the early side, probably around 6:15 and will also be holding a meetup sign after the Q&amp;A session near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208819456000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206486480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dry Season </name><id>7601767</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208646000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7601767/</event_url></item>