<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Not strictly an American phenomenon,  filmmaking is still dominated by men- quick, name your top five favorite directors. Does you list include any women? Probably not. What's up with this? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WIFTI's Short Film Showcase Celebrating International Women's Day 2008 featuring nine outstanding short films by some of today's best female directors, culled from five of the world's top Festivals, will be screened in seventeen WIF Chapters around the globe, featuring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A MOMENT - Directed by Valeria Ruiz&lt;br /&gt;BLACK AND WHITE - Directed by Kirsty McDonald&lt;br /&gt;CHINESE DUMPLINGS - Directed by Michelle Hung&lt;br /&gt;DESIRES - Directed by Kate Jessop&lt;br /&gt;HAPPINESS - Directed by Sophie Barthes&lt;br /&gt;MEET-MARKET.ca - Directed by Geneviève Poulette&lt;br /&gt;ONE HUNDREDTH OF A SECOND - Directed by Susan Jacobson&lt;br /&gt;ORCHIDS - Directed by Bryce Dallas Howard&lt;br /&gt;SEXY THING - Directed by Denie Pentecost&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I strongly urge you to buy your ticket online before the event to avoid possible disappointment on Saturday.  You never know how popular a given special event at The Brattle will be and $1.29 seems a small price to pay for &amp;quot;Happiness&amp;quot; (the title of one of the films being screened, get it?).  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;  You can buy your tickets here: &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Women In Film &amp;amp; Video New England Presents&lt;br /&gt;International Women's Day Short Film Showcase at 2:30  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Women in Film &amp;amp; Video New England is pleased to present a short film showcase celebrating the best of Women's Cinema today. As part of an international alliance of female filmmaking organizations, Women in Film and Television International is presenting a Short Film Showcase Celebrating International Women's Day 2008. This line up of nine outstanding short films will be screened in seventeen cities worldwide. Join our local Women in Film &amp;amp; Video New England Chapter, the Brattle Theatre and others around the world in celebrating female filmmaking on International Women's Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to descriptions of each film: &lt;a href="http://wifti.org/2008sfs/" target="_blank"&gt;http://wifti.org/2008...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Needless to say, we should be seeing some great films and have an engaging discussion afterward as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Nina&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the films . Tom originally posted this and then saw that he'll be at the MFA for a film earlier in the day. Thanks so much Nina for agreeing to host this in my place!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203041977000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9 Short Films by Celebrated Women Directors</name><id>7334018</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1205004600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7334018/</event_url></item>