<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Brattle presents the animated works of the Quay Brothers. Born is the US, the twin brothers  moved to London and have produced stop-motion works with obvious Eastern European influences. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brothers Quay generate a powerfully specific vision that seldom screens in theaters and yet translates poorly to the small screen...all self-respecting cinephiles must get to this far-too-rare 11-film retrospective. Flavorpill&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This prolific duo have cranked out some of the most imaginative, mesmerizing animation since the late 1970s. The massive retrospective attests to the animators unparalleled vision and the collection forms a gorgeous visual spectacle. &lt;br /&gt; Eric Kohn, New York Press&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unlike anything you've ever seen even in your dreamiest dreams. JAMI BERNARD, NEW YORK POST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From their Wikepedia entry: &amp;quot;Most of their films feature dolls, often partially disassembled, in a dark, moody atmosphere. Perhaps their best known work is Street Of Crocodiles, based on the short story of the same name by the Polish author and artist Bruno Schulz. This short film was selected by director and animator Terry Gilliam as one of the ten best animated films of all time.&amp;quot; Read more here: &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brothers_Quay" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brattle has broken down the Quay's shorts into two programs. The first starts at 2:00 pm and the second at 3:45. Our group will see both and go to a nearby restaurant to discuss afterwards if these are overlooked works of art or if they are justly rarely screened.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, Tom will be  near the front row when the films are over holding a meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;I'm not sure if these films require two ticket purchases  and will keep the group informed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173809076000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171926337000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Brothers Quay- "Gorgeous and Haunted Landscapes"</name><id>5495246</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1173636000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5495246/</event_url></item>