<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to come spend a few days with over 10,000 airplanes and 800,000 of the best people on earth?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come with us to Airventure this year!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if you have just &amp;quot;dreamed&amp;quot; of going, please sign up and fill out the survey questions. It might be easier to go than you think. I would like to see what people would like to do and see if we can get a group or a few groups to go.  One option would be to get a few of us to drive out in an RV for the week. It would be a cheap way to spend the week as well as maybe a place to stay midweek for people who will just fly themselves in for a night or two. Arrangements could be made to bring out supplies as well. For instance, if you don't have room in your plane for a lounge chair or suit case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is Airventure?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is an excert from &lt;a href="http://airventure.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://airventure.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you want to enjoy a typical day at the Convention, get your walking shoes on and dress casual. The gates open at 7 a.m., but get there early to see as much as you can each day. Longtime attendees will tell you that you need more than one day to really see it all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you arrive, the number of people, size of the site and the rows and rows of magnificent aircraft are simply overwhelming. If you were to walk past ... not down ... each row of airplanes, you would cover 5.2 miles! Typically about 2,500 show aircraft participate at EAA AirVenture Oshkosh, including homebuilts, antiques, classics, warbirds, ultralights and rotorcraft.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure you get a map, because even if you've been here before, the new site improvements in 2009 bring a new look to one of the world's great aviation events. You don't want to waste a minute while you're here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first thing to look at is airplanes on the flight line. As an EAA member, you can inspect firsthand the craftsmanship and design advancements that come from the hands and minds of EAA members. If you're interested in a particular airplane chances are you'll find it in Oshkosh. As you walk along the flight line you'll see many of the newsmakers and personalities who make the world of aviation so exciting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling across AeroShell Square, AirVenture's main display ramp, you might see anything from the Spirit of St. Louis to a Stealth fighter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss KidVenture! Since landing at Wittman Regional Airport, KidVenture has attracted thousands of participants young and old alike with its hands-on, educational-and fun-aviation-based demonstrations and presentations. After all, kids get to build their own gliders and rockets, fly simulators, see aviation legends tell their stories, ride in a tethered hot-air balloon, and so much more.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Scales</member_name><member_id>6873008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282095962000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263327669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EAA Airventure 2010</name><id>12300968</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280142000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/12300968/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/9/global_4880393.jpeg</photo_url></item>