<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Temple St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.304740</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 498-2500</phone><name>Criterion Cinemas</name><city>New Haven</city><id>664405</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Every year, Criterion Cinema's in New Haven puts on a selection of the SHORT Films nominated for the Oscar Awards.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I (A.J.) Plan to go to Wednesday Night's 7:20 showing of the Shorts in the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Live Action&lt;/span&gt; Category.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Everyone is in charge of getting their own ticket.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will plan to be at "Kelly's" just around the corner for a pre-film drink starting at around 6:30, and will start &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;migration to the theater around 7:05.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss migration and do not see us in the lobby before going in, &lt;strong&gt;I will keep my phone (315-345-9348) on until they dim the lights, but after that you're on your own.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have not made it out to them previous years, but it seemed cool to do as some thing a little different. These are SHORT films, not full length features, they're each in the 10-25 minute range. (So 5 of them add up to your normal full length feature time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, I'm seeing the "Live Action" category on this evening, so be sure you get the right one as there is also a set of Animated and Documentaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If people wish to socialize about the films afterward, we can either do so in the lobby seating area or go back to Kelly's.&amp;nbsp; (It is a work night though, so I won't be out too late.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some thing to keep in mind: Everyone's got to start some where, and many great directors have had shorts nominated before they were famous for full length films.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a list of the films they are supposed to be showing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pentecost (Peter McDonald and Eimear O'Kane)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raju (Max Z&amp;auml;hle and Stefan Gieren)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Shore (Terry George and Oorlagh George)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time Freak (Andrew Bowler and Gigi Causey)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuba Atlantic (Hallvar Witz&amp;oslash;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look at Kelly's before hand or wait in the Lobby till 7:05.  If you miss us you can try to call AJ before the lights Dim: 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330042978000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329842213000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2012 Oscar Shorts @ Criterion: Live Action Category,  Drink before @ Kelly's</name><id>53189792</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329953400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/53189792/</event_url></item>