<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 N. Wilmot Rd.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03287</zip><lat>43.421871</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wilmot Public Library</name><city>Wilmot</city><id>1180179</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.935647</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;presented by the New Hampshire Humanities Council &amp;amp; the Wilmot Historical Society&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more than 200 years historians believed that Darby Field made the first climb up Mount Washington in 1642. However, in the last several decades, questions have emerged about his use of Native American guides, about the likelihood of prior ascents by Native Americans, about the route Field may have followed on the mountain, and about whether Field actually made the ascent as claimed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allen Koop, Dartmouth College, will examine how historians reconstruct the truth, when given scant, vague, and even contradictory evidence. Mr. Koop is an excellent lecturer having spoken at a previous Meetup last Fall entitled: White Mountain Huts Past and Present.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: I will be leading hike on this day somewhere in the local area.&lt;/b&gt;  More details to follow.  I am thinking of &lt;b&gt;Cardigan&lt;/b&gt;.  By starting from Cardigan State Park in Orange, it is only 45 minutes to Wilmot.  An early start time will allow us to make it to the presentation.  If anyone has any other hiking ideas please send me an email.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293569104000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265150884000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Washington Presentation - Darby Field &amp; the “First” Ascent? </name><id>12500601</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267390800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12500601/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/b/global_12924811.jpeg</photo_url></item>