<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Copley Square</address_2><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349493</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Public Library</name><city>Boston</city><id>1452790</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079011</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2nd Annual Boston Storytelling Festival at the Boston Public Library with massmouth, inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Attention families and fans of storytelling!  At the tail end of this February Vacation,&lt;strong&gt;massmouth, inc.&lt;/strong&gt; is offering a &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt; storytelling festival!  &lt;strong&gt;On Saturday, Feb 23rd, 2013 at the Boston Public Library&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9:30 am - 4:30 pm)&lt;/strong&gt; storytellers from &lt;strong&gt;massmouth, inc&lt;/strong&gt;. will make you laugh, sing and think as they present the art of storytelling through folk and fairy tales, songs, story slams and personal narrative. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The second annual Boston Storytelling Festival features a variety of storytelling experiences -- from workshops to traditional and contemporary storytelling to slams: the works. These events appeal to all ages and are accessible to everyone who has ever been intrigued by storytelling. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt; storytelling workshops will be offered for beginners and experts alike. The Boston Public Library's Rabb Lecture Hall will host ongoing concerts throughout the day that festival-goers can attend as they please. A score of acclaimed storytellers have signed on to perform, including several award-winning storytellers from &lt;strong&gt;massmouth&lt;/strong&gt; slams. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Traditional storytellers include: Judith Black, Doria Hughes, Norah Dooley, Andrea Lovett, Ben Cunningham, Jackson Gilman, Cindy Rivka Marshall, Katie Green and ToRena Webb Thomas. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Storytellers “for the 21st century” include: Scott Schultz (award winner, Big MouthOff Season 2), Ben Cunningham (award winner, Big MouthOff Season 2), Robin Maxfield, Norah Dooley, Andrea Lovett, Laura Packer, Kevin Brooks, Michael Anderson (award winner, Big MouthOff Season 1), Jackson Anderson, Katie Liesener (award winner, Big MouthOff Season 2. These storytellers will be joined by some of the winners from our Season 3 finale, which SOLD OUT at The Coolidge Corner Theater! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Best of all? Honoring our commitment to bring storytelling to the widest audience possible,&lt;strong&gt;massmouth,inc.&lt;/strong&gt; presents this entire event &lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt; and open to the public.  In order to secure a place in your workshop(s) of choice, pre-registration is strongly recommended but not required. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We look forward to seeing you on February 23, at what has become an annual celebration of the art of storytelling in its many forms in the city of Boston! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This program is sponsored in part by the Boston Public Library and &lt;strong&gt;massmouth, inc&lt;/strong&gt;. -- a 501(c)3 non-profit organization promoting the art of storytelling. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Storytelling has been entertaining human beings since time immemorial, but the art form doesn't always get the attention it deserves. Boston-based &lt;strong&gt;massmouth, inc&lt;/strong&gt;. is changing that. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In 2009 &lt;strong&gt;massmouth,inc&lt;/strong&gt;. hosted first story slam in Boston. Since then we have held hundreds of live events, taught thousands of people to tell their stories, including high school students in over 10 public schools, and have a robust online presence that includes audio, video and social media sites. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

"&lt;em&gt;Storytelling is our 'birthright' art.  We aim to reacquaint people&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;with their own creativity and imaginations. In doing so, we bring&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;people together in meaningful and rewarding way&lt;/em&gt;." – Norah Dooley, co-founder and Executive Director.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check us out on Facebook and Twitter, and at: &lt;a href="http://www.massmouth.com/"&gt;www.massmouth.com&lt;/a&gt;, www.massmouth.org, &lt;a href="http://www.massmouth.blogspot.com/"&gt;www.massmouth.blogspot.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/3/c/event_198203612.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361722069000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>storytellers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>storytelling-28</urlname><id>1247871</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Greater Boston and MA Storytelling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358910153000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Boston Storytelling Festival - FREE</name><id>100935952</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>25200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361629800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/storytelling-28/events/100935952/</event_url></item>