<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me at the Brattle to enjoy an afternoon of Alfred Hitchcock films: &lt;i&gt;The Man Who Knew Too Much&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;North by Northwest&lt;/i&gt;.  We'll meet and discuss after &lt;i&gt;North by Northwest&lt;/i&gt; and should finish up around 7:00, giving those of us that have to work the next day plenty of time to get home.  If you’re only able to see one of the films, please indicate your intention when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Man Who Knew Too Much&lt;/i&gt; (screens at 1:00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before the colorful 1950s remake starring Jimmy Stewart and Doris Day, Hitchcock made this suspenseful, black-and-white version of his tale about a couple whose son is kidnapped in order to keep them quiet about an assassination plot. The English-language debut of the immortal Peter Lorre (and a little-less-singing-thank-you-very-much) make this rarely screened gem well worth seeing, especially on the occasion of its 75th birthday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North by Northwest&lt;/i&gt; (screens at 2:45)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alfred Hitchcock’s stone-cold classic of mistaken identity, high adventure, and intrigue features Cary Grant as a suave executive who is mistaken for a spy by a group of nasty characters, and forced to uphold the charade both to stay alive, unravel whatever plot they are hatching, and get a little closer to the scrumptious Eva Marie Saint. Stunning action sequences and bold suspense abound in this Technicolor masterpiece! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it’s off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241976358000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hitchcock Double Feature: The Man Who Knew Too Much &amp; North by Northwest</name><id>10379588</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244394000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10379588/</event_url></item>