<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1285 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02189</zip><lat>42.195063</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-367-7397</phone><name>Julie Hart Fitness Studio</name><city>Weymouth</city><id>1120673</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.924401</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>FREE Boot Camp Class, Don't wait until New Years to start!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indoor Boot Camp class located at Julie Hart Fitness Studio 1285 Washington Street, Weymouth, MA. (rt 53)&lt;br /&gt;Date: December 12th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Time: 11 AM&lt;br /&gt;Description: 45 minutes of Boot Camp class followed by a 10 to 15 minute stretch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This boot Camp class will work your entire body, muscles and heart by going from one exercise to the next with little rest.  This workout will include calisthenics like pushups, jumping jacks, crunches and other body weight exercises... I will also add some weights into the mix.  It is time to challenge your body to the limit and burn calories like crazy! You can stick around for a Question and Answer type seminar on Nutrition and what Julie's Personal Training Studio offers after the stretch, so sign up today for this free class.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Max capacity: 12 people, Group members only.  (Closer to the event if space is available, this event will be opened to guests.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: annual members free, $2 members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, December 11th @ 5pm ~ Please see our No-Show Policy on the About Us page for more info on RSVP Deadlines. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***As this is a free event being offered with limited space, no-shows will be EXTREMELY frowned upon.  Please be courteous of other in the group if you rsvp yes and take that space.  ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please fill out a Medical History form which is in the Files Section saved as Julie Hart's form. You can bring it with you that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class offered by:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julie Armstrong&lt;br /&gt;Owner Julie Hart Fitness&lt;br /&gt;(781) 367-7397&lt;br /&gt;www.juliehartfitness.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4336960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260807101000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258935536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Boot Camp by Julie Hart Fitness</name><id>11934698</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260633600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11934698/</event_url></item>