<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This event will feature a presentation by Sivan Borowich, the Founder and President of Jewish Heart for Africa, at Harvard Kennedy School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jewish Heart for Africa (JHA) is a new non-profit organization that brings Israeli clean technology to rural African villages.  JHA aims to promote development in Africa through the use of clean, alternative energy in order to fight climate change and provide for sustainable economic development, while also improving the overall health and living standards in rural Africa.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jewish Heart for Africa is currently active in Ethiopia, Tanzania, and Uganda, and you can learn more about JHA and its projects at &lt;a href="http://www.jhasol.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jhasol.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also encourage you to RSVP at &lt;a href="http://www.jhasol.org/apresentation.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jhasol.org...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is sponsored by the Israel Caucus and the Jewish Caucus at Harvard Kennedy School.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sivan Borowich&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sivan Borowich is the Founder and President of Jewish Heart for Africa.  Born in Israel and raised in Nice, France, Sivan traces her roots back to the African continent where her father was born in Algeria and her mother in Tunisia.  Sivan first traveled to Africa as part of her work for a multinational clothing company, verifying compliance issues in the company's African manufacturing facilities.  Sivan was immediately moved by the pervasive poverty she witnessed and began to look for ways to transform and improve the lives of African people.  Following a brief stint as a mortgage banker, Sivan joined the United Nations Development Program (UNDP) and developed the groundwork for what became Jewish Heart for Africa.  Sivan graduated summa cum laude with a degree in finance from Pace University and hold's a master's degree in international energy management and policy from Columbia University's School of International and Public Affairs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250117733000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235751011000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Solar Power from Israel: Catalyzing Development in Africa</name><id>9837723</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236895200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/9837723/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/b/global_7476379.jpeg</photo_url></item>