<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>418 State St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305546</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-772-0544</phone><name>Olde School Saloon and Bistro</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1207967</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Olde School Saloon and Bistro&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;From Dev: Some people break for animals. I break for new restaurants : )  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I drove down State Street and saw that a new place was opening... I had to stop by. The staff was friendly, and the smells coming from the kitchen were amazing – and apparently prepared by one of the owners (I have a soft spot for the places where the owner’s in the back, working harder than anyone).  The owners are also active in the community, as they’re both teachers for ACES, and work with troubled youth.  These seem like good, genuine people.  Yep, they’re old school alright!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Olde School Saloon and Bistro is located at State near Court St, across from the train station.  From the vintage copper bar right down to the classic antique punch-button cash register, this is a great place.  The smell of brisket, corned beef, or their yucca fries with chipotle sauce doesn’t hurt their charm either : )&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;They have generously offered to start their usual great Monday evening special early for us.  25 cents wings (and not just buffalo - they also do caribbean jerk and garlic rosemary!) and $2 Miller and Miller Lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The contact for this event is Dev, phone number in RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://oldeschoolsaloonandbistro.com/Olde_School/Home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://oldeschoolsalo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268690565000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267714056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Olde School Saloon and Bistro</name><id>12781257</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268089200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/12781257/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/a/global_13448554.jpeg</photo_url></item>