<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Where Rte 27 &amp; Rte 16 overlap</address_2><address_1>2 N Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 655-2143</phone><name>The Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>322287</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We hope you've set aside Sunday, July 15, 1 PM for the chance to be&lt;br /&gt;together and explore the unique and wonderful setting of the Peace Abbey,&lt;br /&gt;visit the animals, enjoy a great vegan potluck meal, and hear Will&lt;br /&gt;Tuttle, PhD speak on his book _The Word Peace Diet_. His presentation&lt;br /&gt;will include an interlude of his original piano music, and his book and&lt;br /&gt;CDs will be for sale and signing afterwards -- a good chance to buy gifts&lt;br /&gt;for those you care about. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or shine, it will be a beautiful day. Please bring friends, family,&lt;br /&gt;and non-vegetarians -- we especially want non-vegetarians to experience a&lt;br /&gt;fabulous vegan meal and hear this speaker! But never hesitate to come&lt;br /&gt;alone; lot's do, and we're a friendly group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below are the details you'll need:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) RSVP&lt;br /&gt;2) Volunteering&lt;br /&gt;3) Donation for the Peace Abbey&lt;br /&gt;4) Car pooling&lt;br /&gt;5) Directions to Peace Abbey&lt;br /&gt;6) Free parking&lt;br /&gt;7) Logistics - Seating, rest rooms, speaker site&lt;br /&gt;8) Overnight accommodations on site&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It helps us to plan, so please hit &amp;quot;Reply&amp;quot; and give the names of people&lt;br /&gt;attending. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) CAR POOLING - DRIVERS needed - all replies by Thursday. 7/12 5 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Car pooling is a good way to meet some people before arriving at the&lt;br /&gt;event, and to save fuel resources. Riders, please offer to chip in for&lt;br /&gt;gas. Here's how it works:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you CAN GIVE or need a ride, please reply by Thurs., 7/12 at 5 PM,&lt;br /&gt;using the below format only, so I can quickly cut and paste info into a&lt;br /&gt;group e-mail. On Thurs. PM, I'll compile the responses and send them to&lt;br /&gt;the group. Then respondents can get in touch with each other to work out&lt;br /&gt;their own arrangements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please reply only in this format**:&lt;br /&gt;Your Name&lt;br /&gt;Your E-mail Address&lt;br /&gt;Your Phone Number&lt;br /&gt;Can you give a ride? / Do you need a ride?&lt;br /&gt;Your Town (or where you can meet)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Peace Abbey&lt;br /&gt;2 North Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Where Route 27 and Route 16 overlap&lt;br /&gt;Sherborn, MA (next to Natick, 35-40 min. west of Boston) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;From Boston:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 West and exit at Route 16 in Wellesley. The Rt. 16 sign is&lt;br /&gt;easy to miss, but it follows a yellow blinking light and a sign for Mass&lt;br /&gt;Bay Community College. Turn left at end of ramp onto Rt. 16 West.&lt;br /&gt;Follow directions below from Rt. 16 exit off Mass Pike.&lt;br /&gt;~ OR ~&lt;br /&gt;Take the Mass Pike West to Exit 16 (Wellesley) Take Route 16 West,&lt;br /&gt;winding scenically through Wellesley, Natick, and into Sherborn. Watch&lt;br /&gt;carefully the Rt. 16 signs, because Rt. 16 takes some sharp left turns. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*You are almost at the Peace Abbey* when you see the Sherborn Inn on your&lt;br /&gt;right, then the Sherborn Fire House (white) on your left. When you ride&lt;br /&gt;over a small railroad track, and go up a small hill, the Peace Abbey is&lt;br /&gt;just ahead on your left, just after an area of trees. There are signs&lt;br /&gt;and a large statue of Gandhi out front.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;From the West:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 East, then take Route 27 South through Natick and into&lt;br /&gt;Sherborn. Rt. 27 will overlap with Rt. 16 in Sherborn, so see directions&lt;br /&gt;above for landmarks on Rt. 16/27.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6) FREE PARKING&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a) The small paved lot at the Abbey will be for special needs / handicap&lt;br /&gt;parking, speakers, and press ONLY. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;b) Street parking: Approaching from the north (that is, if you are on&lt;br /&gt;Rt. 16W or Rt. 27S, which overlap), pass the Peace Abbey driveway on your&lt;br /&gt;left. Go just beyond the Gandhi statue and take the next left. Park&lt;br /&gt;along this road &amp;quot;Village Way&amp;quot; ON ONE SIDE OF THE ROAD ONLY. Two sided&lt;br /&gt;parking is *not allowed*. This road leads to a housing complex. Park&lt;br /&gt;ONLY along the entrance road. Do *NOT* park in the visitor or resident&lt;br /&gt;spaces for the housing park!&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: They will tow cars parked where I've said not to park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;c) Church lot: We can park in the Unitarian Universalist Church lot&lt;br /&gt;just a 2-3 minute walk from the Peace Abbey. This is where the speaker&lt;br /&gt;presentation will be. If you like, you can drop off your potluck dish at&lt;br /&gt;the Peace Abbey gate, then go park. We'll put your dish on the stone&lt;br /&gt;fence till you return. Approaching from the north, pass the Peace Abbey&lt;br /&gt;on your left, and you will face a fork in the road. Go to *right* of&lt;br /&gt;fork (Rt. 16). Continue a very short bit further and you'll see the U.U.&lt;br /&gt;Church (white wooden historic church) on your left. Park in the lots on&lt;br /&gt;both sides of the church. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7) LOGISTICS - to make your visit easy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walk up the wooden ramp into the main building to the kitchen. There&lt;br /&gt;will be seating for eating on the main level, plus go down the stairs&lt;br /&gt;(via the kitchen) to the large basement room, where there will be lots of&lt;br /&gt;tables and chairs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rest rooms are on this lower/basement level. When we move to the&lt;br /&gt;church for the speaker program, there are rest rooms there, too, just&lt;br /&gt;behind the speaker room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;beverage station&amp;quot; will be set up just outside the kitchen, on the&lt;br /&gt;lawn. It's smart to bring your own water bottle, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 2:50 please start your stroll to the white church for our speaker program at 3 PM!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184692335000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184328114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BVS Peace Abbey event...vegan potluck and a speaker!</name><id>6018265</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184518800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/6018265/</event_url></item>