<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.406082</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781) 648-4340</phone><name>Capitol Theater</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Shahrukh Khan and Yash Chopra's new movie is releasing in 2 weeks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://yashrajfilms.com/Movies/MovieIndividual.aspx?MovieID=8e90dfac-ef4c-4e33-ad47-8dbaf15bfcf7" target="_blank"&gt;http://yashrajfilms.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Capitol Theater, 204 Mass Ave, Arlington, MA 02474. Tel 781.648.6022&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets can be bought online at &lt;a href="http://bombaycinema.com/beta/index1.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://bombaycinema.com/beta/index1.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://bombaycinema.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will highly recommend buying tickets early as tickets might be sold out. I bought mine already.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sypnosis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever stopped to think if the most ordinary, uninteresting, unobtrusive man you might see on the road or around you might have a love story to tell?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe not! How can an ordinary man have a breathtaking, goose flesh igniting, awe inspiring love story of all things to tell?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But guess what - love does not differentiate between the ordinary and exceptional, the uninteresting and interesting, the unattractive and attractive. Because love knows no distinction. It can happen to anyone and once it does it engulfs us into it completely and gives us those miraculous experiences that only love can yield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what happened to Surinder Sahni (Shahrukh Khan) - a simple, clean hearted, honest man working for Punjab Power, leading a humdrum life, when he meets his total opposite and finds love in the flamboyant, fun-loving, vivacious - Taani (Anushka Sharma) for whom the whole world is her canvas and she paints her own life with the colours of rainbow all until unforeseen circumstances changes it all and brings them together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What follows is a journey filled with laughter, tears, joy, pain, music, dance and a lot of love. A journey that makes us believe that there is an extraordinary love story in every ordinary jodi.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let us meet inside the theater in the lobby at 1:45. My cell is 508 314 7742.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230407725000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227770445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bollywood Movie Night - Shahrukh Khan Movie - Rab Ne Bana di Jodi </name><id>9238716</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229194800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/9238716/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/9/global_4274761.jpeg</photo_url></item>