<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>292 Centre Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.358246</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-527-7726</phone><name>Prana Restaurant</name><city>Newton Corner</city><id>1033348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thepranacafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thepranaca...&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I still haven't figured out how to insert images so I'll have to encourage you to go to the website and see the raw yummy goodness for yourself.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Prana Website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our food is prepared with love and is Raw*, Organic, and Vegan. We use no animal products or processed food of any kind. Every dish is dairy free. Some selections contain nuts. &lt;b&gt;We also offer a variety of gluten-free options.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the freshest, most vibrant food that you can eat. And it makes you feel good! Now you can, quite literally “have your (chocolate ganache) cake and eat it too.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Congratulations on treating yourself to the very best – starting now with what you are putting into your body.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We put only the finest, freshest, cleanest, most amazing ingredients into our Raw Vegan Organic food, so that you will feel and be the finest, freshest, cleanest, and most amazing ever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taste what really fresh food tastes like – prepared just for you today. And watch your body, your attitude, and your life transform.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please note that our fabulous menu is life like, ever changing, according to the flow of the Universe (and the availability of Organic ingredients). As such, certain items may not be always be available. Much gratitude in advance for your understanding, and see you soon at The Cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*There are a few non-raw options on our menu for our “transitioning” friends.&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255977551000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254709537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Late Lunch at Prana  Cafe in Newton</name><id>11548129</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255804200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/11548129/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>