<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a double feature with the Touch of Evil showing afterward.  I am not going to see the Touch of Evil (did about 7 mos. ago at MFA), but others are welcome to stick around as it is included in your $12 admission.  Welles' daughter Chris Welles Feder will be at the Brattle between the two movies at an earlier showing (1,3:40).  She has written a book, IN MY FATHERS SHADOW, and will be discussing that (and selling it!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: The Brattle flier states the showtime as 5:45.  They have changed this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the showing of Lady from Shanghai we will go to a local restaurant/pub to discuss (Hey they have a Doyles in Harvard Square too!) .  If you're going to join us mention that in your response, or say you're sticking around for the second feature (Touch of Evil).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Brattle site: &lt;br /&gt;(1947) dir Orson Welles, w/w/Welles, Rita Hayworth, Everett Sloane [87 min] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the most deliriously beautiful, prodigiously crazy films ever made. At once Welles' farewell to his estranged wife Rita Hayworth and a seriocomic exploration of the everyday viciousness of the rich and powerful, this remains one of his most consistently inventive films. The convoluted story, featuring an itinerant sailor (Welles at his most endearingly hammy) who falls for a radiant young woman of mystery (Hayworth) while falling in with her treacherous husband (Sloane) and his cohorts, allows Welles to create an inside-out world, leading to a spectacular shoot-out in a hall of mirrors. – Notes from the Jacob Burns Film Center &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RottenTomatoes synopsis (RT rating 85)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/lady_from_shanghai/#" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rottentoma...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Synopsis: THE LADY FROM SHANGHAI, an atmospheric film noir based on Sherwood King's novel IF I DIE BEFORE I WAKE, features Orson Welles as producer, director, co-screenwriter, and star. Welles plays rogue... THE LADY FROM SHANGHAI, an atmospheric film noir based on Sherwood King's novel IF I DIE BEFORE I WAKE, features Orson Welles as producer, director, co-screenwriter, and star. Welles plays rogue seaman Michael O'Hara, complete with Irish brogue. After saving beautiful Elsa Bannister (Rita Hayworth) from thieves in Central Park, O'Hara is requested to serve on the yacht owned by Elsa's husband, Arthur (Welles veteran Everett Sloane), an older man who needs special crutches in order to walk. A fiery passion lurks underneath the relationship between Michael and Elsa; in actuality, the marriage between Welles and Hayworth was ending at the time the film was shot. Enter George Grisby (the eerie-sounding Glenn Anders), one of Bannister's associates and a man with a very special offer for O'Hara, luring him into a web of lies and murder. Although Welles claimed he made THE LADY FROM SHANGHAI just to finance other projects and the film does not show off his typical Wellesian flair, it still plays like a classic noir that draws the viewer in and never lets go. The characters are complex and fascinating, and the tension runs high and hot as the truth behind all the lies starts to come out. The film is most famous for its thrilling climax, which takes place in a hall of mirrors. Welles might have considered THE LADY FROM SHANGHAI workmanlike, but this noir thriller is only as workmanlike as any Welles film can be.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the Movie, right side of the theater near the screen.  Should have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276007416000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275589631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Lady from Shanghai</name><id>13686929</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275861600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13686929/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/5/0/global_15481872.jpeg</photo_url></item>