<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Garden St &amp; Waterhouse St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>7813011791 (Chris' Cell)</phone><name>Cambridge Common</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>442822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yes, indeed, it's true: the holidays are upon us. And with the holidays (no matter which you celebrate!) comes eating. Lots and lots of eating. And you know what? That's not such a bad thing. Eating is one of my favorite activities. For me, eating really only comes second to one other activity: shopping. Er, I mean, frisbee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO. With that in mind, do come out to play frisbee at 7 PM on Cambridge Common (right near Hahhhvard Square.) I will arrive with the glowing frisbees and the warm, cozy welcomes. And you will arrive as well and we will play frisbee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me emphasize that we are so, so welcoming to newcomers. Even though it's the beginning of December and I know, I know, it's cold out -- regardless of all that, you should still show up. And all the veterans too. Don't let a little &amp;quot;wintry mix&amp;quot; get you down. Meteorologists don't know what they're talking about -- it's not like they went to school to study the weather or anything. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO. We will probably stop playing frisbee right around 9:30. BUT. Don't think you are free to go after that. I will lasso each and every one of you together and drag you all out to Herrell's or Uno's or whatever strikes our fancy. And we will eat and warm up and smile and enjoy each other. There will be snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on the field with your mittens and your scarves and your smiles. &lt;br /&gt;- Chris (the gluttonous one.)&lt;br /&gt;781 301 1791 (call me and we can chat for hours. for fun.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(PS. you know what's really cute? Children that look like big fluffy balls in all their winter gear.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197590590000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197256721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Frisbee Bonanza on Cambridge Common</name><id>6886003</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197417600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/6886003/</event_url></item>