<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358156</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>708011</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063692</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Every year Boston By Foot creates the Big Foot tour - a spectacular that is given on Labor Day and that lasts 5 hours.  This year's tour is entitled &amp;quot;Don't Tread on Me: Transformative Movements in Boston, 1620 to Present Day&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the very beginning, Bostonians have been restless rabble-rousers.  We threw a whole ship of tea in the harbor to protest unfair taxes and that lead to the creation of our country.  That's the history we all learn in school.  But that's not all of the social change that started in Boston and this tour is gonna show the rest to you.  Learn more about religious movements, rights of African Americans, rights of women, public school education, and the labor movements on this tour that starts at the State House, winds down around Beacon Hill, follows the Freedom Trail for a bit, marches though the factories in Chinatown, and ends up in the Public Garden.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the tour we'll all be heading over to the Taj Hotel for some refreshments and a sit down.  You can chat with Nerds and the BBF guides about all you've seen and learned.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Fine Print:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour starts promptly at 10:00am.  The cost is $15 per person ($5 each if you are a card-carrying member of Boston By Foot - &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;click here to sign up&lt;/a&gt;).  Please show up early to pay and get organized into groups.  We expect a large turnout, so earlier is better.  Look for me wearing both a Meetup Button and a Boston By Foot button.  I'll be handing out Meetup stickers too so you know who is part of the Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252845601000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251737117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Epic BBF walking tour - Don't Tread on Me: Transformative Movements in Boston</name><id>11247304</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252331100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11247304/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/global_5310283.jpeg</photo_url></item>