<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome-Introductions Gathering-- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mission- Find a monogamous, long term-life time partner or marriage! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date and Time: Feb. 9, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: &lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth &lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington St. &lt;br /&gt;Burlington, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Format: &lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, loving and relaxing environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $10.00 &lt;br /&gt;DJ -  Dancing will be available &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your last name begins with the following- please bring: Will change monthly: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A-G - Desert and a bottle of wine &lt;br /&gt;H-P - Appetizer and bottle of wine &lt;br /&gt;Q-Z-  Entree and soft drink or water &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer and Host Home &lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host- Richard Tosti &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. &amp;quot;Time of party: 6:00PM -11:00pm&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;2. &amp;quot; Dress code- &amp;quot;business casual&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;3. &amp;quot;You can enjoy the music and dance if you like&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purpose is to Socialize with similar people of our age who are searching for a lifetime partner. &lt;br /&gt;40-65 age group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I began these parties in my home in July 2006-twice a month &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our common Values: Common denominator &lt;br /&gt;Have fun meeting old and new friends &lt;br /&gt;Circulate, talk to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;If someone is alone go up to them and say hi! &lt;br /&gt;Nonsmokers &lt;br /&gt;Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are coming because you got this email, this is your invitation. Please invite other friends, Particularly men. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is not necessary to inform me that we have more woman. I know that fact. Women are more gregarious and open-minded than many men. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all need to exert an effort to invite men.  &lt;br /&gt;This group was formed on the principle of synergy.  Working together to invite quality people. It is our job to take responsibility for inviting people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can sign up on &lt;a href="http://dance.meetup.com/393/"&gt;http://dance.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You do not need to email me personally. &lt;br /&gt;250 guests only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the time, the location , what you should bring.  Let's have fun!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions &lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth &lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;Burlington,MA  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128 North &lt;br /&gt;Exit 32 B Middlesex Tpk (Burlington/Arlington) &lt;br /&gt;Fork right-Middlesex Tpk Burlington-on the left is Burlington Dodge/Barnes/Noble &lt;br /&gt;Right on to Burlington Mall Rd-on left is Longs Jewelers &lt;br /&gt;Take left after Kohls-Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;Burlington MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three Parking lots on the right side of building.  Enter through the side entrance . &lt;br /&gt;Park in Rear lot first.&lt;br /&gt;Also, Two houses up is a Church, park there also. Then walk 1/10 of mile&lt;br /&gt;See you on Feb. 9th &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blinking light at entrance of 16 Lexington St. Burlington, MA
My Rd Town and Country Van will be at entrance to parking lot.
Our building is brick. On the left side of road, coming from Mall Rd.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203018976000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>48</count></rating><why>Because we had 75 women on Jan. 5th and 60 men.

Our goal for Feb. 9th is 100 women and 100 men.</why><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>243</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199718480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction Gatherings - Private Singles Party-Special Valentines Dance </name><id>7053497</id><headcount>155</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202598000000</time><rsvp_limit>250</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/7053497/</event_url></item>