<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>334 S Water St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821033</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mile and A Quarter</name><city>Providence</city><id>10109582</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.404701</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and event scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Mile and A Quarter!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, so this location is where the old Barnsiders "used to be", but really that's been gone so long I don't think it really counts, but let's just mention it for old times sake. If you've been paying attention to the S Water Street area, you might have noticed that they've been preparing to open for a few months now......at long last, the time is here and they opened last week!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I popped in the other night to check it out and wow - it seems like a  great new addition to neighborhood! The bar and lounge area are spacious and comfortable, the drink selection is great and the food looks good too. With a decor of warm, neutral contemporary leather and dark wood, the bar/lounge area in the front of the restaurant is perfect for a casual cocktail after work and for a nice dinner, the more intimate dining room over looking the river is perfect. They even have a small bar in the dining are for those interested in a little quieter setting then the lounge. Overall, I was very impressed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, here we go on our first NEW RESTAURANT ALERT Monday Night Meetup, and let's check it out!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the brown and pink scarf in my picture, but we're hard to miss and very friendly!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352527511000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351808598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Mile and a Quarter! NEW RESTAURANT ALERT!!!!</name><id>89540572</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352156400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/89540572/</event_url></item>