<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The low for Tuesday night is 28 degrees. Is that going to stop us from kicking some butt in frisbee? Nay, I say! Nay! Frisbee lives on! A little below freezing weather isn't going to stop us! We will fight onward and upward through the spring. Snow will cower in fear at our greatness! I refuse to be beaten by a mere 28 degrees. It's going to take a lot more degrees than that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I love exclamation points!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You got all that? SO. We'll meet around 7 pm on Cambridge Common (outside Harvard Square), throw the discs around for a while and learn each other's names and jolly red faces, then play ultimate starting around 7:30. All are welcome, regardless of skill level -- just as long as you want to have fun and bring all your inner sunshine to the field! And maybe some heat, that would be great.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually call it quits between 9:30 and 10, but considering the weather, who knows how long we'll actually last. If someone turns into a big ice cube out there, we probably will be accommodating and call it a night so they can thaw somewhere nice and warm. Somewhere like Uno's or Tealuxe for warm beverages, snacks or (brr) ice cream -- everyone is encouraged to come along. It's really great to get to know some of the people we've been playing frisbee with in the dark. Especially YOU ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;- Chris (the fat one.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;781 301 1791 (Add me to your address book so I will feel cool and loved.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196394732000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196049558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frisbee and Freezing on the Common</name><id>6803000</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196208000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/6803000/</event_url></item>