<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Ipswich St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347467</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-437-0300 </phone><name>Jillians</name><city>Boston</city><id>790541</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094019</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Boston Couples, its the first Friday night of Spring and how better to celebrate then with a night of bowling in a happening location.&amp;nbsp; Jillians on the same block as Fenway Park has 3 levels of bars, games and bowling plus there are a ton of lively bars near by to go to after words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost is $6 per game and approximately $4 for shoes.&amp;nbsp; Even if you don't want to bowl still come and hangout with us it will be fun.&amp;nbsp; This event is being co-hosted with Ex-Midwestern meetup group so its a great opportunity to come and meet some new people you may not have had a chance to meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is 145 Ipswich in Boston right by Fenway so its right of the Greenline(Kenmore stop) for people taking the T or there are blocks of street parking around and since the Sox are not playing yet you should have pretty good luck finding a spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP as soon as possible because there is limited space.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the front lobby at the Bowling Level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve rosen</member_name><member_id>3640517</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301165584000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Everybody loves to hang out and bowl, ok maybe most people love to "roll some strikes"!  But I know everybody loves to hang out in a fun social setting and Jillians is great.  Three levels with bars, games and lots of drinks!  Plus its Friday night!</why><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300283768000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bowling at Jillians by Fenway-Friday March 25th 6:30</name><id>16942002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301092200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/16942002/</event_url></item>