<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>936-1150 Pawtucket Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.642242</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>lowell boat ramp</name><city>lowell</city><id>2486761</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.374939</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday nights Heritage Farm Ice Cream of Lowell puts on FREE concerts across the street at The Sampas pavilion. They also sponsor a classic car show (begins at 6pm) -cars from days gone by. Full schedule is here: &lt;a href="http://heritagefarmicecream.com/index.php?link=11" class="linkified"&gt;http://heritagefarmicecream.com/index.php?link=11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's put boats in at the Lowell ramp just upstream from the Brunswick bowling lanes. Paddle downstream about 1 1/2 miles to the Sampas Pavilion and idle there to enjoy the music. Be sure to bring stern lights and a headlamp for safety. Bug spray, some snacks and beverages would be wise as well. Also, there is a landing ramp alongside the park with a whopping 500' walk to yummy ice cream! Total paddle length will be a torturous 5 miles if we're lucky. If you're late, don't worry. Hit the water, take a left and listen for music. If you go over the Pawtucket falls, you went too far. (..and maybe you're deaf too. Bummer.) &lt;br /&gt;

As always, my cell is 603.557.6055&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who know me - I don't have a problem getting wet. If it rains though, the live music doesn't happen since this is an open air venue. We'll cancel the event and try again next Monday&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Featured this week: THE MIGHTY BAD HABITS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mighty Bad Habits continue to soar to new heights playing rock &amp;amp; roll, funk, and the blues in it's purest form. The Mighty Bad habits have proven that the blues as well as rock &amp;amp; roll are alive and here to stay&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill_J</member_name><member_id>4839704</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344348463000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343824308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enjoy FREE, Live music kayaking on the Merrimack</name><id>75826392</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344290400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/75826392/</event_url></item>