<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This time we will be meeting at &lt;a href="http://www.bentara.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Bentara&lt;/a&gt; again! The speaker will start at 6.30.  Schmoozing begins 5:45 and continues from 7:30 onwards after the speakers. &lt;b&gt;Please RSVP&lt;/b&gt; so we know how many to expect, thanks!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker Aaron Sherrill shares his experiences in the industry as a Flash developer. Aaron will be discussing techniques for improving your online portfolio with simple tricks and tips to get the most out of your work. If you don't have an online portfolio, fear not, Aaron will be offering complementary flash galleries and free hosting through a site he has started for the Greater New Haven Design and Marketing Meetup Group.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Aaron Sherrill is Senior Interactive Developer for Digital Surgeons, LLC, a full service internet marketing and design agency in New Haven, CT. Aaron specializes in creating dynamic, intuitive, and stylish web presences for companies looking to capitalize on the internet's ability to reach their broad audience. His clients include MasterCard World Wide, Alize, Heineken, MTV, eTrade, Guess Watches, and Dyson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;David&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PS - Speakers needed for future events, please volunteer!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have reserved the back part of the restaurant for our event. See you there!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alicia Guzman</member_name><member_id>5290549</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 6649257</member_name><member_id>6649257</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215534641000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>6</count></rating><why>To meet other members of the community and to hear about how designers and marketers can work together.</why><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207176954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GNH Design and Marketing May Meeting</name><id>7660834</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210801500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/7660834/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/c/global_701868.jpeg</photo_url></item>