<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;OhMiGosh, Michael, this place sounds like a blast!  Of course I have heard of it, but I've never been.  Well I certainly will now!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.medievalmanor.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Medieval Manor&lt;/a&gt; is a place where we get dinner and a show.  It's a very unique experience.  Everyone will &amp;quot;fool&amp;quot; around during dinner. Awaiting you is a bawdy extravaganza often imitated but never equaled.  In this recently updated rollicking romp through the middle ages, the minstrel, jester, oaf and wenches respond to the Lord of the Manor's every whim with song, story and slapstick while sweeping you up in the fun.  As spirits flow and Canterbury beckons, laughter and camaraderie will soon reveal why so many return so often for such foolishness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As guests of the King, you're also offered a six course banquet eaten without fork, knife or spoon.  It begins with warm loaves of bread, pepper cheese trenchers and faux Dragon soup.  Mixed shellfish, beef ribs and salad precede the final course, roasted herbed chicken with steamed vegetables.  Vegetarian substitutes and cakes (some customers bring cupcakes) are available with 24 hours notice. There are plenty of napkins to keep fingers dry and tidy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All shows have the same adult content (self rated at PG-15) suitable for most families with older children.  While there is no nudity or network TV banned words, there are puns, sight gags and other sexually suggestive comedic material unacceptable to some regardless of age.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The feast is $35.00 per person, but includes the show and a flagon of beer, wine or lemonade.  I'll need to give a head count and pay a deposit of $10 pp to make reservations, so please reserve your seat ASAP by paying a $10 deposit via Paypal.  The cutoff date to reserve for this event will be November 14th.  Hope to see ya there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you prefer vegetarian, please indicate that when you RSVP because I need a 24 hour notice.  thanks.&lt;br /&gt;debbie &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael B</member_name><member_id>2958968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196642380000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>divorcesupport-249</urlname><id>368805</id><group_lat>42.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston/Burbs Life after Divorce Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193976460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Medieval Manor</name><id>6660818</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196469000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/divorcesupport-249/events/6660818/</event_url></item>