<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What We Have to Fear . . . is Fear Itself&lt;br /&gt;a workshop with Father Pether Bowes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More people are enslaved by fear than by any other force on earth. Fear prevents us from the kind of dynamic relationships for which many of us long, while foiling great ideas and important breakthroughs. Fear makes both taking risks and experiencing life changes that bring new energy and joy nearly impossible. In this seminar, we will discuss how we become trapped by fear, how to liberate ourselves from fear, and how to live life fully, in faith, confidence, and joy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** refreshments will be served **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has devoted his life in service to God; for over 20 years, he has served as a Priest and Master Teacher. Currently, he serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ Sophia, teaching and ministering to his spiritual students, and guiding thirteen Centers of Light and their ministers around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father Peter's music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Center of Light in Jamaica Plain is located just around the corner from the Stony Brook T stop on the orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210548744000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206765629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What We Have to Fear . . . is Fear Itself</name><id>7625672</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210375800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/7625672/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/8/global_1017208.jpeg</photo_url></item>