<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1815 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.387146</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-354-7766</phone><name>Tavern in the Square - Porter</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>859456</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118996</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's time again for Science by the Pint.&amp;nbsp; This time the Tavern has promised us more tables and space, so let's go grab us a few of them.&amp;nbsp; Based on last month's experience, I'm not guaranteeing everyone will get to sit together, but we'll give it a shot.&amp;nbsp; The event starts at 7:00, but I'm gathering us at 6:30 so we have a better chance (you can come later if you like). Depending on the level of interest, I'll shoot Marshall at SITN an email and see if he can help us save a few tables for Nerd Fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From SITN:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 13px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Today  is the first Tuesday of the month, and you know what that means: SITN  is hosting an all new Science by the Pint a week from today! Come join  us Tuesday, March 8th at 7pm at the Tavern in the Square in Porter  Square to meet Alex Bradley and his colleagues, who will talk about  molecular fossils and evolution. Alex will briefly introduce his  research and take some questions before he and his colleagues mingle  from group to group answering your questions about his work and science  in general.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The Tavern in the Square has guaranteed us five more tables than  last time in addition to lots of mingling space at the bar and between  tables. There will be waiters/waitresses to take your orders for table  service this time, or you can purchase food and drinks at the bar. If  you're planning on taking advantage of the great menu for your dinner  next Tuesday, make sure to arrive early so you have your food during  Science by the Pint. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We'll also raffle one $10 gift certificate for every ten people who come. We hope to see you a week from today!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The SITN staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a Meetup sign and try to garner us a few tables</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299670522000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299067272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science by the Pint: Molecular Fossils and Evolution</name><id>16765083</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299627000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/16765083/</event_url></item>