<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Finding the New Creative: Convergences in Fine Art and Commercial Photography&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, January 17, 2008&lt;br /&gt;6pm&lt;br /&gt;Location to be announced &lt;br /&gt;FREE&lt;br /&gt;Reception at the PRC to follow&lt;br /&gt;This program is co-presented with The Ad Club and AIGA Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The PRC is pleased to present this panel discussion in conjunction with its current exhibition AD | AGENCY. The exhibition features fine art photographers who utilize the visual language of consumer culture and commercial photography to explore the cycle of consumption. This panel will explore the shifting and dissolving boundary between fine art and commercial photography, as commercial clients strive for a unique ?vision? to associate with their products. Topics to be discussed include the growing trend of fine art photographers being hand picked for commercial jobs, how industry-based photographers have fostered a fine art aesthetic in their work, what art directors and designers look for when producing breakthrough advertising campaigns, and how creative directors integrate photographic images into brand identity. This is a must for all photographers looking to expand their client base as well as all designers and art and creative directors seeking new approaches for their creative material.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists&lt;br /&gt;John Goodman, world renowned photographer (www.goodmanphoto.com);&lt;br /&gt;Adam Larson, award winning designer and Founder/Creative Director of Adam&amp;amp;Co. a studio specializing in creative direction, illustration, and design (www.adamncompany.com);&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Moehlenkamp, Executive Vice President and Chief Creative Officer at Hill&lt;br /&gt;Holiday, a full capability, multi city, communications agency (www.hhcc.com);&lt;br /&gt;Kathryn Tyrrel, Photographer Representative at Stockland Martel, one of America's premiere photo agencies, (www.stocklandmartel.com); &lt;br /&gt;Gary Leopold, President and CEO at ISM, Boston's premiere marketing agency for travel and leisure companies, will moderate the panel (www.ismboston.com).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a reception at the PRC following the panel. Enjoy this special opportunity to view AD | AGENCY while networking with new friends and colleagues&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200937573000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199277178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Finding the New Creative: Convergences in Fine Art and Commercial Photography</name><id>7011171</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200610800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/7011171/</event_url></item>