<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Ensign Dr</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06001</zip><lat>41.811771</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>residence inn</name><city>Avon</city><id>1561542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.834343</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/5/9/event_22017689.jpeg" width="215" height="214" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Janice and Sonja are back after a winter of surgeries, crutches and no hiking.&amp;nbsp; I am starting my promised recovery hikes to usher in the Spring.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This will be a 100% beginners event.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; There will be paved trails and zero verticle gain.&amp;nbsp; No special hiking equipment is required and sneakers are acceptable.&amp;nbsp; I would bring water and maybe a camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will park at the Marriott in Avon and walk over to the rail trail that hugs the Farmington river.&amp;nbsp; This is an out and back walk of no more than 3 miles.&amp;nbsp; If the river recedes in the next few days, we may take a detour.&amp;nbsp; Our pace will be determined but it is not a race and fast is not required.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those of you who are used to my usual (6 to 10 miles climbing something) hike will need to be patient.&amp;nbsp; Pay attention to the calendar for some interesting stuff coming up soon. All are welcome to come and reconnect after the long snowy winter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can all stay for lunch as we will be in walking distance from First and Last but other suggestions are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am being more relaxed about number of attendees because parking is unlimited and there are no serious risks, except crossing Rt. 10 and 202. I will be, though,&amp;nbsp;the only leader that day.&amp;nbsp; But still with me, no dogs and no children please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Start the season off active!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Mapquest link to the parking area&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?name=Residence+Inn+by+Marriott&amp;amp;city=Avon&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=15+Ensign+Dr&amp;amp;zipcode=06001&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.812531&amp;amp;longitude=-72.833412&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=261516023"&gt;http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?name=Residence+Inn+by+Marriott&amp;amp;city=Avon&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=15+Ensign+Dr&amp;amp;zipcode=06001&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.812531&amp;amp;longitude=-72.833412&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=261516023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Residence Inn Marriott, 15 Ensign Dr. Avon CT 06001</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300715278000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>You have been sitting on your doopa all winter.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300108547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recovery walk at the Rail Trail, Avon CT</name><id>16913798</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300543200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/16913798/</event_url></item>