<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;THIS IS A JOINT EVENT. PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP IF YOU ARE IN OTHER GROUPS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kitty OSheas is an awesome spot to host another Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party for 160 members on Friday Feb 20, 2009. This is not a Singles party. Anyone can come which means &lt;b&gt;couples and singles are welcome&lt;/b&gt; to party and socialize.&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty OSheas is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St  Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100   Website &lt;a href="http://www.kittyosheasboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kittyoshea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2nd floor can hold 160 people. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/shock.gif' border='0' alt='shock' /&gt; There are 2 Bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor, plus its own bathroom upstairs so we would truly have our own private party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Note: Music will medium levels in main room upstairs. Music will be tuned very low in the back room so members can have a separate area to chat!&lt;br /&gt;Till about 9PM them the Dancing and music starts, then its gets loud please do not complain since people came to dance and hear the music too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 Bartender upstairs: 2 at the upfront Bar and 1 in the back .&lt;br /&gt;Biagio has ordered and paid for over &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;$200&lt;/span&gt; worth of appetizers (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) because their Kitchen is too small and we will never get enough food for 160 members. The bar will refill any appetizers platter just once.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The $5 &lt;b&gt;Biago&lt;/b&gt; will collect covers the cost to rent the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders +the DJ so its not all just to cover the food. Please find &lt;b&gt;Biagio&lt;/b&gt; at the party and please give &lt;b&gt;him&lt;/b&gt; the $5.  &lt;b&gt;No one dollar bills  please&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;After you get inside there is Security at the stairs please&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt; tell them you are with Social Fun to get in&lt;/span&gt; (Even if you are with a different group) . If you say any other group they will not let you in. We had issues with this last time so this is new.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please have the $5 ready in hand at the top of the stairs if you take too long Security will make members to go back downstairs. Sorry we cannot block the stairs. Please introduce yourself to Biagio, let him know what group you are in, and be Social.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Let me make this clear: &lt;b&gt;everyone pays $5&lt;/b&gt;, except the Social Fun Organizers and other Invited groups Organizers.&lt;br /&gt;2.  After 9PM you will have to pay another $15 as a cover charge for the Bar Entrance fee to get in so that $20 total. $15 to bar and $5 to cover the cost  to rent the 2nd floor.&lt;br /&gt;3.  If you get in before 9PM you only have to pay $5 to Biagio to cover cost to rent. Make sure you get there early!&lt;br /&gt;4. It will be packed.&lt;br /&gt;5. If you come after 7:30PM you might not even get in right away and will have to wait in line downstairs to go upstairs. So come at 7PM to get in.&lt;br /&gt;6. They will not let you upstairs till 7PM so please wait downstairs till 7PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With all that aside and if I have not scared you away then please join us for all this fun Friday  starting at 7 till the cows come home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Meetup Groups that are invited to come:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt; Social Fun  &lt;/b&gt;   &lt;a href="http://socialnetwork.meetup.com/887/"&gt;http://socialnetwork....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt; The Boston Happy Hour &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://nightlife.meetup.com/421/"&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt; Beantown and Beyond 20-40 Singles &lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1169/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt; The Metro West 30's to 40's Singles Meetup Group &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1555/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt; The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group 28 Members &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.com/76/calendar/8809188/"&gt;http://euro.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Maybe RSVPs will be moved to NO RSVPs 1 week before the event with no exception.&lt;/span&gt; We hit the target to get 250 YES RSVPs to hopefully get 150 members to actually show up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS IS BIAGIO: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/members/3847345/photos/"&gt;Biagio's Photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ONE FINAL NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;  Biagio has told me that at the last Mix &amp;amp; Mingle a couple of people were very rude to him.  This is NOT cool!!  He goes through a lot of effort to put this event in place.  Please, be courteous of Biagio and the other organizers.  Suggestions are always welcome but rudeness is not.  Come and have a good time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have the whole 2nd floor of Kitty OSheas to ourselves. Look for Biagio</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>3305855</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>20</waitlist_count><updated>1235610262000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233705865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Mix + Mingle Joint Event</name><id>9666531</id><headcount>47</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235174400000</time><rsvp_limit>57</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/9666531/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>