<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8129392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120926</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brattle Theater is showing Studio Ghibli films for two straight weeks! I thought two of the double features would make good meetups. This is for the first one. See the full schedule at &lt;a href="http://brattlefilm.org/category/calendar-2/repertory-series/spirited-away-the-films-of-hayao-miyazaki-and-studio-ghibli/in"&gt;http://brattlefilm.org/category/calendar-2/repertory-series/spirited-away-the-films-of-hayao-miyazaki-and-studio-ghibli/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday September 1st, the double feature starts at 7:00 with my absolute favorite Studio Ghibli film: My Neighbor Totoro (subbed), then continues with Kiki's Delivery Service (dubbed this time, but still worth watching!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As with the last Brattle meetup, I'll be in front of the theater 15min before the movie wearing a red fedora, so I'll be really easy to spot, just come find me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a double feature, so the ticket price of $12 covers admission to both films. The double feature price is $10 for students, seniors, and children &amp;lt; 12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These films are some of the younger leaning Studio Ghibli offerings, but beautiful and magical enough to be enjoyed at all ages! There are earlier showings for both of the films, the earlier showings of Totoro are dubbed, and they're also showing on Sunday so there are options for those of you who want to take your kids (which I would highly recommend!), even if this meetup is too late for your young 'uns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synopses from Brattlefilm.org:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Neighbor Totoro&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 in Japanese with English subtitles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1988) dir Hayao Miyazaki [86 min] &lt;br /&gt;

 One of the most endearing and internationally renowned family films of all time, MY NEIGHBOR TOTORO is a deceptively simple tale of two girls who move with their father to a new house in the countryside. The girls soon discover that the surrounding forests are home to a family of Totoros, gentle but powerful creatures who live in a huge, ancient tree and are seen only by children. Based on Miyazaki’s own childhood imaginings, Totoros look like oversized pandas with bunny ears and they take the girls on spinning-top rides through the tree tops and introduce them to a furry, multi-pawed Catbus — a nod to Lewis Carroll’s Cheshire Cat. MY NEIGHBOR TOTORO’s playfulness and narrative simplicity belies a depth of wisdom and an almost spiritual reverence for the power of nature. The viewer is left with a sense of wonder at the beauty, mystery and preciousness of the world all around us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kiki's Delivery Service&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 English language version only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1989) dir Hayao Miyazaki [102 min] &lt;br /&gt;

 KIKI’S DELIVERY SERVICE is the beloved story of a resourceful young witch who uses her broom to create a delivery service, only to lose her gift of flight in a moment of self-doubt. It is tradition for all young witches to leave their families on the night of a full moon and set out into the wide world to learn their craft. When that night comes for Kiki, she embarks on her life journey with her chatty black cat, Jiji, landing the next morning in a seaside village, where a bakery owner hires her to make deliveries. Rarely has the animator’s art been so brilliantly rendered as in this delightfully imaginative film – a beautiful and timeless story of a young girl finding her way in the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346572618000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346041665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Castles in the Sky: Studio Ghibli Retrospective part 1</name><id>79518972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346539500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/79518972/</event_url></item>