<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1615 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.339143</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-277-2975</phone><name>Brookline Tai Chi Center</name><city>Brookline</city><id>836151</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134531</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>3:30 -4:55 pm   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open yourself to the invigorating flow of your own vital energy! Become enlivened by the co-created field we all tap into. Learn the key to experiencing hands-off, clothes-on full-body orgasms. All within a safe space of respectful and fun energy exploration. Open to all. No previous experience or partner necessary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Offered as part of DNE Boston Weekend. Check out &lt;a href="http://dancefriday.org/events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://dancefriday.or...&lt;/a&gt; for a full list of classes and dances March 5-7&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Bodyworker, Tantra Educator and Intimacy Coach with over twenty years experience in the fields of Somatics, Spirituality and Consciousness Relating. Brynn assists individuals and couples in increasing their capacity for Intimacy and Pleasure, and in accessing their full Aliveness and Passion! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her training in Taoist and Hindu Tantric Practices, the Hakomi Method of Body-Oriented Psychotherapy, Mindfulness Practices, Chi Gong, Orgasmic Meditation, Massage Therapy, CranioSacral Therapy, SomatoEmotional Release, Authentic Movement and Expressive Arts Therapy provides a uniquely integrative perspective and skill set she brings to her classes and private sessions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email her to find out about private sessions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268080725000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266971639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Erotic Energy Play</name><id>12689524</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267907400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/12689524/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/b/e/global_11488798.jpeg</photo_url></item>