<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10253922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please Update your RSVPs for Wednesday night. Melody is looking to possibly make Laurie's a regular monthly meeting place but we need more Wakefield Weeknights people to join us on Wednesday night, check out Laurie's and give us some feedback. Unlike some of the other local places they are not charging us a cover to occupy their two bar areas! Melody is out of town so look for Maria, Frank and Bob from Laurie's at the bar when you arrive. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check this out... Bob from Laurie's is a lot of fun.  He wrote to me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"It will PLEASE PLEASE ME if you LET IT BE&lt;/span&gt; Laurie's 9:0&lt;span&gt;9 your group want&lt;/span&gt;s to come and have dinner after seeing the place and I&lt;span&gt;F I FELL IN LOVE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;with your g&lt;/span&gt;roup and you our place would &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;LOVE ME DO to have you come back mor&lt;/span&gt;e and more. &lt;span&gt;But WAIT&lt;/span&gt; even if the RAIN or if we see that &lt;span&gt;HERE COMES THE SUN as time goes by I WILL you to enjoy THE ONE AFTER 909 ....yeah yea&lt;/span&gt;h yeah..............."  ha ha...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's kick off 2013 with a great "Happy Hour" like we used to do regularly the first week of each month!  Let's call this one First Hump Day (of the month).  Get over that mid-week slump by coming out to this fun, new venue in Wakefield!  :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob and Laurie are giving Wakefield Weeknights and More members exclusive use of the two bar areas (one side of the room is a raw bar).  They have a great dinner menu you can order from the bar! And $1 oysters 5-7 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have a special Beatles themed drink menu including $9.09 martinis!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early or come later...this can be a sort of drop in event where you can stop by anytime throughout the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plenty of parking in the lots on Tuttle St.!  And since this place is ON the train platform, here is the Commuter Rail scoop - Check out the MBTA Haverhill/Reading Line Schedule. Trains leave North Station Boston at 5:15, 5:35, 5:55, 6:20, and 7:20. It's a 20 minute ride to the Wakefield stop in front of Laurie's. Trains depart from Wakefield to Boston at 8:05, 9:09, 10:19 and 10:59&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've heard nothing but great reviews of their food.  Here is a link to their menu and the rest of their website: &lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;http://www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you come in the door take a left and you'll see the bar areas to your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please MAKE SURE maintain your own tab or pay as you order and PLEASE tip your servers.  Credit cards will be held by the servers at Laurie's if you want to have a tab.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make sure you have an easily recognizable FACE PHOTO of YOU as your main profile pic on your page in this group!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the bar! Ask for Maria, Frank or Bob from Laurie's.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maria (cruise director)</member_name><member_id>13843401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360251110000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357324625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Laurie's 909 Steakhouse/Raw Bar Exclusive happy hour/dinner/drinks for our group</name><id>97904822</id><headcount>17</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360191600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/97904822/</event_url></item>