<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello, &lt;br /&gt;please see below for details about this really moving movie to bring consciousness to the trials and tribulations that the veterans from the war have been through.  The Center of Light is hosting this movie at 3 different locations and 3 different times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would love to meet you there...&lt;br /&gt;In Light, &lt;br /&gt;Rev Gabrielle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stay tuned for some more great events coming up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FILM VIEWING AND DISCUSSION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE GROUND TRUTH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you wondered what politicians mean when they ask us to ?support the troops??&lt;br /&gt;Does it mean they want us to support the Iraq war, no questions asked?&lt;br /&gt;Does it mean that we are supposed to root for the U.S.A. to defeat ?the enemy??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What if supporting the troops meant taking the time to listen to their stories? To empathize with them? To be with them in their struggles.&lt;br /&gt;This is the idea behind a powerful new documentary film called ?The Ground Truth,? which chronicles the journeys of Iraq war veterans and their families as they struggle to re-claim their lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us on this evening as we come together to initiate the first night of a nationwide movement to engage in conversation and listen to the real stories of Iraq veterans.&lt;br /&gt;Our discussion will focus on honest conversation about the war in Iraq and how to put real meaning behind the words ?support the troops.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As people join across the country from October 4 -11th, we acknowledge the four-year anniversary of the Congressional authorization of ?Use of force against Iraq? and we reflect on the four years that have passed, and we renew our resolve to pray and act for a peaceful resolution to this war.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To view the trailer for this film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sojo" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sojo...&lt;/a&gt;. net/index. cfm?actionfiltered= action.display&amp;amp; item=060915_ groundtruth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to spending this evening with you and uniting with many in the spirit of love and support for our brothers and sisters across this land. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm October 3rd ? Jamaica Plain ? 617.852.2822&lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm October 5th ? Newton ? 978.808.2330&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge ? 617.794.8208 ( this location has a $5 donation)&lt;br /&gt;Center of Light ~Boston&lt;br /&gt;  centeroflightboston@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540564000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1159147628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A movie viewing for peace and consciousness</name><id>5150331</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1159916400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/5150331/</event_url></item>