<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>NH Route 113</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.742256</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Cotton Mountain Trailhead</name><city>Holderness</city><id>12657162</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.578705</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/8/0/event_230781632.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; Depending on the level of exercise you get this could be considered an easy-moderate hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Trailhead Directions:&lt;/span&gt; Take I-93 North to Exit 24, at the end of the ramp turn right and take US3 to Holderness for 4.4 miles, make a left onto NH 113 for 1.1 miles, Cotton Mountain Parking Lot on the left side of the road. &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;So everyone has room to park please use head in parking.  Do not park sideways along the road unless the parking lot is already full.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be hiking the Cotton Mountain and Crawford-Ridgepole trails to the summit of Cotton Mountain (1,200') and Livermore Mountain (1,500'). There are good views of Squam Lake near both summits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.1 miles round trip, with an 900' elevation gain for the hike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/d/a/event_230789402.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The last few tenths of a mile of the hike will be along a tarred road with traffic so you may want to leash your dogs there.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least at that point they will be less rambunctious, so will do better on lead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Bring a lunch, we will eat at the top&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;of Livermore Mtn. while we enjoy the views of Squam Lake.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first picture was taken at the summit of Cotton Mtn. and the second picture was taken from the summit of Livermore Mtn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Given the distance this hike is up north a car pool will be set up.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Car Pool Location:&lt;/span&gt; I-93 N exit 8 Manchester, NH parking lot opposite the fire station on Mammoth Road.  Also next to the Derryfield Restaurant and Golf  Course.  Leaving at 7:45 AM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I-93 Exit 14 Concord, NH  Fort Eddy Rd back of parking lot in between Hannafords and LL Bean.  Leaving at 8:00 AM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I-93 N exit 2 park and ride, Salem, NH. Leaving at 7:30 AM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any adult guest you want to bring should &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/98448272/"&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt; on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368288622000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365128166000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>COTTON AND LIVERMORE MOUNTAINS - 900' Elevation Gain - 4.1 miles</name><id>112778542</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367758800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/112778542/</event_url></item>