<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>suggested donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We will be discussing &amp;quot;The Glass Castle&amp;quot; by Jeannette Walls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From BarnesandNoble.com:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gossip columnist Jeanette Walls dishes the dirt on her own troubled youth in this remarkable story of survival against overwhelming odds. The child of charismatic vagabonds who left their offspring to raise themselves, Walls spent decades hiding an excruciating childhood filled with poverty and shocking neglect. But this is no pity party. What shines through on every page of this beautifully written family memoir is Walls's love for her deeply flawed parents and her recollection of occasionally wonderful times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note new location and time.  The Creamery is located near BC and is T-accessible via the green line- last stop on the B train.  This establishment does not sell coffee or tea but there's a Dunkin Donuts right next door and a nice (but very small) coffee shop- French Press a few doors down.  The Creamery doesn't mind if you bring a drink into their shop.  Thanks in advance for your flexibility and patience as we find a suitable location for our group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, I would like to continue this group after June so we need to decide which books we'd like to read and discuss.  Please bring a list with you to the next meetup or post your suggested titles on the message board.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!  &lt;br /&gt;-Sabina&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sabina</member_name><member_id>1638720</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182888252000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179691817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Brookline Book Club June Meetup</name><id>5799151</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182715200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/5799151/</event_url></item>