<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Lawton Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02780</zip><lat>41.876511</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-824-4866</phone><name>Silver City Skateland</name><city>Taunton</city><id>1207433</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103167</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Fellow meetup-ers, this event has changed slightly as of March3. Apparently (from Birthday Emily's camp), due to the poor management and customer service at United Skates of America, they have canceled our party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But don't you fear!! We have a new venue lined up. It is the next-closest skating rink, Silver City Skateland in Taunton, MA. We also have a room reserved at, Benjamin's, a local restaurant for dinner and drinks before hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taunton is about a 30 - 40 minute drive from Providence depending on which route you take. Feel free to contact others you may know to arrange for car pooling if you'd like. If you are doing the driving please get detailed directions from the internet ahead of time, use your GPS, and call the venues if you need further assistance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm - 9pm&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin's Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;698 Bay St.&lt;br /&gt;Taunton, MA 02780&lt;br /&gt;508 - 824 - 6313&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The room is reserved under &amp;quot;Emily's Birthday Party&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;- They will serve drinks on a cash basis, but food will be combined on one or two checks, so please bring cash if you can.&lt;br /&gt;- The full menu will be available. If you are going to order a meal, please get to the restaurant at 7 to allow adequate time. If you get there later you are welcome to order appetizers or desert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9pm - 11pm&lt;br /&gt;Silver City Skateland&lt;br /&gt;1 Lawton Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Taunton, MA 02780&lt;br /&gt;508 - 824 - 4866&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- This is still a private party, so it will be just our group&lt;br /&gt;- The price remains at $15 each, which includes two hours of skating fun and skate rental. Please pay the meetup coordinator, Stephanie when you get there.&lt;br /&gt;- The snack bar will remain open from 9 to 9:30 for hot food, and all night for drinks. (No alcohol is allowed.) They have a fully stocked snack bar (pizza, hot dogs, burgers, fries, etc.) Any food or drinks at the snack bar are on a cash basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We really hope you can still make it to the birthday party! And we also hope that everyone has a great time and a bruise-free bum by the end of the evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEE YOU THERE!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268093211000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266679093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Roller Skating Private Party</name><id>12655246</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267920000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/12655246/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>