<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to $10 per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Rescheduled to this new date now that Eric is feeling better!!!.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are very lucky indeed to be hosting Eric Toensmieir, author of Perennial Vegetables, here in Portland for an evening slideshow and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perennial vegetables can provide years of harvests with very little care.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maine gardeners can grow many of the world’s best species.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;These crops have excellent potential for small-scale agriculture projects around the world and their use can mitigate many of the negative impacts inherent in annual cropping of similar species.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 pm potluck supper! bring a dish/beverage or other treat to share.&lt;br /&gt;7:15 pm slide show and discussion to follow&lt;br /&gt;wrap up between 8:30 and 9:00 depending on questions...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Eric Toensmeier has comprehensively filled a huge gap in the sustainable landscape. Perennial Vegetables lets you put away your tiller, and covers everything you need to grow, harvest, and eat vegetables and greens that will keep coming back year after year.&amp;quot; —Toby Hemenway, author of Gaia's Garden.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric Toensmeier is the author of Perennial Vegetables: From Artichokes to ‘Zuiki’ Taro, a Gardener’s Guide to Over 100 Delicious, Easy-to-Grow Edibles. He is also co-author of Edible Forest Gardens with Dave Jacke. In addition to being a famous “plant geek,” Eric runs Nuestras Raices Farm, an immigrant farming project in urban Holyoke, Massachusetts.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you would like to get on the waiting list for an open spot, RSVP &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; with a comment that you'd like to get in...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224943719000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224003371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Perennial Vegetables with Eric Toensmeier</name><id>8960168</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224282600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/8960168/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/f/global_5132031.jpeg</photo_url></item>