<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>PLEASE NOTE:  I have update the viewing time for this movie.  The actual time of the movie is 11:10am, and it is the first viewing matinee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the highly anticipated second installment of the Millennium Trilogy, Lisbeth Salander (Noomi Rapace) is a wanted woman. A researcher and a Millennium journalist about to expose the truth about the sex trade in Sweden are brutally murdered, and Salander's prints are on the weapon. Her history of unpredictable and vengeful behavior makes her an official danger to society—but no one can find her anywhere. Meanwhile, Mikael Blomkvist (Michael Nyqvist), editor-in-chief of Millennium, will not believe what he hears on the news. Knowing Salander to be fierce when fearful, he is desperate to get to her before she is cornered and alone. As he fits the pieces of the puzzle together, he comes up against some hardened criminals, including the chainsaw-wielding 'blond giant' (Micke Spreitz)—a fearsomely huge thug who can feel no pain. Digging deeper, Blomkvist also unearths some heart-wrenching facts about Salander’s past life. Committed to psychiatric care aged 12, declared legally incompetent at 18, this is a messed-up young woman who is the product of an unjust and corrupt system. Yet Lisbeth is more avenging angel than helpless victim.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AFterwards we'll go to Doyles, CBC or the Friendly Toast.  I've put a poll question up so you can make a suggestion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Up front, right side of the screen - AFTER the movie.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278809345000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277659861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Girl who played with Fire</name><id>13926118</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278774000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13926118/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/6/global_16007334.jpeg</photo_url></item>