<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our first meeting was a success.  As a group we picked &lt;u&gt;Sense and Sensibility&lt;/u&gt; by Jane Austen for our next book club meeting on July 8th.  Many of you may have already read this book but I think that the people who have read it will enjoy reading it again.  It will make a good summer read.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The venue is great!  The downstairs of Molly Malones is unused during the week.  We had the entire dining room to ourselves which was beautifully decorated with Celtic flare and very comfortable.  The ambiance was perfect.  Irish music playing in the background, our own private waitress to bring the libations and ghosts.  Yes, ghosts.  Apparently, our official book club room is haunted!  The owner was there to give us a little history on the room including its well known haunts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pick up Sense and Sensibility and plan to meet us in July!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the entire room downstairs so you will know us when you come in!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216335910000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Enjoy a relaxing evening out and away from the kids, meet people, talk about fav</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213143163000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club July Meeting - Sense and Sensibility</name><id>8119293</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216162800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/8119293/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/4/global_4424564.jpeg</photo_url></item>