<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 6:05, so let's meet inside the ticket lobby at 5:30. Then I'll buy us all tickets and we can get snacks, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This movie, presumably, was bumped from several theaters at the AMC for the Harry Potter that opened last weekend. So sorry for the early showing, but it's outta my hands!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the earlier time affects your plans to attend, please make sure to update your RSVP, so that I know who to wait for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks and hope to see you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809998238/info" target="_blank"&gt;Megamind &lt;/a&gt;just may be the perfect silly animated start to Thanksgiving weekend. So come giggle with me at a movie that seems to be doing pretty well in the box office!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Megamind is the most brilliant super-villain the world has ever known... and the least successful. Over the years, he has tried to conquer Metro City in every imaginable way -- Each attempt, a colossal failure thanks to the caped superhero known as &amp;quot;Metro Man,&amp;quot; until the day Megamind actually defeats him in the throes of one of his botched evil plans. Suddenly, the fate of Metro City is threatened when a new villain arrives and chaos runs rampant, leaving everyone to wonder: Can the world's biggest &amp;quot;mind&amp;quot; actually be the one to save the day?  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Megamind!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290555454000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289942668000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Megamind</name><id>15468695</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290551400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/15468695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>