<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>UPDATE:   Rally will be held at Ballard Park from 10 AM to Noon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This protest regarding the Stimulus Bill, Mortgge Bail Out and high taxes was broguht to our attention over the internet. The organizers are Andrew &amp;quot;Skip&amp;quot; March of Ridgefield, Chris Murray of Ridgefield and Michael Taylor of Stamford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizers are asking for an RSVP. You can contact them through:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://brainflation.wordpress.com/2009/03/02/ridgefield-tea-party-on-march-21st" target="_blank"&gt;http://brainflation.w...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ronpaul.meetup.com/384/calendar/9915107/"&gt;http://ronpaul.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you ready to have your voices heard?  Do you feel that the incredibly wasteful and reckless spending of the current administration and Congress will do great harm to all Americans?  Do you want to meet like-minded citizens who oppose the incredibly dangerous and wasteful policies of this administration?  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please join fellow patriots for a “Tea Party”:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;·         Saturday, March 21st in&lt;br /&gt;·         Ridgefield, Connecticut at&lt;br /&gt;·         10 a.m. to noon in&lt;br /&gt;·         Ballard Park&lt;br /&gt;If you are planning to attend, confirm at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://brainflation.wordpress.com/2009/03/02/ridgefield-tea-party-on-march-21st"&gt;http://brainflation.w...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and let us know how many will be in your party.  The Ridgefield Police will be on hand to keep us safe and they’ve asked us to estimate the number of attendees.&lt;br /&gt;This is your chance to let other Americans know that they are not alone in opposing destructive federal spending!&lt;br /&gt;Here are some particulars you may want to know:&lt;br /&gt;·         Ballard Park is located on Main Street, adjacent to the CVS Pharmacy and directly across from the town library.&lt;br /&gt;o    Please do not park in the CVS parking lot.  Understandably, CVS would like this lot to be used by their patrons. Be respectful of the businesses here in town, they are taxpayers just like you!  Patronize them if you can.&lt;br /&gt;·         Parking.  There is plenty of free parking within a block or two of Ballard Park.  We recommend the FREE municipal parking lots behind Town Hall off of Bailey Ave.  (Bailey is a one way street.) Look for the green and white parking signs.&lt;br /&gt;·         Overflow Parking is available off of Prospect St.&lt;br /&gt;·         Sign in desk at the entrance to the park, strictly voluntary.  We will respect your privacy.&lt;br /&gt;·         “Honk If You Are Paying My Mortgage” bumper stickers available for purchase, while they last.&lt;br /&gt;·         Bring your own signs, if you like.  Some sign-making supplies will be available.  Be positive and witty in your messages!  The media may be covering this event.&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a fun, positive day in Ridgefield..&lt;br /&gt;Remember to RSVP with the number planning to attend.&lt;br /&gt;Just as concerned citizens in 1773 started something larger than themselves, let this event lead us to more responsible government.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave L.</member_name><member_id>2749382</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237937066000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236637557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ridgefield Tea Party</name><id>9918165</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237644000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/9918165/</event_url></item>