<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Park Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02493</zip><lat>42.335751</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 891-6575 </phone><name>Weston Ski Track</name><city>Weston</city><id>820849</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.268159</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey guys - in an effort to diversify during the winter months, here is an excellent chance for you to learn how to XC ski and/or snowshoe close to home, at the Weston Ski Track!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read the description below from their website -- there are a number of different options from just demoing the latest snowshoes for 15-20 minutes (for free) to renting some XC skis and getting a beginner's lesson for 75 minutes. The&lt;a href="http://www.skiboston.com/skitrack/rates.php" target="_blank"&gt; rental costs&lt;/a&gt; seem like a bargain (adult trail pass: $15, boots/poles/skis: $15, snowshoes: $13)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP to the event, please check whether you'd be interested in carpooling to Weston. From what I hear the event is well attended and I know other meet-up groups already have this on their calendars. Perhaps we could pick a spot near the Weston Track and drive over as a group...otherwise we'll just meet at the track!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skiboston.com/skitrack/events/specialevents.php#wintertrails" target="_blank"&gt;Winter Trails Day&lt;/a&gt; is a national event each January focusing on introducing people to the great fun of getting outside in the winter on cross-country skis or snowshoes. The event will run from 9am-2pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snowshoeing&lt;br /&gt;For 2010, all snowshoe events will be free and do not require pre-registration. Everyone will receive a free snowshoeing trail pass,there will be free snowshoe demos, and we will be leading a number of free guided tours. There will be a limited number of demo snowshoes available; those who want to use snowshoes for more than 15-20 minutes can rent them from us at the regular rate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;XC Skiing&lt;br /&gt;Free ski lessons will be available with pre-registration and the purchase of a trail pass (and rental if needed); see our regular rates. Free ski lessons are only available with pre-registration and payment. To register or view a class schedule, go online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bethany</member_name><member_id>10111481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263218995000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Grinders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group</urlname><id>1500421</id><group_lat>42.0600013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Foxboro Grind &amp; Grub Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262097473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Trails Day - Skiing/Snowshoeing</name><id>12167476</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263045600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group/events/12167476/</event_url></item>