<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome-Introductions Gathering--&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mission- Find a monogamous, long term-life time partner or marriage!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date and Time: Decided by Host&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dec. 1- Sat. 6:00PM-11:00PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Format:&lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, relaxing environment of a home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $5.00&lt;br /&gt;If your name begins with the following- please bring: Will change monthly:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A-G- Entree and soft drink or water&lt;br /&gt;H-P - Appetizer and bottle of wine&lt;br /&gt;Q-Z - Desert and a bottle of wine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer and Host Home&lt;br /&gt;Organizer Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;Host Home- Rose Di Bartolo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host decides: Quotes from our Host-Rose&lt;br /&gt;1. Time of party: 6:00PM -11:00pm&lt;br /&gt;2.  Dress code- &amp;quot;wear what is comfortable.?&lt;br /&gt;3. &amp;quot;You can enjoy the music and dance if you like&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;4. &amp;quot;Keep your shoes on if you like&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;5. &amp;quot;Everyone can play pool or checkers&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purpose is to Socialize with similar people of our age who are searching for a lifetime partner.&lt;br /&gt;45-65 age group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I began these parties in my home in July 2006-twice a month&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our common Values: Common denominator&lt;br /&gt;Have fun meeting old and new friends&lt;br /&gt;Circulate, talk to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;If someone is alone go up to them and say hi!&lt;br /&gt;Nonsmokers&lt;br /&gt;Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are coming because you got this email, this is your invitation. Please invite other friends, Particularly men.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is not necessary to inform me that we have more woman. I know. &lt;br /&gt;that fact. Women are more gregarious and open-minded than many men.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all need to exert an effort to invite men. &lt;br /&gt;This group was formed on the principle of synergy.  Working together to invite quality people. It is our job to take responsibility for inviting people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can sign up on &lt;a href="http://dance.meetup.com/393/"&gt;http://dance.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You do not need to email me personally.&lt;br /&gt;100 guests only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the time, the location , what you should bring.  Let's have fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions&lt;br /&gt;40 Pleasant St&lt;br /&gt;Dover, MA&lt;br /&gt;508-785-3434&lt;br /&gt;From North of Newton:&lt;br /&gt;Exit 22 - Route 16W &lt;br /&gt;Travel approx 5.5 miles on Route 16 west (it takes a sharp left turn just before Wellesley Center ? watch the signs). Take a Left at the set of lights onto Pleasant Street (you will see the following landmarks: Charles River Waterfall, Bacon Free Library, White Eliot Church)&lt;br /&gt;Follow Pleasant Street for ONE MILE- passing along the way LOOKOUT FARM ? Be sure you go past the Farm. Once you see Pegan Lane my house will be the next on your Right.  PLEASE NOTE: The numbers on Pleasant St prior to Lookout Farm are in Natick, Pegan Lane is the first street in Dover. I'll put balloons on the mailbox.&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128 North (From Southshore)&lt;br /&gt;Exit 16B ? Route 109 Westwood. Take 1st Street on RIGHT ? GROVE STREET and follow to end (you will drive between two golf courses). At end (Dedham Street) take a left and travel 2.2 miles. Take a RIGHT onto HAVEN ST. and follow to the end (it is a twisting road that makes a sharp right turn near Church St but just keep on Haven) At the Second Stop Sign take a right onto Main. Keep to the left where Main St will become Pleasant. We are #40 on the left. A white house with Green Shutters.&lt;br /&gt;Rose has a 5000 Square foot home- 3 car garage- two 3 feet high stone pillars in the entrance. Look for balloons on the mailbox. My red Town and Country Van will be parked in front of house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park on the right side of street.  Enter the house on the garage side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rose and I look forward to seeing you on Oct. 27th.  100 guests only&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196723122000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>33</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>121</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193526088000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction Gatherings - Singles Party Meetup</name><id>6628757</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196550000000</time><rsvp_limit>125</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/6628757/</event_url></item>