<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Westbound-behind Chuck E. Cheese)</address_2><address_1>3 Vision Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.300643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitney Place Assisted Living</name><city>Natick</city><id>766030</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;Bridging the Gap - A mother to mother conversation about children with special needs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mothers of typical and special needs children will meet and have a group discussion about talking to you children about special needs, supporting friends and families of children with special needs, and other topics relevant to the participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;As this is a &amp;quot;moms only&amp;quot; event, potential members are welcome to attend! (non-mobile infants are welcome to attend.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many other events will be held in April-August (available to paid members only due to insurance liability policy requirements.)To become a member of the Framingham Area chapter of Mothers &amp;amp; More, you must either mail in an official membership form with your dues, or fill out the enrollment form online and pay via credit card at &lt;a href="http://www.mothersandmore.org/AboutUs/join.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mothersand...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact Asst. Organizer, Kate to have memberships forms and more chapter information mailed to you. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mom and Kids Lunch at Bugaboo Creek &lt;br /&gt;See the Big Trucks at the Framingham DPW truck lot &lt;br /&gt;Southwick Zoo Trip &lt;br /&gt;Tour of Whole Foods &lt;br /&gt;Berry Picking &lt;br /&gt;Ice Cream at Gerards &lt;br /&gt;Family Baseball Night -watch the Lowell Spinners &lt;br /&gt;Davis Farmland and Splashpad Visit &lt;br /&gt;Ice Skating &lt;br /&gt;Family Cookout &lt;br /&gt;Hopkinton State Park Beach day &lt;br /&gt;Water Fun Sprinkler/Slide/Wading Pool party &lt;br /&gt;Playground Drop-ins at designated Parks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Other events that Mothers &amp;amp; More offers- Movie Mamas monthly movie night at the AMC Framingham, Book Group, Cooking Group, Unfinished Object Night (scrapbooking, knitting, general projects on your to-do list.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanya</member_name><member_id>7153030</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249247180000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240324589000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bridging the Gap </name><id>10233519</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245886200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/10233519/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/a/global_8459978.jpeg</photo_url></item>