<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ravine Lodge Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03279</zip><lat>43.979644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ravine Lodge</name><city>Warren</city><id>1018290</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.820953</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for hikers who haven't given up on their love of hiking and being in nature despite their age or level of physical conditioning. We hike at a pace 50% slower than the AMC Trailguide book time. There are three other hiking Meetup groups if you want a faster pace or more challenging hikes (The New England Hiking Meetup, 4 Seasons Hiking Group, New England Over 40 Hiking Group). Our goal is to stay fit while enjoying the camaraderie of hikers who have similar skills and goals. This is a dog free hiking group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead: Take I93 north to exit 32,take NH112 west,make left onto NH118,make right onto Moosilauke Ravine Lodge Road.Park at the end of the road in front of Dartmouth's Ravine Lodge.We can meet at the turnaround by the lodge.We will be hiking on the Gorge Brook Trail to the summit of Mount Moosilauke (4802').Views in all directions from the bald summit. 7.4 miles round trip,2450' elevation gain,AMC book time 5 hours,8 hours estimated time for our group.-----Steve &amp;amp; Cindy-----As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release,hold harmless,and indemnify the organizer and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage,injury,illness and/or death,including those caused by negligence and or other reasons.You also agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Black Colorado pick up truck NH2431202</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve A</member_name><member_id>6009756</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312030857000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1413769</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>New England Over 50 Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309048394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>STRENUOUS  HIKE-MOUNT MOOSILAUKE</name><id>23522931</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310821200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group/events/23522931/</event_url></item>