<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In the past I usually do this hike in the winter.  I am curious to see it without snow.  I am planning a 5.2 mile hike through Bigelow Hollow.  This is a familiar area with beautiful terrain and no terrible ups.  It does roll up and down quite a bit.  We should be out for about 4 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please plan on bringing water, snacks, sunscreen, lunch for this adventure.  Hiking boots are strongly recommended.  I am told that we can expect a good deal of bugs so be prepared to bathe in Deet, deep woods strength.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bigelow Hollow State Park and the adjoining Nipmuck State Forest offer over 9,000 acres of recreation opportunities, including miles of hiking trails and an 18-acre pond in Eastern Connecticut. This park is beautiful, and this is a great time of year to hike it.&lt;br /&gt;I am planning to hike the Mashapaug Pond View Trail (blue/white loop) counter clockwise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hike as a group and are only as fast as our slowest member.  Please understand that working with the group dynamic is key to my events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Labor Day weekend so the charge to enter the park will be $9.00 according to the web site.  When you enter the park, head up the road and we will meet at the 2nd parking area along the road from the entrance, which is a picnic area. It will be on your left side as you drive in (it has the water pump, 2 dark colored outhouses, and a bulletinboard). On the map, it is the 3rd marked parking area from the entrance. If you reach the boat launch and the end of the accessible road you've gone one parking area too far. In the event the parking area is full, we will still meet at that location as the trailhead we are using is there. Please allow some extra time in case you need to walk to this area from available parking. Note that there is virtually NO CELL reception at the park!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always with me, NO DOGS-NO CHILDREN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/directions for entrance to Bigelow Hollow State Park off of Rte. 171 in Union, CT via Mapquest: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Bigelow+Pond&amp;amp;city=Stafford+Springs&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.99204&amp;amp;longitude=-72.131743&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=13881594" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking map: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/big_nipm.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rough indication of topography via Google Maps (click Terrain button, if needed):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=Bigelow+Hollow+State+Park,+Union,+CT&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.002908,-72.132711&amp;amp;spn=0.016775,0.023947&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=A" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the park: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325174&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284426883000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282579820000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Bigelow Hollow State Park, Union CT</name><id>14512087</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283695200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/14512087/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>