<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>333 Rindge Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.393736</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Russell Field</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>714161</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.136597</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We play at 8pm on the football field at Russell Field by Alewife Station. We generally play 'til 10:00 and then coordinate some form of post-frisbee hangouts.  Before attending our events, please review our About Us page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/350/about/"&gt;http://fitness.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map of where we play can be found here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonfrisbee.com/images/russell_sat.jpg"&gt;http://www.bostonfris...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As shown on the map, there's a parking lot next to the field.  If you take the Red Line to Alewife, look for signs upon exiting that will direct you to Russell Field.  Do not go to the parking garage.  There is no frisbee there, only hundreds of sad, lonely cars pining for the open road and days gone by.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a light-colored shirt (for visibility's sake), water and a fist fulla awesome. We'll provide cones, frisbees, glowsticks and fun new friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Organizers pay out of pocket for the equipment. If you wish to donate, consider bringing a couple bucks or donate online (link available at &amp;quot;About Us&amp;quot; page above)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE RSVP.&lt;/b&gt;  We're anticipating lots of new players now that the weather is getting warm and it's extremely helpful for us to know how many players to expect.  For now, we'd prefer not to enforce any sort of &amp;quot;you can't play if you don't RSVP&amp;quot; rule--but such a thing may be on the horizon.  Our top two priorities are safety and fun, and neither is served well if 90 players show up when we expected 25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more and make our lives complete by RSVPing 'yes,' go to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/350/calendar/7750448/"&gt;http://fitness.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, don't hesitate to contact the Organizers through the website!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, and see you on the field!&lt;br /&gt;-Jim O. &amp;amp; co.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be on the astroturf field, throwing LED discs or warming up near the bleachers.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim O'Neill</member_name><member_id>4585507</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209385671000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Because you're a fun, exciting person, and we're a fun-loving, exhilarating community of frisbee players!</why><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208882610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friztastic - Ultimate at Russell Field</name><id>7789981</id><headcount>36</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209168000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7789981/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/7/global_1405527.jpeg</photo_url></item>