<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Bay Colony Corporate Center, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street - Suite 4000</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.408169</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 895 5900</phone><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1311652</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.274474</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome all to the 1st 2011 Boston Cloud Services meetup!&lt;br /&gt;We have a packed agenda with a quick intro to &lt;a href="http://cloudyn.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Cloudyn&lt;/a&gt; - a new, free, AWS TCO reduction service, followed by a talk about the state's new $100M Cloud project (a.k.a 'where did all my tax money go') and wrapping with a &lt;a href="http://www.scalebase.com/" target="_blank"&gt;ScaleBase&lt;/a&gt;, new start-up company offering a technology that helps power all these clouds...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Formal Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;=========&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Tsahy Shapsa : 5 minutes intro of &lt;a href="http://cloudyn.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Cloudyn&lt;/a&gt; - a free hosted service that helps you understand and analyze the costs associated with your AWS cloud infrastructure. Cloudyn is non-intrusive (zero footprint), secure and requires no installation. Just sign up for our service by providing your AWS credentials, and gain clear visibility into your IaaS cloud spending&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Massachusetts Cloud Project - A compressive look at the building of a community cloud for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;    Presenter: James Baker, CISSP CISM C|EH, CEO @ ABCecurity Consulting&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Security strategist and architect of a 110 Million dollar state wide project to consolidate and secure the Commonwealth’s private information. The project includes the building of a green, lights out tier three data center that will host a Community Cloud managed by the Commonwealth of Massachusetts for the State’s Secretariats.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Boston Cloud Start-up of the day: &lt;a href="http://www.scalebase.com/" target="_blank"&gt;ScaleBase&lt;/a&gt;™ is a new cloud&amp;#8209;based service that provides high availability and scalability for your SQL databases. It is an extremely sophisticated load balancer that provides your databases with as much cloud elasticity as you need by enabling significantly more concurrent user connections and SQL commands for any type of SQL database applications!&lt;br /&gt;Presenter: Liran Zelkha, Co-Founder&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tsahy Shapsa</member_name><member_id>8753907</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297108052000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-cloud-services</urlname><id>1460349</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>Boston Cloud Services - All things Cloud,  SaaS, PaaS, XaaS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294970030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2011 Cloud Opener </name><id>16043043</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296775800000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-cloud-services/events/16043043/</event_url></item>