<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Peddlers Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06437</zip><lat>41.294704</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Westwoods Trails</name><city>Guilford</city><id>219766</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.708824</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In honor of Monday's holiday, lets get out and do a little exploring! I'm not quite hoping to get so lost we wind up on the wrong continent and start misnaming the people there, but something a little smaller scale would be cool. I've never been to Westwoods in Guilford, and have heard a lot of good things about it. The current weather forecast for Monday is sunny with highs in the 60's, so this should be a perfect time to go check it out! &lt;br /&gt;   I'll update this with more info about which trail head we'll meet at and which trails we'll take after I've looked at the maps more. For now, it'll be one of parking lots off of I-95 exit 57 in Guilford. If you know the park and/or have a preference, feel free to chime in. If not, below are some cool descriptions and photos from their site.&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The WestWoods trail system is the largest recreational area for hiking in Guilford. Westwoods contains 39 miles of trails on 1,200 acres. The ownership of the land is divided between State Forest, Guilford Land Conservation Trust (GLCT), City of Guilford and private ownership.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It contains a wide diversity of interesting natural formations such as: cave structures, water falls, salt and fresh water marshes, inland tidal lake, carved rock sculptures and rock formations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photos: &lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/pictures.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interactive Trail Map: &lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/inter_map.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255533043000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255121735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Columbus Hike!</name><id>11591134</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255359600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11591134/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>