<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Unfortunately, I have to miss this one, but I'd like to tell everyone who hasn't seen Best in Show, that it's hilarious and a modern classic. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;Coolidge Corner's Science on Screen series &lt;/a&gt;does it again...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's all about dogs and the people who love them at the Coolidge Corner Theatre's March 15, 7 pm presentation of Science on Screen, featuring a special screening of Best in Show, master mockumentarian Christopher Guest's hilarious send-up of competitive canine culture. Guest (This is Spinal Tap, Waiting for Guffman, A Mighty Wind) wrote and directed this inspired gem, which follows a colorful group of contestants as they prepare for one of the greatest events of their lives - the Mayflower Dog Show. Winner of American, British, and Canadian comedy Awards and a critical darling, this mostly improvised film features a stellar ensemble cast thatperfectly captures their characters' anxieties, eccentricities, neuroses, and, most of all, their desire to win.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before the screening, world-renowned veterinary behaviorist Nicholas H. Dodman explores the sometimes curious bond between people and their pooches. Some show owners, for example, seem &lt;br /&gt;to regard their dogs as an extension of their personality and live vicariously through their pet's success (or defeat) in the ring. What is the nature and cause of the intensity of this relationship? Do the dogs really think and react, feel and anticipate, as their owners believe? Are they really proud when they win and distraught when they lose -- or is this interpretation a product of their owners’ overactive imaginations? What is the evidence for dogs' intelligence, and do we over- or underestimate our canine charges?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Dodman, BVMS, MRCVS, is professor and program director of the Animal Behavior Department of Clinical Sciences at Tufts’ School of Veterinary Medicine. He founded the Animal Behavior Clinic – one of the first of its kind – at Tufts in 1986.  Dr. Dodman is the best-selling author of The Dog Who Loved Too Much, Dogs Behaving Badly, and The Well-Adjusted Dog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $9.75 general admission, $7.75 students and Museum of Science members, and free for Coolidge Corner Theatre members. Tickets can be purchased at www.coolidge.org or at the &lt;br /&gt;Coolidge box office, 290 Harvard Street, Brooklne.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I won't be there, but look for other meetup members if they RSVP!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268866949000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267121649000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NoOrg -- Best in Show</name><id>12706799</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268694000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12706799/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>