<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>FILM SCREENING AND DINNER&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gold Standard Social Club at the Narragansett Theater has agreed to show the entire 3.5 hour film THE MONEY MASTERS. This film is a MUST SEE . This 3.5 hour film is professionally produced in the style of a A&amp;amp;E Biography and covers the history of monetary reform from Roman Times to the present. The film explores the role of privately owned central banks in public policy making, national budgeting, and foreign policy. REMEMBER THE FEDERAL RESERVE IS ABOUT AS FEDERAL AS FEDERAL EXPRESS. Come to this film screening and learn how our country is being systematically manipulated by a powerful private banking cartel. This is not the first time this has happened in US history. We have abolished central banks before in the US and this film will argue that we should do it again. It also offers suggestion as to how to protect you and your family from the inevitable detrimental effects (recession / depression) of a central banking system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be an intermission with&lt;br /&gt;Delicious catered dinner sandwiches and snacks included in the admission price.&lt;br /&gt;Cash bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Join us and bring a friend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We highly recommend that every American watch The Money Masters&amp;quot; - Zeldon Nelson, CEO National Center for Constitutional Studies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Absorbing and very enlightening! There was not a boring minute in the whole thing.&amp;quot; - Marilyn Brannan, Associate Editor, Monetary and Economic Review&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a name tag and a big beaming smile</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachael McIntosh</member_name><member_id>5611356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304859622000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FreedomIsFundamental</urlname><id>1191429</id><group_lat>41.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>FREEDOM IS FUNDAMENTAL Book Club and Discussion Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217091643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THE MONEY MASTERS dinner and a movie</name><id>8415878</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218578400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FreedomIsFundamental/events/8415878/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/c/global_4925052.jpeg</photo_url></item>