<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kayak for a Cause&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img src="http://" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us as the leaves turn to kayak the Upper Pawtuxet River for fun, and help raise funds so that children in state care can receive art scholarships at The TSETSE Gallery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll go rain or shine (except for lightning storms). So far it could be awesome with over 50 boats! We can shuttle cars to parking nearby. Thjis is shaping up to be one cool event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday, October 4, 2009  9:00AM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                   &lt;br /&gt;Kayakers will paddle to the end by the Scituate Reservoir and on their way back, will stop at a private residence along the Pawtuxet for a fantastic lawn party lunch.  At this stop, you will be provided with a variety of specialty salads, burgers, spring water, juices, wine and beer.  Specialty salads include: Asian Orange, Chicken, Chef and Fruit Salads. Upon fulfilling your tantalizing needs, the paddle will continue back to the put in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are requesting a donation to The TSETSE Gallery of $20 or more. Please mail checks to:&lt;br /&gt;   The TSETSE Gallery, 101 Orange Street, Providence RI 02903 or&lt;br /&gt;you may give the money to Mark Roberts at the paddle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leader:&lt;/b&gt; Mark Roberts, hrmMark@gmail.com  603-865-1946&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrive by 9:00; depart on the water by 9:30 AM  PFDs Required&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that parking is limited. If necessary, we will shuttle cars to a large parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suitable for all boats and levels of experience. This is a beautiful paddle in pristine waters of the upper Pawtuxet coming right from the reservoir.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Street GPS Address: 11 Hope Furnace Road, Hope RI&lt;br /&gt;GPS Coordinates: N41 43.868  W071 33.930&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Hope Landing Access&lt;br /&gt;Take I-295 to EXIT 4 - PLAINFIELD PIKE/RI-14 W.  &lt;br /&gt;Turn LEFT onto COMSTOCK PKWY.  &lt;br /&gt;Turn RIGHT onto SCITUATE AVE/RI-12. Go 3.3 miles&lt;br /&gt;Turn LEFT onto NORTH RD/RI-116. Continue to follow RI-116 for 2.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;Turn RIGHT onto HOPE FURNACE RD. &lt;br /&gt;11 HOPE FURNACE RD is on the Right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.tsetsegallery.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The TSETSE Gallery Mission: Now going into our 15th  year, we at The TSETSE Gallery believe that art can lift the voices of the unheard, provide a pathway to cultural understanding, &amp;amp; promote healing &amp;amp; peace of mind for those in need.  Challenged children are at the heart of our programs, ‘Building Community Through Art’ is at the pinnacle of our goals &amp;amp; serves as our mission.  We trust that art as a tool can help us overcome obstacles to success &amp;amp; assist each of us in reaching our fullest potential. Art is both a lens for the examination of societal ills &amp;amp; the canvas on which the solutions can be worked out. The TSETSE Gallery is committed to providing a culturally artistic space for all ages, ethnicities &amp;amp; abilities with the expectation to further the community’s understanding &amp;amp; compassion towards social justice.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255187446000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250885481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak for the Cause: Upper Pawtuxet River -- Party Paddle!</name><id>11167540</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254661200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/11167540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/a/global_10308906.jpeg</photo_url></item>