<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's late and I am feeling very tired as I am writing this, so I'm just going to rip off my own website on the subject of angst.  &lt;i&gt;Angst&lt;/i&gt; is really an unfathomable anxiety about an individual's relationship to his own existence, his life and his death. It concerns the meaning of a person's life and the meaning of life itself, and the inscrutable nature of whatever it means. We are an anxious species, we humans. We worry about this and that, we oftentimes worry just about everything. If there was no meaning we wouldn't care. If we did not think we would not care. If we were machines we would not care, because despite all of the arguments that the human mind is nothing more than a very intricate computing machine thinking is more than the following of programmed instructions no matter how complex or elegant they might be. And meaning is not possible without thought, any more than a car knows the meaning of the road that it rides on. We worry because our minds want and need not only to exist but to be and to become. Anxiety about life itself is the general state of mind itself. We must all suffer some angst to be truly alive and to be free, free to confront our demons, our reality, and our dreams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I might rewrite this because I'm suffering some angst in quoting myself.  (Or is it a sense of writers' guilt?) But I think that existentialism is one of the most important developments in all of philosophy.  It is the psychology of freedom and the art of existence and is absolutely pregnant with philosophic possibilities. Kierkegaard and Nietzsche put magic into philosophy!  So, bring along your angst, anguish and anxiety about the meaning of life or yours in particular.  It's existentialism night at Uno's!  (Oh, if Uno’s is existentially unappealing, I’m open to suggestions for alternative venues).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture (to the left!)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287868313000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283915890000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ANGST!</name><id>14693321</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287788400000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/14693321/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/6/a/global_17799946.jpeg</photo_url></item>