<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a discussion of Chapter 10 of &amp;quot;The Artist's Way&amp;quot; or Chapter 9 of &amp;quot;Finding Water.&amp;quot; Chapter 10 is &amp;quot;Recovering a Sense of Self-Protection.&amp;quot; We'll take up topics from the chapters, including drought, flow, and touchstones. Then we'll turn to a playful exercise...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last week we did the first two parts of a multi-part exercise on &amp;quot;creative u-turns&amp;quot; from &amp;quot;The Artist's Way.&amp;quot; In the last part of that exercise, Cameron suggests that the reader &amp;quot;choose an artist totem... the point is to choose something you immediately feel a protective fondness toward.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week, we'll take up the thread again with an exercise from &amp;quot;Walking in This World&amp;quot; involving creativity totems and creativity monsters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll take a few minutes, and each put pen to paper to jot down negative attributes for a creativity monster of our own devising. These could be details recalled from a critical experience, or details from a cartoon version of one's Censor. Next we'll jot down positive attributes for a creativity totem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then if we choose, we'll have a chance to create a monster or totem or both... using marshmallow bunny peeps! (Or crackers, for those who don't care for sugar.) We'll have stuff to decorate them, as well as ziplocks bags and lotsa napkins for cleanup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;i&gt;WITW&lt;/i&gt; exercise recommends destroying the creativity monster once you've made it. Doubles as a snack. Or you can bring it home; same with the totem. Should be fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a copy of the book you're following, and a pen or pencil. More information on finding either book is on the message board (under the &amp;quot;discussions&amp;quot; tab). Information about parking and public transportation near Gallery 263 can also be found on the message board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;**Please note that we are still meeting at 7pm **&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;If you are able, please bring a $5 donation to the Gallery for the use of their space -- thank you!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will greet you at the door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brooke</member_name><member_id>8390120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271976111000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Artists and Creators!</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Artists-Way-Boston-area</urlname><id>1471304</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Artists Way Boston Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268356249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Artist's Way Cambridge Meetup</name><id>tppfnyngbtb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271372400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Artists-Way-Boston-area/events/12854258/</event_url></item>