<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>91 BEVERLY HEIGHTS</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06459</zip><lat>41.549161</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-301-0204</phone><name>STARR MILL BUILDING</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1235736</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.677349</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>60.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Stephanie Borrelli will be teaching this class.  The class is expected to run 3-4 hours but may extend beyond that time to cover every topic that is listed below.  Please bring snacks and bottled water will be provided.  The topics to be covered are listed below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PSYCHICS/MEDIUMS, THE SPIRITUAL LAWS, THE WAYS WHICH INFORMATION IS RECEIVED&lt;br /&gt;THE 4 C'S&lt;br /&gt;DISCUSSION ON THE CHAKRAS, THEIR COLORS AND WHAT THEY REPRESENT ALONG WITH TWO EXERCISES TO FEEL THE ENERGY&lt;br /&gt;DISCUSSION ON THE AURA, THE LAYERS, HOW TO SEE IT AND WHAT THE COLORS MEAN&lt;br /&gt;VISUALIZATION EXERCISE, HOLDING AND ENHANCING IMAGES, BRINGING IN THE DETAILS AND SYMBOLS&lt;br /&gt;WHAT IS MEDITATION, PURPOSE, BENEFITS AND NEED&lt;br /&gt;PROTECTION MEDITATION, EXERCISE VISUALIZATION METHODS TO ACHIEVE WHEN WORKING WITH SPIRIT&lt;br /&gt;CHAKRAS MEDITATION, WHAT THE COLORS MEAN, OPENING THE ENERGY, CLEARING THE BLOCKAGES AND A MEDITATION EXERCISE FOR OPENING TO THE ENERGY&lt;br /&gt;HEALING VISUALIZATIONS INTENT, PURPOSE, AND A RELEASE EXERCISE&lt;br /&gt;BRAIN TRAINING DISCUSSION ON THE LEFT AND RIGHT SIDES&lt;br /&gt;CONNECTING TO YOUR GUIDES, WHO ARE THEY, ANGELS/GUIDES AND A MEDITATION EXERCISE&lt;br /&gt;THE FORMS OF COMMUNICATION&lt;br /&gt;DREAMS, TYPES AND HOW TO TELL THE DIFFERENCES&lt;br /&gt;VISITS AND COMMUNICATION&lt;br /&gt;EGO AND LETTING GO&lt;br /&gt;INNER CHILD&lt;br /&gt;AFFIRMATIONS, WHY THEY ARE IMPORTANT AND WHAT THEY ARE&lt;br /&gt;YOUR SOUL'S PURPOSE&lt;br /&gt;SOME READINGS WITH THOSE IN THE GROUP&lt;br /&gt;SHUTTING DOWN, WHY WE SHOULD AND AN EXERCISE TO DO SO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  I-91 South to Rt. 9 South.  Take exit 15/Rt. 66W which is also Washington St.  Go approximately 2 miles and turn left at light onto Boston Rd.  It is just before the Home Depot on the other side.  If you pass Home Depot, turn around then take second left off of Boston Rd. onto Beverly Heights.  There is a sign which is on a pole, look carefully.  Follow the parking lot until you get to the end where the 2 brick buildings are down the hill.  The class will be in the right hand building.  Follow the signs once you are there and park where needed.  Enjoy the waterfall and come in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A PAYMENT OF $60 MUST BE MADE OUT TO STEPHANIE BORRELLI AND RECEIVED BY HER BY APRIL 15 TO RESERVE A SPACE.  PLEASE SEND YOUR CHECK TO 836 BROOKS ROAD, MIDDLETOWN, CT, 06457. &lt;br /&gt;PLEASE RESPOND ON THE MEETUP PAGE ALSO SO I AM AWARE OF HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE ATTENDING.&lt;br /&gt;THANK YOU,&lt;br /&gt;JO&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I WILL BE IN THE ROOM GREETING PEOPLE WITH STEPHANIE.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jo-Ann Blanchette-Silverio</member_name><member_id>9921229</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273598159000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270322450000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic Development Course Level 1</name><id>13077554</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273424400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/13077554/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/0/global_11198048.jpeg</photo_url></item>