<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>P.O. Box 270896</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06127</zip><lat>41.762336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1447422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CT REIA Virtual Trade Show: Accumulate And Preserve Your Wealth with Lee Phillips December 26, 2011 through January 3, 2012. 12:00pm to 1:00pm and 8:00pm to 9:00pm each day Free Online Event Register and learn more at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=401" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt; It's not enough to MAKE money - you need to PRESERVE your wealth too! In this program first presented to CTREIA at the very snowy 8th Annual New England Real Estate Conference and Trade Show, Lee Phillips will show you: * Nine Legal loopholes that will let you grow wealth faster than you ever thought possible. * The #1 asset protection structure that the wealthy use to guard against business failure, accidents, lawsuits. * The &amp;quot;ins and outs&amp;quot; of the 2 greatest money making gifts the IRS has given us. * Important tax tips the IRS doesn't want us to know. * The ugly truth about probate that attorneys keep to themselves. * How to avoid hidden dangers that take away peace of mind and financial security. * Have confidence and make more money because your legal affairs are in order. * Secrets of financing your property the way the wealthy do. * Six easy steps to protect your identity. * Super-size your retirement. * Discover amazing secrets about using Trusts like a master. * The Ten Best Asset Protection tips you need to grow wealth. * The 1031 secrets the IRS hopes you never uncover. * Break the 1031 cycle, defer taxes and keep your cash flowing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325038725000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325011853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA Virtual Trade Show - Accumulating And Preserving Your Wealth</name><id>45604692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325034000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/45604692/</event_url></item>