<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday&amp;nbsp;Night Meetup&amp;nbsp;series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Aruba Steve's on the corner of Dorrance and Waybossett streets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, Aruba Steve's is one of the latest additions to the the DownCity repetoire of local watering holes. So new in fact, their website barely has anything on it -EXCEPT that its " One Happy Bar". Well, and there's this description from another site: "If you have been to Aruba you know it's always 88 degrees sunny. I can't change the weather outside but I can inside Aruba Steve's. Upon stepping inside you will feel like you are in Aruba. The weather, the drinks, the food, the colors and of course the music will have you transported to a Caribbean getaway; even if only for a short time." Here's a link for more info: &lt;a href="http://tonightinri.com/arubasteves"&gt;http://tonightinri.com/arubasteves&lt;/a&gt; and tomorrow night is Coney Island Dog night&amp;nbsp; - $3 each - apparently trivia will be coming soon as well. Who knows, maybe by now its there already! A few poeple have mentioned that they'd like to try it -so okay, here we go - let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.  &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf - I promise I'll remember this time! Anyway, we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303219365000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Its's fun, and this is a brand new place that opened in January!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303073110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Aruba Steve's</name><id>17337641</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303164000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/17337641/</event_url></item>