<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A lot of people have asked about finding an indoor space with the weather getting colder and all. One member had suggested a place (thank you!)  that had mentioned being open to this: &amp;quot;Cause to Paws&amp;quot; -- a cute little dog boutique in Coolidge Corner in Brookline. I just went there and talked to them, and they'd be happy to let us have a meetup there as a trial -- and if it works out, it could be our winter place. OR if the location isn't good for everyone, maybe we could find another place outside of Boston and alternate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to do it off regular store hours -- so the time that worked best was Sunday at 11am. The poll showed that Sunday was the preferred day, so hopefully this is better for everyone anyway.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Web site to the location is www.causetopaws.com. There is a map there. Also, there is a parking lot on Center Street just near there for those that drive. For T-ers, it's the C line, Winchester stop, then walk a blockish towards the center of Coolidge Corner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a cute place. Of course I walked out with some chihuahua couture as well! And a free treat sample that the dogs LOVED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's see how this works this weekend and go from there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273539931000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1128783907000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Chihuahua November Indoor Meetup</name><id>4778835</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1131897600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/4778835/</event_url></item>