<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Magic happens on the holidays! Wise men (astrologers) following a star in the east to a miraculous child. The miracle of one day's supply of oil lasting eight days. A magical man in a red suit who flies in a sleigh pulled by reindeer. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Magic happens in dreams! Objects appear and disappear. People change into animals and animals to people. You can walk through walls and walk on the ceiling. You can levitate objects with a wave of your hand. You can fly. You can get really small or really large. You can manifest your heart's desires - your perfect lover, your greatest pleasure, incredible wealth, abundant love, peace, joy, bliss. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 What magical dreams have you had? What magical dreams would you like to have? This month we explore the magic in dreams. This is our last gathering of the year. Let's celebrate! Bring snacks and/or dreams to share if you want. Happy holidays! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by parking lot, up stairs, down hall, left through angel doorway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357262952000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354808798000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Magical Dreams</name><id>94321072</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355875200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/94321072/</event_url></item>