<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/8/4/event_83748772.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Go for a hike, then sample our local wines and cheeses!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll take a 2-3 hour hike through Maudslay State Park before driving to Jewell Towne Vineyard for a &lt;strong&gt;wine and cheese tasting event with Cabot Creamery.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/6/c/4/event_167122212.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maudslay State Park&lt;/strong&gt;: The former Moseley family estate on the Merrimack River, this park features 19th century gardens and plantings, rolling meadows, towering pines, and one of the largest naturally occurring stands of mountain laurel in Massachusetts. Most breathtaking are the ornamental trees and masses of azaleas and rhododendrons that bloom in May and June. It's a great place for walking, biking, and in winter a portion of the park is off limits due to roosting bald eagles, but the remainder provides excellent cross country skiing and winter walks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/5/c/event_83748732.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jewell Towne Vineyard&lt;/strong&gt; has a beautiful, rustic tasting room featuring a warm stove and the works of local artists on the walls. Staff will be on hand to answer all your wine questions and to help you sample their many products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Pets.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: 10:45 AM from the Portsmouth Bus Station 185 Grafton Ave. Portsmouth, NH. Arrive Maudslay @ 11am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; to Maudslay State Park: I-95 exit 57 to Rt. 113 west. Follow 113/Storey Ave west for half a mile and turn right on Hoyts Lane. Go half a mile to the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; to Jewell Towne: Jewell Towne straddles the border between South Hampton, NH and Amesbury, MA. Set your GPS to: 183 Whitehall Road, Amesbury, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jewelltownevineyards.com/visit.php"&gt;Directions are on their website here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;winery&lt;/span&gt; if you get lost: 603-394-0600&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/9/4/event_167121652.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352843011000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349786275000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk, Wine, &amp; Cheese!</name><id>86181902</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352565000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/86181902/</event_url></item>