<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Salisbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.273173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 799-4406 </phone><name>Worcester Art Museum</name><city>Worcester</city><id>719621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802015</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>There is this amazing show at the Worcester Art Museum of photos of musicians. We thought it would be fun to have the Worcester Photo Meetup/ Worcester Photo Center do a tour of the show with one of the knowledgeable and personable tour guides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So on April 17 we are meeting at 11AM in the Lancaster Lobby of the Museum (that's the side with the big parking lot near the educational wing) to get ready for our own private tour. It only costs 2.00 to join us for this event! So please come with cash in hand. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your friends, and afterwords you can check out the other exhibitions at the museum and if you want to join us for food at the cafe after it's over we can chat about what we just learned and saw.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you will join us!&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.worcesterart.org/Exhibitions/who_shot_rock.html" target="_blank"&gt;About the Exhibition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock &amp;amp; Roll became the American rite of passage in the twentieth century. Each generation since World War II has created various concoctions of African-derived blues and European folk ballads, mixed with American jazz. The visual expression of this music and its history are represented in Selections from Who Shot Rock &amp;amp; Roll: A Photographic History, 1955 to the Present. Rock &amp;amp; Roll intentionally speaks a language that adults cannot understand, capturing the anxiety of youth, its pent-up fury, and awakening sexuality. The photographs reflect these feelings and ideas, with all their contradictions, excitement and energy. In Rock &amp;amp; Roll, many Americans have their first genuine experience of art. When melody, rhythm, and lyrics speak directly to the listener, a young life can be changed. The exhibition includes the work of photographers who used their cameras to explore and interpret the music, striving to share its creative energy. These images are different from those executed for marketing and publicity, examples of which are also exhibited, presenting another paradox of twentieth century culture. Who Shot Rock &amp;amp; Roll includes the work of over 100 photographers. The visual expression of the music and its history feature candid, posed and live-performance shots, publicity portraits, and album cover art of rock stars like Tina Turner, Michael Jackson, Elvis Presley, Mick Jagger, Madonna and Amy Winehouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the Lancaster Lobby- Near the educational wing!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271689457000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269892205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tour of the Who Shot Rock and Roll Show at Worcester Art Museum</name><id>13028014</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271516400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13028014/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/0/global_14007840.jpeg</photo_url></item>