<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>54 Merrimac Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.812039</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-848-1111</phone><name>Newburyport Whale Watch</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>881128</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.873046</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>23.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP DEADLINE IS FEB 26th FOR TICKETS AT THIS PRICE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have scheduled the Whale watch at an amazing $22.50 per ticket.  Regular price $45.00.  If you sent me a message on the board, please RSVP your request to join.  I am setting up online payment, and have to unfortunately charge an additional dollar to cover expenses of using this system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP, please send me an email with your address so I can send you the ticket.  I can also hold onto it if you'd like, but please send the email with your basic information so I can clip your name onto the ticket for reserve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I need a count for the discounted ticket no later than Tuesday, next week.  Other's will be able to join in closer to the date, but will have to pay full price.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have reserved 20 spots at this price, but if it books up with YES, fully paid RSVP's, send me an email and I'll see if I can add you.  The person that I spoke to at the Whale Watch place is very flexible, however he said that this special is going to be removed shortly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can do only a CASH payment, email me right away to let me know, and I'll see what I can work out for you.  I'd rather you be able to join, than have to worry about how to get the payment in, we can figure that out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions, and I'll update you with more details later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laura&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245078354000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234915478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whale Watch</name><id>9763337</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244905200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/9763337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>