<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Recently NPR held a conference on the importance of remembering the holocaust and getting first hand accounts of it while we still can.  I wasn't able to attend, but it really got me thinking.  Daily some world leaders are denying the holocaust even existed; other people haven't heard much about it and it just 'isn't really on their radar' as something to think about. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe ten years ago I had the pleasure of hearing a Dutch resistance fighter (Who, like many of the brave Dutch volunteers, was not Jewish.) He spoke of a time when he was almost caught sneaking food into a camp.  He quickly hid under a truck, but unfortunately the truck was leaving. Having no other alternative (than to be found and certainly killed), he hung on to the pipes at the bottom of the truck as it drove off.  He clung to those burning hot pipes until it was safe to let go - two hours later.  I barely remember anything that happened ten years ago, but this story has always stayed in my mind of both the horror and desperation of the Holocaust, and the resilient amazing people who survived that time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think it is vitally important for everyone to hear a first-hand account, because most of our children won't have that opportunity.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After having these thoughts, I got an email from Southern saying that they were going to have a lecture by a Holocaust survivor. I can't guarantee a 'fun' evening per se - but I am sure that it will be interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Programs Council would like to invite the entire SCSU community to a very important campus lecture presented by a remarkable woman, Nesse Godin. The event will take place on Monday, February 25th at 7:30pm, in the Ballroom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nesse Godin is a survivor of the Shauliai, Lithuania Ghetto, the Stutthof Concentration Camp, four labor camps and a death march. She has dedicated her adult life to teaching and sharing memories of the holocaust. Nesse has the ability to translate the Holocaust into a personal glimpse of this enormous and horrifying drama.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has appeared  before a variety of audiences including the Naval Academy, West Point Military Academy, the department of  Defense, the Department of Energy, numerous Schools, Churches, Synagogues, Civic groups and Teacher's Conferences. The United States Holocaust Memorial Museum is fortunate to have Nesse Godin as a member of their Speaker' bureau.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nesse is the President of the Jewish Holocaust Survivors and Friends of Greater Washington. She is also on the Board of Directors and Founding Member of several Holocaust Survivor groups. Nesse served on the Board of Jewish Federation of Greater Washington and is a board member of the Anti-Defamation League, The Jewish Community Council and many other worthy Organizations. She has participated as a speaker for the Capitol Children's Museum of Washington, D.C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Numerous awards and honors have been given to Nesse including the &amp;quot;Myrtle Wreath&amp;quot; by the Hadassah Council and the Chaim Solomon Freedom Medal by B'nai B'rith Argo Lodge. She has also received the Woman of Valor Award by three different organizations- B'nai B'rith Women, Naamat USA, and Amit Women Birah Chapter.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact for this event is Devorah 203-314-4329.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When the event gets closer we can talk about where to meet up.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204159009000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201198749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holocaust Survivor Lecture at Southern</name><id>7186793</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203985800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7186793/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/c/global_351724.jpeg</photo_url></item>