<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>VA</state><lat>37.431572</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>1180298</id><country>us</country><lon>-78.656891</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;CT REIA and Than Merrill presents a Free Webinar (Replay): Find out what's working in Real Estate right now and how to build a Real Estate business that is automated and not dependent on you all the time.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;August 2 through August 4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;(Watch the replay anytime from August 2, 12:01AM EST through August 4, 11:59PM EST)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=r&amp;amp;i=275" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE to Register For This Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be sure to check out your email after registering.&lt;/b&gt; We will send you the password and url to watch this webinar replay. The password to access the video will work from August 2, 12:01AM EST through August 4, 11:59PM EST.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What You Will Learn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What area of Real Estate can you make the most money from in CT now...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* What niches of real estate are the most profitable right now and what types of properties you should focus on buying?&lt;br /&gt;* How to manage your time if you only have a few hours a week to invest actually making Real Estate investments&lt;br /&gt;* How to reverse engineer your business by figuring out how many leads, how many offers, and what types of deals you should go after to reach you income goals&lt;br /&gt;* How to train, hire, and manage other people so you can actually reach your income goals&lt;br /&gt;* What books had the biggest impact on him and helped him grow&lt;br /&gt;* What his day looks like: how does he spend his time, what do his employees do, and what his business model looks like&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://ctreia.com/res/upload/pix_events/0/0/0/0/3/357.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than Merrill, the star of A&amp;amp;E's &amp;quot;Flip This House&amp;quot; and founder of FortuneBuilders.com and CT Homes LLC, is one of the most successful real estate investors in the nation. Than is currently buying between 9 and 10 properties every single month. In the past five years he has bought and sold a total of over 350 properties nationwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than is typically referred to as the &amp;quot;Marketing Maven&amp;quot; and he coaches over 2000 active real estate investors around the country. The key to his student's rapid success and his company's exponential growth is the turn key marketing and business systems he has developed which help his students generate leads from both buyers and sellers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than's systems are some of the most advanced in the industry and his students around the country are experiencing unheard of success by using the systems he teaches. Than's mantra is derived from the belief that &amp;quot;Business Process Automation&amp;quot; is the key to insuring guaranteed success in any marketplace. Than is totally committed to helping other investors obtain financial freedom by teaching them the principles of smart investing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than Merrill is a graduate of Yale University and a former NFL football player. After a very successful college football career, he played two year with the Chicago Bears and Tampa Bay Buccaneers before moving into a career in real estate development. Than is a national speaker for many Real Estate Investment Clubs around the country and has shared the platform with some of the top speakers in the country including Donald Trump, Tony Robbins and Robert Kiyosaki at the Learning Annex events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280725900000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280414623000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Webinar Replays with Than Merrill: Learn What's Working In Today's Market</name><id>14251886</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280721600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/14251886/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/d/global_14829629.jpeg</photo_url></item>