<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>259 Massapoag Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02334</zip><lat>42.059466</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-238-6566</phone><name>Borderland State Park</name><city>Easton</city><id>793864</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.166649</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's time to work on the &amp;quot;etc&amp;quot; part of &amp;quot;Providence Bicycling, etc meetup&amp;quot;!  Who's up for some snowshoeing?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of our members has graciously offered to show us the ropes as we try this fun outdoors activity.  Don't be nervous if you've never snowshoed before - I haven't either!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start congregating at 1:15pm near the entrance of the park and hopefully be ready to go by around 1:30pm.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The planned route is a 3 mile snowshoe around a pond.  The walk is on an old carriage trail and should take about 2 hours.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can rent snowshoes from EMS, REI and The Ski House in Somerset MA for roughly $15 a day.  I've asked a few people &amp;quot;in the know&amp;quot; and they seemed to indicate that you don't need expensive snow shoes for flat terrain. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;PLEASE BE SURE TO TAKE OUR PHONE NUMBERS (401) 699-7304 (Adam) or 201-673-7502 (Terry).  Meet at the visitors center at the entrance off of Massapaog ave.  There is a $2 fee to park in the lot at the state park.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From north: Take Rte. 128 south to Rte. 95 south (towards Providence). Take exit 10 (Sharon, Walpole and Coney Street). Take a left at the end of the ramp and follow this road, two or three miles to the traffic lights in Sharon Center. Go straight thru this intersection and immediately bear right onto Pond St. Follow Pond St. for 1-1/2 miles until you come to a traffic rotary. Go half way around the rotary and continue onto Massapoag Ave. for three miles to the park entrance, on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: Take the southeast expressway south to Rte. 128 north and then to Rte. 95 south. Follow directions from above.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From west: Mass Pike to Rte. 495 south to exit 10 (Easton and Rte. 123). Take a left at the end of the ramp and follow Rte. 123 east towards Easton. Rte. 123 will merge with Rte. 106 east. After this merge look for the brown &amp;quot;Borderland&amp;quot; sign, on the left about a half mile from the merge. Take this left onto Poquanticut Ave. After about a mile the road will fork, bear to the left onto Massapoag Ave. and follow the signs to the park, approximately another two miles. Entrance will be on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From east (Brockton): From Rte. 24 north take exit 17B (Easton). Follow Rte. 123 west to the intersection of Rte. 138. Take a right onto Rte. 138 north and follow to the second set of traffic lights (approx. one mile), take a left onto Main St and continue about one mile into the center of North Easton. In the center the road will fork, continue straight up the hill, Lincoln St., and follow to the end, approx. two miles. Take a right onto Bay Rd., then an immediate left onto Allen Rd. Follow Allen Rd. to its end, approx. one and a half miles. Take a right onto Rockland St. and follow for just under a mile to a four way stop sign. Take a right onto Massapoag Ave., the park entrance will be one mile on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From south (Fall River): From Rte. 24 north take exit 16 (Rte. 106 west and Mansfield). Follow Rte. 106 west through four sets of traffic lights. Go thru the fourth light, which will be the intersection of Rte. 123 and 106, continue west on Rtes. 123 &amp;amp; 106 for one half mile. A brown park sign will be on your right, take this right onto Poquanticut Ave. Follow the signs to the park, approximately three miles. &lt;br /&gt;From south (Providence): Take Rte. 95 north to exit 7A (Mansfield &amp;amp; Rte. 140 south). Take Rte. 140 south to the intersection of Rte. 106 east. Follow Rte. 106 into Easton. Rte. 106 will merge with Rte. 123. Continue 1/2 mile after the merge and turn left at the brown Borderland sign onto Poquanticut Ave. Follow Poquanticut Ave. and then bear left onto Massapoag Ave. to the park, which will be on your right, approximately 3 miles from the turn at Rtes. 106/123.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a guy with black jacket and a grey hat or try my cell: 401-699-7304.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry</member_name><member_id>7612729</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297005676000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294678012000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Terry's Snowshoe Adventure!</name><id>15993609</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295115300000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/15993609/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/2/6/global_20728134.jpeg</photo_url></item>