<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Health Benefits of Tai Chi and Qigong with Alan Krentzel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you interested in learning more about the therapeutic benefits of Qigong and T'ai Chi ?   Qigong  and T'ai Chi are practiced today for numerous health benefits which include reducing stress, promoting balance and flexibility, enhancing the immune system, and easing arthritis pain.  Qigong is a Chinese discipline for health maintenance and healing practiced by millions of people for thousands of years.  T'ai Chi is a form of Qigong that is more well known in the West due to its martial arts focus.  Qigong practices can be classified as healing/medical, spiritual/meditative and martial arts.  Qigong and T'ai Chi integrate posture, movement, breathing techniques, and focused intent. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Learn more from Alan Krentzel, a Certified T'ai Chi Instructor with over 18 years experience.  Alan is a graduate of the University of Massachusetts Medical School's Mindfulness Based Stress Reduction Practitioner Practicum and is a Professional Member of the National Qigong Association.  He also has a Masters in Business Administration.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the beginning of each meeting, we have a chance to get to know one another and our professional specialties. We share a potluck lunch, and then have a featured presenter share about his/her work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know what you'll bring to the potluck when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5 meeting fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will welcome you at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Marks</member_name><member_id>5692888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231520394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Alternative Health Practioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>alternative-703</urlname><id>1152400</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221589108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies December  Meetup:  Health Benefits of Tai Chi</name><id>8769323</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229099400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/alternative-703/events/8769323/</event_url></item>