<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Memorial blvd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02840</zip><lat>41.485974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newport Cliff Walk</name><city>Newport</city><id>1016197</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.296517</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's about time we did a walk along Newport's famous Cliff Walk. I know it's fall and getting chilly, but I wanted to get this in before the end of the year! There's always spring time for the next Cliff Walk, but for now, it's fall and we'll probably have a better shot at parking since it's colder :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cliff Walk along the eastern shore of Newport, RI is world famous as a public access walk that combines the natural beauty of the Newport shoreline with the architectural history of Newport's gilded age. Wildflowers, birds, geology ... all add to this delightful walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1975 the walk was designated as a National Recreation Trail ... the 65th in the nation and first in New England. The walk runs 3.5 miles (7 miles round trip ~ 2.5 to 3 hr walk) and about two-thirds of the walk is in easy walking condition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you walk further south you have to scramble from rock to rock and proper shoes are a must. Even with good shoes, fine sand on some of the rock surfaces can be very slippery. However, don't be discouraged, as this is only a small section of the walk. Most of the trail is paved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the main things to watch for is Poison Ivy which grows well in rainy summer weather along some areas of the path. Just in case, be cautious and alert while on the walk. You may want to wear pants as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available at Newport's Easton's Beach (First Beach) and at parking meters on Memorial Boulevard. Cliff Terrace and Seaview are no-parking zones. The meters are a maximum 3 hr limit, which should be plenty of time for the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to bring water, and a snack if you get hungry during the walk. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Will send an email out if weather conditions have to cancel this event. Also, attendees with RSVP Yes will receive an email with contact information in case you get lost or will be late.***&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking is available at Newport's Easton's Beach (First Beach) and at parking meters on Memorial Boulevard. I will be waiting by the sign that says "Cliff Walk" near the entrance of the Cliff Walk.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289681181000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287530792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Stroll along the Cliff Walk! It's a 7 mile round trip walk along the ocean.</name><id>15164674</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289055600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/15164674/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/5/global_18900501.jpeg</photo_url></item>