<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302 &amp; George Street</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.078011</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>837242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.283012</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the Brettl-Hupfers for some skiing and ziplining at Bretton Woods!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what we have planned:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Head up to the club Friday night to hang out and meet the people you'll be skiing and zipping with.&amp;nbsp; Enjoy our cozy fireplace and our friendly, fun atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning wake up early and head to Bretton Woods for a full day of skiing/snowboarding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be apres ski events Saturday evening for those who are interested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday morning head back over to Bretton Woods for a 3.5 hour zip line canopy tour.  &lt;br /&gt;Check out the site: &lt;a href="http://www.brettonwoods.com/activities/canopy_tour/overview" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brettonwoo" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2175b1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://brettonwoods.com/activities/canopy_tour/overview"&gt;http://brettonwoods.com/activities/canopy_tour/overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reservations must be made on your own in advance.&amp;nbsp; Call Bretton Woods and ask for the Sunday, March 6, 10:00am tour to zip with our group (mention the Brettl-Hupfers Ski Club).&amp;nbsp; There are 6 spots currently available for zipping but if we have enough interest we may be able to get another guide to lead a group at 10:30am.&amp;nbsp; Not everyone who is coming up to the club will be doing the ski and zip so be sure to call Bretton Woods to check the availability for ziplining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost for the ski and zip package is $129.&amp;nbsp; If you wish to zip only, the cost is $110.&amp;nbsp; The lift ticket at Bretton Woods is $76 on weekends so the ski and zip package is a great deal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don't want to do the canopy tour, there will be other members of the ski club skiing at other mountains and we have access to some discount lift tickets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there! RSVP yes for more info and directions to the club. RSVP'ing yes does NOT guarantee you a zipline spot just a bed at the club.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sara Hickson</member_name><member_id>7424991</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Holly</member_name><member_id>10533654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299555462000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298310175000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend Skiing &amp; Zipline Canopy Tour</name><id>16646356</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299283200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/16646356/</event_url></item>