<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>near Arlington T Station</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351852</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Public Gardens</name><city>Boston</city><id>272992</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Attention: Meetup Location and food details have been updated!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: May 5th, 3-6 pm (Rain date will be May 6th, 3-6 pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Boston Public Gardens, near the Arlington T Station&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Type: Social&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring:  Lunch for you and other Meetup members, something to drink (no alcohol, please), friends and family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hanami: &lt;br /&gt;Literally translated as 'flower viewing', typically Hanami involves eating excellent food, drinking sake, and relaxing under beautiful cherry trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's that wonderful time of year again, Hanami! Well, actually, the weather in Boston has been absolutely crazy these last few weeks, but we're hoping that the cherry trees around the city will still be in bloom this upcoming weekend (and if not, please come anyway to enjoy the afternoon and some great conversation!). Thanks to your input, we have decided to make the picnic in the style of Pot Luck. This means that we are asking as many of you as possible to bring a homemade dish that you would like other Meetup members to try. Foods from any culture are welcome, as are any type of drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for places with cherry trees, Yutaka and I visited several parks around Boston in search of good picnic locations. Taking into account travel time, scenery, and a family-friendly atmosphere, we have opted to host this year's picnic at the Boston Public Gardens, right off of the Arlington T stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following is a map that indicates one of two possible locations where we will be located - both places are quite near each other and can be seen from the bridge that passes over the Lagoon. I will make sure to have meetup signs visible from our final location as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/rschuman/www/boston_publ_gardens_map.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/rs...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan on staying for a while after our picnic, feel free to bring a frisbee or anything you would like to throw around. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Your friends at the Boston Japanese &amp;amp; English Language Club&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>24</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179204779000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177419347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ohanami~~ (Updated)</name><id>5703382</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178391600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/5703382/</event_url></item>