<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.367581</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1168541</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089590</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi gang,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make this showing, will include Q&amp;amp;A afterwards with biologist Ken Miller and science/religion scholar Karl Giberson.  The official announcement:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Saturday, Jan 23, a movie about Charles Darwin is being shown at the Landmark Kendall Square Cinema, &amp;quot;Creation&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the 7pm screening, the theater will host a Q&amp;amp;A panel with two world-class scholars: Dr. Kenneth Miller and Dr. Karl Giberson. Miller, a biology professor at Brown University, is author of one of the most widely used high school biology textbooks in the U.S. and author of &amp;quot;Only a Theory: Evolution and the Battle for America's Soul&amp;quot;. Dr. Giberson, a noted science and religion scholar, and president of the BioLogos Foundation, is the author of many books on science and faith, including &amp;quot;Saving Darwin: How to Be a Christian and Believe in Evolution&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheatres.com/Films/films_frameset.asp?id=83966" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.landmarkth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" target="_blank"&gt;https://tickets.landm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creation is the powerful and true-life tale of Charles Darwin and the most explosive idea in history. A world-renowned scientist, and a dedicated family man struggling to accept his daughter’s death, Darwin (Paul Bettany) is torn between his love for his deeply religious wife (Jennifer Connelly) and his own growing belief in a world where God has no place. He finds himself caught in a battle between faith and reason, love and truth. This is the extraordinary story of Charles Darwin and how his masterwork The Origin of Species came to light. It tells of a global revolution played out in the confines of a small English village; a passionate marriage torn apart by the most provocative idea in history—evolution; and a theory saved from extinction by the logic of a child. John Collee wrote the screen adaptation, based on the book Annie's Box by Randal Keynes, the great, great-grandson of Charles Darwin. Described by director Jon Amiel as part ghost story, part psychological thriller, part heart-wrenching love story, the film promises a Charles Darwin as you've never seen him before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Appearance at the Kendall Square Cinema (Boston, MA):  Brown University professor Dr. Kenneth Miller and Dr. Karl W. Giberson, author of Saving Darwin, will appear In Person Saturday, January 23 for a Q&amp;amp;A following the 7:00pm show.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264464575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264090109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Creation"  7 pm this Saturday, Kendall Square Cinema</name><id>12382558</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264291200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/12382558/</event_url></item>