<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are having our monthly movie night! Each time, we have a movie that has a spiritual theme or message. We get together to watch it on a big screen (a big projector screen!), pile ourselves in with pillows and blankets and big bowls of fresh popcorn (this is the real stuff: no microwave!). Afterward, we hang around and talk about the movie. It is a warm, casual, friendly evening spent with people who like to see movies that mean something and have real conversations. &lt;br /&gt;The movie this month is called &amp;quot;Whale Rider&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;One young girl dared to confront the past, change the present and determine the future&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the east coast of New Zealand, the Whangara people believe their presence there dates back a thousand years or more to a single ancestor, Paikea, who escaped death when his canoe capsized by riding to shore on the back of a whale. From then on, Whangara chiefs, always the first-born, always male, have been considered Paikea's direct descendants. Pai, an 11-year-old girl in a patriarchal New Zealand tribe, believes she is destined to be the new chief. But her grandfather Koro is bound by tradition to pick a male leader. Pai loves Koro more than anyone in the world, but she must fight him and a thousand years of tradition to fulfill her destiny. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you all!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347399000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200935047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night: "Whale Rider"</name><id>7163849</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201307400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/7163849/</event_url></item>