<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Prospect St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365826</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 354-7345</phone><name>The Field</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669160</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103740</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Based on Stephanie Hoban's popular event idea, let's meet at The Field in Cambridge's Central Square to view the Oscars on the pub/restaurant's big screen Sunday night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Field is on Prospect St., very near the main intersection w/ Mass. Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie has a connection at The Field and thinks the owner might be able to throw in some spot prizes and free food to make the night more interesting.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To hold the event, I'd like to get at least 10 Yes RSVPs.  (Given the number of folks who liked the idea, I hope that's still a doable minimum goal, even on this short notice.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've set the RSVP choices to only Yes and No 1) because the event's last-minute, and 2) I'd like to give The Field a solid number to work with.  (Btw, sorry this is a last-minute event; I didn't know my w/end plans sooner.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finding the group:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stephanie -- ok, you can see she's pretty much leading this event!  ;-)  -- will be at The Field for the full pre-game festivities (Barbara Walters &amp;amp; red carpet) at 7.  She'll be in the back room with a makeshift Meetup sign and will be reachable Sun. night at 508-283-0240.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I'll be there at 8 keeping an eye out for people -- kickoff time for the awards is 8:30 -- and will be reachable at 617-852-9428.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's unlikely that The Field will be packed on a Sun. night, which should help.  Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See full event description.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave M.</member_name><member_id>7526742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275960720000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267833710000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Event:  Oscar Night at The Field</name><id>12796689</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268006400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/12796689/</event_url></item>