<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Due to a conflict, I have had to reschedule this Meetup to the following Friday, July 29th. Thank you to all who have responded so far, and I look forward to seeing you on the 29th. Original Meetup description is below:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_____________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello Metro West Investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Meetup Group has been inactive for some time and I'm looking forward to reconnecting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm actually inviting a small group of you to meet at my home for a very exciting opportunity to put our resources together and make money in this unprecedented real estate market. There are tons of short sales, foreclosures and other distressed properties, and this opportunity will not last forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The evening will entail networking and food from 6:00-6:30 pm - there will be enough food to take care of your hunger so skip the dinner and come over. From 6:30-7:30 I will present a plan for how we will move forward and discuss what is expected of each member to both benefit and be benefited from their participation in this group. From 7:30-8:30 we will have open discussion on opportunities that each of us are working on or may need help with.&amp;nbsp;We each have unique resources - investment money, experience with construction, real estate sales, mortgages, etc. and if we combine them, we can all be in a much better position to benefit from that wealth of resources. In addition, we each have a neighborhood that we are familiar with that other members of the group are not - you may see a property with great potential, and by bringing the deal to the group, the chances of putting a deal together go up exponentially and each player benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting place is my home, so there will be a limited number of people that can attend. Please bring $5 to cover the food. I look forward to seen you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vahe Ohannessian&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vahe Ohannessian</member_name><member_id>4198202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311981528000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>InvestMetroWest</urlname><id>214680</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Metro West Investors - Boston area Real Estate Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310352412000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's meet at my place!</name><id>25280271</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311976800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InvestMetroWest/events/25280271/</event_url></item>