<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>VOLUNTARY payment</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per carload!</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Be sure to join us on the THIRD Sunday in May - the second Sunday in May is Mother's Day, don't forget that either!  We are having the meetup in Shar's back yard again, courtesy of Buford, Millie and Max.  Shar has just about the best back yard in all of south of Boston for Puggie meetups, so we hold our meetups there as often as she lets us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, if you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know.  We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR LAST MEETUP...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first meetup of the year was great fun, despite a cold and rainy start.  Pugs and their owners showed up anyway - as one person told me, &amp;quot;I thought I'd just come and if no one else was there, I could always turn around again and go home!&amp;quot;  Fortunately, about 30 people had the same idea, and by the time your organizer arrived, the party was already underway.  Fortunately, the rain stopped, and the sun even came out for a few minutes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pugs had a wonderful time, despite the damp and the cold.  We even had a Jack Russell Terrier in attendance, and some of the faster Pugs even gave him a run for his money.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Chris and Jeff for the soft doggie treats - the Pugs loved them (so did the two French Bulldogs and the JRT!), and even Clovis had his share, broken up into tiny pieces for him.  Thanks to Sharon for providing the soda and the paperware, and thanks to the folks who brought the cookies and the rice crispies treats!  Stoney and I love those things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rumor has it that Millie is running for Selectman in Carver.  That's her with her campaign manager in the last picture.  Who said a Pug couldn't run for office?? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets pray  for warmer weather for our May meetup!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be biscuits for the dogs and soft drinks and something to snack on for the adults! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. We want everyone to have fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $19.95 per month for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have! If you would like to help defray the costs, make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend. Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis and Stoney's faces when Puggie Sunday rolls around. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211335889000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208113573000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug May Meeting</name><id>7731953</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211133600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/7731953/</event_url></item>