<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Sandy Pond Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.428527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-259-8355</phone><name>DeCordova Museum</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>723551</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.313601</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The weather forecast says it will be a lovely, warm day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Established in 1950, deCordova Sculpture Park and Museum is the largest park of its kind in New England encompassing 35 acres, 20 miles northwest of Boston. In 2009, deCordova changed its name from deCordova Museum and Sculpture Park to deCordova Sculpture Park and Museum to emphasize its renewed focus on sculpture and to support the institution’s goal of becoming a premier Sculpture Park by 2020. Providing a constantly changing landscape of large-scale, outdoor, modern and contemporary sculpture and site-specific installations, the Sculpture Park hosts more than 60 works, the majority of which are on loan to the Museum. Inside, the Museum features a robust slate of rotating exhibitions and innovative interpretive programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the fall exhibitions: &lt;br /&gt;

 www.decordova.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it's a nice day, well check out the sculpture park first -- in case of inclement weather, we'll start and finish inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Culture Vulture money-saving hint of the day:  If you buy a membership to the Decordova, you can get into the Peabody-Essex Museum and the Institute of Contemporary Art, also.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron R.</member_name><member_id>4515948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352780762000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351886621000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Veterans Day Monday at the DeCordova Sculpture Park and Museum</name><id>89684322</id><headcount>13</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352739600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/89684322/</event_url></item>