<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Ferry Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01835</zip><lat>42.772040</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-374-9683</phone><name>Crescent Yacht Club</name><city>Bradford</city><id>1120809</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073668</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't Call me Shirley&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have seen this band before in Newburyport and in Georgetown.  They play a lot of familiar songs. Don’t Call Me Shirley plays contemporary, popular, and classic hits from the 1960’s to today’s favorites. DCMS is a “wicked fun” band that entertains music lovers with a wide range of tastes from the folk rock of Simon and Garfunkel to the hard rock of the Rolling Stones. Shirley is a party band for the local lounge or the backyard summer blow-out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crescent Yacht Club &lt;br /&gt;30 Ferry Street &lt;br /&gt;Bradford, MA 01835 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Let’s meetup at 8:15, the band starts at 9:00ish.  &lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting outside for everyone, we will only wait 15 minutes before we head in, if you get there later than 8:30 come on in sign the guest book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; Free (for the band) and to get in to the Yacht Club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Crescent Yacht Club: &lt;br /&gt;The Crescent Yacht Club is a member of the Massachusetts Boating and Yacht Club Association.  I haven’t been to this venue yet, but I have been in contacted them.  Let’s meet outside and then go in together.  We will have to sign their guest book upon arrival, then when we get there grab some tables then we will enjoy the band.  Drinks will be available at the bar they have a dance floor! So come on out and listen to a great band, enjoy some laughs, check out a new place, remember to bring your dancing shoes, let’s have some fun w/some new and old friends, you never know who you are going to meet.  I checked w/them The Crescent Yacht Club does not serve food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snow may cancel this event please check back the day of the event to see if there are any updates.  &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to see you!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside by my car.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261413614000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258313489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go check out a GREAT band......</name><id>11879856</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261185300000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11879856/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/5/global_11821717.jpeg</photo_url></item>