<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 Old Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01342</zip><lat>42.545420</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Historic Deerfield</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>1337370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.608890</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/e/4/event_149318372.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Come stroll our pets down the quaint little village of Old Historic Deerfield. Main Street is 1 mile long and we can walk our dogs along the sidewalks up one side and back on the other to see the historic houses of the village. It is a nice, tree-lined street that is an easy walk. Dogs MUST be On Leash. &lt;br /&gt;

We should park at the end of Albany Street which is next to the Old Burying Grounds. After we come back, there is a path at the Burying Grounds in the woods that we can also check out with our dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

Directions from Springfield are to take exit 24 off Rt 91 and head north on routes 5&amp;amp;10. Continue on this road for about 5.4 miles. Look for the brown signs for Historic Deerfield on the left. Take a left onto Memorial St and take a right at the end, this is Old Main St. &lt;br /&gt;

Directions from Greenfield are to go south on Routes 5 &amp;amp;10, look on the right for brown signs for Historic Deerfield, take a right onto Memorial St, and go to the end. Take a right at the end, this is Old Main St. &lt;br /&gt;

Once on Old Main St, look for the Town Common on the left and take that left onto Albany Road. Go to the end and park. &lt;br /&gt;

We will meet there. &lt;br /&gt;

Here is the link to Historic Deerfield: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.historic-deerfield.org/"&gt;http://www.historic-deerfield.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;National Dog Day is August 26, was started in 2004, and is a day to honor your dog and the love you have for your dog. Show your dog a little extra appreciation this day by joining me in walking my little girl I rescued from a shelter, Maggie. If you can't make it, that's OK, give your dog an extra big hug, donate to your local animal shelter, or some other way to make this a special day for the dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

It's All About The Dogs!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the website: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a&gt;http://www.nationaldogday.com/ &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;Browse around that page and there are links on suggestions for how you can celebrate National Dog Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook has a page for National Dog Day: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/NationalDogDay?ref=stream"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/NationalDogDay?ref=stream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346597764000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345077650000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate National Dog Day, walk our dogs down Old Main St in Historic Deerfield</name><id>77936792</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345987800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/77936792/</event_url></item>