<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>185 High St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.554166</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wesleyan Univ. Alpha Delta Phi</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1122195</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.654301</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Anyone want to appear in an unusual party scene in Middletown for a short film I'm starring in?  You'll be a background performer, part of a strange crowd scene, so no experience or particular skills required with acting, memorizing, etc.  Any gender, age (over 18), height, weight, or race is welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards, if anyone's interested, Middletown has a fantastic Indian restaurant (Haveli India), as well as a &lt;a href="http://www.newworldlasertag.com" target="_blank"&gt;laser tag/arcade place&lt;/a&gt; (including PS3, Wii, XBox, &amp;amp; PCs), and some clubs that might be good for dancing (or we'll head to New Haven).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll have an interesting experience, you'll be fed, &amp;amp; you'll get credit in the film.  The precise schedule isn't decided yet, but it'll be something like 10am-5pm on Sunday.  There will likely be a number of breaks during the day, since it can sometimes take quite a while to setup camera &amp;amp; lights for a shot, and you probably won't be in every shot.  Bring a chatty nature, a book, an iPod, a smartphone, or all 4.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT THE SHOOT:&lt;/b&gt; The film is a high quality &lt;a href="http://www.wesleyan.edu/about/campusmap.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wesleyan Univ.&lt;/a&gt; student film (senior project) being shot in black &amp;amp; white on 16mm film.  It's a conceptual, mood-driven, surrealistic drama.  This scene is part of a dream sequence they're shooting.  The shoot is at the Alpha Delta Phi building at Wesleyan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested, while I'd enjoy seeing your RSVP so I know who to look for at the shoot, if you're interested, RSVPing is not enough...&lt;b&gt;YOU MUST CONTACT THE ASSISTANT DIRECTOR and be given a spot&lt;/b&gt;.  His name is Ankur Verma, 860-262-0780 (texting ok too), averma94@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He's been having some problems lately with email, voicemail, and texts, so you should also text or call me and I'll make sure he knows you're coming.  I'm 203-901-4957&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They already have about 25 people for the scene, they're looking for 10-15 more.  In the dream scene, you'd either be a dancer, or a party attendee (tell Ankur which you want to be).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone will be given a masquerade mask to wear (I believe a cat mask).  Dress like you're going to a nice cocktail party.  Women should wear flowing dresses, men wear dressy pants, buttoned shirts, and if you've got it, blazer/jacket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dancers would have to go to Middletown (Schoenberg Dance Studio, 247 Pine St) for a few hours (11am-1pm) the day BEFORE (on Sat.) for a free workshop in how to waltz (I will not be at workshop).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the shoot, I'll be going through the crowd looking for a lost friend.  At the end, the crowd mobs me and captures me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know, your standard cat party dream. ;)  Except no dismembered rodents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOST:&lt;/b&gt; Jason, 203-901-4957.  Texts are fine too&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259075669000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258433017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sun 11/22 - Be an animal, get free food. Free waltz lessons &amp; laser tag optional</name><id>11892552</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258902000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11892552/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>