<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A new time!  In order to be more flexible we're changing our hours;  we'll start at 4 for those who are available early, and continue through the evening for the working folks....At six or so we'll send out for pizza or whatever, so bring a few extra bucks for food, or bring your own.  You're welcome to come when you can, and leave when you like within the 5-hour time frame.  Just be sure to RSVP, so we'll know to expect you at some point!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've changed the name of our Tuesday Open Studios...it's now "Studio Time"!    Here's a chance to relax in the middle of your busy week, and enjoy our cool art space...plenty of room to spread out and work on any project you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to work on art journals, and would love to share ideas.  Altered books, journals, handmade books...lots of ideas, materials and tools to use.  We've also got a couple of shelves full of books to look through for inspiration and instruction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've used this time in the past for painting...trying out new things, experimenting with color, studying and emulating artists past and present.  You're welcome to continue or join this journey. Or if you have ATCs to make for the next Meetup, or any other art that you're working on, you're welcome to work on those projects as well.  Anything goes; just come prepared to relax, enjoy,  and make art!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Simply bring your basic art kit, and any project you'd like to work on...journaling, ATCs, altered books...and there's inspiration to spare, if that's what you need!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/strong&gt; Tuesday, July 10, from 4-10 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. A/C. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, some aprons, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $10 to defray cost for the space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/strong&gt; Anyone, but you must sign up on the NE ATC+ Meetup site (which requires joining that group; it's free with no obligation).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. Please RSVP for your guests as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; In the unlikely event that we need to cancel---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348017619000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347484287000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Studio Time:  A Mid-week Art Evening</name><id>dnltldyqmbxb</id><duration>18000000</duration><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347998400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/82106362/</event_url></item>