<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm hosting an EFT tapping group next month and thought you guys might be interested to attend...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EFT is a powerful healing tool that, by combining gentle acupressure with western psychology tools and an awareness of your emotional state(s), allows you to target the specific issue you want to heal. A little bit like laser surgery for the energetic baggage that we all accumulate through life's little or big hurts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides, groups are wonderful! They help bolster your commitment and motivation, they supply you with opportunities to get ahead on your journey, and they provide support from the other members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when it comes to EFT, groups are even more wonderful! Not only is there a synergy created between the tappers increasing the potency of healing received, but even when the tapping isn't related to your particular problem, you still bet to borrow benefits from it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And after the effort, relaxation! A potluck will be held after the tapping circle, at 6pm. More tappers will join us in socializing, mingling and discussing healing and many other topics, I'm sure!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendance is not required, you can choose to go to either one event, but keep in mind that the amount of people allowed in the tapping circle is limited to 10. If you need to cancel your reservation, please do so at least 3 days in advance so that someone else can come in to the event...&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314553073000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Healing Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-healers-network</urlname><id>511093</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Healers Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311424715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EFT Tapping Group</name><id>26746641</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314473400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-healers-network/events/26746641/</event_url></item>