<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>297-2053</phone><name>Trinity College Life Sciences Center Auditorium</name><city>Hartford</city><id>440540</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us at 6 p.m. at the Cave on the Trinity College campus to chat in Spanish and then watch the Argentinean movie &lt;b&gt;Bolivia[/b from 7 to 9. The movie is free and followed by a discussion with the audience which is led by Trinity College staff. You can come for all or part of this event. Here is a link to the campus map &lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/AboutTrinity/VisitingTrinity/CampusMap.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie will be shown in the Boyer Auditorium in the Life Sciences Center. There is parking behind the building. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions, send Karen an email at kdwo543210@yahoo.com or call my cell 860 922 7997. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bolivia&lt;/b&gt; tells the story of Freddy (Freddy Flores), a Bolivian  with a gentle disposition, who, after Americans burn down the coca fields where he is employed, loses his job. With little work opportunities in Bolivia, he leaves his wife and three daughters and travels to Argentina to search for employment as an undocumented worker. He hopes to make money and later return to his family. He lands a job as a grill cook in a seedy Villa Crespo café where the brutish owner (Enrique Liporace) is happy to skirt Argentinian immigrant laws in order to secure cheap labor. It is in this café that Freddy meets the characters who affect his life: Rosa (Rosa Sánchez), a waitress of Paraguayan/Argentine descent, and an outsider by virtue of her mixed heritage; Héctor (Héctor Anglada), a traveling salesman from the province of Córdoba who's gay; a Porteño taxi driver (Oscar Bertea), and one of the driver's buddies. Freddy also has to deal with various Argentine café patrons who view all Paraguayans and Bolivians with disdain due to their ethnicity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bolivia&lt;/b&gt; Sinopsis:&lt;br /&gt;Freddy (Freddy Florez) es un boliviano sin documentos que trabaja en Buenos Aires como parrillero en un bar. Su caso, como miles de otros, muestra la incomunicación, la pobreza, el racismo, y sobretodo la natural aceptación de la tragedia. Se relaciona con Rosa, la moza paraguaya (Rosa Sanchez, que en las carpetas de prensa cuentan que durante el rodaje trabajaba como empleada doméstica) y con su jefe, Enrique (Enrique Liporace, en muy buen reencuentro con el cine). También están los parroquianos, el taxista, apodado &amp;quot;El Oso&amp;quot; (Oscar Bertea), Marcelo (Marcelo Videla), Mercado, otro taxista, y un vendedor ambulante compuesto por el recientemente desaparecido Hector Anglada. Un film cotidiano, chiquito, potente y un nuevo exponente del cine argentino de exportación..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Dworski</member_name><member_id>2589505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287932577000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285553916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and a Movie-La Cena y Una Pelicula</name><id>14905969</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287612000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/14905969/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/2/8/global_17427880.jpeg</photo_url></item>