<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The meetings are in Beth Israel Deaconess Needham Campus (the Old Glover Memorial Hospital).     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have suddenly found yourself widowed at a young age, or if you were widowed in the past but would still benefit from interaction with others in the same situation, please join us.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An informal , peer supported, drop in meeting held on the 4th Tuesday of every month (Sept through June) from 7 - 8.30pm.    The discussions cover topics such as family, work, financial changes, social changes, grieving through the holidays and finding the day to day strength to move forward.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being widowed at a young age can be a very isolating experience.  This group provides a safe and supportive environment in which to discuss day to day issues as well as larger questions about the future.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to join us at one of our monthly meetings.        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note: Conference Room A is not always easy to find!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please park in the lower lot to the right of the main hospital building and enter through the side door.  Turn right toward the Emergency Department.  After passing through the ER department take a left as if to go to the elevators.   Follow that corridor (through the doors) all the way to the end and make a right.   Follow this corridor to the end and Conference Room A will be on your right.  (You will feel like you are lost in the laundry room, but keep going.  The conference room is hidden down the hall).   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to meeting you in Conference Room A.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take care,       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate Findlen&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate</member_name><member_id>6037244</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366772472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Widows and Widowers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>widow-38</urlname><id>165673</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Young Widow and Widowers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Young Widow and Widowers Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>zbddnyrgbfc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366758000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/widow-38/events/112467962/</event_url></item>