<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Grafton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.260381</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Liberty Clubhouse</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1148723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.793863</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Liberty Supporter,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You already know that an active citizenry is required in order to preserve and restore liberty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But being active by itself does not guarantee you a win, and using the wrong techniques can do more harm than good. &lt;br /&gt;

... &lt;br /&gt;

If you are going to spend your time and treasure trying to reclaim the Republic, then let’s do it to win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This September 29, you can learn all the inside secrets of how to win at the Capitol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign for Liberty is hosting a One-Day Grassroots Activist School with Kirk Shelley, our Senior Political Consultant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this school you will learn proven methods for forcing change in your legislature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This intense training covers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Real Nature of Politics - why “educating” people won’t result in change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Biggest Lie in Politics - and how the political class uses your convictions against you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to Work Effectively at the Capitol - getting a bill sponsor and roll call vote despite the leadership&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to Build a Group - putting pressure on legislators&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still finalizing the details for this class, but I wanted to give you advance notice of the date right away so you would be sure to save the date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll be sending you the rest of the details soon, but be sure to mark Saturday, September 29, from 9AM to 5PM on your calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no prize for second place in politics--you owe it to your ideas and principles to learn how to win at the Capitol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Liberty,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brad Wyatt &lt;br /&gt;

State Coordinator &lt;br /&gt;

Massachusetts Campaign for Liberty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Don’t miss the chance to be a part of the solution. Our One-Day Activist School will be held on Saturday, September 29, from 9AM to 5PM. Be sure to save the date!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PPS - From 5-7PM - will be developing the Plan to promote Liberty in Massachusetts for 2013 and beyond (local elections, and issue advocacy) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.training4liberty.org/facl/worcester_train.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.training4liberty.org/facl/worcester_train.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://facl.eventwax.com/massachusetts-one-day-activist-school-1" class="linkified"&gt;https://facl.eventwax.com/massachusetts-one-day-activist-school-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348934843000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348087805000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Training for Liberty</name><id>83165682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348923600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/83165682/</event_url></item>