<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In view of the looming leadership transition -- from a one-person Directorship to a formal non-profit structure with officer positions, a board, and one hopes, a refreshments committee -- I'd like to remind everyone to pay their dues for the year. Only members in "good standing" -- who have attended at least one event in the past year, and who have paid dues for the most recent year -- will be eligible to vote in the leadership elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an especially good idea now, since the steering/transition committee may well decide to increase the annual membership rate from $1 to a level of commitment more in keeping with the ambitious programs we continue to talk about when we get together for meet-ups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among those ideas are: the development or sponsorship of SOCAS training seminars for local teachers earning continuing education credit; the annual high school essay contest award; camperships to Camp Quest; monthly charitable giving; paid speakers; mutual aid programs; more focused work on public messaging (like the Secular Massachusetts calendar) and advertising ("This is what an atheist looks like" billboards); paid BA tables at New England secular convention events; co-sponsorship of a metro-area secular culture community center facility (read: rent obligations); and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All very exciting, but all in need of your support. (And, if you'd like to be part of the team that makes those plans and puts them into action on behalf of the hundreds and hundreds us in the group, please think about attending the steering committee on 12/12/12, as at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/94302742/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/94302742/&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please submit your dues! Cash or check payments may be sent to Boston Atheists, PO Box 15274, Boston, MA 02215, payable to Zachary Bos; or may be submitted using Meetup's built-in PayPal function.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356930322000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354797338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Atheists 2012 Dues Drive</name><id>94303862</id><duration>1173600000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355756400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/94303862/</event_url></item>