<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Apache Pivot (&lt;a href="http://pivot.apache.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://pivot.apache.o...&lt;/a&gt;) is a platform for building rich Internet applications (RIAs) in Java. It combines the enhanced productivity and usability features of a modern RIA toolkit with the robustness of the industry-standard Java platform. Pivot includes a number of features that significantly simplify development of modern GUI applications, including an XML markup language for declaring the structure of a user interface, data binding, animated effects and transitions, and Web services integration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this session, Pivot founder Greg Brown will provide an overview of the Pivot platform and walk through the implementation of a simple but practical application that highlights key platform features and development best practices.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio:&lt;br /&gt;Greg Brown is a senior software architect with 15 years of experience developing applications in both a services and R&amp;amp;D capacity. He is the founder and PMC Chair of Apache Pivot, an open source platform for building rich Internet applications in Java. He holds a bachelor’s degree in Computer Systems Engineering from the University of Massachusetts Amherst.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask for the java meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279164608000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275012040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Java Meetup - Introduction to Apache Pivot</name><id>ljcdnynjbcc</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278973800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/13619821/</event_url></item>