<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What on earth is homosexuality and why are we having so much difficulty making sense of it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Same-sex love is incomprehensible to those who refuse its existence, obviously, but also to homosexuals. By all accounts, homosexuality is a biological paradox — a “mistake” of nature, if you will. But if same-sex behavior is an aberration, from a reproductive standpoint, why is it widespread among humans, primates, and so many other animal species? How can it be an anomaly then? And if homosexuality isn’t a “mistake” of nature, then what is it and why has it been favored by evolution?  We all know about Christianity’s obsession with anything homosexual. And yet, how can we explain why more homosexuals died under Communist and Nazi rules than during the entire Christian Inquisition?  Why has Islam, traditionally so tolerant, become so virulent against homosexuals today?  Ultimately, why does homosexuality have the history that it has?  And how does homosexual identity evolve?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspired from the profoundly innovative work of Ken Wilber and Integral Philosophy, Gilles has contemplated homosexuality through the three Platonic domains of human existence — the True, the Good, and the Beautiful — the basic and irreducible perspectives that give their title to the three parts of &lt;a href="http://www.themissingmyth.com/The_Missing_Myth/Prelude.html"&gt;The Missing Myth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; With this, Gilles has embarked on a daring ambition: to bring homosexuals — individually and as a community — to a real and deep sense of closure with regard to their personal history as well as the grand history of homosexuality, and by doing so, help them metamorphose into authentic and responsible actors in history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight, Gilles will offer a provocative discussion around these topics in a way that redeems the full humanity of a group so often reduced, diminished, and misunderstood. &lt;em&gt;(Note: This talk is open to and will engage people from all sexual orientations.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.themissingmyth.com/The_Missing_Myth/Author.html"&gt;Gilles Herrada, Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, is a research scientist, a writer, and life coach. He has worked at the universities of Nice, Paris, Columbia, and Harvard and is published internationally. While at Harvard, he discovered a large family of genes involved in the detection of pheromones, those “secret” odors that trigger animal sexual and social behaviors. Gilles also attended and facilitated programs in what is commonly labeled as “personal development.” These workshops gave him the rare opportunity to discuss and inquire into the mechanisms of homophobia empathically, that is from a homophobic standpoint. Part of his research work regarding homosexuality’s history was presented at the First Integral Theory Conference in 2008 soon to be published by SUNY Press, and he has more recently released his first book, &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Missing-Myth-Vision-Same-Sex-Love/dp/1590792424/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1363616285&amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;keywords=missing+myth"&gt;The Missing Myth: A New Vision for Same-Sex Love&lt;/a&gt;. Gilles is also the former Integral meetup organizer in New York City, where he still resides today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367636857000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363616455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Missing Myth: A New Vision for Same-Sex Love</name><id>109807802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367622900000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/109807802/</event_url></item>