<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>501 Wolcott Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06010</zip><lat>41.649011</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 583-1234 </phone><name>Indian Rock Nature Preserve</name><city>Bristol</city><id>1060854</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.964041</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I HAVE UPDATED THIS MEETUP IN ORDER TO CHANGE THE TIME. WE ARE NOW GOING ON THE RIDE AT 9:00 PM DUE TO POPULAR DEMAND!!! LOL THE TIME HAS BEEN CHANGED DUE TO THE NATURE OF THE EVENT. THIS RIDE HAS A MORE &amp;quot;ADULT THEME&amp;quot; SO IF YOU ARE OFFENDED BY &amp;quot;ADULT HUMOR&amp;quot; PLEASE BEAR THIS N MIND. IF YOU ARE COMING FOR THE BONFIRE ONLY...WE WILL BE RETURNING AT 10:00 PM. SO PLEASE ADJUST YOUR TIME ACCORDINGLY. ALL ARE WELCOME TO BOTH FUNCTIONS!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, you think you're brave? Well, we can put you to the test. Come ride the haunted trail with us and check it out! We're hayriding in the DEAD of night...LOL. Do you dare?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a Haunted Hayride into creature lurking back woods. People say they see and hear things that come alive. So maybe if you’re lucky you may see their shadows and hear the horror of the victims cries as they roam by. Are you afraid of things that go bump in the night? Than come take a ride. Your adventure will transport you to a world of spooks and ghosts: where monsters lurk in the darkness waiting for you to venture past. A delightful mix of fright and fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the hayride, we will be heading back to my house where we will light a huge bonfire and frolic around the pit. BYOB and also a finger food or snack. I'm going to have a witches brew ready for you. Yes, all witches know how to make a witches brew! LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, bring a chair and your sense of humor and lets have a devilishly good time!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charge is $10.00 for the hayride. Ride is an hour long. AS ALWAYS, YOU WILL HAVE TO GO TO THE THE HAVE FUN, WILL TRAVEL MEETUP SITE IF YOU WISH TO PAY ONLINE. OTHERWISE YOU CAN SEND A CHECK TO TERRI BRUNO, 319 TODD ROAD, WOLCOTT, CT 06716&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell # is 203-808-5829...address is 319 Todd Road, Wolcott, CT 06716...You are nvited to the Bonfire even if you do not come on the hayride. Just Rsvp and say &amp;quot;Bonfire Only&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be holding my Meetup sign!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256604257000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252528433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Haunted Hayride...join us for the fright of your life!!! Bonfire to follow!!!</name><id>11331161</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256430600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11331161/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/c/c/global_10623788.jpeg</photo_url></item>