<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-345</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>337655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Picking Winning Emerging Market Stocks, by Paul Goodwin, Editor of the Cabot China and Emerging Markets Report&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP! If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them as your guest or send them a link to this announcement.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Goodwin's presentation is the only item on the agenda.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Paul will outline his view of current market dynamics focusing on the emerging markets of China, India, Russia and Brazil.  Using stock recommendations from the top-performing Cabot China &amp;amp; Emerging Markets Report, Paul will talk about the Cabot approach to growth investing, including the use of market timing indicators, Cabot's guidelines for stock selection and the sell disciplines Cabot uses to control risk.  He will also talk about the appeal and the limitations of investing systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Paul Goodwin edits the Cabot China and Emerging Markets newsletter, which returned over 70% each of the past two years.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cabot China &amp;amp; Emerging Markets Report is a bi-weekly investment newsletter for moderately aggressive investors seeking to invest in major countries whose economies are among the fastest growing in the world. Currently, the main focus is on China, Brazil, Russia, and India.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Under Paul's stewardship, Cabot China &amp;amp; Emerging Markets Report was ranked Top Performing Newsletter by Hulbert Financial Digest for 2006 with a 78.6% return and for 2007 with a 74.1% return. It was also named as the 2007 Investment Letter of the Year by Peter Brimelow of CBS MarketWatch. As of April 30, 2008, it remains the top performing newsletter according to Hulbert with a 79.4% gain over the past 12 months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Cabot China &amp;amp; Emerging Markets Report, Paul applies the Cabot growth investing process to his stock selection and market timing calls. This strategy originated in 1970 with the Cabot Market Letter and has been fine tuned and adapted to emerging markets stocks with tremendous success. Basically, stocks are selected for both fundamental and technical characteristics, but sold mainly for technical reasons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Biographical Sketch:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Paul Goodwin has been a researcher and writer for over 30 years and brings a lifetime of inquiry to the task of figuring out whether stocks and markets are likely to go up or down. A skilled and entertaining speaker, Paul has spoken on emerging markets equities on Bloomberg TV and at the World Money Show and been interviewed by numerous financial news organizations including CNBC, CBS MarketWatch, WallStreetReporter.com and TopStockAnalysts.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;IBD Group Rate for Upcoming Level 1 Seminar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a effort to help members get started on their own journey learning the IBD (TM) Method, we have secured a special offer from IBD for 50% off on the June 28 seminar in Boston! To learn more, go to this link: &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/81154/Boston%20IBD%20Meetup%20Special%20Offer%20-%20Level%201%2C%2028Jun08.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;To join our online discussion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; go to &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212621082000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>20</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>114</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210711305000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picking Winning Emerging Market Stocks, Paul Goodwin</name><id>7931052</id><headcount>120</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212447600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/7931052/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/e/global_938062.jpeg</photo_url></item>