<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be a rehearsal for the &lt;b&gt;Legends Hall of Fame Meetup&lt;/b&gt; later in the week on Wednesday.  We can throw a band together and go play for at least 1/2 hour, maybe more later that nite.  Any back up instrument musicians necessary will be supplied.  This is a great opportunity to feature some singer songwriters, originals, whatever, in a nice low pressure venue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can feature guitars, bass, drums, other instruments (violins, banjos ...) and singer songwriters, but extras will be there in case they are necessary.  See other meetup for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make it to this rehearsal, we can set a separate non meetup time, or if not, email and tell me what you would like to do and what songs you would like to do.  We can schedule you in with our group or you could perform separately - I just need to co-ordinate with the organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for the short notice, but I just found out about this opportunity yesterday, when the Legends Open Mike started.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268759546000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268329221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rehearsal for LEGENDS Hall of Fame Open Mike</name><id>12849764</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268586000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/12849764/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>