<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.512054</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>781-953-4638</phone><name>Lake Quannapowitt</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>982094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072876</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;Hi everyone!  Only Karla and I have signed up for this event,&lt;br /&gt;but I am posting this in case there&lt;br /&gt;are any folks who decide to show up spontaneously.  It's a&lt;br /&gt;beautiful day for a walk around the lake!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't know how to describe a place to meet.  I'm sure there&lt;br /&gt;will be lots of people milling about and&lt;br /&gt;it may be hard to find each other.  And I don't know of any&lt;br /&gt;landmarks, having only been there once&lt;br /&gt;before.  If am going to send a email to everyone in the&lt;br /&gt;group with my cell phone number so if&lt;br /&gt;you decide to come, you can call me.  (And Karla, I have your&lt;br /&gt;number via your email so I will call you.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;Laura &amp;amp; Molly&lt;br /&gt;*********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 3rd Annual Paws 4 A Cure Canine Cancer Walk is being held on Sunday, May 16th, 2010 at Lake Quannapowitt, in Wakefield, MA to benefit the dogs of the Magic Bullet Fund.  Let's show our support and walk our Cavs around the lake!  The lake is approximately 3.2 miles around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• The registration table will be open at 1:00. &lt;br /&gt;• Raffle winners announced at 2:00. &lt;br /&gt;• Opening ceremonies will kick off at 2:15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each person has to register separately.  To avoid a long line at the registration table on the day of the walk, they are asking that we register online or by mail.  After you enter your registration information, you will be redirected to pay a $20 donation/registration fee through PayPal. PayPal is a secure website where you can pay by credit card or check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your registration/donation tax deductible receipt from Paws 4 A Cure will be sent via email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information including including info on raffles, vendors, and sponsor sheets, go to &lt;a href="http://www.paws4acure.org/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.paws4acure.org/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.paws4acure...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>790021</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274039956000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272940082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Shore Cavalier King Charles Spaniel May Meetup</name><id>13376165</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274029200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/13376165/</event_url></item>