<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Western Mass 9/11 Truth will be offering this free public screening of a truly outsanding 9/11 documentary produced by Ken Jenkins. Here is a description of the video:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Composed of two powerful speeches given the masterful Philosopher and Theologist Dr. David Ray Griffin at The Commonwealth Club in San Francisco (4/3/06) and at The Grand Lake Theater in Oakland (3/30/06), 9/11: The Myth and The Reality exposes the official story of 9/11 for what it truly is: a sacred myth.  Throughout this incredible video, enhanced with forceful images and video segments, Griffin details nine of the most commonly held myths and misconceptions about the events surrounding 9/11 and with logical precision proves the fallacies of each one.   Each speech is followed by an in-depth question &amp;amp; answer section featuring hard-hitting questions about 9/11 posed to one of the subject's foremost scholars.&amp;quot;               Run time: 102 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will host a moderated discussion following the film for those viewers who wish to participate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also will have copies of this dvd, as well as many others, plus books and pamplets regarding 9/11 and related issues of geo-politics, for sale before and after the film screening.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541000000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171042120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Film Screening at 7pm of "9/11: Myth &amp; Reality" featuring David Ray Griffin</name><id>5467223</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1172016000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/5467223/</event_url></item>