<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;** WAIT - WE HAVE ONE MORE SPOT LEFT **&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;turns out there were three people who were going to make their  deposits. I spoke with the people down here and for a slightly elevated  price in order to hire more help, we can open this up to 15. With these  three we currently have a very healthy 14 people so we have one more  available if someone by chance wants it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"The" Trek"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;]THE TOTAL COST: (approximately)          &lt;strong&gt;$1700, Deposit = $1000&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;*Includes basically everything, from international flight to internal flight, hotels, meals, incidentals, and trek  &lt;br /&gt;*Based on 20 people. Price will go up $100 if we only have 10. Don't sweat it.   &lt;br /&gt;*At the time of posting, One way r/t airfare from Boston on Spirit for $521. See www.sidestep.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://peruahora.files.wordpress.com/2009/05/choquequirao-acueductos.jpg?w=300&amp;amp;h=452" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome what to what could be my last planned adventure to the Peruvian Andes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://images.channelone.com/img/2002/03/incan_village_l.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've put the pieces in place for an exceptionally adventurous trek through the Peruvian Andes. The themeis to discover some of the most spectacular ruins in all of the Inca Empire. Choquiqueroa is considered the "other" Machu Picchu and was built by Pachacuti's son, Tupac Inca. (Pachacuti was responsible for MP)  It is also the sight the Inca retreated to just before they escaped to their final resting place and true "lost city of the Incas," Vilcabamba.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll fly out of NYC on SATURDAY, APRIL 23d to LIMA. Arrive at night and spend the night with the group (this is standard fare for most foreign travelers). We take the early 5am flight out of Lima to Cuzco arriving early on Sunday the 24th. For two days you acclimate - we don't want altitude sickness. So much to do in Cuzco :) Then the 11 day trek returning to Cuzco on May 6th and fly home either on the 7th or 8th depending on your preference. Or stay like me :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.peru-explorers.com/galery/vilcabamba-2.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://t1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:CG7F6X-59UVGeM:http://i33.photobucket.com/albums/d74/samitavares/cuzco%20y%20choquequirao/DSC00297.jpg&amp;amp;t=1" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://image52.webshots.com/52/7/34/53/2819734530051065895oFtRxA_fs.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERE ARE THE DETAILS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Altitude: 1500 &amp;ndash; 4600 m/4921 &amp;ndash; 15092 f  &lt;br /&gt;High-season: May - November  &lt;br /&gt;Duration: 11 days - 10 nights  &lt;br /&gt;Level of difficulty: Difficult  &lt;br /&gt; After the conquest by the Spanish, Manco Inca and his successors dominated the region of Vilcabamba. It included several centers and settlements built to honor the last dynasty of the Inca: Manco Inca, Sayre Tupac, Titu Cusi Yapanqui and Tupac Amaru I. According to customs and traditions of other pre-Incan cultures, a Neo Imperial state was created to preserve all knowledge in religion and astronomy.  &lt;br /&gt; Vilcabamba is located northwest of Cusco, in the province Convenci&amp;oacute;n, in the eastern mountain range of the Andes. It has a chain of snow-covered peaks and high forest mountains with constant climatologic changes. The region is bounded by two very deep canyons, the canyon of Apur&amp;iacute;mac on the left and Willcamayu on the right. Through both run very fast-flowing rivers which have carved and still carve one of the most beautiful and spectacular landscapes of our Andean region.  &lt;br /&gt; 1st Day: Cusco &amp;ndash; Cachora &amp;ndash; Chiquisca      &lt;br /&gt;We will leave Cusco early in the morning at about 5:30 am. First we will head for the little village Cachora (2850m/9350f), a nice place surrounded by beautiful mountains and the majestic glacier Padreyoc (5571m/18278f). Here we will also meet our horsemen who will accompany us during the trip. After having passed the village Capuliyoc (2800m/9186f), we will continue descending to our camping site called Chiquisca (1930m/6332f).  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: warm  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: Approximately 6 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 2nd Day: Chiquisca &amp;ndash; Playa Rosalina &amp;ndash; Marampata &amp;ndash; Choquequirao  &lt;br /&gt;After breakfast, we will first descend to La Playa Rosalina (1550m/4921f) and then climb up to the village of Marampata (2850m/9350f). From here we will have a nice view of the archeological complex of Choquequirao (3033m/9951f). If we are lucky we will even see a condor fly at nightfall. Our camping site in Choquequirao is about 25 minutes from the ruins at 2950m/9678f.  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: both warm and cold  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: 7 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 3rd Day: Choquequirao &amp;ndash; Choquequirao pass &amp;ndash; Pinchaunuyoc  &lt;br /&gt;At dawn, we will first head for the citadel of Choquequirao called &amp;ldquo;Cuna de Oro&amp;rdquo; - the &amp;lsquo;Cradle of Gold&amp;rsquo; - and enjoy the quietness at this place. Beyond, we will explore this archaeological site, of which only 30 % is restored, in more detail: we will visit the section of the palaces, the liturgics fountains, the temple of the high priest, the section of the llamas and the Ushnu. Thereafter, we&amp;rsquo;ll take the pass of Choquequirao (3270m/10728f) and finally we&amp;rsquo;ll go downhill towards our camp site of Pinchaunuyoc (2450m/8038f).  Climate: warm with mosquitoes  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: 3 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 4th Day: Pinchaunuyoc - R&amp;iacute;o Silvestre &amp;ndash; Maizal  &lt;br /&gt;After breakfast, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the settlement of Pinchaunuyoc thereafter we will head down to the deepest point of the small canyon known as R&amp;iacute;o Silvestre (1900m/6234f). From there, we will begin the difficult ascent towards the tropical forest of Maizal (3000m/9843f). After four hours, we will arrive in the community of Maizal where we will spend the night. Maizal is a nice place to enjoy a spectacular view of mountains and glaciers, such as the Qori Wayrachina (5512m/18084f).  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: warm and cold with mosquitoes  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: 5 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 5th Day: Maizal - Qoriwayrachina  &lt;br /&gt;A pathway will bring us to discover the settlement of Qoriwayrachina which is still protected by high mountains and impenetrable forests. Based camp site is Maizal. Hiking time 8 hours approximately  &lt;br /&gt; 6th Day: Maizal &amp;ndash; San Juan pass &amp;ndash; Yanama  &lt;br /&gt;Our journey continues following the Inca trail. Due to erosions, the road is not in good conditions, so watch your steps carefully. First, we will ascend to the top of the San Juan pass (4170m/13681f). From here, we will have a beautiful view of the valleys, mountains and glaciers, from which some peak more than 5000m/16404f. Due to the ecosystem&amp;rsquo;s constant changes, the mountain range of Vilcabamba is without any doubt one of the most complex regions. Our camping place will be in the little village of Yanama (3530m/11581f).  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: 6 hours  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: cold  &lt;br /&gt; 7th Day: Yanama &amp;ndash; Yutupata &amp;ndash; Lazuna pampa  &lt;br /&gt;In Yanama we will experience the Andean life, its traditions and costumes. Our trek continues up and down through tropical forests such as Urpipata, Yutupata (3300m/10827f) and Tucarhuay and leads to the cave of Quellccamachay. Our camping site is called Lazuna pampa (3800m/12467f).  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: cold; hiking time: 7 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 8th Day: Lazuna pampa &amp;ndash; Choquetacarpu pass &amp;ndash; Huancacalle (Pillaupata village)  &lt;br /&gt;After breakfast, we will walk up for a while until we get to the Choquetacarpu pass (4600m/15092f). Here we will have a short break and explore the area of the Andean hills. If we are lucky we will also see a Condor flying. After our break, we will descend to the little village Pillaupata (3200m/10499f), where our camping-site is situated.  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: cold; hiking time: 8 hours   &lt;br /&gt; 9th Day: Huancalle &amp;ndash; Vitcos, &amp;Ntilde;ustahispana (Yurac Rumi) &amp;ndash; Santa Mar&amp;iacute;a &amp;ndash; Santa Teresa  &lt;br /&gt;In the morning, we will visit the archaeological sites of Vitcos Rosaspata (3080m/10105f), &amp;Ntilde;ustahispana (Yurac Rumi) (3050m/10007f) and recent excavations. Thereafter, we&amp;rsquo;ll take our bus downstream to Santa Maria where we will take a break for instance to enjoy the exotic fruit. And finally we will continue towards Santa Teresa village where we will spend the night in tents or accommodation.  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: tempered and cold with mosquitoes; hiking time: 2 hours  &lt;br /&gt;Transport time: 04 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 10th Day: Santa Teresa &amp;ndash; Hydroelectric &amp;ndash; Aguas Calientes (3400 &amp;ndash; 3000m)  &lt;br /&gt;After our breakfast, our trail leads us to Aguas Calientes (2050m/6726f), where we will spend the night in a hotel.  &lt;br /&gt;Climate: warm with some insects  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: 6 hours  &lt;br /&gt; 11th Day: Aguas Calientes &amp;ndash; Machu Picchu - Cusco  &lt;br /&gt;We will leave our hostel after breakfast at 5:30 am and head for Machu picchu (2400m/7874f) by tourist bus. We will arrive at the citadel around 6:00 am. After a guided tour around the archeological site, including information about life and culture of the Incas, you will have enough time to enjoy Machu picchu and Wayna picchu (2750m/9022f) on your own. We will leave Aguas Calientes by train either at 2:55 pm or at 6:10 pm. Until then, you will have time to have lunch in one of the nice restaurants. Moreover, you can visit the hot springs in Aguas Calientes to relax a bit.  &lt;br /&gt;Hiking time: 02 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Included:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Transport:  &lt;br /&gt;Private transport from the hotel to Cachora  &lt;br /&gt;Transport from Huancacalle to Santa Teresa  &lt;br /&gt;Bus up and down to Machu Picchu  &lt;br /&gt;Tourist train from Aguas Calientes to Cusco or train from Aguas Calientes to Ollantaytambo and to Cusco by bus  &lt;br /&gt;Entrance fees to Choquequirao  &lt;br /&gt;Entrance fees to Vilcabamba  &lt;br /&gt;Entrance fees to Machu Picchu  &lt;br /&gt;Basic hotel in Santa Teresa  &lt;br /&gt;Hotel in Aguas Calientes  &lt;br /&gt;Meals during the excursion (breakfast, lunch, dinner and snacks)  &lt;br /&gt;Dinner in Aguas Calientes  &lt;br /&gt;Professional bilingual guide   &lt;br /&gt;High quality camping equipment (professional 2-persons tents, Doite, Model Kailas 3, extra light/4.5kgs and Doite, Model Himalaya, extra light/4.5kgs, both are for 2 persons. Mattresses, eating tent with table and chairs, bathroom tent)  &lt;br /&gt;Cook and cooking equipment  &lt;br /&gt;Horseman and mules, for our camping and personal equipment of customer  &lt;br /&gt;Emergency horse  &lt;br /&gt;First-aid kit, oxygen bottle and safety rope  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Not included:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Sleeping bag (rentable)  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;remember, you can still sign up for the December Trip&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEPOSIT: $800:&lt;/strong&gt; Earlier deposits get room preference. Also be aware of Airfare increases.  Make though Paypal to keng223@gmail.com. If you pay via CC then add 2.9%, via bank account is free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Machu Picchu Trek: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hvhikers/calendar/14723582/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Vilcabamba Trek: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hvhi"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken</member_name><member_id>68115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303561804000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288734312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peru - Vilcabamba, Choquequirao, Cota Coca and Corihuayra + Machu Picchu</name><id>15315840</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303556400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15315840/</event_url></item>