<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's the &amp;quot;the holiday season&amp;quot; and a time of joy and/or angst for many.  It's also a great time to put on your philosopher's hat and reflect on the meaning of the holidays or, perhaps, to critique their commercialization or various degradations.  In my view, there's probably much room for both positive and negative critique to go around, so let's have a philosophical kickoff of the holidays!  This is an Impromptu, of course, so the topic can morph once we get going.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is tentatively going to be held at Panera Bread in Watertown, but if anyone has an idea for a new venue I would be very open to it.  Any pubs in the area that are conducive to conversation on a Friday night?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, a reminder that &amp;quot;Atheism, Theism, Deism and The Rest of Us&amp;quot; is happening the following Friday, December 10th.  It will be in the big, quiet, and private room at  Uno's restaurant.  This Impromptu Philosophizer can, perhaps, serve as a nice segue!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The regular Impromptu Philosophizer introduction follows&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Impromptu Philosophizer is a casual meeting at a cafe or pub that may or may not have a specific topic, and may even be scheduled “on the spur of the moment!&amp;quot;  It's great to know that there is now a way for philosophically minded people to meet but with no particular agenda other than that of satisfying the need to talk about what's on your mind.  Whether the interest or concern involves current events or politics, cultural or intellectual issues, personal stuff, pure philosophy or whatever else is on your mind we can all benefit from sharing philosophical perspectives.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Therapy for the sane,&amp;quot; a term used by Gerd Achenbach (founder of the modern &lt;a href="http://www.integralhypnosis.com/philosophical_counseling.htm" target="_blank"&gt;philosophical counseling&lt;/a&gt; movement), may partially suggest the Impromptu Philosophizer concept but it is more multifaceted than, say, an occasional &amp;quot;therapy&amp;quot; session after a trying day.  IPs are designed to be fun, engaging and unique opportunities for creating a near spontaneous venue to meet other group members for the purpose of sharing thoughts, ideas and concerns from a philosophical perspective.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Impromptu Philosophizers are spontaneous, existentially driven meetings and discussions.  Of course, continue to check back often for the scheduling of the somewhat more structured, topical meetings  that are regularly scheduled by Boston Area Philosophy Discussions!     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPECIAL NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;  By its very nature, an Impromptu Philosophizer may often have a small turnout. Accordingly, in order to prevent situations in which the event host arrives and there is no one else who shows up, in some cases those who 'Yes&amp;quot; RSVP may be asked to email a further confirmation.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture (Look for the Meetup sign).  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291599426000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290356687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Impromptu Philosophizer:  Holiday Edition</name><id>15516433</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291420800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/15516433/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/a/global_15047834.jpeg</photo_url></item>