<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>4th Floor</address_2><address_1>595 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.349299</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BU School of Management</name><city>Boston</city><id>939527</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099815</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Panel Line-up:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Local Motors will design, manufacture, and bring to market innovative, lightweight, efficient cars. These cars will revolutionize not only automobiles, but also the very structure of auto-making, auto-selling, and auto-servicing. At Local Motors, auto-making and product choice is a participative open-development/crowdsourcing process taking place both at Local Motors’ regional Micro-Factories, and via www.local-motors.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local-motors.com hosts monthly car design competitions inviting the community of customers, designers and enthusiasts to design, vote and choose winners, as well as which cars are developed and brought to market for specific local regions. Local Motors customers join experts at regional Micro-Factories to build their cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * uTest crowdsources on demand software, application, and quality assurance testing through an international community of professional software engineers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Acquia provides commercial support for open source Drupal, a leading web Content Management System.&lt;br /&gt;    * Venture Capitalist: TBD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration: &lt;a href="http://www.ultralightstartupscrowdsourcing.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ultralight...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * What is crowdsourcing and how similar is it to open source?&lt;br /&gt;    * What are the benefits of crowdsourcing?&lt;br /&gt;    * What companies are using the model? How are they saving money? What results are they achieving? &lt;br /&gt;    * What is decentralize intelligence and how can it improve businesses?&lt;br /&gt;    * Why is crowdsourcing a disruptive business model? How are they changing the competitive landscape? What trends are emerging and how can these be leveraged to create more efficient systems?&lt;br /&gt;    * How do feedback loops relate to crowdsourcing? Will this model help produce better products and services?&lt;br /&gt;    * What are the advantages/disadvantages?&lt;br /&gt;    * Can crowdsourcing help save the automotive and financial industries?&lt;br /&gt;    * What are the most effective ways to build communities?&lt;br /&gt;    * How can companies utilize crowdsourcing to develop new products?&lt;br /&gt;    * What are the reasons behind uTest, Local Motors, and Acquia/Drupal's success?&lt;br /&gt;    * How can crowdsourcing be used to get to market quicker?&lt;br /&gt;    * How can crowdsourcing enhance quality assurance?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Doron Reuveni, CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of uTest [Crowdsourced Software/Application Testing]&lt;br /&gt;    * John B. Rogers, CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Local Motors [Crowdsourced Car Design]&lt;br /&gt;    * Jay Batson, Co-Founder of Acquia [Open Source Drupal]&lt;br /&gt;    * Venture Capitalist: TBD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Alex Lindahl, Boston Organizer of Ultra Light Startups&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex Lindahl</member_name><member_id>9182832</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255043979000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ultra Light Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>uls-boston</urlname><id>1414584</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Ultra Light Startups: Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240457423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crowdsourcing Business Panel</name><id>10248888</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241562600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/uls-boston/events/10248888/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/global_7770175.jpeg</photo_url></item>