<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For our Wednesday night fly-out how do you feel about flying into Hartford (HFD) for some Mexican to celebrate Cinco de Mayo?       Ok one day late.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have arranged for a crew car or a line person to transport us to and from a restaurant called Margaritas, a short distance off of the field that I have been told has great food. We could meet at FIT and fly out as a group down to Hartford wheels up at 5:30.    &lt;br /&gt;The Airport is very nice and the people at Atlantic Aviation are very friendly and more than willing to help us.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our flight to Marshfield last Wednesday was a lot of fun. We had a large group of 18 with a total of seven planes. Very nice scenic trip had by all. Flying has been great... If you want to come usually plenty of room. Please RSVP so that I can let the restaurant know how many to expect for dinner. Remember to keep your Wednesday nights free...thats Fly-out night!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, if anyone has a place that they would like to go, please let one of your orginizers know. We will be more than happy to add it. Always looking for fun destinations!!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.airnav.com/airport/KHFD" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.airnav.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.margs.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.margs.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary Archer</member_name><member_id>6716312</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242473907000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241150076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cinco de Mayo at Margaritas, Hartford, CT</name><id>10309252</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242250200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/10309252/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/c/6/global_8430454.jpeg</photo_url></item>