<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Seminar: A Mystical Interpretation of the Christmas Story&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, Decmeber 22 - 7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you desire to have a more meaningful Christmas this year, join us and get your season started with an in-depth look at the inner meaning of Christmas and how we can enter into the experience of a truly spiritual holy season. Mystics interpret all the events in the life of Jesus and Mary as not only being literal events but also symbolizing each step along the spiritual path for those who desire transformation. In the Christmas story, not only do Jesus and Mary symbolize specific aspects of us, so do Joseph, the wise men, the shepherds, the star, the animals in the stable, and the stable itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has devoted his life in service to God; for over 20 years, he has served as a Priest and Master Teacher. Currently, he serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ/Sophia, teaching and ministering to his spiritual students, and guiding fifteen Centers of Light and their ministers around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father Peter’s music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within. Listen to his music on Sophia Radio. When not traveling, Father Peter lives at the Center of Light in Chicago, IL.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Located just around the corner from the Stony Brook T-stop on the orange line.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230165453000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229469696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Seminar:  A Mystical Interpretation of the Christmas Story</name><id>9349321</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229992200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/9349321/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/1/c/global_6658380.jpeg</photo_url></item>