<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 64 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Loeb Drama Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>202202</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;FREE TICKETS are available to Boston International/Arthouse  &lt;br /&gt;Movie Meetup Group members for this Saturday, December 2, 2:00  &lt;br /&gt;pm matinee. See below for how to make reservations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not sure of the number of tickets that are available and please reserve seats and RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only if you are sure you can attend. If a good number of people can make it, I'll make reservations at a Harvard Square locale. If not, we'll just wing it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The American Repertory Theatre invites you to WINGS OF DESIRE,  &lt;br /&gt;a world premiere stage adaptation of Wim Wenders' award-winning  &lt;br /&gt;movie featuring music by Andy Moor (The Ex), live news reader  &lt;br /&gt;Robin Young (WBUR), and Mam Smith, a professional aerialist.  &lt;br /&gt;WINGS OF DESIRE is a co-production with Toneelgroep Amsterdam.  &lt;br /&gt;Prior to its U.S. debut, the production has played to audiences  &lt;br /&gt;in Amsterdam and toured throughout The Netherlands and Belgium.  &lt;br /&gt;de Groene Amsterdammer calls it &amp;quot;a magnificent viewing  &lt;br /&gt;experience!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The performance lasts approximately 1 hour, 45 minutes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To make a reservation, please complete the following form: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amrep.org/wings/ticketoffersat_rsvp.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amrep.org/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The deadline for RSVPing is Friday at 5pm.  You will receive a  &lt;br /&gt;final confirmation by Saturday morning at 9am.  Tickets will be  &lt;br /&gt;ready for pickup the day of the show (Saturday, December 2nd at  &lt;br /&gt;noon). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: Subject to availability. Limit two tickets per  &lt;br /&gt;person. Tickets may be picked up beginning at noon on the day  &lt;br /&gt;of the selected performance. Any tickets that have not been  &lt;br /&gt;claimed by fifteen minutes prior to curtain will be released.  &lt;br /&gt;Seats are assigned on a first-come, first-served basis when  &lt;br /&gt;tickets are picked up, so arrive early for the best selection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about WINGS OF DESIRE, visit  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amrep.org/wings" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amrep.org/...&lt;/a&gt; where you can download video and  &lt;br /&gt;audio podcasts featuring interviews with Associate Artistic  &lt;br /&gt;Director Gideon Lester and actor Bernard White; read the  &lt;br /&gt;ARTblog, including daily posts from Bernard White, and see  &lt;br /&gt;photos of the production during its European tour. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165259354000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1164936622000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Members Only: Free Tickets for "Wings of Desire"A.R.T. Theater Production</name><id>5299959</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165086000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5299959/</event_url></item>