<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I think its easier for everyone if i just stay parked in the boat launch area till its picanick time....at least you can find me...LOOK FOR THE ORANGE CONES...im going to get close to the water as i can...dont like carrieing them yaks..LOL&lt;br /&gt;some can paddle with the AMC and some can paddle with anyone they want...&lt;br /&gt;when its over..food tiem in the other area, this area is also central to the other activity anyway...&lt;br /&gt;Ok i see a bit cooler..a bit windy..but should be pretty good...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK if any new persons are comming GO to the boat launch area...first and fins us...&lt;br /&gt;Oh forgot  THA SHABOO thing is in willymantic starting about 5..maybe a plan for that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go To the wethersfield kayaking group meetup for further details....and rsvp there..&lt;br /&gt;most are paddlers..but if you didnt indicate..i dont knowe...and no sence in looking for you in both places...&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK this is a combined meetup with my kayak group..they will be kayaking on the gret waters of the lake...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddling starts at 10..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There wernt enough kayaks for me..so i wanted to walk/bike the area anyway..AND HAVE A PICKANICK after the kayaking is done..&lt;br /&gt;thae trickey part is the pickanick is in a different part of the place than the boat launch...pretty close though..ya pass the area on the way to the boat launch..but i have to leave my car there with the trailer..etc...can get the table and stuff as needed a bit later..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you are a kayaker...see my inforo on the wethersfield kayaking thing..just look..im not doing everything for ya LOL..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the kayaking is supposed to go about 4 hours or so...so pickanick for them is about 3 or so...i want to bike/walk ..etc for about the same time &lt;br /&gt;and meet ya at the picknick area...&lt;br /&gt;the customary orange cones will be in view somewhere for you to spot..2 on the car..2 at the pickanick area...the place might have a lot of tables filled..dont know..i bring my own...&lt;br /&gt;grill and stoves too..etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO if you want, i see Kevin has a hike run by someone that seems to know the mountain..havent met him yet....hike the mountain then visit us..&lt;br /&gt;we most likely stay till dark anyway..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF not enough of you rsvp from this site..then i just keep the table etc in the car at the boat launch and use the launch as my center of travel...&lt;br /&gt;or we can meet at the pickanick area..INDICATE below..:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you are already signed up for the paddle...just say PADDLING...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN CANCELS THE EVENT.. I will update as the event draws closer..and as usual my part of the trip dosent end when the thers go home... &lt;br /&gt;its usually cook dinner and have a fire pit going later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Boat Launch: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-84, south on rte 195 (exit 68) through Storrs to Mansfield ctr (about 11 miles from 84) &lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. (licquer store at the intersection too) &lt;br /&gt;Its saturday..GET SOME..LOL&lt;br /&gt;Will see a picknick area on left &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For kayakers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(the boat launch is a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-384, follow rte 6 to toward Willimantic. &lt;br /&gt;6 and 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6. &lt;br /&gt;Follow ths highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte633 or s. frontage rd.) it is acually a parallel to rte6 connector to rte 195, &lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too, &lt;br /&gt;Go north on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, same info from here as above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue Toyota Avalon with the kayaks on a old sailboat trailer. maybe even one kayak with a 55 horsepower motor on it and a torpedo prop... &lt;br /&gt;The RedNeck Jet....runs on pure moonshine... &lt;br /&gt;That will get that pesky mother in law over the dam in no time...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For users of GPS or Mapquest.. &lt;br /&gt;use 300 Bassetts Bridge Road, Mansfield Center, CT&lt;br /&gt;for the boat launch location...&lt;br /&gt;or 200 for the pickanick area...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indicate Biking/Walking or Paddling..cant be in both places at once...&lt;br /&gt;pickanick is for both later..&lt;br /&gt;MAYBEES..i just think are NO'ses..and im not into picking ...ok not banking on maybees being there anyway...but i understand things are dependent on things...&lt;br /&gt;so there...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;oh if ya cant read that well...and ya missed stuff in da middle above..(most people say they dont read all the stuff i put in the middle)..and ya couldnt figure out what is going on at both locations..woe..you must be more stupiders than i am..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok summer is almost over...&lt;br /&gt;the future of this site for cold weather will be fo cussing on going to dingy smelly loud bars to find your love..get outside while ya can...LOL..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187619031000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187188300000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPDATE:Walk, Bike, Kayak, Pickanick at Mansfield Hollow/dam</name><id>6184754</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187445600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6184754/</event_url></item>