<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The MEETUP group is invited to join the amazing Annual&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;DRUMMING FOR THE MARATHON!&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/4/8/b/event_18029835.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the 11th year we've been drumming at the start of Heartbreak Hill. Organized by your Meetup leader, John Tracy and drummers from The DrumConnection. There are usually about fifty drummers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Runners say it's the highlight of their trip. Some even like us so much they stop a moment and try the drums.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Onlookers smile, police and military wave, TV cameras pass by, children dance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Really special! Don't miss it!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP so we know how to set up the space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No drums? We will have a few extra, and people will share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click for a video of us:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XUpBcIqParc"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XUpBcIqParc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;____________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;PLEASE CHECK THESE DETAILS CAREFULLY.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;THEY ARE CRITICAL!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you need so you can get there without stress or parking problems, and be there right at the drumming spot, with an easy route out for when you leave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHERE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We set aside a private area near the corner of Chestnut St. and Commonwelth Ave. (rte 30) in Newton. You can park right on Commonwealth Ave, on the small parallel local road that is next to the main-thruway of Commonwealth where the runnenrs go. If this is full when you arrive you can park on local streets nearby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One good approach is to enter Chestnut St. at Beacon St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a map of the local streets of print one from mapquest.com or google maps. You may need this if you need to find a route around police barriers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHEN:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get there early and avoid traffic and get through to park. &lt;em&gt;Worth the effort&lt;/em&gt;. Yes. I know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wheelchair start: 9:22 a.m., Runners start: 9:32 a.m., Wheelchairs arrive at our spot at about 10:17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newton police say they start putting up roadblocks at 9:00. We have found this is a bit uncertain; sometimes a bit earlier, sometimes a bit later. My guess from past experience at our events, and from living there, the roadblock at Chestnut and Beacon St. goes up a bit later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plan to be there before 9:00!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I do is get there by 8:30 at the latest so I can be sure about the best spot, and set up our area then relax, chat with people, lie back in the car for a snooze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are late and the barrier is up you can politely tell the police you are a musician with the group performing and need to get through to unload your instruments. Some will let you through, some will not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are blocked, go to a connecting road that is NOT blocked and get close. It is ok to park on residential streets. For example, on Beacon and Chestnut they have a barrier, BUT if you go one block further towards Newton Center you can go left then in a block, go left again and get on th Chestnut St. Drive up to Commonwealth and park on a side street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MBTA:&lt;/strong&gt; You can avoid parking, and take the GREEN LINE to the WABAN stop. This is the last one before end at Riverside terminal. It is a walk of about 15 minutes to the drumming spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A drum.&lt;/strong&gt; No drum? We will have a few to share, and you will find people will take breaks and you can borrow drums. Yeah - bring non-drumming friends.. it's always a fun celebration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A folding chair.&lt;/strong&gt; The cheap metal ones are best, and bring a cushion. The canvas chairs are too low and at wrong angle for comfortable drumming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water. Snacks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe suntan lotion (I hope! .. This day often surprises. Can be cold and gray, can be very hot and sunny)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, there are porta potties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAIN??&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ... Drums don't like rain. If it rains steadily we will not be there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE DO -  SIMPLE  RULES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;For the best experience, so we sound good and are welcomed by the onlookers, we should mostly play simple rhythms so everyone can connect. We need to be CLEAR and simple.  Fine to add an occasional solo if it is clear and fits with the rhythm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2)&lt;/strong&gt; Those who can lead know who they are - and are welcome to take responsibility. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;3)&lt;/span&gt; Essential to STOP for periods of quiet.&lt;/strong&gt; No drumming.  We have found it is important for the crowds.  Non-stop drumming is an irritant, people complain, we risk losing the privilege. SO - when we stop - everyone stops.  Yes - if a key runner or group comes by and waves, when we are quiet, we could do a quick roll, but then return to being quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;_______________________________________&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;ANY questions - call me anytime  617-967-2962&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;John Tracy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boston Marathon Location</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alan</member_name><member_id>1328052</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Tracy</member_name><member_id>3644559</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366067693000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drummers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>DrumConnection</urlname><id>886763</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>The Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365619127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drumming for the Boston Marathon!</name><id>113688582</id><headcount>65</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366034400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/DrumConnection/events/113688582/</event_url></item>