<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>396 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01330</zip><lat>42.526200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 628-4003</phone><name>Elmer's Store</name><city>Ashfield</city><id>1142897</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.792400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>At our last event, someone suggested that we toss out the chance to gather more informally at local spots, no registration fee, no charge, just a chance to get together. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Technically, our first &lt;i&gt;scheduled&lt;/i&gt; event is the Soup Swap, but this is our first &lt;i&gt;chronological&lt;/i&gt; event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet for Solstice at Elmer's in Ashfield! I for one will be there...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The annual Ashfield return-to-light celebration will begin about 5:00 pm at Elmer’s where we’ll have hearty stews and soups and good, stout bread to sustain you until the light comes back.  Then you’ll want to go outside to the Common where they’ll have a bonfire, songs, stories and Morris Dancers in gorgeous, ancient traditions.  No hankies this time—THIS is the dance you want to see the dancers perform!  Dressed in black, they wear real caribou horns on their heads and perform a quiet ritual that is as solemn and as old as time itself.  Then the dancers come back to Elmer’s where they sing, eat and drink, and at some point we hang high the lanterns ho and they jump up and perform a variety of rowdy songs and dances, ending up with the marvelous and miraculous sword dance.  THIS is the Morris dance you want to see!   And it’s the celebration of all celebrations in Ashfield!  Very worth seeing!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who couldn't make it to our EatUp! there, Elmer's is in Ashfield, MA, right on Rt. 116. The address for your GPS or Mapquest is 396 Main  Ashfield, MA 01330. (413) 628-4003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, it sounds like fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;warmly,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jessica&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261605784000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261062354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>our first "twixt and tween" event!</name><id>12103201</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261432800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/12103201/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/e/global_11197662.jpeg</photo_url></item>