<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Brookline Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.342051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fenway Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>721899</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103992</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Want to try all the best dishes from local restaurants in a fun party atmosphere?  Phantom Gourmet is running a food festival to do just that!  Door price gets you all-you-can eat once inside and there are parties going on at all the bars and restaurants. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Let's all meet there and have a great time!  Tickets are just $30 for a limited time available from the tickets link on thier website:  &lt;a href="http://foodfest.phantomgourmet.com/Home.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://foodfest.phant...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll send out an email with a meeting place inside the event once we get closer to the date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q&amp;amp;A from Phantom Gourmet's website...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How much are tickets and where can I get them?&lt;br /&gt;For a limited time tickets are $30! Tickets are $40 in advance and $50 at the door if available.&lt;br /&gt;Click links on homepage for details.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When is the event?&lt;br /&gt;Saturday September 25, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Noon-5PM (gates will close at 4PM, there will be no entry after that time)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where is the event?&lt;br /&gt;On Lansdowne and Ipswich Street behind Fenway Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When should I arrive?&lt;br /&gt;We recommend arriving no later than 1PM. &lt;br /&gt;Does the ticket include food and drink?&lt;br /&gt;The ticket includes sampling of 80 of Phantom's favorite foods and entry into Lansdowne Streets famous clubs. Beverage is not included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What does the VIP ticket include?&lt;br /&gt;It includes access to Ernie Boch Junior's special party.&lt;br /&gt;Also special catered food from your favorite Food Festival Stars and early&lt;br /&gt;entry to the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will there be other beverages beside beer?&lt;br /&gt;Yes: soda, and water.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Can infants or children attend?&lt;br /&gt;No, this event is strictly 21 plus, proper I.D. is required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm obviously over 21 years old. Do I need I.D.?&lt;br /&gt;Yes, every person will need to present valid identification.&lt;br /&gt;A valid driver's license&lt;br /&gt;A valid State Liquor ID&lt;br /&gt;A valid US passport&lt;br /&gt;A valid active duty Military ID&lt;br /&gt;All other forms of ID may be acceptable, but does not guarantee service of Alcoholic Beverages or entry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How can I get there by public transportation?&lt;br /&gt;There are T stops within walking distance.&lt;br /&gt;Take the Green Line to the Kenmore stop using any Green Line train, except the E. If on the Green Line - D branch, use the Fenway stop. Pedicabs will be available at both green line stops&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can I bring a cooler, bag, food, drinks or my pet?&lt;br /&gt;No.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What about will call?&lt;br /&gt;Will call will be in front of Game On.&lt;br /&gt;Will call will be open from 11am-2pm&lt;br /&gt;You must present valid I.D. to prove that the will call tickets are yours,&lt;br /&gt;then you'll be admitted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do all the people in the group for my will call order need to pick up&lt;br /&gt;tickets at the same time?&lt;br /&gt;No, however, the person in your group who bought the tickets will need to&lt;br /&gt;authorize someone else to pick up those tickets. &lt;br /&gt;Any questions about purchased tickets please contact&lt;br /&gt;Ace Ticket at 1800 MY SEATS &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside in front of the House of Blues at 12:30.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacy Goodman</member_name><member_id>3216337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285614392000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280685635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Phantom Gourmet Food Festival</name><id>14281496</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285430400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/14281496/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/b/global_16864923.jpeg</photo_url></item>