<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join if you are --truly-- ready to put into practice the realtime Laws of Attraction within a supportive connection to community. If you want to overcome any fear or hesitation around having what you truly desire, then this is the group for you! &lt;i&gt;(It is preferred that you have read or listened to the Laws of Attraction book by Michael Losier, as this will help the group move along more easily.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group is intended to help you heal limitations of the past and reclaim your power in whatever area of life most important to you; your relationships, your career or life work, finances, education.. and on. You can benefit from a mutually supportive group focused on the same LOA principles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most importantly, this group is about supporting each another as we take on our individual and personal challenges and remove the sense of isolation that we feel when we want to manifest something personal. &lt;b&gt;This group is about establishing clarity around your personal vision for you and your life while making tangible progress.&lt;/b&gt; By doing this your power to manifest becomes instantaneous!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before joining, please understand that this is &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;NOT&lt;/span&gt; any form of or replacement for therapy, or group therapy or a crisis support group. This is a group with a specific mission, and that is to gain confidence in your ability to create prosperity without reservation and watch it unfold.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing green and and the book displayed on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jackie Major</member_name><member_id>8847113</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241280263000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>MegaMagnets</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PLOAConnection</urlname><id>1426391</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Laws of Attraction Connection</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238881264000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Laws of Attraction Connection April Meetup</name><id>10115945</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240671600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PLOAConnection/events/10115945/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/9/1/global_7978497.jpeg</photo_url></item>