<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston, MA</address_2><address_1>135 Causeway St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.365456</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-222-5146</phone><name>MBTA - North Station</name><city>Boston</city><id>196352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's on. Weather forecast is OK. Isolated thunderstorms do not scare Jim. Purchase your tickets from Amtrak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past decade our Assistant Organizer Jim has made an Annual Day Trip to Old Orchard Beach Maine via the Amtrak Downeaster. Jim will be the tour guide for his group this Saturday, August 18 and is inviting Red Sox Natives and friends and guests to join him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be at North Station Saturday morning between 8:15am and 8:30am to buy your downeaster tickets at the amtrak window or kiosk. Duncan coffee may also be needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Board  at approximately 8:40am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Train leaves at 8:50am. Arrives at 10:58am in Old Orchard Beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More ticket info at amtrak.com where tickets can be purchased on line in advance. Cost is approximately $22.00 if you buy before boarding and avoid the service charge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suburban folks should consider catching the train at the Anderson Woburn station at 9:08am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jim will return on the 8:15pm (last) train from Old Orchard Beach arriving in Boston at 10:30pm. Although I am told he took a room over night 1 year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expect an entertaining train ride with Jim and his peeps. Plan on lots of beach time, sand dollar hunt at low tide, amusement park time, lunch, dinner, drinks and shennanigans. Or you could watch the Sox Yankees game too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pack accordingly but lightly. Jim will show you how to rent a cheap locker to store your baggage.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions please E Mail Jim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All are welcome including the confused, the nuns, translators and XXX's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally I attended once about 5 years ago and contributed to the complete mayhem but had a blast. Time to return to the scene of the....! A story for later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP now if you want to go. Event is weather permitting. Jim will post an update and send out a confirmation on Thursday that the trip is on.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I dare you to go. You may be asked to sign a waiver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>North Station Buying Tickets and Waiting To Board The Downeaster</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Monaghan</member_name><member_id>3471546</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345588483000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344956571000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jim's Annual Day Trip to Old Orchard Beach, Maine via Amtrak Downeaster</name><id>77693652</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345292100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/77693652/</event_url></item>