<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone, I think Al summed it up pretty well below.  Let's get together and celebrate the holidays.  I'm having a holiday gathering at my house (in Middletown)and hope you can make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a dish for the table and whatever you like to drink and maybe a little to share.  I'll provide plates, cups, etc., probably a cold cut platter and a few other surprises - and hopefully some good music, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not required, but if you want to bring slippers and be comfy, please do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The limit is set to 20 right now, but could change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So save the date and hope you can join the party.  I'll send the address to the definate yes RSVP's about a week before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone - hope to see you on December 15.   LauraZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its the time of the year to enjoy our Holidays with friends whom we have known over the years and all of this or any of season(s) of paddling, hiking and other related events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a Pot Luck dish that you like and some more of it for others to try. You can add the info by your RSVP if you like .  Yeah this time of year means snow, ice and sand.. slippers help keep homes cleaner inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Event will be at Laura z's home in Middletown sort of near the Mettabassett River/Lowe's on rte 372 and Miner Hills Golf course for general landmark references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets hope for good weather and clear roads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;al-r&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;The exact GPS/Map address will be E-mailed out to those signed up in a separate e mail shortly prior to the event day.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please drive safely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See the details in the event write up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>LauraZ</member_name><member_id>4225554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355702790000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352130196000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*EVENT FULL &amp; (Soon your Stomache too)* - LIVE DIABLO CUCARACHAS EATING CONTEST</name><id>90044142</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355612400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/90044142/</event_url></item>