<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>42.85000 N, -71.88694 W</address_2><address_1>Hwy 101 E</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03458</zip><lat>42.898100</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Millier State Park parking lot</name><city>Peterborough</city><id>498382</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.218630</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is an all age light snowshoe hike.  This is a traverse from the north trailhead to the parking lot of Miller State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://mt0.google.com/mt/v=w2.92&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;x=2460&amp;amp;y=3014&amp;amp;z=13&amp;amp;s=Ga" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We meetup at the Millers State Park parking lot so we can park a few cars to end here ( the Meetup Location) and then pile into a few cars and drive to Old Mtn Rd. to the N Trailhead for the start of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Highlights: &lt;br /&gt;Wapack Trail, 2 summits, great views&lt;br /&gt;Near: Greenfield, NH  &lt;br /&gt;Scenery: &lt;br /&gt;Distance: 4.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain: 1600 ft&lt;br /&gt;Hike Time: 3-4 hours&lt;br /&gt;Difficulty: Moderate for fit hikers, good cardio workout&lt;br /&gt;Trail Condition: OK, but a few difficult spots. Summit was icy the last time we were here- traction was needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.wapack.org/images/WapackTrail-NPackbyDougWeise2005.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wapack Trail (yellow blazes), a 21-mile footpath that extends from Mt. Watatic in Ashburnham, Massachusetts to North Pack Monadnock in Greenfield, New Hampshire, traverses the summit of Pack Monadnock. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Route 101 parking area at the base of the auto road, to the summit via the Wapack Trail is 1.4 miles. North of Pack Monadnock the Wapack Trail continues 3.8 miles through the Wapack National Wildlife Refuge, over North Pack Monadnock to Old Mountain Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After spotting a few cars at the Miller S.P. parking lot we will start the  Wapack Trail (yellow triangle blazes) from the north trailhead in the Old Mountain Rd Trailhead. From there you can steeply ascend to North Pack Monadnock Mt where you get spectacular views of north, and western New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After enjoying the views, descend through the Wapack Trail, and then quickly ascend again into the Pack Monadnock Mountain. There you will find an observation tower that will allow nice views of Massachusetts and New Hampshire on sunny days. Mt. Monadnock can be seen on the distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue on the Wapack trail south through a very rocky descent that will bring you to a couple of viewpoints, and finally to the Miller State Park parking lot where  the carspot  cars will be waiting.&lt;br /&gt;42.85000 N, -71.88694 W&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the North trailhead: &lt;b&gt;Old Mountain Rd in Greenfield, NH. 2.6mi W of NH 31 or 4.3 E of US 202 via Sand Hill Rd. from Petersborough, NH. Enter the woods on the S side of the road. &lt;br /&gt;(Lat:42.90013 Lon:-71.87089)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=Greenfield,+NH&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.975516,-71.872559&amp;amp;spn=0.242148,0.499878&amp;amp;z=11&amp;amp;iwloc=addr&amp;amp;om=0]google" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt; maps&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can end with a Après-hike location for drinks and eats in nearby Petersborough if the group likes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers are required to be prepared for full winter conditions. Proper clothing, and foot traction are standard equipment on all winter hikes. Snowshoes could be needed for this trail. Please fit and test out your equipment before the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is encouraged for all events.&lt;br /&gt;Diane 603-477-5116 cell phone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Miller State Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93 (Southbound):&lt;br /&gt;Take I-89 north to Exit 5 onto Route 202/9 follow Route 202 to Route 101 then follow signs to Miller State Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93 (Northbound):&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 101 west and follow signs to Miller State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 101 west and follow signs to Miller State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91:&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 3 in Brattleboro in Vermont, follow Route 9 to Keene and then follow Route 101. Follow signs to Miller State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Concord, NH (1 hour, 15 minutes)&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA (1 hour, 30 minutes)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Miller State Park Parking Lot,   to carpool to start of trail</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237989749000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233790155000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WAPACK Trail  NH- Pack Monadnock: North Trailhead </name><id>9675096</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237730400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9675096/</event_url></item>