<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>North vs South &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mason vs Dixon &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grey vs Blue &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;April is full of USA history. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In April 1861 the Civil War began at Fort Sumter and in April 1865 it ended at the Appomattox Court House. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In April many states have as a state holiday - confederate memorial Day. This day honors those men who fought for the confederacy. many of the veterans of the confederate army helped to settle the south west and created the Texas oil industry among other accomplishments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In April the USA suffered the greatest destructive environmental event in history. Centered in Kansas but reaching from coast to coast, Black Sunday was the result of poor farming practices and marks a pivotal moment in the Dust Bowl years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;April is also the time of the first Great Earthquake and Fire in San Francisco, a northern city. If you are interested Los Angels would be a southern city. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are all about the food and drink! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Southern food has limited influences that have helped to create a definable style of cooking, though there are wide ranges within that style. To learn more visit  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://southernfoodcom.stores.yahoo.net/history.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://southernfoodco...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northern food is harder to define. Thanks to the immigrants from Ellis Island and beyond, northern food is a literal melting pot. Throughout the northern USA there are foods that define regions. What will you decide is Northern food? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can't wait to see how we all come together to create a united state of yumminess! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, this is about your creativity and personal interpretation.  &lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook onsite unless your recipe takes more than an hour to prepare. The fun is in the cooking here all together. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As God is my witness they're not going to lick me. I'm going to live through this and when it's all over, I'll never be hungry again. No, nor any of my folk. If I have to lie, steal, cheat or kill, as God is my witness, I'll never be hungry again.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;-- Scarlett O'Hara from: Gone with the Wind (1939) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to see the clip &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rgjHuOnwhFA" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>my home so you will notice me and the dogs will send address a few days before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241822478000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236989597000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes April Meetup</name><id>9949833</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239404400000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/9949833/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/c/global_7664572.jpeg</photo_url></item>