<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>donation</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us for the next installment in our 2010|2011 &amp;quot;Bad News/Good News Movie Night Series, in which we will, in turn, immerse ourselves in some of the&lt;b&gt; challenges of our time&lt;/b&gt; and then &lt;b&gt;explore the solutions at hand&lt;/b&gt;.  The first three films could be considered the dark side and the next set of films after the new year will no doubt inspire, educate and motivate.  These films will be held the first Tuesday of each month on the campus of, and co-sponsored by, the University of New England.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In January we finally get to some of the &amp;quot;good news&amp;quot; (phew!) with a showing of the inspirational&lt;b&gt; First Earth.&lt;/b&gt;  &amp;quot;This is a documentary about the movement towards a massive paradigm shift for shelter -- building healthy houses in the old ways, out of the very earth itself, and living together like in the old days, by recreating villages. It is a sprawling film, shot on location from the West Coast to West Africa. An audiovisual manifesto filmed over the course of 4 years and 4 continents, FIRST EARTH makes the case that earthen homes are the healthiest housing in the world; and that since it still takes a village to raise a healthy child, it is incumbent upon us to transform our suburban sprawl into eco-villages, a new North American dream.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a potluck (bring an appetizer/snack or beverage to share for a grazing-style meal) and your potluck kit (plate/utensils/cup/napkin).  6:30 potluck and 7:00 announcements and film.  Discussion to follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lori Power</member_name><member_id>4201073</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294275369000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292864897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Bad News/Good News Movie Night Series: First Earth</name><id>15780737</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294183800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/15780737/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/7/global_20383479.jpeg</photo_url></item>