<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>early bird b4 april 1st</description><amount>29.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a very special 1/2-Day Workshop on the &lt;strong&gt;fundamentals of Edible Forest Gardening&lt;/strong&gt; which relies heavily on building mutually beneficial "guilds" or polycultures of plants that can provide food, forage, medicine, fuel, fiber, and much more.  Jonathan Bates of Food Forest Farm Permaculture Nursery will be our instructor/facilitator for this must-attend event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to see &lt;strong&gt;permaculture plantings that work&lt;/strong&gt;? Through images and discussion enjoy a thriving Edible Forest Garden that produces loads of fruits, roots, shoots, greens, seeds, flowers, mulch, eggs, knowledge and fun. Come learn how to use the plants (and other yields) from this permaculture paradise in your own garden.  After that Jonathan will help us to learn &lt;strong&gt;how we can build our own guilds&lt;/strong&gt;, or perennial polycultures in a process that we can replicate at home as needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portland location (venue being confirmed based on RSVP levels)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8:30 Getting parked &amp; settled, coffee and general meet/greet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9:00 Start of Edible Forest Gardens fundamentals presentation/slideshow (concepts + examples)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10:30 Short Break&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10:45 How to Build Your Own Perennial Polyculture (including exercises/practice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12:15 Potluck Lunch; bring a dish to share and your own potluck kit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1:30 Plant Pickup (for those who have pre-ordered) plus permaculture plant sale (for those who have not pre-ordered; check comments here for details closer to the date on what will be available)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;If you would like to pre-order some of the amazing plants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; that Jonathan offers from Food Forest Farm (many that are difficult to find), please use this spreadsheet to indicate what you want to order.  Order deadline is April 15 so that we can collate and get it to Jonathan.  He will deliver our orders at no charge on May 22 AND (if we order at least 30 plants as a group) we will get 20% off the prices listed!  Order here: &lt;a href="https://spreadsheets.google.com/ccc?key=0AppLRJ-lecSudGM0N1Nxei1iVjdVN2pEUENZeGxzcWc&amp;hl=en&amp;authkey=CIjs4I0H" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://spreadsheets.google.com/ccc?key=0AppLRJ-lecSudGM0N1Nxei1iVjdVN2pEUENZeGxzcWc&amp;hl=en&amp;authkey=CIjs4I0H" target="_blank"&gt;https://spreadsheets.google.com/ccc?key=0AppLRJ-lecSudGM0N1Nxei1iVjdVN2pEUENZeGxzcWc&amp;hl=en&amp;authkey=CIjs4I0H&lt;/a&gt; Half-day workshop including hand-outs and refreshments $29/person if registered by April 1 ($35 after that).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More about Jonathan:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jonathan runs Food Forest Farm Permaculture Nursery, a source for useful, edible, hard to find plants and seeds. He’s been studying, creating and working with rural and urban gardens in the Connecticut River Valley for the last ten years, and is a co-designer and inhabitant of an edible forest garden in Holyoke, MA. &lt;a href="http://permaculturenursery.com/"&gt;Visit his web site to learn more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306365956000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><why>You will leave with a solid foundation of knowledge about Edible Forest Gardening and Food Forests.  You will become proficient in designing successful ~edible perennial polycultures~ to suit your site and needs.</why><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298406311000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edible Forest Gardening &amp; Creating Perennial Polycultures</name><id>16663126</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306067400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/16663126/</event_url></item>