<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Sandy Pond Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.428527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-259-8355</phone><name>DeCordova Museum</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>723551</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.313601</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Day-trip to deCordova Sculpture Park &amp;amp; Museum. &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 21st&lt;br /&gt;51 Sandy Road, Lincoln MA&lt;br /&gt;*Meet in the museum parking lot at 10AM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Museum Admission Fees: Adults – 12.00, seniors &amp;amp; college  students &amp;amp; youths (6-18) – 8.00, children (0-5) free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Museum doors open at 10AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There might be a parking fee ... not sure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pets are permitted on the grounds, but not inside the museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event was suggested by Allen, who will be taking his bike on the 8:35AM MBTA train (Fitchburg line) out of North Station, arriving in Lincoln around 9:15 AM. There is no fee for taking bikes on the train. It's about a 10-minute ride from the Lincoln train stop to the museum, where we can hang out until the auto-folks catch up with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This would likely entail a good part of the day because there  is so much to see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;deCordova encompasses 35 acres of beautiful rolling woodlands  and lawns in Lincoln and is the largest park of its kind in New  England. A former private estate, the outdoor sculpture park is  open to the public every day of the year from dawn 'til dusk,  and contains approximately 75 artworks at any given time. Many  of them are hidden like lost treasures or archeological wonders  among the trees – some so clever as to seemingly blend in with  their surroundings, and they come and go such that there is  almost always something new to be discovered. It can take a  whole afternoon just to wander the grounds, and the museum  itself features some of the best in contemporary artists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions are available on the website at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Day-trip" target="_blank"&gt;http://Day-trip...&lt;/a&gt; to deCordova Sculpture Park &amp;amp; Museum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Also, please note that the museum does have a small café  inside with sandwiches and drinks, but the prices are somewhat  high and selections are limited. People might want to bring  their own snacks and water along with them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*There is also a great gift store on the property located in a  separate building so you don’t have to buy an admission ticket  just to peruse the wares and baubles of many local artisans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CURRENT EXHIBIT:&lt;br /&gt;The current main exhibit within the museum features the work of  Chakaria Booker, one of America's most important contemporary  African-American sculptors. Chakaia Booker: The exhibition  includes monumental outdoor sculptures, indoor sculpture in a  wide variety of formats and sizes, drawings, and photographs.  Chakaia Booker is best known for her work in recycled materials  featuring cut-up automobile tires that are reassembled on  wooden or steel armatures to create abstract sculptures. Thes  sculptures, and the surface patterns that they create,  reference African textiles and body decoration to evoke issues  of black culture, identity, gender, and environmentalism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This show closes at the end of the month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To see examples of her work visit the museums link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.decordova.org/art/exhibitions/current/booker.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.decordova....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282698802000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281977008000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Day-trip to deCordova Sculpture Park &amp; Museum</name><id>14438614</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282399200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/14438614/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/c/global_2171756.jpeg</photo_url></item>