<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is one of Jean Luc Godard's classic movies.&amp;nbsp; And it's being shown in a new print.&amp;nbsp; If you love to talk politics and want to see what French movies were like in the late 60's, this is the movie for you.&amp;nbsp; Sure to generate great conversation and very funny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's more from the Brattle web site:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jean-Luc Godard&amp;rsquo;s scathing late-sixties satire is one of cinema&amp;rsquo;s great anarchic&amp;nbsp;works. Determined to collect an inheritance from a dying relative, a&amp;nbsp;petit-bourgeois couple travel across the French countryside while civilization&amp;nbsp;crashes and burns around them. Featuring a justly famous centerpiece single&amp;nbsp;take of an endless traffic jam, WEEKEND is a surreally funny and deeply&amp;nbsp;disturbing expression of social oblivion that ended the first phase of&amp;nbsp;Godard&amp;rsquo;s career -- and, according to the credits, cinema itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Year after year, Jean-Luc Godard has been chipping away at the language&amp;nbsp;of cinema. Now, in WEEKEND, he has just about got down to the bare&amp;nbsp;bones. This is his best film, and his most inventive. It is almost pure movie.&amp;nbsp;It is sure to be ardently disliked by a great many people, Godard fans&amp;nbsp;among them. But revolutionary films always take some time for audiences&amp;nbsp;to catch up.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Roger Ebert,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Chicago Sun-Times&lt;/em&gt;, 1969&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;One of [Godard]&amp;rsquo;s most energetic statements of cinematic &amp;eacute;lan, venturing a&amp;nbsp;dialogue among filmmaker, movie, and the viewing world whose depth and&amp;nbsp;seriousness have no real rival.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Michael Atkinson,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Village Voice&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;After, we'll go someplace for dinner and conversation.&amp;nbsp; Where we go depends on how many movie lovers we are.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please don't RSVP yes unless you truly plan to attend.&amp;nbsp; And if your plans change, let me know as soon as possible.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Looking forward to sharing this great experience with you. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be waiting inside the theater where the screen is on the side where you exit after.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323692864000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323046794000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Classic Godard Movie at the Brattle:  Weekend</name><id>43386722</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323554400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/43386722/</event_url></item>