<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Commonwealth Salon Room at BPL</name><city>Boston</city><id>12327132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077744</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;THE BOSTON NATIONAL POETRY MONTH FESTIVAL&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

FREE ADMISSION &lt;br /&gt;

Friday, April 5- Commonwealth Avenue Salon Room at the BPL: &lt;br /&gt;

12:00-1:00 P.M. Dan Tobin, Afaa M. Weaver, Christine Casson &lt;br /&gt;

1:00-2:00P.M. David Ferry and George Kalogeris &lt;br /&gt;

2:00-3:00 P.M. Rhina P. Espaillat , X.J. Kennedy &lt;br /&gt;

3:00-4:00P.M. Kathleen Spivack, Richard Hoffman, Judith Steinbergh &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

56 Major and Emerging poets will each do a ten minute reading &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

ALSO &lt;br /&gt;

Featuring 5 extraordinarily talented prize winning high school students: from Boston Latin High School,; Boston Arts Academy, and Harvard University, Daniel Schwartz. These student stars will open the Popular Poetry Marathon portion of the Festival April 6th at 10:00 A.M. SAM CORNISH, Boston’s current and first Poet Laureate will open the formal part of the Festival at 11:00 A.M. 55 additional major and emerging poets will follow with a POETRY MARATHON: &lt;br /&gt;

Some of the many luminaries include SAM CORNISH, Rhina P. Espaillat, Afaa M. Weaver, Christine Casson, Dan Tobin, X.J. Kennedy, Alfred Nicol, Kathleen Spivack, Ifeanyi Menkiti , Richard Wollman, Doug Holder, Elizabeth Doran, Richard Hoffman, Lucy Holstedt, Kirk Etherton, Charles Coe, Lawrence Kessenich, January O’Neil , Regie O’Gibson, Kate Finnegan (Kaji Aso Studio), Victor Howes, Lainie Senechal, Harris Gardner Susan Donnelly, Jack Scully, Rene Schwiesow, Tomas O’Leary, Marc Goldfinger, Gloria Mindock, Tim Gager,Barbara Helfgott Hyett, Stuart Peterfreund, Elizabeth McKim, Beatriz Alba Del Rio, Valerie Lawson, Michael Brown, Mignon Ariel King, Tom Daley, Molly Lynn Watt, Chad Parenteau, Joanna Nealon, Walter Howard, Kim Triedman, Zvi Sesling, Irene Koronas, Fred Marchant, Sheila Twyman, Ryk McIntyre, Robert K. Johnson, Chris Warner, C.D. Collins and a Plethora of other prize winning poets. &lt;br /&gt;

This Festival has it all: Professional published poets, celebrities, numerous prize winners, student participation, OPEN MIKES, WORKSHOP, BOOK TABLES.  &lt;br /&gt;

Even more, it is about community, neighborhoods, diversity, Boston, and Massachusetts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;FREE ADMISSION&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

FOR INFORMATION: Tapestry of Voices: &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;617-306-9484&lt;/a&gt;- Library: &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;617-536-5400&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Wheelchair accessible. Assistive listening devices available. To request a sign language interpreter, or for other special needs, call &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;617-536-7855&lt;/a&gt;(TTY) at least two weeks before the program date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365193204000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363622894000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston National Poetry Month Festival Day 1</name><id>109825542</id><duration>14400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365177600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/109825542/</event_url></item>