<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Sunday will be a great day for hiking. How about a hike along the Skyline Loop? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While I will be away, one of our members, Karine has agreed to lead this hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will begin at the Park and Ride lot off Rt 138 (exit 2 off I-93) (For those who don't know it, the lot is on the left - a bit past the gas stations), NOT at the trailside museum lots which are further up 138 on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Hike&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is not an easy trail. Expect a lot of ups and downs and occasionally having to hold on for balance on steep climbs. A &lt;b&gt;healthy&lt;/b&gt; beginner can do it, but it is not walk in the woods.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At a few points you will be near the headquarters, crowded areas, and by a road - so leashes are required.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough water and snacks for you and your pets. &lt;br /&gt;I strongly recommend hiking shoes or boots. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since I will not lead this event I will limit the the dog count to 7. Please be considerate of this limit. Please list your animal count when you sign up. I will ask that each of us limit our pet count to 2 max. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note** I ask that everyone be responsible for their own pets. All owners must be able to control (voice or leash) their animals at all times. If you have any doubt err on the side of caution. Personally I carry muzzles and leashes, even if they're never used.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Karine will be in a dark red honda civic with a rhodesian ridgeback, Della.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luis </member_name><member_id>6933069</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257869327000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257450719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills Skyline Loop.</name><id>11804972</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257696000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/11804972/</event_url></item>