<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>215 First Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.364294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Athletic Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1390330</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079257</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=186658761377334"&gt;Facebook invite with more details&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;All levels welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excerpt:  &lt;br /&gt;The Masacote School will be teaming up with the CAC and moving into a new studio location starting April 5th, but why wait to hear about all the upcoming additions to the Masacote School, Performance Team, and schedule?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Us for our Open House this Saturday, March 26th as we open our doors to the public. Get a FREE SAMPLING of ALL our classes! From Core &amp;amp; Stretch to Salsa to Guaguanco to Styling and more! And tour our new location!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come speak to our world famous instructors, and learn more about all the revolutionary changes Masacote will be undertaking in the upcoming months. We want to tell you what we are all about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View our schedule below, and BRING YOUR FRIENDS! There will be raffle prizes, finger food, performances, mixing, mingling, and social dancing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* FIRST 5 PEOPLE THROUGH THE DOOR GET A FREE INSTRUCTIONAL DVD!  &lt;br /&gt;** DISCOUNTS ON CLASSES FOR EVERYONE WHO SIGNS UP AT THE OPEN HOUSE!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=186658761377334"&gt;Facebook invite with more details&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lmdfs0e7swo"&gt;Video of classes with Masacote&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301277370000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>It's FREE, and because it's a good opportunity to check out classes by one of the world's most famous salsa dance companies!</why><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300646971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Open House at Masacote Dance School</name><id>16988057</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301162400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/16988057/</event_url></item>