<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Faneuil Hall Marketplace</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359656</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-248-8800</phone><name>Ned Devine's</name><city>Boston</city><id>442998</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055944</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Here's an opportunity for you to party with 'stars'.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've copied an event &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/members/4305566/"&gt;Diane&lt;/a&gt; (who is a warm and giving sweetheart) has scheduled on the Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch,  &amp;amp; Dinner calendar. This is a worthwhile cause which I believe deserves as much exposure and support as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What follows is the description from the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/calendar/8978117/?success=event_edit_short&amp;amp;eventAction=editing"&gt;BBLD event&lt;/a&gt;.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of reasons I came from New York to Boston is this..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been volunteering with the Boston All Stars (www.bostonallstars.org) since I moved from NY.  This is a youth program dedicated to promoting human development through the use of an innovative performance-based model.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What I love about the All Stars is that it meets young people where they are, on the streets, and invites them to do what they love to do, &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;perform&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; And then together, we create the opportunity for learning and growth. I love being able to be a part of the lives of young people from poor neighborhoods. Especially, when being a part means being a partner in their development.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you'll join me in supporting the Boston All Stars by coming out to an evening of FUN with performances put on by our youth!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am one of Tri-Chair's of this fundraiser for the Boston All Stars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boston All Stars Perform!: On the streets where we live&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It's a benefit with a silent auction.  I'm really excited to have an opportunity to invite you to join me at this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some Items for Auction:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Luxury Timeshare in Cabo Mexico&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.lynda.com --1 Year Premium Membership for access to all courses, plus exercise files&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;A deluxe tune up from Ferris Wheels Bike Shop&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;-- Tutoring in Math and Social Net Working,&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;10-spinning classes at Synergy&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the one I am most proud of.  I wrote Meetup.com and they responded with the following..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;2 – Six month membership coupons to organize the group you always wanted on Meetup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $30 before and $35 at the door. Also, here are other ways we could use your help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;-- You can win even if you are not at the event.  With payment in advance, we will enter your name into the bags of the many raffles we will have..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Donate an item we could include in the raffle or silent auction, such as a gift card, tickets to a sporting event, time at a vacation home, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Ask friends or family if they would like to make a donation for the raffle or auction.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to hearing from you and I hope you can join us!! .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To buy your ticket's in advance you can follow this link to paypal.. &lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_flow&amp;amp;SESSION=k7r5CRwObFLEGMQHK0Hel0hqNLA9nKQtoRnIxkWrUizTQUl40I6sb1ijL4C&amp;amp;dispatch=5885d80a13c0db1f38432c9462fe7313791b4c12e10393700fb86c39eca5ec92"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boston All Stars PayPal&lt;/a&gt; site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or you can mail your check to us at the following address.&lt;br /&gt;Boston All Stars&lt;br /&gt;891 Center Street&lt;br /&gt;Jamaica Plain, MA  02130&lt;br /&gt;617 524-8111 for more info..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will give more details to meeting up at the event soon..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226183832000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225164985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston All Stars Perform!  On the Streets Where We Live: Cocktails &amp; Fundraiser</name><id>9045207</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226010600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/9045207/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/6/global_6072710.jpeg</photo_url></item>