<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im still not really sure what the weather will be like, reports indicate that the afternoon may have rain ?, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what i see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/full_loop.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://radar.weather....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;we can modify the trip as we need. I will have my weather rad on while we are out and it will let us know if thunder or severe marine weather will occur nearby.&lt;br /&gt;We have numerous &amp;quot;get out&amp;quot; points  if necessary, one being rocky neck beach if necessary...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use this link for a prediction:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHVN&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF IT RAINS LATER ? 7 FALLS MAY NOT BE THAT GOOD BUT LETS DISCUSS THAT AND ALTERNATE STOPS FOR DINNER OR OTHER FOR LATER. I will have the grille loaded anyway, some food,  and some bugg juice in the trunk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather and sea conditions will be watched the few days prior and all the way up to the day.&lt;br /&gt;-------&lt;br /&gt;apx:&lt;br /&gt;Tide: LOW @ 8:32 am-- High 2:45 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our snack/lunch area will be the Beach area after we have ventured up the Pattaganset river and a few islands. The day will be hot and swimming should be good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Trip:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After leaving 4 mile river take a left and head towards the LARGE island, take a left at the island then go North right behind the island up the river, after the river exploration its play around the remaining islands till its snack and beach time.&lt;br /&gt;After we can explore a few more areas then its head back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN, WIND OVER 10 MPH AND SEAS 1-2(Absolute Max) FEET IS MY SET MAX LIMIT  FOR any RECREATIONAL  YAKS on any  trip, however there is always an alternate plan within an event if necessary so if its listed its safe enough but stay close to someone or stay  in a group..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please have some safety gear, one of which should be a whistle, this is really something cheap and lets those know you are in trouble. MOST OF US HAVE PUMPS, PADDLE FLOATS, PADDLE LEASHES AND STUFF, so there is enough of us to help you if you don't.&lt;br /&gt;Floation bags for recreational yaks is a good thing to have also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;For an informative view of the area we plan to paddle use the link below.&lt;br /&gt;Coastal Kayak has this tour if you can't make my event, check out their offerings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctcoastalkayaking.com/files/pattagansetttourmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctcoastalkayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;The barbie q can be done later after the trip at our returning home spot of 7 Falls Park (exit 10 (aircraft rd) off of route 9, take right , go apx .5 mile, park on left...Bring some Pot Luck food and some scrap wood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;Getting to the PADDLING SPOT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;apx GPS address: #  20 Oakridge Drive, Old Lyme CT LOOK for boat launch signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;take I- 91 south to rte 9 south,&lt;br /&gt;Go to end and take left onto I 95 North, go 2 exits.&lt;br /&gt;Take exit # 71 = 4 Mile River Road (This is beach season so there is usually traffic, i may take the previous exit and go through town).&lt;br /&gt;At end of exit take left, this is 4 Mile River Road going SOUTH to the shore.&lt;br /&gt;Stay on 4 Mile River Road for apx 0.7 miles.&lt;br /&gt;You will meet rte 156 = Shore Road,&lt;br /&gt;Take the right onto Shore Road heading South.&lt;br /&gt;in apx 0.6 miles look left for OAKRIDGE DRIVE.&lt;br /&gt;TAKE THE LEFT ONTO OAKRIDGE DRIVE.&lt;br /&gt;go about half way around the circle, look for the brown boat launch sign and a road off to the right going to the river..go to end and unload then go back to parking lot..walk back to water.&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Paddle &amp;amp; Paddle Leash, Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doughnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any &amp;quot;Wide Butt&amp;quot; (greater than 17&amp;quot;~18&amp;quot; butts) yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;Don't laugh, its serious, some will not fit in a yak thats too small (ie the Greenlander Pro) of an opening and i will feel sad you cant go..etc..the other option is to maybe trade with someone..etc ..if you need to.&lt;br /&gt;This has worked in the past very well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a yes and by persons i have some familiarity with ?..(ie paddle skills matched to the boat, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybee's obviously can't reserve any yaks &amp;amp; if ya reserve one and don't show up, ya won't ever get a second chance to again unless its some real good excuse..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer. They get stolen too easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF USING MY YAKS YOU CANT LOOK LIKE A BONEHEADED BEGINNER AND STEP INTO THEM VIA THE FLOOR (yes the lightest kayaks have thin fiberglass or wood and your feet will go through them) OR DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. ( In an 18 foot long boat you will still be 10 or so feet out in the water at a greater depth.) Only Novices in short wide cheap plastic boats do that kind of thing.  :-)~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way and you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro and impress the others who don't know how. Then you may laugh at the ones that fall in on entry and exit who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: Always enter and exit while being parallel to shore.&lt;br /&gt;-----------------&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for most of you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes , paddling  style, and  fit adjusted...if you have your own please bring it..&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;I only have one &amp;quot;GOOD&amp;quot; life jacket for someone that can fit in it.&lt;br /&gt;Its a Medium Kokatat* Ladies MsFit  Tour: (this is also purchased by guys since it has a great fit and versatility) Its really too small for  me...but i like the way it works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/product/751058" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/pr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths (220-230) and types (strait, or ergonomic bent, small and normal shaft dia's.) of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;You choose your preference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some cheap metal ones for that.)-&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourite Yak Pad's optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer, Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with Novice and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-------&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;-----RESERVED FOR HELENA  ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro, Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (120-175 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt;Note: This kayak is limited to a Maximum Butt width of apx 12-13 inches because of the installed hip braces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stabilities, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----&amp;gt;  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---AL-R ?? --.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Advanced Composite (Fiberglass), Red and White, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the medium sized cockpit kayak of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (42 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----AVAILABLE----&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;-------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Fiberglass), Yellow, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest and has the smallest cockpit of the Eliza series @ 40 Lbs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;=&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR KATE  --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model (50 lbs) and larger cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt;(To be Hopefully replaced with another Gullimot Cedar Strip Night  Heron next year)&lt;br /&gt;So try this one before you buy if interested. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----AVAILABLE--&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; --.--&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guillemot Cedar Strip Night Heron.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Greenland Paddle available also if desired for the authentic Greenland look and feel but most use the Werner)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with beginner/intermediate and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (45 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;------&amp;gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR ELSA --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya all there,&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear my Bright Orange Hunting Hat near the put in spot and while paddling.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280184918000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279498342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Saturday Kayak 4 Mile Riv to Pattagansett Riv &amp; Beach Time. </name><id>14140813</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279985400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14140813/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/0/global_16409552.jpeg</photo_url></item>