<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>271 Washington Terrace</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.560261</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.685.2695</phone><name>Center for the Arts (CFA) Theater, Wesleyan University</name><city>Middletown</city><id>742115</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.655809</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This little fiilm was suggested by Devon.  It is playing at the CFA Hall on Wesleyan University campus. It is located Washington Street (Rte 66) in Middletown.  Check out the site www.wesleyan.edu/virtualtours and campus Maps.  THe CFA stands for Center for ther Arts.&lt;br /&gt;THe film starts at 8:00 pm. there is Indian food and a talk by the creator/director.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shakti presents a screening this Friday of the award-winning and critically acclaimed 2009 animated film “Sita Sings the Blues“, followed by a lecture and discussion led by its creator, cartoonist and free culture activist Nina Paley.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also billed as the “greatest break-up story ever told,” the film is a post-modern retelling of a fundamental story from the ancient Hindu epic the Ramayana, about the goddess Sita’s kidnapping and forced separation from her beloved husband (and Lord) Rama.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented with an innovative mix of eclectic visual styles and interspersed with musical interludes set to warbling 1920’s recordings by jazz singer Annette Hanshaw, a running commentary by irreverent Indian shadow puppets, and a Squigglevision account of the breakup of Paley’s own marriage, “Sita Sings the Blues” is a subversive, original, and often hilarious tragicomic story of “truth, justice and a woman’s cry for equal treatment.”&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I won't be there, but enjoy the film.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271086335000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270769716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sita Sings the Blues</name><id>13129650</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270856700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13129650/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>