<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-225-0888</phone><name>Tommy Doyle's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>835734</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi- Since there's a  talk with the filmmakers I thought it would be best  to meet at the restaurant &lt;b&gt;before&lt;/b&gt; the film at 5:30 so we don't have too late of an evening. I hope this time change doesn't effect people's plans. Tommy Doyle's is in the outdoor mall across the street from the  entrance to the Kendall Theatre parking garage. Their phone number is 617-225-0088 if you need more directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advance Tickets (highly suggested) are available for purchase on-line now:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" target="_blank"&gt;https://tickets.landm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Filmmakers Ilisa Barbash and Lucien Castaing-Taylor will be at the 7:10 screening of &lt;b&gt;Sweetgrass&lt;/b&gt;  considered to be the first essential movie of this young year. (NY Times). &lt;b&gt;Sweetgrass&lt;/b&gt; gets a 96% Rotten Tomatoe Rating to boot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An unsentimental elegy to the American West, &lt;b&gt;Sweetgrass&lt;/b&gt; follows the last sheepherders to trail their flocks up into Montana’s Beartooth Mountains for summer pasture. &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Without commentary&lt;/span&gt;, this astonishingly beautiful film reveals a world in which nature and culture, animals and humans, climate and landscape, and vulnerability and violence are all intimately meshed. &amp;quot;In the summer of 2003, a group of shepherds took a herd of sheep one final time through the Beartooth Mountains of Montana, in the extreme northwest of the United States. It was a journey of almost 300 kilometers through expansive green valleys, by fields of snow, and across hazardous, narrow ridges—a journey brimming with challenges. The aging shepherds do their very best to keep the hundreds of sheep together; the panoramic high mountains are teeming with hungry wolves and grizzly bears.&amp;quot;  Kendall Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to the trailer: &lt;a href="http://sweetgrassthemovie.com/trailer/" target="_blank"&gt;http://sweetgrassthem...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breathtaking, abstract Western. Awe-inspiring and often hilarious. Big Sky country has never looked more spectacular… and, after &lt;b&gt;Sweetgrass&lt;/b&gt;, it will never look the same. FILMLINC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breathtaking… close to heaven… Fascinating. Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie truly belongs to the sheep, which turn out to be fascinating, almost hypnotic subjects for the camera, whether they’re comically bleating at one another like rush-hour subway riders or swarming across the range like a single organism. The filmmakers make brilliant use of extreme long shots throughout, inserting breathtaking panoramas into the mix that convey the surrounding grandeur even as the images also suggest that however much man tries to dominate nature, nature prevails. NY Times  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2010/01/06/movies/06sweet.html?partner=Rotten%20Tomatoes&amp;amp;ei=5083" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replace this text with the first item of your list&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replace this text with the next item&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can add more items by adding lines that start with a &lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will have a red meetup sign at our  table  at Tommy Doyle's</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269480001000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sweetgrass- Filmmakers In Person</name><id>12985309</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270330200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12985309/</event_url></item>