<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For those of you not going to Montreal...&lt;br /&gt;This walk will be through a bit of the Arnold Arboretum, then over to and around Jamaica Pond.  We will then have lunch at Dogwood Cafe. Meet at 10:15 inside the Forest Hills subway station, near the donut shop. Parking in the T lot is about $3.50, but there is on street parking nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It took civic visionary Frederick Law Olmsted, Sr. (1822-1903) almost twenty years (1878-1896) to create the six parks now known as the Emerald Necklace. The Back Bay Fens, Riverway, Olmsted Park, Jamaica Park, Arnold Arboretum and Franklin Park stretch five miles from the Charles River to Dorchester and make up over 1,000 acres of parkland. &lt;br /&gt;The Necklace comprises half of the City of Boston?s park acreage, parkland in the Town of Brookline, and parkways and park edges under the jurisdiction of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. More than 300,000 people live within its watershed area. &lt;br /&gt;The Emerald Necklace is the only remaining intact linear park designed by Frederick Law Olmsted, Sr., America?s first landscape architect. As such, it is listed on the National Register of Historic Places. Green and open spaces, rivers and ponds, and a wealth and diversity of trees, shrubs, flowers, wildlife habitat, riparian life, bridges and other structures make up this urban jewel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.emeraldnecklace.org/index.cgi?page=necklace" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.emeraldnec...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dogwoodcafe.com/lunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dogwoodcaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogwood Cafe&lt;br /&gt;3712 Washington St. (across from forest Hills T)&lt;br /&gt;Jamaica Plain, MA&lt;br /&gt;02130&lt;br /&gt;617-522-7997&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180362317000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178739061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jamaica Pond walk</name><id>5760553</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180188900000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5760553/</event_url></item>