<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Next Best Weekend of Your Life!! **For this weekend we are only accepting RSVP's for a two night stay** Join us for a fun filled weekend of skiing, snowboarding, racing and after ski events. This is always a popular weekend in the Mt Washington Valley so sign up quick before we sell out!! We welcome new and returning guests to the Brettl-Hupfers. It is a great chance to meet and socialize with our members and guests, visit our ski club lodge, and enjoy everythng the Mt Washington Valley has to offer. Highlights: Saturday ski tickets at Attitash for just $39 (as a guest of the house) - just 2 miles away!! Optional low cost after ski events on Saturday afternoon and evening Optional catered dinner at the Brettl-Hupfers Ski Lodge A guided full moon snowshoe on Saturday night along the river behind our house. First and Second time guests get $10 guest lodge fees per night (1/2 price) For the hardcore winter lovers we are located close to Wildcat, Bretton Woods, Cranmore, and Black Mountain. Cannon, Loon and Waterville Valley can all easily be skiied on the drive between greater Boston and our house as well. There is great snowshoeing, cross country skiing, outdoor ice skating and don't forget about the outlet shopping in North Conway!! There is plenty to do to fill a Friday, Saturday and Sunday. Once you RSVP full directions and information will be given. All guests must be 21+&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be up at the house on Friday Night!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Buckley</member_name><member_id>3881633</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nung</member_name><member_id>8898177</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Ryan</member_name><member_id>9462624</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332881734000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326921796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Next Best Weekend of Your Life</name><id>48658922</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328918400000</time><rsvp_limit>38</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/48658922/</event_url></item>