<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Edge of Heaven&lt;/b&gt; Turkey/Germany 2007  122 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Actual screening time is  indeed 7:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of 4 German Film Awards, including Best Picture, Director, Editor and Screenplay. This quietly compelling drama of fractured families, dislocated cultures and bridged gulfs is masterfully written and directed by Turkish-German Fatih Akin (Head-On, Crossing the Bridge). Expatriate widower Ali (Tuncel Kurtiz), seeking a little home comfort, invites prostitute Yeten (Nursel Köse) to live with him, a move his son Nejat (Baki Davrak), a professor of German literature, disparages. When tragedy ensues, Nejat travels to Turkey seeking Yeten's daughter while she, unknowing, searches for her mother in Germany. Kendall description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Edge of Heaven&lt;/b&gt; is a film to be seen, savored and thoughtfully appreciated. NY Observer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Edge of Heaven&lt;/b&gt; is about something more exasperating than crossed paths; it is about paths that almost cross but don?t, and the tragedy of the near-miss. New Yorker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a beautiful, unexpectedly enrapturing story about a world in transition and both the closeness and unbridgeable divide between generations and cultures.  L.A. Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to the NY Times review: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2008/05/21/movies/21heav.html?ref=movies" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there- we'll be going to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion directly after the film&lt;br /&gt;Cheers- Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216077398000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213828803000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Germany's The Edge of Heaven</name><id>8168654</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215903600000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8168654/</event_url></item>