<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.340054</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common Gazebo</name><city>Boston</city><id>2417401</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Incubators,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Sunday, May 6th is World Laughter Day!! What a better way to come out and celebrate then by doing some laughter yoga and other fun improv games in the sunshiine on Boston Common. We'll meet at the gazebo off tremont st. near the tennis courts at 1pm. And if you are late no worries, you can join in anytime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those unsure of what laughter yoga entails, i assure you its not about sweaty hot hard to do poses. It's about just laughing for no reason at all. We'll discover ways of being kids again and just laughing for the sake of laughing. We'll surely put in some awesome improv games too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a link to a great youtube video with the famous comedian John Cleese and Laughter Yoga! &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yXEfjVnYkqM"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yXEfjVnYkqM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me know if you have any questions!! I hope to enjoy and laugh with many of you! And if you can't make it, please spread the laughter anyway you can that day. I leave you with a message from the founder of the laughter clubs worldwide:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Dear Friends of Laughter,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is World Laughter Day, customarily celebrated on the first Sunday of May every year. It gives me great pleasure to inform you that this year this day is being celebrated in more than 70 countries around the world. Our mission to bring Good health, Joy and World Peace is once again being reaffirmed by thousands of people gathered to promote the benefits of unconditional laughter. For centuries, everybody knew laughter is the best medicine, but there was no reliable delivery system. Laughter Yoga is a breakthrough exercise routine, which allows people to practice laughter without depending upon outside conditions and reasons of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughter Yoga Clubs movement which started in 1995 with just 5 people has grown into a global phenomenon and has become a community of social Laughter Clubs. In addition, Laughter Yoga today has permeated many other areas such as fitness centers, companies and corporations, schools, colleges and universities, hospitals, senior centers, prisons, police and even the army. It is helping several people to beat the modern stressors and generate an all round body-mind wellness. Unconditional laughter creates a positive mental attitude and brings out our true spiritual nature of unconditional love, kindness, appreciation, forgiveness, generosity and willingness to help and serve others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The celebration of World Laughter Day is a positive manifestation for world peace and is intended to build a global consciousness of brotherhood and friendship. Laughter is a universal language which has the potential to unite the entire humanity and establish a common link between various countries and cultures to create a new world order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We strongly recommend that the opening ceremony of Olympics should start with one minute of laughter for world peace by athletes and people in the stadium urging millions of people to join in as they watch the live telecast worldwide. This will help to bring close the entire human race for a cause that will eventually bring more laughter, happiness and joy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To further this cause of global happiness the biggest step forward is the recent United Nations resolution which has invited member states to discuss the pursuit of happiness and well-being in development with a view to guiding their public policies. Laughter Yoga is already playing an important role to achieve U N objectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this auspicious day, let us laugh together by raising our arms and sending out positive vibrations of love and peace to make the whole world an extended family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr Madan Kataria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Founder, Laughter Clubs Movement.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://worldlaughterday.org/images/stories/wld_2012/mensaje_del_d_%eda_mundial_de_la_risa_wld_message_sp.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow the sounds of laughter to the gazebo area!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336328428000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336227549000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Laughter Day!! Sunday on the Boston Common!!!</name><id>63533342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336323600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/63533342/</event_url></item>