<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What is the Boston Townhall meet up?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First of all come to the meetings to find out.  We get lots of new members and welcome them.  Each of the members has different ideas of what should be accomplished, but while we figure that out we certainly enjoy each other's company in conversation of a political/conservative leaning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston-area conservatives can &amp;quot;meet and greet&amp;quot; and discuss issues of the day.  Many of us find our workplace-, extended family-, or friend-network-conversations' views heavily tilted towards the left.  This meeting can serve as an antidote, as a friendly respite, as a place to pass on and gain conservative perspective and ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course there is no one single conservative perspective on issues.  We debate, we listen, we learn.  This is a good meeting for friendly discussion.  The people who come are bright, lucid, open, and forthright.  Some people are more politically active than others.  There's no specific political activity requirement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People not familiar with &amp;quot;townhall&amp;quot; conservativism can go to the web site: &lt;a href="http://www.townhall.com/" target="_blank"&gt; Townhall, conservative web site: Hugh Hewitt, Bill Bennett, Michael Medved, etc.&lt;/a&gt; for increased perspective.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to having new members come.  Discussion is interesting, please bring your views, your self.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Tuesday of each month, we will be at Bertucci's restaurant in Newton, Massachusetts.  It is actually technically on 275 Centre St, but this portion of Centre Street also is quickly renamed as Galen Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;it is easily accessible from the Mass. Pike exit 17, if you are going west from Boston, and make your way up the exit ramp Bertucci's restaurant is directly on the right half a block, with parking on your left at Pearl Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy Bock, (new) Organizer&lt;br /&gt;Boston Townhall Meetup&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Bock</member_name><member_id>1795100</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196985893000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Conservatives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>townhall-61</urlname><id>155655</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Conservatives' Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194397411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Conservatives' December Meetup</name><id>6691600</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196812800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/townhall-61/events/6691600/</event_url></item>