<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Up the Yangtze&lt;/b&gt; by Yung Chang (Canada, 2007, 94 min.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A look at the building of China's Three Gorges Dam and the displacement of 2 million people.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot;May you be cursed to live in interesting times&amp;quot; is not only a venerable Chinese proverb, it is also an apt description of what many parts of that country are going through today, a situation brought to evocative life in the finely made new documentary &lt;b&gt;Up the Yangtze&lt;/b&gt; LA Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Up the Yangtze&lt;/b&gt; is a masterful exercise in documentary filmmaking, seamlessly blending history, facts and figures, not one but two narrative threads, and almost unbearably intimate cinematography to capture China's past, present, and future in a perfect little microcosm.   Filmcritic.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Up the Yangzte&lt;/b&gt; is largely set aboard a ship making what are billed as farewell cruises up the river. Many of the tourists, we are told, come expecting to see the old China before it disappears. As the boat sails upriver, the landscape is spectacular. At the same time the yellowish haze over the water suggests China's already serious air pollution problem. There are brief glimpses of cities whose gaudy wall-to-wall signs match those of the Las Vegas Strip or Times Square. In these cities what remains of the old China is hidden by the glitter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie offers an Upstairs, Downstairs view of life aboard the vessel, which is crowded with well-to-do American and European tourists catered to by a Chinese staff that is minutely drilled on proper etiquette: Never compare Canada and the United States; never call anyone old, pale or fat (plump is O.K.); never talk about politics. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie observes the culture shock felt by two young employees. Yu Shui, the 16-year-old daughter of illiterate peasants who cant afford to send her to college, is a reluctant dishwasher. Like the other employees she is given a Western name, Cindy. Miserable, sullen and homesick, she has a difficult time adjusting. &lt;br /&gt;Chen Bo Yu, renamed Jerry, is a cocky, good-looking go-getter from a middle-class background. We are told he is an example of the little emperor phenomenon in which male products of the countrys one-child policy grow up spoiled and entitled.  As he engages an American teenager in small talk about girls and sports, he seems eager to shed his national identity and make money: the more the better. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All the while the water continues to rise.  NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just where is China taking us besides up the Yangtze River Mr. Yungs film does not even pretend to know, and that is its great strength as it plunges more deeply into the truly unknown.  New York Observer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then its off to a local eatery to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213653960000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Well, at metacritic.com, this documentary has the highest rating of any film screening in the U.S. since the Oscars.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211757612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Up the Yangtze at the MFA</name><id>8010222</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213480800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8010222/</event_url></item>