<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Stuart Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Statler Fountain/Park Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>1090301</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069275</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>($5 for BBF card holders)</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Visit one of Boston's hidden neighborhoods; a miniature, garden-filled area that has maintained its residential charm amidst the surrounding city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Bay_Village" target="_blank"&gt;tour of Bay Village&lt;/a&gt; begins in Park Plaza, overlooking the renaissance and classical revival buildings constructed on the site of the old Boston &amp;amp; Providence Railroad and also features the First Corps of Cadets Armory and the Pope Manufacturing Building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Originally called the Bay Street District, Bay Village was created by the filling of the mud flats leading into the Back Bay during the 1820s and settled by artisans and craftsman, many of whom worked on the homes of Beacon Hill and the South End. The scaled-down brick Federal and Greek Revival row houses contribute to the sense of a small community within a larger urban environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the early 20th century, Bay Village was the center of the New England film industry and was known as “Hollywood East” during a time when many actors and musicians of the Theatre District resided there. The Cocoanut Grove, a local nightclub and former speakeasy, burned in a fire killing 492 people becoming the second worst single-building fire in U.S. history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore the history and architecture of Bay Village, a little-known small harmonious neighborhood tucked alongside Boston's growing skyline. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tour costs $15 (or $5 for card-carrying &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;members of Boston By Foot&lt;/a&gt;). Boston By Foot membership is available for reasonable costs and entitles you to all of the tours on their regular schedule for free. Visit www.bostonbyfoot.org for more details on membership and the tours.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for folks with Boston By Foot badges, bags, hats, etc.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257128303000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255233197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discover Bay Village</name><id>11599099</id><headcount>51</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256493600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/11599099/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/0/global_4708432.jpeg</photo_url></item>