<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Since several people couldn't make it, or couldn't find the place, last month, I thought we'd try Mac Donald Park again! Rufus and I always enjoy this park so much that we go there every weekend anyway, so I'm just inviting the rest of you to join us. This time, there won't be any confusion about the time (11:00). Ron, Rufus &amp;amp; I will definitely be in the parking lot to welcome you. Please realize that it can be tricky to keep Rufus in one place for very long -- last time, he and I were playing ball on the grass at the back of the parking lot and I saw one of you drive in and out of the parking lot before I could get your attention! &lt;br /&gt;

The only entrance to MacDonald Park is on Rt 16. If you are driving East on 16, just make a Right turn. But I think most of you will either be driving West along 16, or else coming along Rt 28. In either case you'll be in the Westbound lane of Rt 16. Then, you will have to drive past the park and make the first legal Up-turn to reverse direction. (It isn't very far, and the U-turn is clearly marked.) Driving back, you will see the park on your right. The entrance is at the very east-most end of the park. If you come to the State Police barracks you've gone a tiny bit too far. If that happens, pull into the State Police lot and ask them the best way to get into the park. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you come to Wellington Circle, you've gone a little further too far and you'll have to go around the circle again to pick up Rt 16 West. (If you were to take Rt 16 East, it would take to Revere.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rufus and I will go into the park at around 11:15 with whoever has come. If anyone who has RSVP'd has not arrived yet, Ron will wait for latecomers in the parking lot. He will have his cell phone (617-803-4530) if anyone needs help. &lt;br /&gt;

We look forward to seeing you!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karla Rab</member_name><member_id>10717717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335118934000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334024321000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk our Cavaliers along the Mystic River! </name><id>59924042</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334415600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/59924042/</event_url></item>