<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>1 Bennett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-5000</phone><name>Charles Hotel </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>744847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;***** You may call the Charles Hotel at (617) 661-5000 to confirm if the jazz is cancelled&lt;br /&gt;Read the last paragraph on this page to find out Plan B *****&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Regattabar at the Charles Hotel and the Berklee College of Music have come together this summer to create a special Monday night series that is free and open to the public. Berklee students and teachers will perform from 5 until 7 in the Upper Courtyard area at the Charles Hotel. During the concerts, Henrietta’s Table will sell $10 burgers (beef or salmon) and $5 beer and wine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regattabarjazz.com/courtyard_series/" target="_blank"&gt;Courtyard Summer Series Schedule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nadia Washington Quartet is tonight's artist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARTIST BIO: &lt;br /&gt;Often compared to the likes of Ella Fitzgerald and Sarah Vaughan, Nadia Washington draws audiences in with her velvety voice. A Dallas native, Washington attends Berklee as a recipient of the prestigious Bill Cosby Presidential Scholarship. She is a former member of the Ralph Peterson Ensemble as well as the Gibson/Baldwin Jazz Ensemble, which performs at Grammy events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Washington has worked with Herb Alpert, Destiny's Child, and Terence Blanchard, and has recorded jingles and commercials for Frito Lay and McDonalds. Down Beat magazine twice chose her as Best Jazz Vocalist, Performing Arts High School Division. She attended the Brubeck Institute Summer Jazz Colony in 2005 and 2006. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With plans that include a live recording and touring overseas, Washington is well on her way to becoming a musical pioneer of today's generation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Less than five (5) minute walk from Harvard subway station on the Red Line and the last stop of the #1 and #66 buses on Mass Ave in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the jazz is cancelled the drinking, meeting and chatting will be held in Noir, the Charles Hotel's bar located in the lobby. You'll find me playing the card game solitaire.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the doorman at the hotel entrance to direct you to the Courtyard...find me seated nearest the stage area, playing solitaire.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281446556000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280829261000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drinks With Music at Charles Hotel Monday August 9th</name><id>14301994</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281387600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/14301994/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/7/global_16790871.jpeg</photo_url></item>