<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Wakefield St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.310800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-332-0757</phone><name>Rochester Community Center</name><city>Rochester</city><id>696394</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.977417</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please Read This!!! We need to Rally on short notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please pass this on to everyone you know (not just Rochester Patriots)... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Dear Rochester Friends (and all others across the state), &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you were at the Rochester City Council Meetings regarding the Granite State Future program, then you know that there were over 33 people that spoke out against the program (all public citizens) -- and only two that spoke in favor of it. Both were government representatives, and both had conflicts of interest. One was Greg Carson, who is the NH HUD Director, and the other is Kenn Ortmann, the Rochester Director of Planning and Development. His position obligates him to be a public servant to do the people's business on their behalf. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

However, he is NOT listening to your voices, nor the City Council's. &lt;span style="color : #990000"&gt;Although the Granite State Future program was VOTED DOWN in Rochester a few weeks ago, Mr. Ortmann is still pursuing his Granite State Future agenda &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;AS A REPRESENTATIVE OF ROCHESTER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. He is now using his appointed position on the Strafford County Regional Planning Commission and the NH Association of Regional Planning Commissions (NHARPC) to bypass the City Council, and push this program's ideologies through NH legislation. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Mr. Ortmann is abusing these positions to push for legislation next year in our Statehouse that will further the objectives that Rochester rejected. This topic is on the agenda for tomorrow's NHARPC meeting, &lt;strong&gt;which w&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ill take place tomorrow (Thurs), September 27th at 7:00 PM at the Rochester Community Center, 150 Wakefield Street, Suite 12, Conference Rm. 1A.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Mr. Ortmann could be a poster boy for what is wrong with our government -- and why we must fix it. I contend that it is our duties as citizens to make our voices heard, and demand for a government by the people and for the people. Tomorrow's meeting is one of those times where your voices will have an impact. Please don't let this moment pass without acting. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Stand up to this man and let others know that he does not speak for you. Equally important, you will learn the names of the other players that are working diligently to subvert our rights -- and they will learn that we are watching them too and we will not stand by quietly by while they continue to usurp our Constitutional Rights. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Each of our voices alone will never be heard, but together we can move mountains. The Rochester City Council's vote on September 4th proves it. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

"When the people fear government, there is tyranny. When the government fears the people, there is liberty." - Thomas Jefferson &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

It's time to choose. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

With sincere respect, &lt;br /&gt;

Ken &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

More info on Ortmann Conflicts of interest: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Community Planning Grant Program provides matching grants for cities and towns to implement local regulations that foster sustainable community principles. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The CPG program is administered by the New Hampshire Housing Finance Authority under a cooperative agreement with HUD. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The NHFFA was awarded $1M for the Community Challenge Grants at the same time the $3.5M was awarded to the SCI program in NH (GSF). The NHHFA is a partner in the Sustainable Communities Initiative. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Mr Ortmann has a conflict of interest, because he is the Vice Chair of the NHHFA. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

With all of the above, Mr. Ortmann should recuse himself from taking a position on the Granite State Future / Sustainable Communities Initiative, and it's associated programs -- because he is on the commission as a Representative of Rochester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Suite 12, Conference Room 1A</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry DeLemus</member_name><member_id>9270878</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348926955000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rochester-912-project</urlname><id>1452537</id><group_lat>43.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>Rochester 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348696199000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ken Ortmann is Pushing Agenda 21/Granite State Futures again. Please ATTEND!</name><id>84242532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348786800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rochester-912-project/events/84242532/</event_url></item>