<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I was talking to some people last night at Oyster Night, and came to the conclusion that many people want to continue surfing through the cold weather but don't because they can't/don't want to spent a lot of money on a winter wetsuit. I mean, come on, a winter suit is expensive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with so many people on the fence about making that large purchase of winter gear, I thought that maybe we could use some group buying power and get a better deal than one person buying a wetsuit on their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So - If you would like to purchase a winter suit, RSVP "YES" to this event. I am going to set Feb 25th as the date (give people a month to save up!), but if you anticipate joining in, please RSVP yes as soon as you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll give it a week (so Feb 1) - and then i will call a couple shops and let them know how many people want to buy a suit, and see if they will give us a bulk deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;of course everyone won't fit the exact same suit/brand, so I will find out what our options are, and let people know of the choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, if you think you know what size/brand you want, please send me a private message and i will let the shop know so they can stock accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* if you only are in need of mitts/boots please put that in your RSVP so i can get an accurate count of suits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise</member_name><member_id>11388242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330187242000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Surfers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>surfing-69</urlname><id>737305</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Surfing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327518695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's getting cold out there! Winter wetsuit group purchase</name><id>49595052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330182000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/surfing-69/events/49595052/</event_url></item>