<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Friend Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364281</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The North Star</name><city>Boston</city><id>6465492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060905</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/8/0/event_189762112.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CROSSLISTED With Boston Happy Hour, Boston San Francisco Crew (BSFC) and Boston Singles!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a San Francisco 49ers RALLY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm already hosting the MeetUp for the Patriots AFC game at 6:30pm, and I will be there at about 2:00pm for the 49ers game also! The manager has reserved us space for this game also. North Star will be LOUD and CROWDED!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at The North Star for a 2013 NFL NFC Championship Playoff Viewing Party to watch the San Francisco 49ers take on the Atlanta Falcons on Sunday, January 20.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early at 2:00pm to get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing. Game Time is 3:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no event fee for our reserved section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for the whole game or leave when ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives have been organizing weekly Patriots viewing parties over the last 2 years with guests from several other invited groups attending. We had a blast with up to 80 people attending at various locations in Boston, Woburn and Wakefield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Star will be our Home for watching the 2013 New England Patriots and all other 2013 NFL Playoff Games through the Super Bowl! For more information on the venue go to &lt;a href="http://www.northstarboston.com"&gt;www.northstarboston.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff will welcome you to The North Star with Cornhole to add to the Tailgate feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Star is super conveniently located next to the TD Garden and on the Green and Orange Lines and Commuter Rail at North Station. The Red and Blue Lines are within a 10 minute walk and street parking is also available if you arrive early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food and drinks. PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER AND TIP YOUR SERVER. Credit Cards will be collected by the North Star.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Isabel and the Red Sox Natives Team&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jeff has reserved a large section for us and invited groups. Ask the hostess to direct you to The Red Sox Natives section.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358719665000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358172913000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>49ERS NFC Championship Viewing Party at The North Star- vs Atlanta Falcons</name><id>99514882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358708400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/99514882/</event_url></item>