<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Mount Carmel Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06518</zip><lat>41.420751</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 789-7498</phone><name>Sleeping Giant State Park</name><city>Hamden</city><id>683125</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.898515</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi folks! It's the perfect time to get out and hike at Sleeping Giant, where we can indulge in the fresh spring air, burn some calories on the trail, and comfortably walk and talk with a group of friends.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: This Meetup will take place at Sleeping Giant, which is a Connecticut State Park located in Hamden.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLAN: Sleeping Giant is a great park for any level of hiking.  We'd like to walk the tower trail, which is relatively short, has a mild incline, and requires very little maneuvering over rocky places.  We will have a break at the tower for snacks and chit chat, and we can split up into two groups after our break -- some members walking back down the tower road, and other members heading down the blue trail, if they desire a greater challenge. The two groups can converge at the parking lot after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN AND WHERE: Meet at the entrance, which is located on Mt. Carmel Avenue, between 8:45 and 9, and we'll try to get rolling onto the trail by five after 9. This particular hike shouldn't take more than 2 hours, with the break, and will be energizing without exhausting us; if we have enough members who wish to take the more difficult trail back, it may take up to 3 hours total for them, so be prepared with water, a snack and energy if that is what you wish to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING: One or two bottles of &lt;b&gt;water&lt;/b&gt;!, and a snack if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEAR: Hiking or other sturdy shoes with treads;  &lt;b&gt;layers&lt;/b&gt; of clothing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: We ask for a donation of one dollar, towards the monthly fee that is charged by the Meetup Website. Please bring any contributions with you on the day of the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Please see link below. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PARKING NOTE: The DEP sometimes charges a fee to park in the lot.  Please take advantage of the street parking on Mt. Carmel Avenue, adjacent to park, ACROSS FROM (not inside) Quinnipiac University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link to park website (with map):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/Dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2716&amp;amp;Q=325264" target="_blank"&gt;Sleeping Giant State Park Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail maps are usually available at the entrance, if you are interested.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Organizer (Sarah) will be wearing red</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah </member_name><member_id>7903956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243793146000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hiking-575</urlname><id>1282762</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Walks in the Woods</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240680939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Haven Early-bird Hiking ALL- INCLUSIVE May Meetup</name><id>10265358</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243083600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hiking-575/events/10265358/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/0/global_7947184.jpeg</photo_url></item>