<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;SAVE the DATE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 representatives from GOOGLE will provide us with an educational session to kick off our first&lt;br /&gt;RE/Group meeting.  We'll be at the &lt;b&gt;Cambridge Innovation Center&lt;/b&gt; in Kendall Square for the Learning part and then we'll walk over to &lt;b&gt;ZA Restaurant&lt;/b&gt; next door (350 Third Street) for networking, drinks &amp;amp; food. &lt;br /&gt;************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small Business/Internet Marketing Seminar featuring Google Experts!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Growing your local business with Google AdWords and Analytics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join other local business owners and internet entrepreneurs to&lt;br /&gt;learn to better use simple, yet effective online tools to accelerate your&lt;br /&gt;business and generate a greater return for less. Google Team Members and&lt;br /&gt;Product Specialists who work with small and medium sized businesses like&lt;br /&gt;yours will be present to share their knowledge and expertise on Google&lt;br /&gt;AdWords and Analytics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll introduce you to ways you can drive online traffic to your website,&lt;br /&gt;evaluate the impact of your marketing initiatives, and make informed&lt;br /&gt;decisions to help you grow your business.  We'll focus on basic and&lt;br /&gt;intermediate features of these products so all experience levels are&lt;br /&gt;welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Details:&lt;br /&gt;Date: JUNE 30, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:00-8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Location: Cambridge Innovation Center, ONE Broadway - Kendall Square;  followed by networking, food  and drinks at ZA Restarant next door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics: Basic and intermediate features of Google AdWords and Analytics to&lt;br /&gt;             improve online sales and leads&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More on Google Analytics&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;Google Analytics is the free enterprise-class web analytics solution that gives you rich insights into your website traffic and marketing effectiveness. Powerful, flexible and easy-to-use features now let you see and analyze your traffic data in an entirely new way. With Google Analytics, you're more prepared to write better-targeted ads, strengthenyour marketing initiatives and create higher converting websites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More on Google AdWords&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;With Google AdWords, you can create and run ads for your business, quickly and simply. Run your ads on Google and our advertising network -- no matter what your budget, you'll only pay when people click your ads. AdWords ads are displayed along with search results when someone searches&lt;br /&gt;Google using one of your keywords. That way, you'll be advertising to an audience that's already interested in your business. You can also choose to display your ads on content sites in the growing Google Network. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check in at the Lobby - Your name must be on the guest list at the door so be sure to register!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lew</member_name><member_id>10673992</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278265027000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275659000000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Google Analytics comes to BIMM - 1st RE/Group meetup!</name><id>13695853</id><headcount>44</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277935200000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/13695853/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/1/global_10196385.jpeg</photo_url></item>