<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a members-only meeting which means you must have paid the full dues of $40.00 and signed the statement of ethics prior to the meeting to be able to attend. No visitors are allowed at this meeting because of confidentiality rules. Being a member of the meetup is not the same as being a member of the Innovators Resource Network. Free books and product samples this meeting only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;===========&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As IRN gets ready to begin its 12th year in the early fall, volunteers are needed to take over the tasks that keep the group running. An information sheet will be available about what is involved and we’ll take a few minutes to answer any questions people may have. The tasks to run the group are fairly simple and it’s possible that many of them can be done by taking full advantage of all that is offered by Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this meeting we will be giving away several books about inventing, marketing, patenting, etc. that we have received as review copies. We also have some product samples for products that were submitted for review, some of which have made it to market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members-only meeting: Please contact Karen at 413-534-3580 or khss10@juno.com if you if you would like to take advantage of the opportunity to seek advice or comments on some aspect of the development of your product/product idea in a non-public forum.. She will fill you in on the procedures used during these meetings.  You may also come with questions you would like to ask if there is free time at the meeting. Next opportunity to present after this meeting is September 1st.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Members who have presented before at a members-only meeting or who have a product that they have moved forward are invited to provide an update. No need to do anything fancy, but it would be interesting to find out what has happened to some ideas we have seen over the years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enterprise Center Training Room - Lower Level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Cormier</member_name><member_id>6323188</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283606586000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282270665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Members-Only Meeting</name><id>14480934</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283381100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/14480934/</event_url></item>