<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey Incubators!!  Sorry for the delay and an alteration...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Thursday I'm inviting you all to come out to a one night only event at ImprovBoston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's Parallelogramophonograph!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One night only from Austin, Texas Parallelogramophonograph's 2009 East Coast Whistle Stop Tour comes to ImprovBoston.  The show that the Austin Chronicle called, &amp;quot;Inspired Improvisation&amp;quot; has been featured at the Chicago Improv Festival, The Hawaii Improgvaganza, the Providence Improv Fest and Out of Bounds.  Their original improvised plays have run the gauntlet of styles - from historic and highly stylized period dramas.  Don't miss your chance to see these gifted award-winning story tellers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I heard their shows a blast so I figure we should drop by and check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you missing out on our usual incubation, I do promise we'll get the flow going again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see some of you there.  I'm fresh off lots of workshops and have tons of fun exercises I can't wait ti pass along!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Might be a good idea to call ahead for reservations for this show too.  It's $10 or $7 for students.  617-576-1253&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason J.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247790142000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246989909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What's a Parallelogramophonograph???  Find out on Thursday!</name><id>10822796</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247184000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/10822796/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>