<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Enjoy silent comedy genius Buster Keaton's hilarious antics in the story of a city-educated college grad returning to small town life to help run his father's Mississippi river boat. Fasten your seat belts for an unforgettable ride!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter Blanchette, composer, producer, and guitar innovator dynamically scores this combination of Jazz Age surrealism and knee-slapping Vaudeville shtick with music that blends avant-garde classical, honky-tonk, and Americana. Using computer assist with live performance of electric guitar, banjo, electric dulcimer, mandolin, piano, voice, and his trademark archguitar, he creates a high tech tour-de-force for the entire family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These events almost always sell out well in advance.  Please do yourself a favor and purchase your ticket now, so that you won't be steam boated by the Coolidge:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=615521cb-c61a-41c9-abd2-f75643670013&amp;amp;evtinfo=6400~3c2614bd-0781-48b8-a8a2-e21eaa37e962&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;Steamboat Bill, Jr. Tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Steamboat Bill, Jr. contains some of Keaton's best and most spectacular sight gags. Keaton plays Willie Canfield, the namby-pamby son of rough-and-tumble steamboat captain Steamboat Bill Canfield (Ernest Torrence). When he's not trying to make a man out of his boy, the captain is carrying on a feud with Tom Carter (Tom McGuire), the wealthy owner of a fancy new ferryboat. Carter has a pretty daughter, Mary King (Marion Byron), with whom Willie falls in love. The two younger folks try to patch up the feud, but this seems impossible once the captain is jailed for punching out Carter. Willie tries ineptly to bust his dad out of jail, only to wind up in the hospital while trying to escape the law. As Willie lies unconscious in bed, a huge cyclone hits town, knocking down tall buildings like kindling. Upon awakening, he does his best to remain standing as the winds buffet him about. He takes refuge in a tree, which is promptly uprooted and blown toward the waterfront. Here is where proves his manhood -- and ends the feud between Steamboat Bill and Carter -- by rescuing practically everyone in the cast from a watery grave. Steamboat Bill, Jr. would be memorable if only for one eye-popping (and dangerously real) sight gag: as the cyclone rages, the facade of a three-story building collapses upon Keaton -- who is saved only because the upstairs window has been left open! - Willie p Hal Erickson, All Movie Guide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;100% Rating from Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will gather before the film across the street at Panera Bread starting at 6:00  to have a bite to eat, catch up, and share our history with Buster Keaton's films.  Look for a table with a red MEETUP sign propped unsteadily for all to silently see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be sitting silently at Panera Bread as early as 6:00 pm with a Red Meetup Sign which will provide the inspiration of all manner of sight gags</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284334047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Sounds of Silents: STEAMBOAT BILL, JR.</name><id>14746251</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285628400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14746251/</event_url></item>