<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>124 Queen City Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.973719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 622-2000 </phone><name>Pho Golden Bowl</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1291703</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464241</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Note:  This event may require a reservation and it may or may not require a deposit by the organizer so all cancellations within 48 hours of the event requires a reason.  Please do not sign up unless you are sure that you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The membership has voted! The June Restaurant of the month is the Pho Golden Bowl.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golden Bowl’s food is fresh and reasonably priced. Two sisters run it, and EVERYTHING is homemade. They make their beef, chicken, (seafood and veg broths too) completely from scratch the traditional way – simmer marrow bones and herbs, scorched onion, etc. They have the usual choices of beef cuts, nice amount of onion, cilantro and white pepper sprinkled on top. She is picky about serving it completely hot too, so when you add bean sprouts it doesn’t cool the broth down too much. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommended: bun (cold rice vermicelli noodle salad bowl); pho (hot beef noodle soup); “chicken pho” (shreds of boneless white meat, some greens and cilantro and the crispy fried shallots as a garnish on top); seafood and veg noodle soups of various types; squid; traditional fish cakes; egg; “Vietnamese beef stew” noodles soup; spicy beef noodle soups (one hue (Vietnamese regional version) type and one satay type); sweet fish sauce; peking ravioli&amp;quot; (the pork filling is juicy and tender, and the wrapper is clearly homemade dough that is thicker than factory made dumpling wrappers, and nice texture); sugar cane shrimp paste appetizer; “fresh” rolls/summer rolls (soft rice paper wrap rolls).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bun (pronounced more like “boon” than “bun”) has vegetables – mint, slivered carrot and daikon and cuke, bean sprouts, shredded lettuce. Plus the grilled pork, or grilled pork and grilled sugarcane shrimp paste patties, or fried spring rolls on top. A nice dusting of ground up peanut as garnish. The rice vermicelli are perfectly prepared, never too soggy or undercooked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As specials, they often have roasted duck with rice or in noodle soup, as well as curry chicken noodle soup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s exit 4 off route 293 and you drive on Queen City Ave, toward Elm Street, but it’s on the right before Elm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Samantha Diep is the sister who runs the floor, and she is great to ask questions of and will explain to you. She speaks four languages – Vietnamese, various Chinese dialects. They do have a few Chinese regional dishes on menu like Taiwanese stir-fry cabbage, pork chop over rice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chow.com/restaurants/13303/golden-bowl" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chow.com/r...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reviews:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cuisine is Vietnamese, if that's what you're asking. I've been there a few times and always left feeling satisfied without breaking the bank. It's usually on my list of places to hit whenever I go to Manchester on business, but then again I love Vietnamese food! Check it out, I don't think you'll be disappointed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://chowhound.chow.com/topics/633709" target="_blank"&gt;http://chowhound.chow...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awesome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I go here at least once a week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay away from the Chinese menu. It's all covered in the same, nondescript brown sauce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The owner is very nice and accommodating and was happy to discuss the ingredients of many of the dishes to determine which were gluten free. No guarantees for your version of GF, but the pork is questionable and the chicken in the rice dishes is fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The service is good as long as they aren't busy. They are understaffed for busy lunch periods and you will inevitably wait for long periods without water refills and the check if they have more than a couple of full tables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I recommend any of the dishes with the marinated pork. The rice with pork(#41), vermicelli with pork(#17), and steamed vermicelli patties with pork(#23) are all incredibly, consistently good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have tried a number of the Pho noodle soups, all of which have been good. I regularly get the Special Beef Noodle Soup(#24). It has a lot of different pieces of the cow, so don't get it if unusual foods bother you. I just had Sate Pho, Extra Spicy Beef Sate Noodle(#37). On a spiciness scale of 1-10, I would say it was a 4. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On one visit, they had beef basil rolls as an appetizer. They were great, but I haven't seen them since. Bring it back!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/pho-golden-bowl-manchester" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newhampshire.com/dining/menus/golden-bowl.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newhampshi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276999734000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275871742000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Restaurant of the Month</name><id>jdcjnynjbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276988400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/13719130/</event_url></item>