<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our next meetup is on March 17th and we will be learning the simple, but effective, technique of producing HDR (HIGH DYNAMIC RANGE IMAGING). We will be featuring a $79  program called Hydra that works as a stand alone program and also is a plug in for Aperture and Lightroom. If time permits we will also demonstrate Portrait Professional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be gifts given away as door prizes, Hydra &lt;b&gt;WILL&lt;/b&gt; be one of those door prizes, compliments of Creaceed. Our special thanks to Topaz Labs for providing  the software program &amp;quot;Detail&amp;quot;as a door prize for our past meeting, Anita was the lucky winner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can take three pictures on a tripod for the meetup, we can use them for the program. Take one picture with correct exposure, take a second one under exposed and a third one over exposed. The Hydra program can merge three photos for HDR results whether taken with, or without a tripod, but the resullts are more quickly arrived at if a tripod is used.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hydra is about mixing a number of under- and overexposed shots to get a natural sight of a scene. It provides human eye-like perception to your photographs by allowing you to create high dynamic range (HDR) images from a series of regular photographs, either from DSLRs or traditional point-and-shoot cameras.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on the 17th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Charge, but donations will be accepted, or if you would like to bring a dish, or refreshment that also would be appreciated. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Exit 495, exit 31 towards Littleton Common, go left at 1st light with Mobile Station, go about 1/4 mile to our street, across from Yantze River Restaurant make a right on Partridge Lane and go to end of cul de sac. 3 Partridge Lane</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269040244000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267363719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The NEW ENGLAND PHOTOGRAPHY ASSOCIATION March 17th Meetup</name><id>12731510</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268866800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/12731510/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/3/global_13006627.jpeg</photo_url></item>