<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The next HAC book discussion will be on Sunday, August1, 3 p.m. until 5 p.m. and we will meet at USNH, 700 Hartford Turnpike in Hamden. The book we will be reading is &amp;quot;Paul Robeson: A Biography&amp;quot; by Martin Bauml Duberman. Note that a paperback edition of the same book is titled &amp;quot;Paul Robeson: A Biography (Lives of the Left)&amp;quot;. Lots of copies are available in Connecticut public libraries as well as in book stores and online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is considered &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;the&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Robeson biography. This book s a real page turner (with a lot of pages), so I think you'll want to start on it soon.--Manny&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/1565849418/humanistassoc-20" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enthralling. . . A marvelous story marvelously told. --The Washington Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A massive classic deserving of the biggest audience for black literature since Roots. -- Kirkus Reviews&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A monumental life-and-times biography....a splendid work....required reading. -- Library Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A superb biography....History written in the grand narrative tradition. -- The New York Times Book Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will rank among the finest biographies of any twentieth-century American figure. -- The Nation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Magnificent...The finest biography I have read in years. -- USA Today&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So powerful and so important that it must be read. -- New York Newsday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Splendid...It certainly is the definitive work. -- Studs Terkel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This big, engrossing, empathetic biography by distinguished historian-playwright Duberman is a major act of cultural restoration. -- Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Product Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Passionate and enormously talented, Paul Robeson lived one of the great lives of the twentieth century. Martin Duberman's classic biography, Paul Robeson, draws on a vast archive of family papers, interviews, and FBI files to chart the course of Robeson's life: from his early days as the son of a former slave to his rise to unprecedented, international acclaim as a stage actor and singer; from his political awakening to his downfall as a victim of McCarthyism and the efforts of the U.S. government to destroy him. In a book The Nation hailed as &amp;quot;[ranking] among the finest biographies of any twentieth-century American figure,&amp;quot; Paul Robeson is a monumental and powerfully affecting portrait of one of this century's most notable performers, political radicals, and champions of racial equality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Author&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Martin Duberman is Distinguished Professor of History at the City University of New York and the author of some twenty books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sholem</member_name><member_id>445389</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280718035000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274885888000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion: "Paul Robeson: A Biography" by Martin Bauml Duberman</name><id>13601291</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280689200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/13601291/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/8/global_15344152.jpeg</photo_url></item>