<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51, Room 315</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>836742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084771</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Boston IBD Main Meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;BASIL CHAPMAN ON THE MARKET, MAMOUD SADRE ON CURRENCIES, MARK PASSACANTANDO ON INVESTING BEHAVIOR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 1: Market Talk by Basil Chapman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Market Talk is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker - usually for the next month and sometimes including longer range predictions. The speaker then makes a short case for defense of the prediction - usually taking about 10 minutes.  The audience is expected to probe or support the speaker's ideas. In general the audience participation portion of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. Historically this market discussion is lively and insights come from all around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Basil Chapman, is the host of the TFNN (Tiger Financial News Network) Tiger Technician's hour Mon-Wed-Friday at 11 am to noon, Editor of the Opening Call (a daily comprehensive newsletter giving market outlook, stock, commodity, currency, ETFs, with recommendations), former editor of The Chapman Marketline, and the CD 'Introducing the ChapmanWave methodology' available on &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basil has presented several times to our group. He presented many times to the Market Technician's Association.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 2: Currency World - Mamoud Sadre&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mamoud will build on his previous currencies talk and explain what developments are most interesting in currencies. Bring your currency questions to enliven the Q&amp;amp;A. He will cover those aspects he deems most interesting at the time we meet, but currently they are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Investing in exotic currencies (e.g. India, Brazil, Argentina.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Carry trade in Australian dollar and New Zealand dollar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japanese yen is hot for those who can handle the volatility.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mamoud Sadre developed a patent pending methodology for construction of semi-structured products for risk management in manufacturing. He founded FTS Electronic Marketplace. His most recent product is an application that uses a currency index as a factor in an asset pricing model.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 3: Behavioral Aspects of Trading by Mark Passacantando&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come unearth your silent trading partner.  While most of us have a cursory understanding that biochemistry has some role in our investment and trading lives, research incredibly suggests that a majority of our decisions are being made WITHOUT a high level of consciousness!  This short, interactive talk will allow you to test your understanding of the invisible trading partner by your side. Once you self-rate the role this partner plays in your investment/trading life, you will have a new understanding of &amp;quot;what is&amp;quot; and be able to use this awareness to your advantage.  After all, we are all in this together and wouldn't it be nice to tip the scales in our favor for a change? Mark will cover: &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A list of subconscious behaviors most investors acquire&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How such behaviors manifest themselves&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How they may be collectively impact the market&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What possibilities exist with your new level of awareness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strategies that incorporate what we don’t know into what we do know&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark is the owner of a comprehensive financial planning firm.  He also serves as an expert witness in securities matters across the U.S.  He is an instructor of Personal Financial Planning at Boston University and Harvard.  He is a part time CFO for a litigation support firm in Boston. His 25 years of experience covers a wide scope of industries starting in insurance and then moving to real estate, banking and investment management.  Mark’s passion for investing, and specifically the technical analysis side of investing, presented itself to the IBD group in the early days when we met in a Brookline restaurant years ago.  One of Mark’s new interests is the behavioral finance aspect of investing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING of the Tiger Financial Network starts at 5:30 PM.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; See &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;the announcement here&lt;/a&gt;. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers by Bob Podd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Doug&lt;br /&gt;7:15 Market Talk by Basil Chapman&lt;br /&gt;7:45 Open Discussion led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;8:00 Stockpicks led by Doug and Chris&lt;br /&gt;8:20 Break&lt;br /&gt;8:40 Talk 2: Currency World by Mamoud Sadre&lt;br /&gt;9:10 Talk 3: Behavioral Aspects of Trading by Mark Passacantando&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to join our online discussion!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are open to the public, there is no admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238717306000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>69</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234907347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston IBD Main Meeting</name><id>9762440</id><headcount>81</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238022000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9762440/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>