<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>P.O. Box 270896</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06127</zip><lat>41.762336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1447422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;August 31, 2011 - 8:00 to 9:00 pm EST&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Register and Learn More at 
&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=364"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=364&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to check your email after pre-registering. We will be sending the info you need to get your access code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;It's Time To Start The Year Off Right (even if it is August)...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;In less than 15 years I built a real estate portfolio worth more than $240 million. Rental checks from more than 7,200 units arrive in my mailbox month, after month, after month...
 &lt;br /&gt;The most important and profitable deal in my entire portfolio was my first one. If I hadn't closed that small 3 family in Brockton and got a taste for cash flow, I would not be enjoying life the way I am today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Whether you are striving to own $240 million in real estate like I do, or if you just want to get your first deal done... I am here to help you. AND there is no better time that RIGHT NOW!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday night I will be holding nothing back. I will teach you what you need to do so you can:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;1. Profit in Multi-Family real estate in 3 different ways:Quick cash now, a nice monthly income for years to come, and a huge windfall of profit from appreciation... without using your own money or credit and with little to no personal risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;You'll be amazed how easy it is to invest in multi family deals, especially in the upcoming year... and why in some cases it's actually easier than residential investing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;2. Follow the 7-steps to doing Multi-Family real estate transactions that will take you to your first or next cash flowing deal! The most amazing thing about multi family real estate is that unlike single family houses, just one deal can set you up for the rest of your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;3. Know exactly where to find Multi-Family deals online and offline.In addition, I will show you how to get a list of the hottest markets to invest in over the next 12 months. I will explain my "key identifiers" for locating massive profits in emerging real estate markets around the country... and for locating sweet deals in your own back yard. There is no one else in the world teaching this proprietary method...but on our webinar you'll see how powerful this information really is. Be prepared to take notes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;4. Use the strategies to make offers well below market value and get them accepted.You'll learn the "Power Of Two" principle to ensure your success in multi family real estate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;5. Easily Fund your deals using up to date funding strategies for today's marketplace, no matter how large or small.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Register Now to ensure your place on the webinar. Don't risk getting locked out. Don't let another year go by where you came up a little short of your goals. You deserve better than that!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314839721000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314561939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Webinar with Dave Lindahl - Profit From Multi-Family Real Estate</name><id>31293052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314835200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/31293052/</event_url></item>