<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>265 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-5927 </phone><name>MIT Museum </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>777893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097664</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This lecture is from this year's Fall Series at the MIT Museum: &amp;quot;Life in the Universe: Are We Alone?&amp;quot;. Tues. 10/25, Wed. 11/9, Tues. 11/15, Tues. 11/29. [I noticed it on the list of events in the Nerd Fun Meetup.] What: Life in the Universe: Are We Alone? Part 4 of 4: Finding Intelligence When: 6:00 pm to 7:30 pm Where: MIT Museum Cost: Free About the lecture, from the MIT Museum site, &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2011/alone.html:" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mu...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;quot;The search for intelligence in the universe is among the most controversial endeavors in astrobiology. Do we even know what we are looking for? To better understand what 'they' might be like, we need to know what is meant by 'intelligence.' Richard Wrangham, Harvard Professor of Biological Anthropology and author of Catching Fire: How Cooking Made Us Human, is renowned for his lucid explanations of the evolutionary origin of humanity, so he will help us explore what it means for animals to evolve intelligence, and how common this event is in the universe. Paul Horowitz, Harvard Professor of Physics and Electrical Engineering, is the Principal Investigator in Harvard's SETI (Search for Extra-Terrestrial Intelligence) program and an expert in custom instrumentation (such as a 3-beam, 250- million-channel radiofrequency Fourier spectrum analyzer performing an all-sky transit survey at the university's 84-foot radio telescope (!)). Professor Horowitz joins the final session of the series to talk about what it takes to search for intelligent civilizations in outer space, looking for, or at, human life on planet Earth.&amp;quot;. Directions to the MIT Museum, from &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/visit/directions.html:" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mu...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;quot;The MIT Museum is located near the north shore of the Charles River Basin in Cambridge, MA, a few blocks from the central part of the MIT campus. The MIT Museum is accessible via public transportation, and is within three miles of two major interstate highways. The Museum is approximately a 30 minute walk from downtown Boston or from Harvard Square. Take the Red Line to either Central Square Station (a 10 minute walk to the Museum) or Kendall Square/MIT Station (a 15 minute walk to the Museum). From Central Square: Walk down Mass. Ave. toward Boston and the main MIT campus. The Museum is on the left at the corner of Front St&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322665047000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322065371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Life in the Universe: Are We Alone? Finding Intellegence @ MIT Museum</name><id>42171532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322607600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/42171532/</event_url></item>