<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The time is an estimate -- I'll update it when the Kendall sets its schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Update 1/13: Kendall set the start time to 3:40. &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pedro Almodovar-Penelope Cruz team is unbeatable, in my opinion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the film: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The eagerly awaited 17th feature by one of the world's leading directors, Pedro Almodóvar (Volver, Talk to Her), is a lavish melodrama tinged with humor, showcasing the spectacular talents of Penélope Cruz. The story is told in flashback by Harry Caine (Lluís Homar, Bad Education), a blind screenwriter, who reveals that before an auto accident took his sight and the life of his love, he was the famous director Mateo Blanc. He had fallen in love with his leading lady, Lena (Cruz), who had made a startling metamorphosis from secretary and bereaved daughter to sought-after movie star when the ruthless industrialist Ernesto Martel (José Luis Gómez) became her lover and patron. The film Mateo is making with Lena (for which the jealous Martel insists on being producer) is a kinky comedy called Girls and Suitcases, reminiscent of Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown. As Mateo and Lena try to get away together for a romantic tryst, Martel's gay son is constantly following and videotaping them for a &amp;quot;making of&amp;quot; feature—which Martel uses for surveillance (even getting a lip reader to decode the lovers' conversations). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A vibrant, mature love letter to the making of movies, the meaning of movies, and the dark-eyed muse Penélope Cruz, Pedro Almodóvar's Broken Embraces doesn't so much break new ground in the filmmaker's instantly recognizable terrain as deepen an Almodóvarian's understanding of how this uniquely stylish Spanish artist sees the world. And as every frame of this chic and playful comedy/melodrama attests, he sees the world — of personal relationships and creative collaboration, of natural landscape and man-made decor — through a cinephile's magnifying lens.  A-&amp;quot;  -- Entertainment Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Can there be such a thing as exuberant melancholy? I can’t think of another way to describe the spirit of “Broken Embraces,” Pedro Almodóvar’s latest film, the title of which carries a telling hint of paradox. It is grave and effervescent, tender and cruel... The narrative reveals an intricate and enigmatic structure, full of twists and reversals. The visual and aural textures are lush and sensual, as we’ve come to expect from Mr. Almodóvar, and yet the rich colors and deep sonorities somehow illuminate an unusually austere emotional terrain.&amp;quot; -- The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for dinner and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263240999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Broken Embraces</name><id>12289666</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263760200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12289666/</event_url></item>