<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Concord St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03064</zip><lat>42.779842</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greeley Park</name><city>Nashua</city><id>671443</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.465775</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sorry about the late notice, but I just got the SummerFun calendar (Opening ceremonies was this weekend) and this looks like a concert that would  interest our members.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The concert starts at 07:00, but we need to be there by 6:45 to get good seats.  You need to bring a lawn chair, blankets, bug spray and snacks as desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing, Nada, Zilch &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Murphy's Blues:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Murphy's Blues is a big, high-energy band known for passionate performances, non-stop dance grooves and seriously fun-minded music. Male and female vocals, full vocal harmonies, a riotous horn section, clean and soulful guitar and bass work, rapid-fire keyboards, dead-on percussion and one mean blues harp. Their song list includes R&amp;amp;B, soul, funk, rock and blues favorites and originals done in their  own playful and powerful style that keeps people out on the dance floor. Murphy's Blues connects with the crowd to build dance-and-jam momentum in every set. Murphy's Blues play at clubs, wedding receptions, birthday parties, corporate and civic events, festivals, and fundraisers---wherever good times are required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://murphysblues.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://murphysblues.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a foil balloon attached to my chair</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245020017000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244382052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SummerFun Rhythm &amp; Blues Concert: Murphy's Blues</name><id>10595628</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244846700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/10595628/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/5/8/global_9013880.jpeg</photo_url></item>