<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Porter Square</address_2><address_1>1920 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.388969</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9180 </phone><name>Christopher's Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669129</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119904</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's a wonderful place for brunch with big plates of french toast, waffles, or eggs and fried potatoes!, so says fellow foodie, Emilie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Emile for suggesting and nearly twenty of you agreeing to check out Christopher's brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the past few years I've heard wonderful things about Christopher's....great meals with generous portions at very reasonable prices in a good location as well as being accessible by public transportation.  I was never able to join the brunches BBLD organizer's arranged, until now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link with the brunch menu, so many choices....fruit stuffed french toast, chorizo omelet, portabello omelet, smoked salmon eggs benedict,,mmmm &lt;a href="http://www.christopherscambridge.com/brunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.christophe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to arrange your driving directions  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Along Massachusetts Ave (meters free on Sundays)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/b&gt; Create your own train and/or bus route here &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Porter Square Station - red line subway (Christopher's is across the street)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Before I list the Reservation Rules, please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to assure you I do understand if you've RSVPd YES and you have a sudden change of plans because you're lost, you don't feel well, you have transportation issues, you don't have the money, or you just don't want to be around people. My only request is for you to let me know as soon as possible so we don't worry about you and our reservation is adjusted. As long as you contact me you will not be considered a NO-SHOW.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rules for Events with Reservations:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVPs are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If event is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended, it is counted as a NO-SHOW if you haven't contacted me to advise you're not able to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW each will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within an hour of the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW if you do not contact me of your change in plans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events with reservations you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me (Tonya) about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will arrive 11:45 AM to to confirm our seating and welcome you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291493430000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281562940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch at Christopher's in Porter Square! - Sunday August 15th Noon 12 PM</name><id>14394664</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281888000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/14394664/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/f/global_17122415.jpeg</photo_url></item>