<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02359</zip><lat>42.104183</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 826-8883</phone><name>Orta</name><city>Pembroke</city><id>884103</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.804404</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Our ever-popular series of &amp;quot;letter&amp;quot; restaurants continues this month with &amp;quot;O&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Orta in Pembroke, our pick of the poll, comes highly recommended from both within and without the group. In fact (as their website points out) they were chosen as Boston Magazine's Best New Restaurant, South, for 2009. They also received a pretty positive review from Devra First in the &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/ae/food/restaurants/articles/2009/05/06/napoletana_rules/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Globe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be heading there on Thursday, October 29th at 7:00 PM. As always, there's a place at the table waiting for &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Orta Restaurant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, October 29th @ 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;75 Washington Street&lt;br /&gt;Pembroke, MA&lt;br /&gt;(781) 826-8883&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ortarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ortarestau...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Mike and Jeanne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to 2 per Member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Pizza selections shown online range from $7.95 to $14.95.  A selection of piattini (&amp;quot;little plates&amp;quot;) are $4.00 each, with other appetizers topping out at $9.25. Main dishes range from $11.95 (Linguini) to $20.50 (Sirloin Steak), with most under $18.000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, October 28th @ 7:00 PM.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to No after this point will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Orta is in a mall called Pembroke Pointe on Washington St. (Route 53) in Pembroke, at the intersection of Routes 53 and 139.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3:&lt;/b&gt; Take Exit 12 (Route 139) and head West on Route 139, passing through the cluster of businesses just off the exit, including a 99 Restaurant on the right side of the road and a Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket on the left. Follow Route 139 for about 1 to 1 1/2 miles until it intersects Route 53 at a stoplight, just after you pass ITZAPARTY on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the stoplight, keep to the right of the traffic island, but stay to your left, as if you were going to turn left onto Route 53. You should see a strip mall with a South Shore Savings Bank directly across from you. This is Pembroke Pointe: Orta is the business located on the far right of the row of buildings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simply drive straight across Route 53 and into the mall. There is some parking designated for Orta in front of the restaurant, and more located behind the shops (warning: we're told that parking out back means climbing a long flight of stairs in order to get to Orta's entrance).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>714439</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258241845000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255579586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Obviously: Orta!</name><id>11631520</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256857200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/11631520/</event_url></item>