<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join other members of the permaculture group in welcoming Dave Jacke, author of the two-volume &lt;i&gt;Edible Forest Gardens&lt;/i&gt;, for a reception and book signing event here in Portland.  To learn more about the books and forest gardening, please see:  &lt;a href="http://www.edibleforestgardens.com/about_book" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ediblefore...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This social event will be comprised of &lt;b&gt;potluck appetizers and beverages&lt;/b&gt; (please bring one or the other) from 7:00 to 8:00 followed by some &lt;b&gt;comments and a reading by Dave&lt;/b&gt; and then the books will be available for &lt;b&gt;purchase and signing by the author&lt;/b&gt; himself!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note:  We are still confirming the exact venue for this, but it will be in or close to downtown Portland.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, remember to bring your potluck kit (dish/bowl/utensils/napkin/cup).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dave Jacke has been a student of ecology and design since the 1970s, and has run his own ecological design firm?Dynamics Ecological Design?since 1984. Dave is an engaging and passionate teacher of ecological design and permaculture, and a meticulous designer. He has consulted on, designed, built, and planted landscapes, homes, farms, and communities in the many parts of the United States, as well as overseas, but mainly in the Northeast. A cofounder of Land Trust at Gap Mountain in Jaffrey, NH, he homesteaded there for a number of years. He holds a B.A. in Environmental Studies from Simon's Rock College (1980) and a M.A. in Landscape Design from the Conway School of Landscape Design (1984).&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219015235000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215650554000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dave Jacke "Edible Forest Gardens" Reception &amp; Book Signing</name><id>8310501</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218841200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/8310501/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/global_3708325.jpeg</photo_url></item>