<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395359</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Please Send Me A Message on Meet</phone><name>Davis Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>735132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122574</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Catch up with us marching with the parade or in Harvard Square. Bring Your Camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday, October 10th from Noon to 2pm over 25 activist street bands from around the country and beyond, will leave Davis Square and arrive at the Harvard Square Oktoberfest at 1pm to &amp;quot;reclaim the streets for horns, bikes and feet.&amp;quot; Grand Parade Marshall's Click and Clack will welcome more than 30 marching bands and rolling, strolling, biking, dancing, performing and walking groups at the reviewing stand from 1-2pm. There will also be live entertainment, restaurant vendors, outdoor beer gardens, street vendors and Honk! bands from around the country performing on stages in Harvard Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information, schedules and updates will be available at www.honkfest.org &lt;a href="http://www.honkfest.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; along with www.harvardsquare.com &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can not properly describe the Honk! Parade. You must go to their web site for more information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a long day. Arrive early for the parade from Davis Square, later or in the middle of the Harvard Square mayhem. I will be attending the Honk! Parade with some friends as I have since its birth. We will be taking a break for lunch or dinner in the heart of Harvard Square.  Taking a break to watch an American or National League Playoff Games is also a possibility. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please note the Honk! Parade begins in Davis Square, Somerville and ends at the Annual Oktoberfest celebration in Harvard Square, Cambridge.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who want to meetup with us should e mail me their cell phone numbers or e mail other attending Natives to meet along the route. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fenway Frank&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286907880000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284409059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Honk! Parade from Davis Sq to Oktoberfest in Harvard Sq </name><id>14756887</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286726400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/14756887/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/2/global_9249538.jpeg</photo_url></item>