<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>E Lake Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03452</zip><lat>42.902729</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt. Monadnock: Pumpelly Trailhead</name><city>Dublin</city><id>639691</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.071834</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The popularity of this hike inspired me to add a second section for Mt. Monadnock plus it gets me off the waiting list. Mt. Monadnock, or Grand Monadnock as some call it, is a very busy place to hike so I'm planning a route that's less traveled. Let's meet in the main parking area. After paying at the ranger station enter the lot and bear left. Drive&amp;nbsp; until you see my gray Subaru with RI License 6730 w/lights on. I should be there by 9:15 AM. This will be our end point. We'll drop a couple of cars there and then, all together, drive back to the Gilson Pond parking lot. After the obligatory stretching and hydrating we'll take the Birchtoft Trail to Red Spot to Pumpelly to 3,165' summit (3.5 miles.) We'll descend the White Arrow Trail to Cliff Walk over Bald Rock to Lost Farm Trail to the welcome cars in the lot. If our timing is good we'll see J&amp;amp;P's group at the summit. See trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/MonadnockHikingTrailsMap_All_2010.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/MonadnockHikingTrailsMap_All_2010.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Hike about 6.0 miles, 1800 ft elevation gain. Bring plenty of water, snacks, lunch, and hiking boots! It can windy at the summit, so make sure you bring an extra layer to wear at the top. Plus rain gear if the forecast looks iffy! Pouring rain postpones but drizzle/showers will not. No dogs/children please. Note that there's a $4 admission fee per person at Monadnock State Park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great Spring warm up hike for experienced hikers, but not a beginner hike. The trail is rocky with some scrambles. We will be moving at a moderate pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its about a 2 hour drive from Providence. My cell: 401-556-8955.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter the main lot and look for gray subaru with lights on-RI Lic 6730</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis </member_name><member_id>8755592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305380350000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We live for the great Outdoors!</why><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303590755000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Monadnock! Overflow hiking team.</name><id>17409401</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304775000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/17409401/</event_url></item>