<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;I've never done this Art Walk before, but this is the 18th year!  It's from Noon-6pm.  Parking in the area might be tough - so probably best to take the T.  Nearest T-Stop is Charles Circle.  Earlier in the day, we'll be at the Tibetan Meditation Class, so we can go to the Art Walk together if we'd like.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Map:  &lt;a href="http://beaconhillartwalk.org/maps2007/sunnymap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://beaconhillartwalk.org/maps2007/sunnymap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://beaconhillartw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://beaconhillartwalk.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://beaconhillartwalk.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://beaconhillartw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;18th Annual Beacon Hill Art Walk features more than 100 artists showing original work among the hidden nooks &amp;amp; crannies of Beacon Hill. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come enjoy orginal art amidst beautiful gardens and live music. Check website for indoor locations in case of rain. Stop in at our Charles Street and Cambridge Street restaurants while you're here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Art Walk is an annual event that takes place on the first Sunday in June, throughout the nooks and crannies of Beacon Hill. Residents open up their private gardens, alleyways, and courtyards and allow artists to display and sell their artwork. It is a chance for visitors to tour for free the private spaces of Beacon Hill while viewing original artwork. Thousands attend each year. It is a popular event in the neighborhood, with a festive atmosphere and volunteer musicians playing in various gardens throughout the day. Around 100 artists usually participate, with a variety of styles, media, and subject matter.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet on Charles St. and Putnam St. in Beacon Hill, just outside the Charles Circle T-Stop (see map link below).  Call Bernadette's cell (617)372-3557.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212509288000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211844889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Beacon Hill Art Walk </name><id>8015235</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212336000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/8015235/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/1/global_4254913.jpeg</photo_url></item>