<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ferris Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02916</zip><lat>41.847016</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ten Mile River Greenway </name><city>East Providence</city><id>904321</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE TAKE THE POLL TO LET US KNOW WHAT YOU ARE GOING TO DO...&lt;br /&gt;WALK, JOG, RUN, BIKE or ROLL.  Click the link below to vote&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Bicycling/polls/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My meetups are just for fun and pleasure. &lt;br /&gt;Anyone and everyone is welcome. &lt;br /&gt;So don't get stressed about having to complete the whole path, just come on out, enjoy the outdoors and meet some new folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ten Mile River Greenway is a 2 Mile Bike Path that goes along the Ten Mile River and parts od Slater Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go at your own pace&lt;br /&gt;Go as far as you want&lt;br /&gt;Stop where ever you want&lt;br /&gt;Stay for as long as you want &amp;amp; leave whenever you want.&lt;br /&gt;NO STRESS!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;East Providence/Pawtucket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;East Providence, Kimberly Ann Rock Athletic Fields&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * From I-195 East: Take Exit 4 to Taunton Ave. (Rte.44) continue on Taunton Ave. for approx. 2 miles, becomes Waterman Ave. after crossing South Broadway, bear LEFT onto Hall Street, bear RIGHT onto Taunton Ave., continue to intersection with Pawtucket Ave., take LEFT onto Pawtucket Ave. (Rte. 114), continue on Pawtucket Ave. to its intersection with Newman/Ferris Ave., bear right onto Ferris Ave., sign for Ten Mile River Greenway is approx. 1 mile on RIGHT.&lt;br /&gt;    * From I-195 West: Take Exit 6 for Broadway, bear right at end of exit, continue straight on North Broadway, passing underneath N. Broadway tunnel, continue on North Broadway which becomes Newman Avenue after its intersection with Greenwood Ave. Continue on Newman Avenue to its intersection with Pawtucket Ave. (Rte. 114) and bear left onto Ferris Ave., sign for Ten Mile River Greenway is approximately one mile on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I drive a white Toyota Highland meet me by my car. We won't leave until 10 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a white Toyota Highland meet me by my car</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242485522000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237150044000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ten Mile River Bike Path - 2 Miles Long - 4 Miles Total Trip Back &amp; Forth</name><id>9960387</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240063200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/9960387/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/d/global_5864541.jpeg</photo_url></item>