<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello H2O Water &amp;amp; Energy Members!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's been a few months, but we're diving mid-way into the 4th quarter with a compelling Water event!  Join us on Thursday, November 5th at 6:00 p.m. at Exemplar Law, 10 Post Office Square, 8th Floor, Boston, MA.  William Staby, CEO of Resolute Marine Energy and Olivier Ceberio, COO of Resolute Marine Energy will be there to present their breakthrough innovations in both wave power generation and on-shore sea water desalination.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though there are multiple applications for each technology, combined they offer a fast and efficient design capable of supplying thousands of gallons of drinking water per day to coastal communities in crisis.  Imagine the incredible relief this could bring people in need under the worst of circumstances.  Think post Hurricane Katrina or post tropical cyclone Nargis off the coast of Myanmar.  The forces of nature not only bring forward all kinds of harsh lessons, they can ignite sparks of inspiration as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to inspire and engage you in this lively presentation, followed by Q&amp;amp;A and, of course, networking!  We'll be providing some basic fare...pizza and beverage (the malted kind!) as this topic is likely to bring about an unquenchable thirst for more exploration!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to contact me for more information about this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Biscoe</member_name><member_id>9316649</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275748809000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Water &amp; Energy Tech. Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>H2O-Boston-Water-and-Energy-Technology-Meetup</urlname><id>1430670</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>H2O Boston:  Water and Energy Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253726280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hot Water!!  Meetup with Resolute Marine Energy on November 5th</name><id>11447463</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257462000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/H2O-Boston-Water-and-Energy-Technology-Meetup/events/11447463/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/7/global_8526711.jpeg</photo_url></item>