<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01929</zip><lat>42.635349</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-768-3722</phone><name>Essex River Basin Adventure</name><city>Essex</city><id>689475</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.782350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;EVENT:&lt;/b&gt; We will be joining Essex River Basin Adventurers, ERBA, www.erba.com to take part in a 3 hour guided tour around the mouth of the Essex River (the “Gilligan” Tour).  This is a trip for both the beginner and intermediate and it explores a relaxed area with lots of islands and wildlife, the kayaking itself will be a fun work out.  Essex is a beautiful, colonial town with a lot of character and a visit for some dinner after our tour may be well worth it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trp Coordinator:&lt;/b&gt; David Goldsmith – dgoldsmith38@aol.com or call 978-740-0345 before 9pm. Calls on the day of the event: 978-548-8019&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP:&lt;/b&gt; You must enroll yourself in the 3:00 the “Gilligan” Tour by July 25th with Essex River Basin Adventurers (978) 768-3722 or use their email address above, make a note that you are with Mosaic &lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;and send me a rsvp&lt;/b&gt; as well&lt;/b&gt;, please include a phone number in case  contact is needed on the 1st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEET:&lt;/b&gt; By 2:00 on the 1st at ERBA’s Barn. The kayaking includes shuttle service and we are requested to arrive 45 minutes before our tour starts for parking and other arrangements.  I will have a Mosaic T shirt and cap on that day.&lt;br /&gt;The Barn is on Rt 133, One Main St in Essex and parking is located at a municipal lot a couple of blocks away. The town is fairly easy to get to, it's just off Rt 128 shortly before Gloucester, and the web site for Essex River Basin Adventurers has driving directions as well as a description of the kayaking trip that I picked out for us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $53 for the “Gilligan” Tour (you can cancel before Thurs at noon and still get your money back) plus $5 for Mosaic which will be credited towards a membership to Mosaic of MA if you  join later this year&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Contact David at the address listed above to make plans</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280752735000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278470132000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Essex River Kayaking Adventure</name><id>14024105</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280685600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/14024105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/0/global_1883520.jpeg</photo_url></item>