<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Asylum Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767876</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-978-2622</phone><name>ArtSpace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1045061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.682486</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, many Americans have poor eating habits.&amp;nbsp; Trying to eat healthier isn't easy -- you may feel like you're swimming against the tide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's the answer?&amp;nbsp; Get support!&amp;nbsp; Spend time with folks committed to making healthier choices!&amp;nbsp; Find out how they achieved their health goals.&amp;nbsp; Share your story.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us!&amp;nbsp; Learn, laugh, and make new friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 pm: Potluck Dinner begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30 - 8:30 pm: Talk and Discussion on &amp;ldquo;How to Achieve Your Health Goals&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 - 9:00 pm:&amp;nbsp; Chattng and cleaning up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our speaker, Vera Halina, has been pursuing her passion for healing for the last 12 years.&amp;nbsp; She has an eclectic background which includes:&amp;nbsp; Chinese Herbal Medicine, Massage, Reiki, Shamanic Healing, Sacred Hot Stone Therapy, Pure Essential Therapy, Ear Candling, and Organic Facials.&amp;nbsp; To make alternative healing more accessible, she founded an exciting new company called Vitality Express Referral Alliance.&amp;nbsp; Also, she blogs and creates radio shows which include interviews with doctors of natural medicine, herbalists and spiritual healers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vera will be talking about different forms of support to help you stick with your health goals and achieve them.&amp;nbsp; Knowledgeable and well-connected, she will answer your health questions and point you to practitioners, centers, and other resources to help you on your healing journey.&amp;nbsp; And she will share information about SuperBetter, a game, inspired by leading-edge research in psychology, neuroscience and medicine, that can help you achieve any health goal &amp;mdash; by increasing your personal resilience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the potluck dinner:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Many people have dietary restrictions. Bring a note card that lists the ingredients in the food you bring or fill out a note card at the potluck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-This a zero-waste event.&amp;nbsp; Please bring your own plate and utensils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This event is part of a series organized by CT Health Foodies which will usually be on the second Tuesday of the month at ArtSpace in downtown Hartford. CT Health Foodies is a supportive community for people interested in learning more about healthy eating. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free parking in the back of the ArtSpace building.&amp;nbsp; Ignore "Resident Parking Only" signs.&amp;nbsp; Parking is allowed during this event.&amp;nbsp; Enter through the back entrance by the murals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you on Tuesday, Feb 21!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>13105264</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329966429000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329157034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck Dinner and Talk on "How to Achieve Your Health Goals"</name><id>52181982</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329868800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/52181982/</event_url></item>