<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everybody,   &lt;br /&gt;As part of their film classics series, The Brattle Theater is presenting Nostalghia by Andrei Tarkovsky. I think that says it all, but I'll continue:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Working under the restraints of the Soviet regime, director Andrei Tarkovsky only completed 7 films yet somehow managed to produce some of the most poetic, personal, and spiritual films in the 100 years of cinema to date. You could consider his films to be  moment-driven: his best scenes are long takes on singular  fragments of time and rely less on the episodic tendencies  of most film-making.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Russians, the  meaning of  Nostalghia is a bit different from the English definition and signifies &amp;quot; a longing for the homeland.&amp;quot;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout his career Tarkovsky returned to subjects concerned with mankind?s role in the larger scheme of things. Nostalghia is a film that challenges the way we live our lives and calls for changes to be made in them, like Kurosawa?s Ikiru. It is also a dreamlike work of film poetry that masterfully expresses a longing for all that makes up one?s conception of home.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plot (so to speak): A Russian writer named Andrei Gorchakov is visiting Italy to research the life of Sosnovsky, a musician from his home country who studied in Bologna during the late 1700s. Andrei is accompanied by Eugenia, an Italian translator who seems to anticipate a relationship forming between the two of them. However, Andrei becomes more intent on understanding a lonely, deranged local man, Domenico, infamous in the community for previously locking himself and his family in their home for several years in fear of the end of the world. Andrei meets with this strange character who asks him to complete what he considers to be a very important task: carry a lit candle across the village spa. Bored and exasperated, Eugenia leaves for Rome to be with another man. Domenico also goes to Rome to make speeches and to stage a demonstration; he burns himself to death in the public square. Back at the spa, an ill Andrei delays his departure for Russia to fulfill Domenico's request. After much effort Andrei finally makes it across the drained pool with the candle where he collapses and, assumedly, dies. The last poetic shot shows him resting serenely in the Russian landscape of his home, all of which is contained within the large structure of an Italian cathedral. Strictly Film School   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you couldn't tell, I'm a bit biased  and so to be fair I must mention that the NY Times review simply says &amp;quot;Nothing happens&amp;quot;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to the traditional favorable review: &lt;a href="http://www.sover.net/~ozus/nostalghia.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sover.net/...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there and as you can imagine I'm really looking forward to seeing this again-   &lt;br /&gt;Tom   &lt;br /&gt;The Good: &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194891103000</updated><rating><average>4.30000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193101257000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tarkovsky's Nostalghia </name><id>6598811</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194710400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6598811/</event_url></item>