<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Actual start time:  7:10 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A thoughtful but outrageous black comedy from Bobcat Goldthwait, &lt;u&gt;World's Greatest Dad&lt;/u&gt; is the story of a man who learns that the things you want most may not be the things that make you happy, and that being lonely is not necessarily the same as being alone. Robin Williams stars as Lance Clayton, a man who has learned to settle. He dreamed of being a rich and famous writer, but has only managed to make it as a high school poetry teacher. His only son Kyle (Daryl Sabara) is an insufferable jackass who won’t give his father the time of day. Lance is dating Claire (Alexie Gilmore), the school’s adorable art teacher, but she doesn’t want to get serious—or even acknowledge publicly that they are dating. Then, in the wake of a freak accident, Lance suffers the worst tragedy and greatest opportunity of his life. He is suddenly faced with the possibility of all the fame, fortune and popularity he ever dreamed of, if he can only live with the knowledge of how he got there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From New York Times Critic's Pick Review:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“World’s Greatest Dad” shoots a poisoned arrow at the grotesque sentimentality that often attaches to the death of a teenager, in this case apparently a suicide, and the toxin leaks all over the place. After watching this extreme satire, written and directed by Bobcat Goldthwait, you may never want to attend another memorial for anyone at which tearful testimonials are read, gooey ballads sung and the memory of the deceased slathered with mawkish bromides. With a merciless acuity this nihilistic comedy ridicules collective grief and the news media’s cynical marketing of inspirational uplift after a death. Ultimately it scorns the human impulse to find a deeper meaning in any tragedy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we'll go to The Friendly Toast to discuss the film.  My dad used to say that the word 'father' could be broken down to a 'fat her'. Not sure if that's relevant, but we'll see . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And I'll see you at the movie,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251587445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World's Greatest Dad</name><id>11234504</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252105200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11234504/</event_url></item>