<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Skinner State Park is just west of Mt. Holyoke Range State Park and a little North of Springfield, MA! This will mostly be an out-and-back hike going from the Notch Visitor Center, west along the MM Trail to the Mount Holyoke Summit House and back. The exact length and path covered on this hike will depend on the weather conditions. We'll hike no more than approximately 6 miles given a 5 hour window for hiking. Most of the hike would be moderate in difficulty with high exertion at the start and at the end. Forest, and quiet solitude will dominate the hike and lovely views near the beginning and at the Summit House.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Those who wish to go need to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;

* Layers of clothing - It will be cool to start, avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. &lt;br /&gt;

* Light Jacket - BRIGHT color best, again it will be cool &lt;br /&gt;

* 1-2 quart of water - MUST bring! &lt;br /&gt;

* Trail appropriate food/lunch - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meetup will be at 10 AM at the Notch Visitors Center at the east side of the park (see the park map). We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 5 hr. and get back to the vehicles at about 3 PM. There is a good chance we will finish earlier than this time. Then the plan is to head out to eat an early dinner together back down MA-116 in South Hadley. We would finish up eating at about 5 PM or earlier and head home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 4 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor leaving at a 9 AM for those interested. There will be a silver Ford Escape SUV. Please chip in for gas and the drive is about an hour. Return at about 6 PM or earlier. It is advised to call Kevin (number in RSVP) or e-mail him so he knows you plan to carpool. If no one calls for the carpool there will be no carpool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location/directions to meet at park&lt;/strong&gt; (park in Visitor Center parking lot)&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=1540+West+St&amp;amp;city=Amherst&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01002"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=1540+West+St&amp;amp;city=Amherst&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location/directions for the carpool meet-up&lt;/strong&gt; (in parking lot area in front of Wal-Mart): &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=69+Prospect+Hill+Rd&amp;amp;city=East+Windsor&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06088&amp;amp;redirect=true"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=69+Prospect+Hill+Rd&amp;amp;city=East+Windsor&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06088&amp;amp;redirect=true&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General park information:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/skinner/"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/skinner/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Park map:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/skinner.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/skinner.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Ford Escape SUV, CT plates. Can meet me in E. Windsor to join in a carpool or to follow up to hike location. Can also meet at hike location at Visitor's Center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349147514000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348200942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Skinner SP in Amherst MA</name><id>83406062</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348408800000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/83406062/</event_url></item>