<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Middletown</address_2><address_1>85 Miner Hill Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miner Hill Golf Course</name><city>Middletown</city><id>567976</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>*GOLF 101 *Develop Your Skills For A Lifetime Of Great Golf – $17/hour       &lt;br /&gt;GOLF 101 Lessons for New Golfers – Learn to Golf &amp;amp; Improve Your Game&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GOLF 102 - Scramble Tournament Playing Lesson&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED GOLF with LEGENDARY GOLF CHAMPION MIKE COLANDRO&lt;br /&gt;Have you always wanted to play Golf? Do you want to improve your Golfing Skills and play better?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn to Golf and Improve Your Skills Without Breaking The Bank with Golf 101 and Golf 102 Lessons - 6 Hours of Hands On Lessons for Only $100 (includes Golf Balls, Golf Clubs and ALL FEES) &lt;br /&gt;- That is less than $17/hour for quality Golf Lessons from a Certified Teaching Professional!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– 6 Hours of hands on group lessons for only $100 (less than $17 per hour) with a Certified Teaching Golf Professional  - small class size of 9 people gives you personal attention&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Includes clubs and all course fees * Choose any 3 classes to fit your schedule &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Classes include * Putting * Chipping * Driving Range * Video Golf Swing Analysis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2009, more than 100 New Golfers graduated from Golf 101 lessons * 2010 Classes are filling up quickly! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* We will notify you of any postponements and to reschedule your makeup class * &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CLASSES AVAILABLE ON: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MONDAYS * 6-8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THURSDAYS * 6-8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAYS * 4:30 – 6:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Classes are held at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miner Hills Golf Course&lt;br /&gt;85 Miner Hills Drive&lt;br /&gt;Middletown, CT 06457&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit 20 off I-91 Country Club Road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10 minutes from Hartford * 10 minutes from New Haven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read about Golf 101 in the Hartford Courant: &lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.courant.com/features/hc-golf-lessons.artaug15,0,2543524.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.courant.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GOLF 101 and GOLF 102 lessons are only $100 Online Advance Registration Discount &lt;br /&gt;or $150 at the lessons (cash only) – call for availability&lt;br /&gt;* SAVE $50 – buy your ticket online *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your spot today – visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Get a FREE certificate for 9 holes of Golf at Miner Hills Golf Course with your GOLF 101 enrollment! Supplies are limited – so sign up today and get your FREE round of Golf *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED GOLF with LEGENDARY GOLF CHAMPION MIKE COLANDRO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR EXPERIENCED GOLFERS ONLY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED GOLF with Legendary Golf Champion gives you a once in a lifetime opportunity to play Golf with and learn from Golf Champion Mike Colandro- and benefit from his years of experience to help you improve your Golfing knowledge and skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED Golf starts out Tuesday at the Driving Range with Short Irons for an unique Golf Lesson that with help you to play better Golf. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next lesson is Thursday at the Driving Range with Fairway Woods&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The third lesson is Tuesday covering Putting and Chipping to make you a great Golfer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday is used as a rain date in case of any bad weather in the first 3 lesson dates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY gives you personalized Playing Lessons out on this beautiful 9 hole Golf Course located in Windsor CT Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LESSONS ARE HELD at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tradition Golf Club At Windsor&lt;br /&gt;147 Pigeon Hill Rd &lt;br /&gt;Windsor, CT 06095&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TUES 6:30 -7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Driving Range -Short Irons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THURS 6:30 -7:30 pm Driving Range &lt;br /&gt;Fairway Woods and Drivers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TUES 6:30 -7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Putting and Chipping &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THURS 6:30 -7:30pm &lt;br /&gt;RAIN DATE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY 4-7 pm &lt;br /&gt;9 holes Playing Lesson&lt;br /&gt;7 pm - AFTERPARTY with Mike Colandro and PRIZES from Titleist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Mike Colandro after the Playing Lessons for more Golf Tips, Golf Stories, PRIZES from Titleist, and a great time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE- Class Size Is Limited To 6 People And Will Fill Up Quickly -Reserve Your Spot Today&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Play Golf with Mike Colandro while he teaches you the skills that he used to win Championships in Australia and New Zealand. ADVANCED GOLF with Mike Colandro is a very unique opportunity to learn from and play Golf with a Golf Legend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your 6 hours of Golf Lessons include Driving Range -Short Irons, Fairway Woods and Drivers, Putting and Chipping, and 9 holes of Playing Lessons out on the Golf Course. Class size is 6 people - that guarantees you personal attention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Mike after the Playing Lessons for an after party to ask questions and talk Golf - Plus PRIZES from Titleist &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED GOLF - $200 for 6 Hours of hands-on Golf Lessons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class Size is limited to 6 people to ensure personal attention&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GIVE DAD THE GIFT HE WILL REMEMBER FOREVER – A ONCE IN A LIFETIME PERSONAL GOLF LESSON WITH GOLF CHAMPION MIKE COLANDRO!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsCT.com/Advanced-Golf.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449 for info&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;See You On The Course! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT OUR STUDENTS ARE SAYING: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ Golf 101 was a fun and inexpensive way to learn Golf from the beginning. Having never golfed before, I was nervous, but our Instructor George did a great job teaching our group, and I am having a great time in Golf 102!” &lt;br /&gt;Rodney P, New Haven CT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ Inexpensive, high quality Lessons in a small group, I made new golfing buddies and am enjoying the game of golf” &lt;br /&gt;June B, Bloomfield CT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ I have taken lessons from golf pros before, but Golf 102 Playing Lessons were more effective and less expensive than any other lessons.” &lt;br /&gt;Jim S, Newington CT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ I was not sure if I would enjoy Golfing so I tried Golf 101 and I love it! The Instructor was very patient and answered all my questions, and made the lessons fun!” &lt;br /&gt;Gloria W, Milford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your spot today – visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for our Golf Instructor by the clubhouse wearing the white www.CTGolfTips.com hat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281966700000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281873152000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*GOLF 101 *Develop Your Skills For A Lifetime Of Great Golf *Less Than–$17/hour </name><id>hvnrnynlbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281904200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/14426766/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/9/global_15226361.jpeg</photo_url></item>