<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For the September meetup, we're going back to that HUGE backyard in Carver, home of Buford, Millie, and Max.  The food is great, there is lots of shade and folding chairs for sedentary owners and lazy Pugs, and for those Pugs that like to run, run, RUN, there is enough room to stage a PUGTONA!   We hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****************UPDATE  09/09/06***************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  &amp;quot;If anyone needs a break from non-stop Pug action...the &lt;br /&gt;Patriots game will be on the the family room on the 65&amp;quot; HDTV!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LAST MONTH'S MEETUP...&lt;br /&gt;We had beautiful cool weather and a record turn out for the August Meetup in King Clovis's backyard, 20 people and at least two dozen Puggies (and a few French Bulldogs!).  We're always happy to see kids come along too - Pugs LOVE kids - but Clovis just had one question... how come we NEVER get to keep the Baby??  Sorry, Clovis,  their mothers get awfully attached to them...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS...&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby.  Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool.  There will be biscuits for the dogs and coffee, soft drinks, and something to snack on for the adults!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs.  If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him.  We want everyone to have fun.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159917892000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1155495780000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug September Meetup</name><id>5075755</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1157911200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/5075755/</event_url></item>