<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>789 Connecticut Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06854</zip><lat>41.093086</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Double Tree Inn</name><city>Norwalk</city><id>1022486</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.451991</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CT REIA and Laura Treonze presents: Quarterly Fairfield County REIA Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 11. 6:30 - 8:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Doubletree Hotel. 789 Connecticut Avenue. Norwalk, CT&lt;br /&gt;$10 for CT REIA Members | $20 for not-yet-members&lt;br /&gt;Register Now at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=244" target="_blank"&gt;www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=244&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking to connect with other investors in Fairfield County and Lower New Haven County?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to attend this first quarterly meeting of the Fairfield County REIA sponsored by the CTREIA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your business cards and deals - bring your team of professionals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be an exciting night where deals will be made.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laura Treonze real estateLaura Treonze, Keller Williams Realty of Trumbull specializes in working with investors. She will be teaching a workshop on investing in real estate in today's market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laura possesses 10 years of real estate investment experience and is a workshop instructor of The Millionaire Real Estate Investor by Gary Keller. She belongs to a global real estate organization dealing in luxury property, has her e-pro designation and is a Number1Expert - representing top selling agents across the country. Laura's success in real estate has been featured in the book &amp;quot;Living The Law of Attraction&amp;quot;. Her prior professional skills include marketing and fundraising. She holds a Bachelor of Arts degree from Stonehill College.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268523797000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267466064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fairfield Country REIA Meeting With Laura Treonze</name><id>12744924</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268350200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12744924/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/4/global_13402740.jpeg</photo_url></item>