<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>By popular demand: Here's a third studio day dedicated to art journals. Whether you're already working on a journal and want to share it or need your colleagues' advice on turning a blank book into a work of art, this is the session for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Please note, though:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;This is a play date, &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; a class; we won't be offering any formal instruction this time. But we'll have a blast while learning from each other, and we may have some workshops down the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Sunday, April 18, from 1 p.m. to ???? (Really, we'll stay as late as anybody wants to stay!) Arrive and leave when you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/b&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (professional-strength paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom. Dinner in or out, if people are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $10 per person. This helps cover the cost of renting our space. Exact change is greatly appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/b&gt; Any member of the NE ATC+, Altered Art/Assemblage or Mass Journaling Meetups and their guests (18+ only, please).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Your own journal, if you have one (or even some cardstock or chipboard to make journal pages). Any kind of journal will do; the format is up to you. (If you'd like to alter an old book, we have plenty available.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•The craft supplies you'll need during the session. No supplies? No problem. Basic tools -- scissors, glue, acrylic paint, collage materials, etc. -- are available for your use at no charge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Something to drink (optional) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Snacks to share (optional) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;/b&gt;NOTE: This Meetup is full, so PLEASE bring just what you need for today (as opposed to everything you own). Thanks!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/b&gt; RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. RSVP for your guests as well. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP. We expect this event to fill and maybe even have a waiting list, so PLEASE &lt;u&gt;do this right up to the start time for the event&lt;/u&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/b&gt; If we need to cancel due to weather or any reason--or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot; So please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Oh, they'll figure it out.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271784021000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269459903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special NE ATC+ Meetup: Yet Another Day of Art Journaling</name><id>12981793</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271610000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/12981793/</event_url></item>