<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-345</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>337655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Campus map of Building E51 (entrance is in the rear):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE THE EARLIER START TIME!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Two feature length talks by favorite Boston IBD speakers. Bring your insights and your questions to make the night interactive!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;First Talk: Trading ETFs by Harlan Rieur&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt; Trading ETFs can seem easy, like a low risk approach to stock trading. This talk focuses on pitfalls and subtleties in the various ETFs currently available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This talk will start with the basic questions such as: What is an ETF? How does an ETF differ from a mutual fund? What are the categories of ETFs? What are the pros and cons of ETFs? Do not confuse basics with fundamentals; many traders lack an understanding of ETF fundamentals. Proper execution and success in almost everything in life requires mastering the fundamentals first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The answers to these questions will be used in the light of the speaker's personal trading experience to offer suggestions on trading them. In particular, Harlan will focus on the following areas:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stripping&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hedging&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hiding Stops&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slippage&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Harlan Rieur has been investing since his father got him started at age 13. Initially he used Graham and Dodd type fundamental analysis. During the 1980's he moved to Technical analysis. Professionally he has been a Chiropractor in Brookline for 22 years. He is a Doctor of Chiropractic, has a degree in business administration and a minor in economics from Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harlan funded his education through investing and continues to be fascinated by this life long passion. He spends half his time in each endeavor (Chiropractic and investing). He is a long-term member of our group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Second Talk: Leading the Way into the 4th Quarter: Markets, Sectors and Stocks  By Basil Chapman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt; Basil will present his interactive preview of the markets as he expects them for 2008's 4th quarter. He will use that preview to offer hot and cold sectors and stocks. A selection from the most current IBD-100 will be discussed in detail as they relate to the ChapmanWave. Are commodity and oil related stocks weak links?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basil has presented his charts before at our Boston Tigers meeting (Bob Podd's regular meeting during the hour before our Wednesday meeting) and members have described the chart analysis and notations as clear and clean - within the context of higher Peaks and lower Troughs. The timeframes (using daily, weekly, and monthly charts) describe the degree of comfort and duration still to go before major Sell or Buy Signals are generated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Basil Chapman, is the host of the TFNN (Tiger Financial News Network) Tiger Technician's hour Mon-Wed-Friday at 11 am to noon, Editor of the Opening Call (a daily comprehensive newsletter giving market outlook, the day's parameters, index, stock, commodity, currency, ETFs, with recommendations), former editor of The Chapman Marketline (frequently quoted in Barron's), and the CD 'Introducing the ChapmanWave methodology' available on &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com...&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basil presented many times to the Market Technician's Association. Over the past year or two he has spoken several times at the Boston Tigers meeting. Some of you might recall that, based on his proprietary indicator, humorously called 'the stork-leg', he was one of the few bulls going into the October 2007 highs. That is when he became cautious and then bearish at the close of the last trading day of December 2007 (the Dow's close under the 9-period exponential moving average furthered the negative technical picture, especially after a doji October candle). He has used his ChapmanWave methodology to identify smaller and shorter turning points since then.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221061176000</updated><rating><average>4.28000020981</average><count>18</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>95</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214034849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Basil on Where We Are, Harlan on ETFs</name><id>8183673</id><headcount>97</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220481000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/8183673/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>