<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Bet. 10th &amp; 11th Aves.</address_2><address_1>544 West 27th Street</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10001</zip><lat>40.750847</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>CAIN LUXE</name><city>New York</city><id>866140</id><country>us</country><lon>-74.004379</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Ladies!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday January 15th is set for CAIN (www.cainnyc.com) for a fun filled night of drinking and dancing.  I will be linking up with the promoter that night (since he will be there) to set up the table and free bottle service since I want this to be a gauranteed thing (the free bottle).  It is free to get in under the guestlist, &amp;quot;Special K&amp;quot; (my alias from back in the day of event planning).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dress code is DRESS TO IMPRESS.  Basically dress like you are going to a club and not a ball game lol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address is: 544 NW 27TH STREET. NEW YORK NEW YORK (OFF 11TH AVENUE)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like us to meet at the &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Astoria Diner&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; (off of the Steinway Street Subway) at &lt;b&gt;10:00&lt;/b&gt;.  The address is: &lt;u&gt;3250 Steinway Street&lt;/u&gt;.  I am very punctual so I will be there at 10:00 p.m.  Cain gets REALLY packed and I don't want us to end up paying at the door so I want to leave by &lt;u&gt;10:15 by cab&lt;/u&gt; or train.  I know a cab service that can pick us up, therefore it would probably cost $5 or less per person to get to the club.  I figured that would be a better idea instead of freezing in the cold. If you can &lt;u&gt;NOT&lt;/u&gt; meet me at the diner and want to go at a later time, feel free to, but please let me know if you will be going alone or with the group! &lt;br /&gt;The bottle service will be free (must be set up that night) but they do require tipping.  So I figured $5 per person and I will cover the rest of the tip.  So I figured for a night out in the city it would cost under $25 (counting cost to get home).  Not bad eh?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So anyway ladies...sorry for the detailed note I just wanted to be clear on everything.  If you have any questions please email me or text/call me at: 646-408-5224&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you ladies on Friday!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263783915000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Madams</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Multicultural-Womens-Network</urlname><id>1530786</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Multicultural Women's Network (MWN): Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262621374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dancing in the City</name><id>12216214</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263610800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Multicultural-Womens-Network/events/12216214/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/7/global_10929047.jpeg</photo_url></item>