<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351844</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-439-3142 </phone><name>The NonProfit Center </name><city>Boston</city><id>1058586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057489</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$20.00 cash at the door</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Uncertain how to work towards a secure financial future while living out your values?&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for a Skillshare on Socially Responsible Investing on August 6, 6:00 - 8:30 PM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We create social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which increases our individual capacity for movement building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;bring your own dinner&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (microwave and water cooler available) &lt;br /&gt;

6:30-8:30 Training and Q &amp;amp; A &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socially Responsible Investing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
How do we manage our finances to best sustain ourselves and support our vision of a more just economy? This is a chance to learn investment basics and discuss financial management with a local progressive activist and finance professional. No prior knowledge expected: we'll start with fundamentals and definitions. Participants should come away with a more intuitive sense of how to use investments, and ideas about how to research and choose between different financial tools without checking your politics at the door. 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Joby Gelbspan&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; is a lifelong progressive activist who has dedicated her career to "translating finance for activists." She holds a Master's in Accounting and an MBA, with financial and management experience ranging from non-profit organizations to the investment management industry. She has served on several nonprofit Boards and as CFO and Financial Consultant for grassroots, progressive organizations. She currently works for Corporate Accountability International, campaigning to change the World Bank's abusive practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* &lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt; - The NonProfit Center&lt;/strong&gt; is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is accessible through the main lobby to people who have restricted physical abilities. &lt;br /&gt;

_________________________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With over 2000 members and almost 6 years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston (130+ events!), Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344462892000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341287366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Socially Responsible Investing</name><id>71752642</id><headcount>22</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344290400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/71752642/</event_url></item>