<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Providence</address_1><state>RI</state><lat>41.823990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waterfire</name><city>Providence</city><id>2956101</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.412834</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Nico from the Providence Euro Meetup Group sent me this informaiton for the 2nd Annual Christmas WaterFire benefiting the work of the Providence Rescue Mission! It is also The 2nd Annual EuroProvidence Glühwein Outdoor Christmas Party. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://waterfire.org/friday-december-14th-2012/" class="linkified"&gt;http://waterfire.org/friday-december-14th-2012/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This will not be an officially organized event, so if you want to go, contact Nico to make sure you can meetup with his group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

These are the details from Nico: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

"There is no Weihnachtsmarkt in RI, so this is as good as it gets. There will be the Glühwein/Glögg in two coffee urns. Bring your mugs and we will stay warm, European style. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In the spirit of giving and to kick off holiday festivities in Providence, WaterFire will light the fires from Waterplace basin to the Steeple Street bridge and transform Waterplace Park and the entire Waterplace basin into a winter wonderland. Festivities will commence in Waterplace Park at 5:00 p.m. Be sure not to miss the Christmas tree lighting in Waterplace basin at 6:00 p.m. immediately followed by the lighting of WaterFire. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

There will be singing of Christmas carols in various languages including German, Greek and maybe Swedish and Italian too. Let Nico know if you know any carols in a European language. Girls, bring your kids to help us sing, and help make this a family event. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I need to raise $150 by this event to keep our group on meetup.com. I am asking each member to donate $5 at this event to keep the group on meetup. Each cup of Glühwein/Glögg will be $5 on a first come, first served basis. But you must bring your own mug, I cannot supply them at Waterfire Park. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For those who have enjoyed our events in the past, this is your chance to contribute to a good group of people."﻿&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Contact Nico to find out where they will be meeting</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355534113000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354037342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Christmas Waterfire 2012</name><id>93023842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355522400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/93023842/</event_url></item>