<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Update: Note to self, when making multiple events, include the event date in the title of the meetup!  To answer questions that have been asked of me instead of just emailing everyone one by one.  Yes we will meet at Walden.  As Jameson suggested, how about we meet at the bathhouse in the parking lot at 6:30.  Please be there on time.  We want to make sure every one is out of the water before it starts to get dark.  Let's keep everyone safe.  The parking lot closes at 8 pm anyhow.  Please also wear the brightest swim cap you have, for safety's sake.  The easiest way to describe how to get there, is head on rt 2 west, and take a left onto rt 126, and the lot will be on your left.  $5 for the day, unless you have a season pass...  No biking group planned, unless you are equipped with a really good bike light, but that is not the case for yours truly.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think that addresses all the questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's plan to do a Walden Swim!  We had a good turn out for the first meet up and I am excited to go from here.  A group will meet up in the brookline/boston area to bike out to walden, and for those still sans bike carpools will be arranged, just let me know if you are in need of a ride out there and we can arrange where to meet up!  I will map out the distances and as with the run try to form 2-3 groups for those who want a longer swim and for those who are having their first open water swim.  For those that can stick around for a bit, I will try to set up some &amp;quot;swim starts&amp;quot; with groups starting close together to simulate an actual swim start with all the craziness that goes along.  We will need to keep this one on schedule as we don't want to still be swimming as it starts to get dark!  Let's keep everyone safe!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;For those of you brand new to the tri community this will be a great chance to experience some open water swimming in a friendly environment. (I sure wish I had at least practiced open water swimming before my first tri!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update with more details soon.  Please contact me if you have questions or check the site for updates.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that I am posting this event for saturday as well, if you can make both, great, if not I also want to try to gauge people's availability.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also as always, if you have suggestions for a meet up whether it be an actual training event or otherwise, let me know!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187390285000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Triathletes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Tri</urlname><id>584357</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8399963379</group_lon><name>Mass Tri</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186638021000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walden Swim 8/15</name><id>6150248</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187217000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Tri/events/6150248/</event_url></item>