<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 New Park Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.747196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>8602366677</phone><name>Bowtie Cinema</name><city>Hartford</city><id>522813</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.713264</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I thought I'd try something a little different and post two movies for the same night at the same theater.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The A-Team starts at 5:15 and ends around 7:12.  Please meet in the lobby no later than 5.&lt;br /&gt;Splice starts at 5:50 and ends around 7:34.  Please meet in the lobby not later than 5:35.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movies we can all meet for dinner and/or drinks.  A good place in the area is The Corner Pug.  (A-Team people will get there a little earlier than Splicers but hopefully will endure the wait).  If anyone wants to skip the movies and join us for dinner that's fine too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The A-Team &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A group of Iraq War veterans looks to clear their name with the U.S. military, who suspect the four men of committing a crime for which they were framed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Liam Neeson, Bradley Cooper, Jessica Biel, Quinton &amp;quot;Rampage&amp;quot; Jackson, Sharlto Copley &lt;br /&gt;Director: Joe Carnahan &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ateam-movie.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.ateam-movie.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Splice&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Superstar genetic engineers Clive (Adrien Brody) and Elsa (Sarah Polley) specialize in splicing together DNA from different animals to create incredible new hybrids. Now they want to use human DNA in a hybrid that could revolutionize science and medicine. But when the pharmaceutical company that funds their research forbids it, Clive and Elsa secretly conduct their own experiments. The result is Dren, an amazing, strangely beautiful creature that exhibits uncommon intelligence and an array of unexpected physical developments. And though, at first, Dren exceeds their wildest dreams, she begins to grow and learn at an accelerated rate--and threatens to become their worst nightmare.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Adrien Brody, Sarah Polley, Delphine Chanéac, Brandon McGibbon, Simona Maicanescu &lt;br /&gt;Director: Vincenzo Natali &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://splicethefilm.com" target="_blank"&gt;splicethefilm.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE note in your RSVP which movie you'll be attending.  Thanks &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277932220000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277500728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The A-Team and Splice and dinner</name><id>13911921</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277672400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/13911921/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/6/f/global_15959743.jpeg</photo_url></item>