<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Building 13</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.509102</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>KFIT</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>908352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.858868</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WX FOR WEDNESDAY LOOKS LIKE A BAD METAR. ANYONE AVAILABLE MONDAY?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I found a place that looked really good and not too far away (63.6 NM) for a nice flight that may include a great sunset, colorful foliage as well as dinner. The bad weather will be soon approaching so how about heading to New Bedford (KEWB) to check out their restaurant? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what I have learned.&lt;br /&gt;The new restaurant in the terminal building had a grand opening on 10/8/09-same name, expanded in size.  &lt;br /&gt;    Response from Bill Whelan, The Airport Grille&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The New Airport Grille has reopened as of October 8th, 2009. While we are about a month behind schedule, we think you'll agree it was worth the wait. Please come and enjoy our new 99-seat restaurant, featuring a 30 seat outdoor covered patio with fireplace. Fernando (the acclaimed chef from the old Grille) is back as head chef, preparing his same sought after cuisine. Renovations were extensive. Visit www.airportgrille.com for menus and pictures. The new owners also own Sandpiper Air, so if you are flying, stop in at Sandpiper and we'll take care of your aircraft and shuttle you to the Grille so you don't have to walk. See you there!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plan is we meet at the airport and group up see who is flying and who may need a ride. Departing wheels up by 5:30 sharp and return between 8-9. Sounds real good doesn't it?? &lt;br /&gt; If you want to come usually plenty of room. Please RSVP so that I can let the restaurant know how many to expect for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  So don't forget to ask your loved one or a friend to join you. Your not going to want to miss this one and don't forget that camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, if anyone has a place that they would like to go, please let one of your organizers know. We will be more than happy to add it. Always looking for fun destinations!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.airnav.com/airport/KEWB" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.airnav.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.airportgrille.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.airportgri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256766087000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256002673000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner in New Bedford, MA at The Airport Grille. DATE CHANGE</name><id>11665552</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256592600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/11665552/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/6/global_11322502.jpeg</photo_url></item>