<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 90</address_2><address_1>45 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 523 5260</phone><name>SunDo Mountain Taoist Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>489318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The body provides our most direct means of accessing profound spiritual transformation. This evening, explore the body-based practice of SunDo Taoist yoga &amp;amp; meditation, which strives to enhance the source of all life - the qi, or vital energy, circulating in the chakra centers and meridian energy channels of the body. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SunDo Taoist yoga &amp;amp; meditation practices can lead us into the universal depths of body. Whereas many meditation practices focus on third-eye or insight meditation, SunDo focuses attention on the second navel chakra for bodily health and building earth energy. By bringing life force energy into this chakra, we connect with the earth in a grounded and centered way. This energy work then provides the necessary basis for properly balancing all the other chakras.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An ancient healing system, SunDo is sometimes referred to as Taoist Alchemy. Taoists believe that, on a grand scale, the powerful energy of nature and the cosmos can be united with the smaller-scale functions of the human body. Through the postures of SunDo, we can come to know all existence and attain complete realization and fulfillment. Together, we will experience immersion in the body through breathing and meditation in the 25 basic postures of SunDo Taoist practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the workshop, SunDo instructors will work with each person in learning Taoist breathwork and meditation. This workshop is limited to just 10 people because of the one-on-one nature of the instruction. A $5 donation goes to support the work of SunDo, an organization dedicated to teaching the principles of Taoist philosopy and practice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sundo.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.sundo.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1262562449000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259715142000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Spirtuality of the Body</name><id>11994808</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260745200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/11994808/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/5/global_12058597.jpeg</photo_url></item>