<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>11012102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts State House rally for the 2nd amendment !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special guest speaker Bryan Doe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special guest speaker veteran Marine Corps officer. Boston College Graduate and 'prospective' Constitutional law student, Chris Nawoichik will be our Speaker at the Feb. 8th 2nd Right Rally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special guest Dan Bidondi INFOWARS.com Reporter will be covering the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are joining the Nationwide 2nd amendment peaceful demonstration, event listed below. NEW ENGLAND is participating! Hopefully you can represent at your state capitol too. &lt;br /&gt;

This Event because of Mayor Menino, Devil Patrick and the city of Boston Anti- Gun Views will be a [Concealed Carry] only event. Make sure you have proper licenses/registrations to take part in this event.No guns allowed on the Boston Common.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am the founder of a collective Liberty loving people who are involved many other political activity's to fight for liberty and the constitution as well. The Goal of this group is to take a stronger and more active political stance and reach out to like minded patriots who Love Liberty Freedom and the pursuit to happiness at a grassroots level. We will gather at the State house and have a peaceful protest for our 2nd amendment which is our right of Freedom of speech. We are looking for a speaker who would like to speak in front of the state house on a Mega-phone to talk about gun control and laws.. and educate the people of their rights as citizens of Massachusetts. We will also march from the state house to Faniuel Hall. Anyone who would like to participate in the march will take place at the end of the rally in front of (OUR) state house. I am open to any input from anyone.The JBS is also backing us! Important Info: it is a concealed carry event. Please do not miss out and express your civil rights. ~Nizzie&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IF you would like to be a speaker Contact Nick M aka Nizzie email @ skyrise2@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;

IF your group would like to take part in the event contact Stephen Rogerson JBS email @ stephen.rogerson@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;

Nizzie Will Cover Massachusetts. Live Free or Die&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362773837000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362340814000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massachusetts State House rally for the 2nd amendment !</name><id>107399862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362762000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/107399862/</event_url></item>