<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Hazard Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.989895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hazard Grille</name><city>Enfield</city><id>950610</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.579881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For April, we have two themed books to choose from: &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;The People of the Book&lt;/i&gt;, by Geraldine Brooks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Those Who Save Us&lt;/i&gt;, by Jenna Blum &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See reviews below to help you choose a book to read for next month's Meetup.  And remember, while reading is encouraged (we are a book club after all) come as you are, 5 pages in or 5 pages from the end - we just want your contribution to the conversation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Those Who Save Us:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blum, who worked for Steven Spielberg's Shoah Foundation, takes a direct, unsentimental look at the Holocaust in her first novel. The narrative alternates between the present-day story of Trudy, a history professor at a Minneapolis university collecting oral histories of WWII survivors (both German and Jewish), and that of her aged but once beautiful German mother, Anna, who left her country when she married an American soldier. Interspersed with Trudy's interviews with German immigrants, many of whom reveal unabashed anti-Semitism, Anna's story flashes back to her hometown of Weimar. As Nazi anti-Jewish edicts intensify in the 1930s, Anna hides her love affair with a Jewish doctor, Max Stern. When Max is interned at nearby Buchenwald and Anna's father dies, Anna, carrying Max's child, goes to live with a baker who smuggles bread to prisoners at the camp. Anna assists with the smuggling after Trudy's birth until the baker is caught and executed. Then Anna catches the eye of the Obersturmführer, a high-ranking Nazi officer at Buchenwald, who suspects her of also supplying the inmates with bread. He coerces her into a torrid, abusive affair, in which she remains complicit to ensure her survival and that of her baby daughter. Blum paints a subtle, nuanced portrait of the Obersturmführer, complicating his sordid cruelty with more delicate facets of his personality. Ultimately, present and past overlap with a shocking yet believable coincidence. Blum's spare imagery is nightmarish and intimate, imbuing familiar panoramas of Nazi atrocity with stark new power. This is a poised, hair-raising debut. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;The People of the Book:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reading Geraldine Brooks's remarkable debut novel, Year of Wonders, or more recently March, which won the Pulitzer Prize, it would be easy to forget that she grew up in Australia and worked as a journalist. Now in her dazzling new novel, People of the Book, Brooks allows both her native land and current events to play a larger role while still continuing to mine the historical material that speaks so ardently to her imagination. Late one night in the city of Sydney, Hanna Heath, a rare book conservator, gets a phone call. The Sarajevo Haggadah, which disappeared during the siege in 1992, has been found, and Hanna has been invited by the U.N. to report on its condition. Missing documents and art works (as Dan Brown and Lev Grossman, among others, have demonstrated) are endlessly appealing, and from this inviting premise Brooks spins her story in two directions. In the present, we follow the resolutely independent Hanna through her thrilling first encounter with the beautifully illustrated codex and her discovery of the tiny signs-a white hair, an insect wing, missing clasps, a drop of salt, a wine stain-that will help her to discover its provenance. Along with the book she also meets its savior, a Muslim librarian named Karaman. Their romance offers both predictable pleasures and genuine surprises, as does the other main relationship in Hanna's life: her fraught connection with her mother. In the other strand of the narrative we learn, moving backward through time, how the codex came to be lost and found, and made. From the opening section, set in Sarajevo in 1940, to the final section, set in Seville in 1480, these narratives show Brooks writing at her very best. With equal authority she depicts the struggles of a young girl to escape the Nazis, a duel of wits between an inquisitor and a rabbi living in the Venice ghetto, and a girl's passionate relationship with her mistress in a harem. Like the illustrations in the Haggadah, each of these sections transports the reader to a fully realized, vividly peopled world. And each gives a glimpse of both the long history of anti-Semitism and of the struggle of women toward the independence that Hanna, despite her mother's lectures, tends to take for granted. Brooks is too good a novelist to belabor her political messages, but her depiction of the Haggadah bringing together Jews, Christians and Muslims could not be more timely. Her gift for storytelling, happily, is timeless. Copyright 2007 Publishers Weekly. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272665240000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268587987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Meetup - People of the Book and Those Who Save Us</name><id>12873570</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272492000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/12873570/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/9/global_14037129.jpeg</photo_url></item>