<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Johnson  Athletics Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358627</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT</name><city>Boston</city><id>1153736</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096481</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Looking for a job experience abroad? Thinking of studying in Europe, or pursuing your professional career on the other side of the ocean? Then this is for you: we cordially invite you to join us at the 14th European Career Fair at MIT. Discover the many opportunities that international companies, academic institutions and non-profit organizations of the “Old Continent” have to offer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 14th European Career Fair in short&lt;br /&gt;· January 29, 2010 - Panel discussions and workshops hosted by the European Commission.&lt;br /&gt;· January 30, 2010 - Career Fair Day with exhibits and presentations by representatives from industry, academia and research.&lt;br /&gt;· January 31 – February 1, 2010 - Interviews for selected candidates. ECF-affiliated seminars on career development, opportunities and other activities!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Why should I attend?&lt;br /&gt;· ECF is the largest career fair of its kind in the US with more than 100 companies and over 3000 participants.&lt;br /&gt;· ECF aims to represent the full breadth of the European job market. Whether you are looking for a job in industry or in the non-profit sector.&lt;br /&gt;· ECF welcomes candidates from all backgrounds and all levels of experience.&lt;br /&gt;· Our searchable database allows employers to view your resume, and schedule interviews with selected candidates.&lt;br /&gt;· In addition, you will have the opportunity to connect with many employers on the day of the Fair!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information visit our website at www.euro-career.com!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a map of MIT with the locations of the career fair: &lt;a href="https://www.euro-career.com/webfiles/campusmap2009.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.euro-care...&lt;/a&gt;.  If you have any questions about the fair, you can contact Catherine at cjchomat@yahoo.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm posting this as an event even though I'm not going to be able to be there. I thought there might be members interested in going.  So we will not be meeting at the fair as a group.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264946799000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262744910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MIT European Career Fair</name><id>12235534</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264773600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/12235534/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/2/3/global_7135059.jpeg</photo_url></item>