<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Beginner Spring Hiking Program 2011&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Five Night Instructional Course - April 19th and 26th. May 3rd, 10th, and 17th.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new to hiking and backpacking the annual Spring Hiking Program being offered by the AMC’s Boston Chapter provides an excellent introduction.  I have helped coordinate trips associated with this program in the past and we will be offering some beginner hiking and backpacking trips for those Randomites that successfully complete the program – be sure to check back to see what we add to the calendar.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;IMPORTANT: Please RSVP here if you plan to participate (this will help me keep track of who is going from our group) but in order to officially register you need to register online at &lt;a href="http://www.hbbostonamc.org/registrationSystem/eventRegistration.php?event_id=63" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hbbostonam...&lt;/a&gt; You will need to create an AMC online account if you do not have one. For registration questions please email Abby Driscoll at atdriscoll@gmail.com.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This interactive course consists of 5 instructional sessions to introduce the basics of spring, summer and fall day hiking and backpacking in New England.  The program includes a series of lectures and demonstrations at AMC’s Cabot Hall on the dates listed above as well as guided hikes during May and June weekends designed to increase and facilitate the safe enjoyment of the outdoors.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The instruction topics on each Tuesday evening are different and include: clothing, heat and energy management, nutrition, footwear, heat injuries/hypothermia, choosing the right gear, backcountry stewardship, physical conditioning, accident prevention, map and compass skills, weather hazards, sleeping bags, tents, and more!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day Hiking topics will be covered the first three evenings and Backpacking topics on the fifth with a mix of subjects on the fourth evening.  A comprehensive course manual and the current AMC White Mountain Guide Book will be included.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program runs on five Tuesday nights from 7:00 PM - 9:00 PM.  The program takes place at AMC Cabot Auditorium located at 4 Joy Street in Boston, MA.  It's near the Park Street T Station, the Massachusetts State House and the Boston Common.  Discount parking passes are available for the Boston Common Garage.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost is $45 if you are an AMC member and $50 for non-members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have general questions about the program, please contact the organizer Robert Knudsen at springhiking@hbbostonamc.org or the registrar Abby Driscoll at atdriscoll@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305073238000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295751377000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginner Spring Hiking Program (Class 4 of 5)</name><id>16149275</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305068400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/16149275/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/7/global_20974039.jpeg</photo_url></item>