<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Okay guys, straight from the new polls (thanks for all who voted!), our next book has been chosen:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Geographer's Library by Jon Fasman&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Excerpts copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/cgi-bin/biblio?isbn=1594200386" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publisher Comments:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;In this brilliant debut, competing visions of an obscure professor's life take a young reporter from a sleepy New England town to the heart of an international smuggling ring that may hold the secret to eternal life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;When a twelfth-century Sicilian cat burglar snatches a sack of artifacts from the king's geographer's library, the tools and talismans of transmutation — and eternal life — are soon scattered all over the world. Nine hundred years later, a young Connecticut reporter finds evidence that someone is collecting them again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;In the process of investigating the suspicious death of a local professor, Paul Tomm finds the dead man's heavily fortified office stuffed with books on alchemy. The Geographer's Library entwines his contemporary reporting with a chain of ancient stories-within-the-story, tracking the last time each of the geographer's tools changed hands — some bought, some stolen, some killed for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Geographer's Library is an extraordinary debut, smart, stylishly written, and full of suspense. It tempts with the glitter of antiquities and hooks with a chilling plot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My work schedule got really screwy for May (sorry), so we've got a lot of time to read this one.  We may have only three weeks for the next one, so get your votes in as I'll try to post it soon (probably happening the first week of June).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, we're totally breaking our mold and meeting on a Tuesday.  If chaos abounds at CCC, and you don't see me, or the book even a little after 7, head across the street to Au Bon Pain 1100 Mass Ave, and look for us there.   Or heck, maybe we'll even be able to make it outside if the weather cooperates.  Will keep you posted, and try to remember to send out my cell # a few days prior to those attending.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for book on the table and, well, me</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242651587000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237996396000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers--The Geographer's Library</name><id>10032860</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242169200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/10032860/</event_url></item>