<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come help support a great community event and have fun too! Volunteer at Project Smile's 4th Annual Halloween and Child Safety Extravaganza on Saturday, October 25, 11:00am-3:30pm (event runs from 12-3pm) at 1023 Southbridge Street, Worcester. Indoor event. This event features safe and fun Halloween activities for Worcester area children and valuable safety information for kids and parents. Last year, over 850 children and parents attended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the event, children will enjoy pumpkin decorating, free candy, games/activities, costume contest, face painting. Safety participants include the Worcester Police, Worcester Fire, Worcester County Sheriff's Department, AAA, Worcester Sharks and more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Volunteers will be staffing registration tables, helping distribute candy, helping with games/activities, face painting and helping with light clean up after the event (removing decorations, stacking chairs, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Volunteers must be able to move around easily and stand for periods of time. Pizza/soda will be available. Must enjoy busy environment with lots of children and families. Halloween costumes are optional, but encouraged. Perfect volunteering activity for groups of friends!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo). Call 774 232 0000 if have trouble finding me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225120160000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223417126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer Opportunity Project Smile Halloween and Child Safety Event</name><id>8917721</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224946800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/8917721/</event_url></item>