<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Imani &amp;amp; John Zito, owners of Alchemy Cafe and the Growing Green Wellness Center lead a free discussion on the benefits of membership in the Green Vibration Collective:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALCHEMY CAFÉ &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An all organic café offering food preparation classes, nutritional lectures &amp;amp; weekly food deliveries. As a member, you earn a 10% discount on all food purchases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GROWING GREEN WELLNESS CENTER &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A community space with ongoing fitness classes, healing arts services, free films &amp;amp; community events. Members get discounted prices on family services, fitness classes, use of the infrared sauna and healing sessions. Plus free films, potluck dinners and seasonal celebrations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GREEN BUSINESS ASSOCIATION &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A network of local, green businesses that supply sustainable services and products to the community. Membership options available for discounted advertising and coupons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Green Vibration Collective is a unique business sustained by members to help meet common needs for a healthy community. The strength and commitment of our membership is vital in helping us achieve our goals. So instead of blindly chasing profits like businesses controlled by shareholders, we are able to steer our business in a more responsible direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We offer everything from food and detox treatments to fitness, gardening and family-friendly events. Our principles of sustainability and natural wellness influence all of these services, which in turn reflect quality and value, honesty and social responsibility. Membership is open to everyone who shares these principles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members show these values by working together for everyone’s benefit, and are encouraged to play a part in our community. Join us on January 5 to learn more about how you can help us continue to focus on providing healthy solutions for our community and working to preserve our environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262909456000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260726416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vision for Growing Green: The Benefits of Membership</name><id>12075990</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262736000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12075990/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/c/5/global_12287061.jpeg</photo_url></item>