<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>72 Commercial St.</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.657610</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Flatbread Pizza Company</name><city>Portland</city><id>130102</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.250145</lon></venue><fee><label>Meal Contribution</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person (if eating)</description><amount>6.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Because I haven't come up with a nice catchy holiday-related theme for this month's meeting (it's just a little too long after St. Patrick's Day to hook into the drink-too-much-green-beer theme), and because we haven't talked about the club itself for a while, let's just have a Plain Old Working Meeting, plus food to help keep it sociable. I've moved the time up a bit so it can be over supper. Please be prepared to contribute to a couple of flatbread pizzas for the group (I've suggested $6, if you are eating), and help us set the direction of the group over the next year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AGENDA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   * Plan Next 6 Months of Meeting Topics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   With warm weather approaching, the more general-purpose topics such as Beginning Bike Commuting, Basic Repair, and Traffic Safety will once again become more topical, as more people than just us winter diehards begin taking to the streets again. This seems a good time to think about what topics will be of interest to people throughout the spring and summer, and schedule them now. Think about what other topics YOU would like to see. (I'll print out that message thread and bring it with me.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   * Outreach and Support&lt;br /&gt;   (or, Group Promotion and Publicity)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   With the ever-increasing awareness of global climate change, and ever the potential for another drastic rise in gasoline prices, I'm predicting warm weather will bring a sharp increase in the number of people trying bike commuting for the first time, or thinking about it. I want to brainstorm and plan what we can do to reach these people with the safety and practical information they need to know, support them as they experiment, and include them in our social events if they so desire. Also of course we still want to attract those who already bike commute and desire the companionship of other kindred spirits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   * Other Advocacy and Education&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   We've talked off and on about what other advocacy and education we'd like to do, such as education among harder to reach non-club adults, giveaways of safety equipment and information, fund-raising for local programs, and so on. Let's get serious about if we want to do something like that this year, and if so, what. We might also to do something with established advocacy events, such as Commute Another Way Day or Bike to Work Month/Week/Day.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Brooking</member_name><member_id>2040136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174687811000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bike Commuters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Bike-Commuting</urlname><id>225788</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Bicycle Commuting</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172146288000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Planning Meeting</name><id>5503705</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174514400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Bike-Commuting/events/5503705/</event_url></item>