<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We have an open mike &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;OPEN MIKE on Wednesday Nites from 7PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; until around 10PM near the Galleria Mall in East Cambridge.  This is a great opportunity to further your music experience and career, jam with other musicians, play solo, play originals, and network.  The goal is to have everyone play as much as possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At present, this is more of a soft rock/folk singer songwriter, acoustic and soft electric open mike.  The sign up procedure is basically &lt;b&gt;RSVPing for this meetup, answer the questions if possible&lt;/b&gt; and then sign in when you arrive.  It's important to note what time you plan to arrive for scheduling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone who would like accompanyment please &lt;b&gt;submit 3 to 5 songs&lt;/b&gt; that you would like to play in order of priority, in the questions.   If you would like to rehearse the songs with the group RSVP for and come to the &lt;b&gt;jam/rehearsal meetup the Sunday prior to the Open MIke&lt;/b&gt;.  If you can bring song sheets for your songs on one page that will facilitate playing.  If you are playing at semi-professional level and are playing solo or don't need to rehearse, just come to the open mike.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm setting up an online group song repository spreadsheet for suggestions and voting, for the regular players.  Then we can determine the songs everyone likes most &amp;amp; focus on them for live performance.  If more performers are needed, we will be contacting wider musician networks, but the focus now is to develop a group of regulars from our meetup.&lt;br /&gt;If you want to be play with acconpanying bass /lead/harmony try to come early at 7PM and bring about 4 copies of 2 or 3 songs you want to play on 1 sheet per song if possible, so we can all play it.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275524315000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274920037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Music Guild Open  Mike!</name><id>cscqnynjbdb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275519600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/13607881/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>