<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Career Transformations: Capitalizing On Your Transferable Skills&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, February 9, 2011&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca's Cafe, Newton, MA&lt;br /&gt;Registration and Reception: 5:00 pm; Program: 6:15 pm; &lt;br /&gt;Post Program Informal Networking: 8:15 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several years into this generation's Great Recession, the biopharmaceutical industry is feeling the ramifications. With mergers, acquisitions, corporate financial challenges and global competition, industry professionals find themselves in transition and/or wondering about their careers. For many it's not just about getting another job; it includes taking into account personal interests, ambitions and how to leverage the valuable skills that they have honed in the industry. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an interactive discussion with audience participation, and includes two panels, each having a professional Career Coach/Counselor and several professionals: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panel #1: Entrepreneurs/small business owners who have departed from traditional employment to pursue entrepreneurial ventures or have become business owners &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panel #2: Professionals who have leveraged their skills and career experience to work in a different function or industry The Coaches will impart their specialized, professional expertise and speak about the soft skills, planning processes, personality profiles and values typically required for success. Our distinguished professionals who have chosen these paths will discuss their success stories. You will hear about: Professional career expertise, Secrets to successful transitions, Managing emotions and risks, Alternative careers and target companies, When to use professional guidance Sources of assistance and information, Transferable skills and experience, Questions to ask yourself, factors to consider &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will gain valuable insight to help you &amp;quot;think outside the box&amp;quot; and consider alternatives, including &amp;quot;taking the plunge&amp;quot; and becoming your own boss, or running a business. Register early as we expect this program to fill up quickly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ispeboston.org/files/ispe_february_9%2C_2011_program.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ispeboston...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297293088000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295580639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Career Transformations: Capitalizing On Your Transferable Skills</name><id>16128139</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297288800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/16128139/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>