<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be joining with another group to discus the importance of restoring our original organic Merkaba energy flows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How these flows should be running (direction and speed), and why this information is VITAL to restore wellness on all levels requires an understanding of our multi-dimensional nature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To facilitate understanding, attendees should first take the time to view 3 free on-line video presentations via this link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.krystalspi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total viewing time is approximately 6 hours.  Since detailed diagrams are presented, it is recommended that this information be viewed a little at a time while taking notes of questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people find it helpful to view the entire presentation several times, since detailed information is explained. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A live presentation will be given at this Meetup, describing various types of Merkaba energy flows and Merkaba vehicles. Details of this copyrited information can be purchased at www.azuritepress.com. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members are invited to visit that website frequently, since it contains a wealth of useful information, including &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;FREE  ENERGY HEALING TECHNIQUES!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The presentation will be followed by a discussion period where members can ask questions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get the most out of  this Meetup, don't forget to first  take the time to view all 3 parts of the video presentation referenced above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This free NH meetup is just 3 miles from exit 22 of I-93, approximately 30 minutes from Concord, Laconia, or Plymouth.  After joining the group, you will be able to access the directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since space is limited, it is important to RSVP early.   The Meetup adjourns at 9:00 PM. Please bring your own refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go up driveway with Meetup sign at the end, NOT the driveway  with ULCS Clinic sign.  Front entrance has another Meetup sign. Don't knock. Just go on downstairs and have a seat in the classroom.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289960694000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Awakening Indigoes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>IndigoInsights</urlname><id>1319438</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Indigo Insights: Awakening to our Full Potential</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280936316000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Merkaba Mechanics and Self-Help Energy Techniques VITAL to complete by Dec. 2012</name><id>pdxpnynpbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289948400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/IndigoInsights/events/14316992/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/1/global_18743441.jpeg</photo_url></item>