<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;CT REIA and Alan Cowgill presents: Unlimited Supply of Money For Residential and Commercial Properties&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://www.ctreia.com/res/upload/pix_events/0/0/0/0/4/451.jpg" alt="Alan Cowgill" width="107" height="107" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;August 15, 2011 &amp;ndash; 5:30 to 9:00 PM
 &lt;br /&gt; Crowne Plaza Hotel. 100 Berlin Road. Cromwell, CT
 &lt;br /&gt; FREE for CTREIA and AOACT members | $30 for guests&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=356"&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;Click Here to learn more and register&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Could You Use An Unlimited Supply Of Money To Do All The Residential And Commercial Deals You Can Find?&lt;/strong&gt; At the August 2011 Monthly Meeting, Alan Cowgill will show you how you can get all the money you need to buy single-family houses, commercial buildings, apartment complexes, or luxury homes, regardless of your credit or financial situation&amp;hellip; within 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;What You Will Learn&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* How to get all the money you need to buy single-family houses, commercial buildings, apartment complexes, or luxury homes, regardless of your credit or financial situation&amp;hellip; within 30 days
 &lt;br /&gt; * Crucial 5 steps to success, so that you can find all the private money you need: Build Credibility, Generate Leads, Secure Private Lenders, Buy/Sell Property, Pay Day
 &lt;br /&gt; * How to pre-screen your prospects and the &amp;ldquo;Magic&amp;rdquo; words to get them to commit
 &lt;br /&gt; * Scripts you should use when talking to people you know, their voicemails, and/or referrals
 &lt;br /&gt; * Why these 4 commonly used types of financing can cripple your real estate business and how to stay away from them: Bank, Line of credit, Hard money lender, Creative financing
 &lt;br /&gt; * How to do all of this with no monthly payments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30 &amp;ndash; Meet the Businesses Who Can Support Your Business
 &lt;br /&gt; 5:45 &amp;ndash; Early Bird Workshop: Speed Networking
 &lt;br /&gt; Someone in this room could be worth $1000, $5000, or more to you. Make the right connection with someone who could lead you to a deal, a contractor, or referral. Bring plenty of business cards and be prepared to share what you are looking for.
 &lt;br /&gt; 6:45 &amp;ndash; Deal Making and Raffle. Hear the hot deals our members are selling. Plus participate in our raffle.
 &lt;br /&gt; 7:00 &amp;ndash; Alan Cowgill. Get the money you need to buy commercial and residential properties, regardless of your credit or financial situation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313448738000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311693853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA Monthly Meeting with Alan Cowgill - Money For Investment Properties</name><id>27086221</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313443800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/27086221/</event_url></item>