<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>220 SOUTHWOOD DRIVE</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.788746</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>COURTYARD BY MARRIOTT</name><city>NASHUA</city><id>1547095</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.501862</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NOTE: If you plan on attending this event, as an organizer of this group, I am asking you to please buy a ticket for and bring along at least one undecided voter. Local media from Ron's last stop in Nashua inferred that only his supporters, and not the general public, showed up to hear him speak. &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=288653247814214" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; Nashua Chamber to Host Congressman Ron Paul ... The Greater Nashua Chamber of Commerce, in partnership with Citizens Bank, is pleased to announce the first installment of the 2011 Fall &amp;quot;Backstage Pass&amp;quot; Breakfast Series with guest speaker and presidential candidate, Congressman Ron Paul of Texas. Space is limited, so register quickly! The Citizens Bank Fall &amp;quot;Backstage Pass&amp;quot; Breakfast Series, now celebrating its fourth year, is a unique program that allows business leaders in southern NH to explore current issues with experts connected to those issues. In keeping with that mission, the 2011 Fall series will feature the top three candidates for the GOP presidential nomination, starting with Congressman Paul on October 28th and continuing in November and December with Governor Mitt Romney and Governor Rick Perry. Breakfast dates for Gov. Romney and Gov. Perry will be announced in the coming days. Please join us on October 28th for the first installment of this unique series brought to you in partnership with Citizens Bank, featuring Congressman Paul. Attendees will have an opportunity to engage directly with Congressman Paul on issues important to the business community - the nation's economy, its business competitiveness, federal regulations, labor/workforce issues, etc. &lt;a href="http://events.nashuachamber.com/sbaweb/events/events.asp?calewhere=cale.eventdiv&amp;lt;&amp;gt;" target="_blank"&gt;http://events.nashuac...&lt;/a&gt;'div003'&amp;amp;details=true&amp;amp;cale_id=232&amp;amp;month=10/5/2011&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320179607000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317847429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Paul at "Backstage Pass" Breakfast Series in Nashua</name><id>36299542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319801400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/36299542/</event_url></item>