<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>200.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ADVANCED GOLF with LEGENDARY GOLF CHAMPION MIKE COLANDRO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR EXPERIENCED GOLFERS ONLY&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED GOLF with Legendary Golf Champion gives you a once in a lifetime opportunity to play Golf with and learn from Golf Champion Mike Colandro- and benefit from his years of experience to help you improve your Golfing knowledge and skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED Golf starts out Tuesday at the Driving Range with Short Irons for an unique Golf Lesson that with help you to play better Golf. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next lesson is Thursday at the Driving Range with Fairway Woods&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The third lesson is Tuesday covering Putting and Chipping to make you a great Golfer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday is used as a rain date in case of any bad weather in the first 3 lesson dates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY gives you personalized Playing Lessons out on this beautiful 9 hole Golf Course located in Windsor CT Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LESSONS ARE HELD at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tradition Golf Club At Windsor&lt;br /&gt;147 Pigeon Hill Rd &lt;br /&gt;Windsor, CT 06095&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TUES 6:30 -7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Driving Range -Short Irons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THURS 6:30 -7:30 pm Driving Range &lt;br /&gt;Fairway Woods and Drivers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TUES 6:30 -7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Putting and Chipping &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THURS 6:30 -7:30pm &lt;br /&gt;RAIN DATE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY 4-7 pm &lt;br /&gt;9 holes Playing Lesson&lt;br /&gt;7 pm - AFTERPARTY with Mike Colandro and PRIZES from Titleist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Mike Colandro after the Playing Lessons for more Golf Tips, Golf Stories, PRIZES from Titleist, and a great time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE- Class Size Is Limited To 6 People And Will Fill Up Quickly -Reserve Your Spot Today&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Play Golf with Mike Colandro while he teaches you the skills that he used to win Championships in Australia and New Zealand. ADVANCED GOLF with Mike Colandro is a very unique opportunity to learn from and play Golf with a Golf Legend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your 6 hours of Golf Lessons include Driving Range -Short Irons, Fairway Woods and Drivers, Putting and Chipping, and 9 holes of Playing Lessons out on the Golf Course. Class size is 6 people - that guarantees you personal attention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Mike after the Playing Lessons for an after party to ask questions and talk Golf - Plus PRIZES from Titleist &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCED GOLF - $200 for 6 Hours of hands-on Golf Lessons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class Size is limited to 6 people to ensure personal attention&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GIVE DAD THE GIFT HE WILL REMEMBER FOREVER – A ONCE IN A LIFETIME PERSONAL GOLF LESSON WITH GOLF CHAMPION MIKE COLANDRO!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out Golf Video Lessons with Mike Colandro on &lt;a href="http://www.CTGolfTips.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTGolfTips...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.AdvancedGolfCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.AdvancedGo...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449 for info&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Mike Colandro at the clubhouse</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>CTGolfTips.com</member_name><member_id>7047572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276645154000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274808840000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ADVANCED GOLF with LEGENDARY GOLF CHAMPION MIKE COLANDRO*FOR EXPERIENCED GOLFERS</name><id>plnrnynjbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276641000000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/13591164/</event_url></item>