<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pine Orchard Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02814</zip><lat>41.908974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sprague Farm</name><city>Glocester</city><id>13463102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.702507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before signing up for this event, Please read the entire Write Up and understand and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Event Rating:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 3 Miles &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Time Duration:&lt;/strong&gt; ~1.25 Hours &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Blaze Orange:&lt;/strong&gt; not required &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sprague Farm is hike #24 in Ken Weber’s book, “Weekend Walks in Rhode Island. The Glocester Land Trust, in cooperation with the Rhode Island DEM, administers Sprague Farm. The distance we will be hiking is about 3 miles, hiking the main loop trail featured in Weber's book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/5/a/event_236387962.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Sprague Farm was a working farm many years ago, but now it is mostly woodlands. There are foundations left from those early farms, and stone bridges also remain that cross the streams in several places on the property. The terrain is mostly flat, with some mild hills. We will be walking on old farm roads. There may be some wet spots, and there is an easy stream crossing so boots are recommended. As always, bring water and snacks for the hike. We will be hiking at a moderate pace, not an easy pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; From the Providence area, take Route 44 West, passing through the village of Chepachet. About two miles west of Chepachet, take a left on Pine Orchard Road. You will pass by a sign for Sprague Farm with a small turn-in area before reaching the parking lot that we will use. You will travel slightly under one mile on Pine Orchard Road, before coming to the parking lot on your right for Sprague Farm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver:&lt;/strong&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety First!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John H.</member_name><member_id>14299089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369063363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368670018000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sprague Farm (Ken Weber Hike #24)</name><id>119630862</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368981000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/119630862/</event_url></item>