<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Wander among crop fields and livestock pastures, wetlands and forest, at America’s oldest, continuously operating farm. A gift of Colonel Francis R. Appleton, Jr., and his wife Joan, Appleton Farms is one of the oldest continuously operating farms in the country, established and maintained by nine generations of the Appleton family. Six miles of footpaths, bridle paths, farm roads and wooded trails, some of which are part of the Bay Circuit Trail crisscross the farm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After visiting Appleton Farms, I now understand why so many of you have fallen in love with this place!&lt;br /&gt;Appleton Farms is a whopping 698 acres and the Grass Rides encompass 255 acres.  If you're a bird lover like me, grasslands here harbor one of New England’s largest populations of bobolinks and meadowlarks. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;I would strongly recommend stopping to use the restroom before your arrival as they are located a little less than a mile from the parking area in the Carriage Barn in the Farmstead&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a gentle-paced 1.5 to 2 hour walk through pasture land and wooded carriage paths, with turn back points for those who want a shorter walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: &lt;b&gt;We will meet in the parking lot located on &lt;u&gt;Highland Street&lt;/u&gt; and and hit the trail at &lt;u&gt;10:10 AM&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;  The reason I am scheduling a smaller group is that the &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;parking lot only holds 20 cars&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  If any of you want to car pool, that would be quite helpful.  Unfortunately, dogs are not allowed here.  I am asking that you vote on a picnic or lunch in town after the walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;It's usually based on an honor system, but members of the trustees of reservations are free whereas nonmembers pay $3&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions are below: But you should probably use Google or MapQuest also to get a better sense of it. The parking area is close to the intersection of Highland and Goodhue Street in Hamilton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: &lt;br /&gt;Highland St. parking area:Take I-95 North to Rte 128 North to Rte 1A North (exit 20A).  Travel about 4.5 mi. north on Rt. 1A and turn left onto Cutler Rd. Follow for 2.2 mi. At intersection with Highland St., turn right, and right again into parking area (20 cars) that also serves Appleton Farms Grass Rides. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: &lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 South to exit 54 for MA-133 toward Georgetown/Rowley Follow Rte 133 to Rte 1A South. After about 2.2 miles start to look for the VERY SMALL Appleton Farms sign on your Right Turn Right onto Waldingfield Rd.   Follow for about 3/4 of a mile and take the left fork onto Goodhue Street.  Follow for about 1/2 mile and then turn left onto Highland Street.  The parking area is about 1,000 feet up on the left.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot and have meetup stickers on</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>13</waitlist_count><updated>1275231378000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273808671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Appleton Farms and Grass Rides Hike and Picnic</name><id>13480121</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274536800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13480121/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/a/global_11174170.jpeg</photo_url></item>