<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;IMPORTANT UPDATE: &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt; On 01/07, I e-mailed details and better directions to everyone who RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;maybe.&amp;quot; (Look for a message with a subject line that says &amp;quot;ooops&amp;quot; because I accidentally sent an incomplete version first.) Let me know if you didn't receive this message and I'll e-mail it again. I didn't post it here because it has my cell-phone number, which I don't want to put on a public Web site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SITE VISITORS (NONMEMBERS):&lt;/b&gt; Please note that this event isn't open to the general public. Only members of the ATC+ Meetup Group who have RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; for themselves (and if applicable, for their personal guests) may attend. But we warmly welcome new members, so if you'd like to attend our Meetups, just join our Meetup group (signup is free and easy). Then RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to attend the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ATC+ MEMBERS: Please keep your RSVPs updated! &lt;/b&gt; Please do this right up to the morning of the event. That way, we know how many -- and who -- to expect. If you've been closed out of the event (i.e., if you can't RSVP because the site says it's full), keep checking back right up to Meetup day--people's plans change and slots are likely to open up.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LOCATION:&lt;/b&gt; I suggest doing a Mapquest, but the venue is just off the westbound side of Route 9 at the Wellesley/Natick line. There's a traffic light at the intersection, which is also well-marked. I've included more specific details in the 01/07 e-mail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Sunday, January 13, from 10 a.m. to 5 p.m.  Note: The store usually opens at noon on Sunday, but the owner has graciously offered to open two hours earlier for our group. So it would be *great* if some of you could join me there at 10 a.m. (There's a Dunkin' Donuts right nearby if you need caffeine and/or sugar to jump-start your creativity.) We need to be out by 5 p.m. sharp. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEALS:&lt;/b&gt; As always, bring your own beverages and snacks. Lunch will be on your own; feel free to brown-bag it or plan to pick up something nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WEATHER:&lt;/b&gt; If the store is closed due to bad weather, we'll have to postpone. If the store is open but travel is treacherous, we'll decide what to do either Saturday night or very early Sunday morning. Either way, the information will be posted on the Web site and e-mailed to you, so check both the site and your inboxes for updates. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WONDERING WHAT TO BRING? &lt;/b&gt; See &amp;quot;ATC Meetups--What to Bring.&amp;quot; Go to the left-hand navigation bar, click on &amp;quot;Files&amp;quot; and look for a document with the suggested checklist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a blonde of a certain age, probably wearing a name tag and possibly wearing a black apron over a red shirt. Or just yell, "Who's Anne?"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200409799000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><why>This fast-growing group is enthusiastic, friendly, generous and, above all, highly creative and talented. We're serious about making art -- but we also have a LOT of fun.</why><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192839863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Meetup of 2008 is on in Wellesley!</name><id>6582432</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200236400000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/6582432/</event_url></item>