<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Chestnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.519805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hamilton Hall</name><city>Salem</city><id>1160330</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.899239</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;2.1.10 UPDATE: We are changing the meetup time for this event to 6:30 (which is when the doors open) I checked their website today and they are saying that it would be best to get your ticket ahead of time, because last year it sold out.  If you are able to get to the Chamber of Commerce in Salem then you can buy your ticket there.  Or you can call ahead of time and give them a credit card and they will hold your ticket at the desk.  The Chambers address is: 265 Essex Street, Suite 101, Salem MA 01970, business hours are from 9am-5pm and their phone # is: 978-744-0004.  Seeing that we are now changing the meetup time we will try to be in the hallway near the bottom of the stairs.  Not sure if we will be in the way there, and we will only wait 15 minutes for everyone to show up, if we are not down stairs then come up the stairs and look around for us. OR you can still buy your ticket at the door. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This luscious tasting event, now in its seventh year, features wine, chocolate and coffee samplings. Last year participants included Captain Dusty’s, Capt.’s Waterfront Grill, Coffee Time Bake Shop, FINZ, Seafood &amp;amp; Grill, Harbor Sweets, Maria’s Sweet Somethings, Nathaniel’s, New Civilitea, Pamplemousse, Rockafellas, Rose Medallion, Salem Wine Imports, Salem Waterfront Hotel, Sophie’s Sweet Shop, Strega Restaurant &amp;amp; Lounge, Victoria Station, Ye Olde Pepper Co., just to name a few. Samples include unusual and unexpected chocolate items. Tickets are $20.00 and can be purchased in advance at the Salem Chamber of Commerce or at the door on the night of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did this event last year with another Meetup group, and it was a lot of fun, tasting all the wine &amp;amp; chocolates it is surprisingly interesting the different recipes the vendors will put the chocolate, in and on.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; There is no dedicated lot for the Hamilton Hall but you can park anywhere on Chestnut Street or any of the surrounding Streets.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the bottom of the stairs near where your buy you ticket.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265585916000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263340534000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Do you like chocolate and or wine?  Let’s go to Salem’s So Sweet event.</name><id>12302947</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265412600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12302947/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/1/global_12604353.jpeg</photo_url></item>