<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Farmington River Watershed Association is excited to once again collaborate with REI West Hartford to host the 2nd Annual Wild and Scenic Environmental Film Festival in Hartford. This tour consists of a selection of films from the annual Wild and Scenic Environmental Film Festival that aims to inspire and motivate people to go out and make a difference in their community and around the world on a variety of environmental issues to help protect our natural resources and wild places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All proceeds of the Hartford Wild and Scenic Environmental Film Festival will benefit the Farmington River Watershed Association and the Park River Revitalization Initiative. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Advance tickets can be purchased at &lt;a href="http://ent.groundspring.org/EmailNow/pub.php?module=URLTracker&amp;amp;cmd=track&amp;amp;j=298198874&amp;amp;u=3313138" target="_blank"&gt;REI West Hartford &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(860)233-2211 at 71 Raymond Road, West Hartford, CT, 06107 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN:    November 14th, 2009 at 2:30 - 6 pm. Doors open at 2pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE:  Cinestudio @ Trinity College - 300 Summit St., Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets $12 in advance at REI, $20 the day of screening at Cinestudio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wild &amp;amp; Scenic Film Festival Program&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;180° SOUTH – 3:42 min. Woodshed Films This is a trailer for the Summer 2009 release of the film, &amp;quot;180° SOUTH.&amp;quot; It is a new film told through the eyes of climber/surfer/writer Jeff Johnson during a 6-month voyage to South America to climb a mythical peak called Corcovado. The film delves deep into the roots of climbing, surfing and the environmental movement's most prolific renegades in the hope of finding a new generation's compass in an over-populated, techno-industrial society. Johnson's gritty story telling conveys a unique voice for environmentalism based on experience rather than pie charts and idealism. His cynical humor and humble approach belie his status as a bone fide underground legend. www.woodshedfilms.com, www.180south.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Litterball – 1 min. Josh Murphy A short film that illustrates the power of vision. If we all wore rose colored glasses, our positive outlook could change the world. Solutions are as easy as changing perspective. (US, 2008, 1min) www.upproductions.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paradise Found: The Phoenix Islands – 20 min. Kate Raisz In a remote corner of the Pacific, the nation of Kiribati has created the world's largest marine reserve, the Phoenix Islands Protected Area. The reserve covers 410,500 square kilometers and is home to thriving coral reefs and abundant sea life, including sharks and manta rays. The film follows scientific expeditions to these islands and the efforts of the people of Kiribati and the international environmental community to create the reserve. (US, 20min, 2005) www.neaq.org, www.phoenixislands.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crossroad at the Columbia: Oregon Confronts America’s Energy Future - 16 min. Spence Palermo, Donna Quinn Controversial Liquified Natural Gas (LNG) receiving terminals are proposed for the lower Columbia River near the historic town of Astoria, Oregon. The passion and power of grass roots activism set against the backdrop of the beauty, heritage and history of the Columbia Pacific Region make this a compelling story of America at the crossroads of fossil fuel dependence, renewable energy and decisions over who controls our and, air, water and economy. (US, 2008, 16min) www.intercultutralimages.com, wwwcolumbiariverkeeper.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Division Street – 49 minutes Eric Bandick This is not your father’s road trip. Roads and cars have fragmented wild landscapes, ushered in urban sprawl, and challenged some of the bedrock values we once took for granted. But as the transportation crisis appears to be spiraling out of control, a new generation of ecologists, engineers, city-planners, and everyday citizens are transforming the future of the American road. From pristine roadless areas to concrete jungles, follow filmmaker Eric as he tours North America, dodging Yellowstone’s grizzlies and Miami’s taxicabs, and highlighting sustainable road projects and wildlife corridors for the 21st century. (US/CANADA, 2008, 49min) www.divisionstreetmovie.com, www.transalt.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;30 minute INTERMISSION (to socialize with area adventurers)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Handcut – 27 min. Nick Waggoner From the hand-fired railroad days in Revelstoke to the miners of Colorado's San Juan Mountains, this classic-style ski film blends old-timer wisdom with self-propelled, big mountain, lines from Alaska, British Columbia, and Colorado. Follow endless pillow lines in the BC interior, exposed descents in the Coast Range, and enjoy the original deep-country blues of John-Alex Mason. (US, 2008, 27min.) www.sweetgrass-productions.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Roadless is More: Taking Care of Our National Forests – 2:22 min. Adam Cramer, Tom O’Keefe, Nat Lopes Backcountry areas that remain road-free provide a host of ecosystem services, such as clean drinking water and a refuge for many imperiled species. They also contain extremely high value recreational opportunities. Now, more than ever, these wild, backcountry areas need the help of those who enjoy them most-outdoor recreation enthusiasts. (US, 2008, 2:22min) www.outdooralliance.net, www.hilride.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Last Descent – 29 min. 2009 Wild &amp;amp; Scenic People’s Choice Award Kathryn Scott, Charlie Center, Scott Ligare Join a group of world class whitewater kayakers to some of the worlds most amazing rivers ... descending them possibly for the last time. The Marsyangdi River of Nepal, the Brahmaputra River in India and the White Nile River in Uganda are all threatened or are in the process of being destroyed by large scale hydroelectric projects. The film closes in California with the Tuolumne River and the growing movement to restore Hetch Hetchy Valley in Yosemite National Park. (US, 2009, 29min) www.thelastdescent.com, www.internationalriver.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe – 2 min. Sam Chou, Chuck Gammage A young perspective in a changing world asks the question: Why are we so scared? Just Maybe, if we all… (Canada, 2007, 2min) www.style5.tv/maybe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the full listing of films on tour,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wildandscenicfilmfestival.org/on-tour/film-bios" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wildandsce...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about the Wild &amp;amp; Scenic Film Festival and the South Yuba River Citizen League, the group that founded the festival: &lt;a href="http://www.wildandscenicfilmfestival.org/about/about-syrcl" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wildandsce...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258400290000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257950192000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wild and Scenic Environmental Film Festival </name><id>11849905</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258227000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11849905/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>