<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>My apologies for the EXTREMELY last minute event.  I've been so distracted with Montreal plans I didn't notice that the French Film Festival at the MFA is already half over.  D'oh! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't expect a huge turnout, but this film looked interesting.  So if you're looking for an escape from the heat, meet me at the MFA, and we'll follow up with a discussion (somewhere with A/C.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that the starting time is actually 12:40, not 12:30.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Michou d'Auber'&lt;br /&gt;SYNOPSIS: In &amp;quot;Michou d'Auber&amp;quot; the plot focuses on 9-year-old Messaoud in his painful battle to leave his war torn home country, Algeria, to go to France. Messaoud's father puts him in foster care, because the father has to take care of his dying mother. A conservative French woman named Gisèle, played by Nathalie Baye, reluctantly adopts the child even though he's an &amp;quot;Arab,&amp;quot; and the adoption would be adoption would be frowned upon in their village. Gisèle goes so far as to dye Messaoud's hair blond, to change his name from Messaoud to Michou and to make him sing in a Christian choir. Slowly but surely, Messaoud wins Gisèle and her patriotic husband Georges (Gérard Depardieu) over and forces them to see that, in the end, it does not matter where you come from.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REVIEW: &amp;quot;Michou d'Auber&amp;quot; offers beautiful performances from all the characters, but the connection between Messaoud and Georges is undeniably fantastic. &amp;quot;Michou D'Auber&amp;quot; is a beautifully thought-out movie that manages to make us laugh at times, and during others, brings us to tears.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216744412000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216432378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Michou d'Auber--French Film Festival</name><id>8368152</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216571400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8368152/</event_url></item>