<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Joy Street  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.380634</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> (617) 625-2572</phone><name>Joy Street Studios</name><city>Somerville</city><id>516366</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088531</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity to spend some time Sunday afternoon checking out the various studios of some of Somerville's best artists!  I have gone the last three years and is one of my very favorite events of the year.  The environment is very casual and relaxed.  Joy Street and Brickbottom studios have over 100 artists showing over the weekend and as always the event is free. Also, parking is free in the Joy Street lot and the city of Somerville is waiving the residence parking permit requirement to park on Joy Street that weekend. The building is also easily accessible by T&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;The building will be open from 12-6pm daily for visitors.&lt;/span&gt; There will be many studios to move throughout as you get acquainted with who's who in the building! &lt;br /&gt;

Joy Street Studios is a continually growing community for the Arts, it houses a cornucopia of options to see inquire about and if the work moves you, purchase!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Agenda:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; 12:00AM We will meet at Jasons Studio (STUDIO #51), inside Joy St studios 86 Joy St.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; 12:15AM Tour the Building, we will probably break up a bit as some might want to spend more time in some studios vs others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; 1:40PM  Meet back at Jasons Studio (#51) Some can catch back up with us here so no worries if you get separated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; 1:45PM walk down to Brickbottom (few min walk)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; 2:00PMish..  Meet anyone in front if they are only going to Brickbottom. Tour Brickbottom (1 Fitchburg St Somerville)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason has grasiously allowed us to meet at his studio.  If his studio is packed I will be just outside his door but it's pretty big. You can get an idea about Jason and his work from his website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.jasonpolins.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #33cccc"&gt;THIS IS A FREE EVENT!!&lt;/span&gt; Entrance and your participation cost you nothing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transportation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joy St studios is located behind union square, as Somerville ave comes down and hits the McGrath highway, RT.28, Joy street is behind the "Autozone" business, then a short 2 minute drive or walk down the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking at the building is free! If you are unfamiliar with the area, then I would say you should use your smart phone for directions from your place...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;86 Joy St, Somerville MA, 02143&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public transportation has a few options:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the T to either Sullivan station or Lechmere Station. It is about a 10-15 minute walk from either station. I would say that Sullivan is easier as it's a straight walk up Cambridge St (that Becomes Washington St) walking towards union square, then a left turn at Joy St. It's about 2 minutes down on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lechmere Station is fine as well. That's a pretty straight walk along the Mcgrath Highway, yes there are sidewalks... walk away from Boston, walking on the right side of the highway is easier I think. You will get to Poplar St, it's a right hand turn, take it. Walk straight ahead thru 2 stop signs and Joy Street Studios will be on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Yellow door with a large 86 above it is the landmark... Plus we will have a few balloons to make the entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralph-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  (Ziggy R)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/0/event_179762192.jpeg" width="493" height="341" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at Jasons Studio (STUDIO #51), inside Joy St studios 86 Joy St</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ziggy R</member_name><member_id>10747159</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353332771000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352848803000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joy St and Brickbottom Open Studios This Sunday</name><id>91270512</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353258000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/91270512/</event_url></item>