<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Stata Center, 32-123</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.367918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Kirsch Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1431097</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.174057</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;NFC is coming! &lt;br /&gt;--- e-Wallets and much more ---&lt;br /&gt;A new territory for &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;APPLICATION DEVELOPERS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Win a free NFC phone of your own!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOKIA will raffle its lastest C7 Smartphone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;-- Seeing is believing --&lt;br /&gt;The event will be fully NFC enabled&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that you must register through the &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/uncategorized/rfid-sig-event-nfc-is-coming-special-jump-start-program-for-nfc-developers/" target="_blank"&gt;MIT Enterprise Forum of Cambridge website&lt;/a&gt;  for this event.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not a member of the Forum, we strongly urge you to join, and you can participate in all this group's event for free! Non-members pay $20. RSVPng on this meetup site &lt;i&gt;does not&lt;/i&gt; guarantee you a spot.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE for STUDENTS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us in room 32 -123 (The Kirsch Auditorium) of the MIT Stata Center for a special introductory discussion by NFC Ecosystems actors about the recent  US “contactless payment initiatives” and on opportunities for developers/entrepreneurs to build NFC Applications beyond payment  Program Moderator for this is Damien Balsan of Nokia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check NFC in action at this NFC event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;object width=&amp;quot;470&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;264&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;embed src=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/v/JrmFOfobxFQ?fs=1&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;quot;" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; type=&amp;quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;470&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;264&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/embed&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/object&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;5:30 - 9:00 pm - Exhibit Tables open&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6:30 - 8:30 pm - Speakers&lt;/b&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Paula Berger, Executive Director of the NFC Forum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Charles Walton, Vice President, Inside Contactless&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damien Balsan, Director - Head of NFC Business Development Americas Nokia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ganesh Sivaraman, Senior Business Development Manager, Forum Nokia &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ivan Lazarev, CEO and Co-Founder of ITN International&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ville Sointu, NFC Developer, TIETO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vik Pavate, VP Business Development KOVIO (an MIT Spinoff making printed electronics NFC Tags)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q &amp;amp; A&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;REFRESHMENTS WILL BE SERVED&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attendees at this event are encouraged to apply for NFC developer kits that will be made available to qualified participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THIS JUST IN!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Google and Apple looking to introduce NFC capable smartphones" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Google and Apple looking to introduce NFC capable smartphones&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Near&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Field Communication Technology&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Near Field Communication (NFC) is a standards-based, short-range wireless connectivity technology that enables simple and safe two-way interactions between electronic devices. NFC technology allows consumers to perform contactless transactions, access digital content, and connect devices with the simplicity of a single touch. NFC technology provides global interoperability of contactless identification and interconnection technologies. NFC operates in the 13.56 MHz frequency range, over a typical distance of a few centimeters. The underlying layers of NFC technology are based on ISO, ECMA, and ETSI standards. NFC technology is supported by the world's leading communication device manufacturers, semiconductor producers, network operators, IT and services companies, and financial services organizations. NFC is compatible with hundreds of millions of contactless cards and readers already deployed worldwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Forum Nokia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nokia's global developer program, Forum Nokia, connects developers to tools, technical information, support, and distribution channels they can use to build and market applications around the globe. From offices in the U.S., Europe, India, Japan, China, and Singapore, Forum Nokia provides technical and business development support to developers and operators to assist them in achieving their goal of successfully launching applications and services to consumers and enterprises. More information is available at &lt;a href="http://www.forum.nokia.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.forum.noki...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Photo Credit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nokia-Visa Photo by Damian Dovarganes/Associated Press&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPEAKER DETAILS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ivan Lazarev is CEO and Co-Founder of ITN International&lt;/b&gt;, an event marketing services and mobile data management company founded in 1999. ITN launched the BCARD Ecosystem, the first ever web and contactless NFC smart card based registration and information management system for the trade show and exhibition industry. He has spent 25 years in the tradeshow lead management and registration services industry worldwide. He has a Masters in Mechanical Engineering from Arts &amp;amp; Metiers in Paris, France, and an MBA in International Business from the University of South Carolina. ITN is an Implementer member of the NFC Forum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Paula Berger&lt;/b&gt; has been managing the &lt;b&gt;NFC Forum&lt;/b&gt; since February 2005, just after the Forum launched. She works with the member companies to develop standards-based specifications that enable interoperable NFC devices and services. Her focus in 2010 has been preparing for the launch of the NFC Forum Certification Program in December 2010. Before joining the Forum, Paula was Director of Corporate Communications at Virtual, Inc. She has 25+ years of experience in communication, specializing in information design and delivery for online and print media. Paula studied Planetary Physics at MIT. She is a Fellow and International Past President of the Society for Technical Communication.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ville Sointu, NFC developer TIETO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ville Sointu leads the development of Tieto's mobile services offering in North America, and currently focuses on cross industry mobile service development, mobile financial services and cloud technologies. Previously, Ville has lead research projects on the subject of mobile banking and has collaborated in industry-related forums.  Over the last 10 years, Ville has held in several key positions worldwide in mobile financial services and was recently a key collaborator in Mobey Forum's white paper &amp;quot;Implementer Guidelines for Mobile Remote Payments&amp;quot;.’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Damien Balsan, Director - Head of NFC Business Development Americas Nokia&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Damien started his career in Mexico at France Telecom, in charge of developing the Minitel concept following France Telecom's investment of $500M in Telmex (Telefonos de Mexico). He was General Manager for Gemplus now Gemalto  in eastern Europe and then south America and initiated the launch of the first mobile banking and mobile commerce applications there. He co-created WAY Systems a leading Mobile POS device maker invested by major payment actors such as Visa recently acquired by Verifone. He has been heading Nokia NFC Business Development efforts in the Americas for Nokia and led multiple pilots and implementations with carriers, banks, transit operators, SIM card makers and card OTA platforms. He now focuses at enabling multiple NFC Ecosystems thru Developers Globally. Damien graduated from MIT's Sloan School of Management.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Miles</member_name><member_id>10116261</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294699705000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287079283000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Near Field Communication (NFC) - The RFID Revolution for your Mobile Phone</name><id>15109916</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292283900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/15109916/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/5/global_20245941.jpeg</photo_url></item>