<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.791451</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online Flex Meetup Group Connect Room</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1473709</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.661575</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 With the introduction of Flex 4 Spark architecture, the process of "skinning" (change the appearance of components) has never been so easy. With the new process of "skinning", the component styling via CSS seems to have been forgotten in the development of Flex applications. Many of the components of the Flex 4 does not offer the same level of support for CSS as its equivalent Halo. However, Flex 4 CSS not abandoned, in fact, it has been enhanced in the Flex 4 SDK to allow new ways of styling components. In this talk, we will walk through the features of CSS in Flex, what's new in Flex 4, and how we can benefit from the CSS styling to offer robust components and more specifically of the skins. Let's rediscover together the process of "styling" in Flex! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Presenters Bio:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
The presenters will be James Polanco and Aaron Pedersen
&lt;strong&gt;James Polanco&lt;/strong&gt; is a web application architect and co-founder of
DevelopmentArc, who focuses on the Flash Platform (Flash, AIR, Flex,etc.). He has been dabbling with Flash since the beginning, but became serious about development and research with the release of Flash MX. Over the years, James has focused primarily on ActionScript development,design patterns and component implementations which became a naturalfit for Flex development and web application planning and architecture.
James has worked on, lead and planned projects such as DevelopmentArc Maque, Scion.com, Lexus.com, Toyota.com, ILM The show, Adobe Kuler,Adobe WorkflowLab and many other projects and applications for startups to Fortune 500 companies. James is the co-author of Adobe Press' "Adobe
Flash Platform from Start to Finish: Working Collaboratively Using AdobeCreative Suite 5" and co-host of the D2W Podcast.

&lt;strong&gt;Aaron Pedersen&lt;/strong&gt; is the co-founder of DevelopmentArc. He brings over a decade of web application experience to the team from working with many startup and Fortune 500 companies. Aaron currently focuses on user interface technologies such as the Adobe Flash Platform (Adobe Flex,AIR) and JavaScript. Aaron has been a lead, planner, and architect on projects that include many private and public web applications. Among the public sites that he
is excited to highlight: DevelopmentArc Maque, Lexus.com, Scion.com, the Yahoo Mail Flickr application, Adobe Marketplace, and WorkflowLab.

&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Join At:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 You can join in at &lt;a href="http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/" class="linkified"&gt;http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Time Check:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check what time this occurs in your time zone at: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/fixedtime.html?hour=18&amp;amp;min=0&amp;amp;sec=0&amp;amp;p1=98" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/fixedtime.html?hour=18&amp;amp;min=0&amp;amp;sec=0&amp;amp;p1=98&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Logging In:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 When you login to the Connect room (the link above) &lt;br /&gt;

 to view the meeting, PLEASE USE THE "LOGIN AS GUEST" option, and USE YOUR NAME, but do NOT attempt to use your meetup.com username/password or any Connect account. Just sign in as a guest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeffry Houser</member_name><member_id>2147426</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312497209000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309207874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Do not just change the "skin" the app, style it!</name><id>23717111</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312408800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/23717111/</event_url></item>