<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been invited to celebrate Aussie Day!  &lt;br /&gt;Down under this celebration is usually synonymous with the words 'sand and surf', but luckily in the midst of our icy winter their buoyant enthusiasm has brought this celebration to our frigid city. So if you find yourself around town on Saturday the 29th, this is a party not to be missed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details from the Aussie Site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ladies and Gentlemen,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are invited to Official Boston Australia Day Party for 2011. This year it will be held at the Asgard Irish Pub in Cambridge on Saturday 29th January and is set to be the best yet. We have live Australian music, Aussie beer, meat pies courtesy of KO Pies, raffles, auctions, giveaways as well as the annual ‘Peter Garrett-off’.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Festivities kick off at 2pm and will go long into the night. Remember to get your Aussie costume together (Show are Canadian colours) as there are prizes for the best dressed!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All are welcome and encouraged to fill their boots regardless of nationality. $10 entry to the best party of the year!&lt;br /&gt;A portion of the receipts will be donated to Queensland Flood victims.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public parking garage available behind the Asgard for reasonable cost.&lt;br /&gt;Central Sq T few mins walk away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your 2011 Aussie Day t-shirt now from www.danmilbourne.com. Order soon as stock is limited and will sell out soon!  &lt;a href="http://www.danmilbourne.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce Turnbull</member_name><member_id>4018534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296407699000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294968332000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Australia Day Party/Queensland Flood Fundraiser!</name><id>16042718</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296327600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/16042718/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/global_20778362.jpeg</photo_url></item>