<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>66 Maple St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.567062</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-777-1879</phone><name>Toys N Things</name><city>Danvers</city><id>1079316</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.937019</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Toys N Things is hosting its second game day. Come play D&amp;amp;D 4.0 in the Forgotten Realms all weekend during the first weekend in November. The first adventure starts Friday Nov 6th at 6PM and goes right through until Sunday afternoon. Can't play the whole weekend? No problem. Each adventure is stand alone so you can play as many or as few as you like. Bring your own character to play or use one of several pregenerated characters available during the weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be two scenarios running during Weekend in the Realms. The first is &amp;quot;The Icy Queen's Crossing&amp;quot; a 1st through 4th level adventure set in the Nar region of Faerun. The second is a series of linked scenarios that take place on Faerun during The Year of Lightning Storms (1374 DR). What scenario is actually played depends on the number of players and which one they'd like to play. The schedule is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday starting at 6PM: &amp;quot;The Icy Queen's Crossing or &amp;quot;A Lost Companion&amp;quot;. A Lost Companion is a 1st through 3rd level adventure where the characters are asked to help members of the Sisterhood of Essembra find a dragon reborn who has gone missing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday starting at 1PM: &amp;quot;The Icy Queen's Crossing&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;What Private War?&amp;quot; What Private War? is a 4th through 7th level adventure. From the dragon reborn the characters learn of a great conflict going on between the Church of Tiamat and the Cult of the Dragon. They both are trying to find a very powerful item, but don't know exactly what the item is or why its so important.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday starting at 1PM: &amp;quot;The Icy Queen's Crossing&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Entering the Great Cycle&amp;quot;. Entering the Great Cycle is a 8th through 12th level scenario that sees the characters playing a role in an ancient battle among dragonkind that has restarted on Faerun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Knowledge of Faerun or the its history is helpful, but not needed to play. Players with Faerun based characters are welcome to play them at the event. Please PM me with any questions or for additional info.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan J</member_name><member_id>10199663</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258072535000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255929947000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend In the Realms Event at Toys N Things</name><id>11658583</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257548400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/11658583/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/7/9/global_11303497.jpeg</photo_url></item>