<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt. Auburn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.371338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-699-1221 </phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>363595</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116469</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Incubators!!!  Stop getting hit in the face with footballs (I hoe someone gets this reference) and come out to an awesome week of learning and watching action.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First off, I've bumped up the time of this week's incubator to &lt;b&gt;7pm&lt;/b&gt;.  We will be rocking out some great new games I picked up from Camprov a few weeks ago along with some of our usual fun.  It'll be a laughing experimental week that I am sure will further your improv skill set in terms of the physical and the dialogue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are starting early and ending early probably sometime around 9-9:30 we'll wrap up shop as my troupe Lost Marbles will be performing right down the road at &lt;b&gt;10:30pm&lt;/b&gt; at Improv Boston in Central Square as part of the Boston Improv Festival. $10 Tickets for that and info on any other show or classes at the Festival can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.bostonimprov.com/bif/#schedule" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonimpr...&lt;/a&gt;  Pre-purchase if you can!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I highly recommend checking out some of the classes as well and they are a steal for the money.  Hurry up though because those are filling up and selling out fast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My idea is that we'll rock an incubator, those interested in coming to the show could grab some grub down in Central than come see the show which will run about one hour or so.  That means we'll still be able to get you all laughing to bed by your usual incubator time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks everyone!! Hope to see you this week!!!!! Bring energy, attitude, friends, and a willingness to let go and laugh! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And remember no previous improv experience required.  For those out there who have yet to attend an incubator, this would be a great week to start!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason J.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy Blackman</member_name><member_id>4979909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252796846000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252345635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>a very Improv sequel !!!  It's a double dose of awesomeness this week.</name><id>11310459</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252623600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/11310459/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>