<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>38 Front Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03869</zip><lat>43.236944</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-617-3590</phone><name>SunMoonStarsHerbals</name><city>Rollinsford</city><id>1170406</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.818798</lon></venue><fee><label>Donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The June 2010 Metaphysical Club meetup will be at 6 PM on Saturday, June 19th, at SunMoonStars Herbals, 38 Front Street, Rolinsford NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The topic of this meetup will be &amp;quot;Sharing Your Spiritual Path.&amp;quot; This will be a time for everyone to talk about their religion/beliefs/personal spirituality... how we got to where we are, how it works for us, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This topic is kind of an outgrowth of our last meetup on the Law of Attraction. In discussing our thoughts and how they manifest in the world, many of us touched on our own spirituality, and it was very interesting to see how different perspectives work in our lives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This ought to be a great topic.... a little like &amp;quot;show and tell&amp;quot; except there may be ideas that each of us can take home and incorporate into our own path!  We'll each get to share our own stuff, ask questions to other folks, compare thoughts and more.  (With this group, this will be fun!) :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a light, easy snack to share if you can, and we may need an extra folding chair or two. The talk will go from 6 to 8 PM... and if you ask Dawnie nicely she may let you do some shopping in her wonderful store afterward! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We do ask a donation of $2.00 per person, which goes to keeping this Meetup.com site going  and helps pay for electricity etc. at SunMoonStars.  This should be great talk, so please put us on your schedule and don't forget to RSVP you're coming! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about SunMoonStars Herbals, check out their website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://stores.homestead.com/hstrial-DEvans181/StoreFront.bok" target="_blank"&gt;http://stores.homeste...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>William </member_name><member_id>4792394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276995441000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Metaphysics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metaphysics-387</urlname><id>682186</id><group_lat>43.4399986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7600021362</group_lon><name>The New England Metaphysical Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273973941000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Metaphysical Club June 2010 Meetup</name><id>13495420</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276984800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metaphysics-387/events/13495420/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/1/3/global_12047907.jpeg</photo_url></item>