<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me for the first feature of the Brattle?s Sing-A-Long weekend ? &lt;i&gt;Grease!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone knows that &lt;i&gt;Grease&lt;/i&gt; is the word. This quintessential high school musical has been oft imitated but never duplicated (take that &lt;i&gt;Grease 2&lt;/i&gt;).  A summertime romance between bad boy Danny (Travolta) and candy-coated Sandy (Newton-John) ends in disaster as the two are reunited at Rydell High, only to be separated once again by the disparaging social classes of high school.  Will the two ever get back together?  Is Rizzo really pregnant?  And just how old is Frankie Avalon?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Love it or hate it, &lt;i&gt;Grease&lt;/i&gt; is an indelible piece of American culture.  So why not start your summer weekend off right with by doing the hand jive with a hundred of your closest friends?  This film print includes lyrics on-screen for the songs, so don?t worry if you can?t remember all the words to ?Look at Me, I?m Sandra Dee.?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Events like this are usually chaotic, so be patient and we?ll all eventually assemble at the front of the theatre.  I?ll be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it?s off to a local restaurant to discuss.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brattle encourages attendees to dress as your favorite character and expect surprises.  I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a Meetup sign at the front of the theatre once the movie ends.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219014294000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214694382000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grease Sing-A-Long!</name><id>8236366</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218841200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8236366/</event_url></item>