<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>96 Winthrop Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372364</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tommy Doyles Irish Pub &amp; Restuarant Harvard</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1532939</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;`Twas the month before Christmas, when all through Beantown &lt;br /&gt;

Not a creature was stirring, no sci-fi fans could be found &lt;br /&gt;

A meetup was posted to the website with care &lt;br /&gt;

In hopes that food, drink, and friends soon would be there &lt;br /&gt;

The members were nestled all snug in their beds, &lt;br /&gt;

While visions of big-damn-heroes danced in their heads; &lt;br /&gt;

I relaxed in my chair at the end of the day &lt;br /&gt;

To watch a bad film and MST3K &lt;br /&gt;

When out on the lawn there arose such a clatter &lt;br /&gt;

I sprang from the chair to see what was the matter &lt;br /&gt;

Out from the window I saw a bright flash &lt;br /&gt;

I heard an explosion, I felt a huge crash! &lt;br /&gt;

An unearthly green tint caused an ominous glow &lt;br /&gt;

To reveal a crashed Borg scout, half buried in snow &lt;br /&gt;

I was very confused, this could not be here! &lt;br /&gt;

My whole body was tense, I was frozen with fear! &lt;br /&gt;

The police could not help, their weapons too dated &lt;br /&gt;

They would only be needlessly assimilated! &lt;br /&gt;

Then my thoughts turned to someone i knew as a child &lt;br /&gt;

A man who was caring, brilliant, and wild &lt;br /&gt;

No one believed me, they called me a liar &lt;br /&gt;

But I saw him walk through that alien fire &lt;br /&gt;

He reached out for me and we took a short ride &lt;br /&gt;

In a phone box that was bigger on the inside &lt;br /&gt;

Before he left me in safety, he whispered to share &lt;br /&gt;

"Do not fear the darkness, for I will be there." &lt;br /&gt;

I called out for the Doctor, I called him by name &lt;br /&gt;

And suddenly behind me, the TARDIS, it came! &lt;br /&gt;

The doors opened, my fears came to their ends &lt;br /&gt;

For the good Doctor had brought a few friends! &lt;br /&gt;

I saw R2-D2, Data, a T-101! &lt;br /&gt;

Chewbacca, Han Solo, and all of SG1! &lt;br /&gt;

Then Picard and Data emerged from the back &lt;br /&gt;

Weapons on kill, they lead the attack! &lt;br /&gt;

I will never forget what I saw in my yard &lt;br /&gt;

A Chrismas Crossover, the Doctor and Picard &lt;br /&gt;

The Borg stood no chance, and soon they were gone &lt;br /&gt;

Our heroes stood victorious on my front lawn &lt;br /&gt;

But before they went home, before they departed &lt;br /&gt;

A few words of wisdom, the Doctor imparted &lt;br /&gt;

"I like this Earth, I think I'll protect it. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp;Your meetup is safe, it shant be affected! &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp;Friends, food, and drink, these things rule. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp;Also, fezzes, because fezzes are cool." &lt;br /&gt;

Then he sprang to his TARDIS, I heard that old whistle &lt;br /&gt;

And away they all flew like the down of a thistle &lt;br /&gt;

But I heard him exclaim, before he did go &lt;br /&gt;

"Merry Christmas to all, and to all, Geronimo!" &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

*****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come out and meet other Boston area Science Fiction and Fantasy fans in a comfortable setting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the regular social meetup for the Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group, which always happens on the First Tuesday of every month. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This is the last social meetup of 2011, and our last meetup before the Winter Holidays. Several people have asked if we could try to do a Secret Santa gift exchange, so I've added a question to this event. If you'd like to participate, just answer YES, and bring a wrapped gift worth no more than $20. Remember that this is a meetup of sci-fi and fantasy geeks, and try to choose something that others might like. (Note: This isn't mandatory, you can just come out, but only those who participate will get gifts.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

There will also be a free raffle for a copy of the Blu-Ray edition of the Jurassic Park Trilogy, thanks to Allied Integrated Marketing and Universal Studios Home Entertainment. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

LOGISTICS: &lt;br /&gt;

* We meet at Tommy Doyle's Irish Pub &amp;amp; Restaurant in Harvard Square, in their basement lounge. We have the whole space for this meetup, so grab any chair you can, because they go quickly. Last month, we had 40+ people, and if we do it again, I can talk to the manager about using a bigger space upstairs! &lt;br /&gt;

Tommy Doyle's website is here: &lt;a href="http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/harvard-square/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/harvard-square/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* There is no theme or agenda, just people talking about Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and geeky things that we like (and dislike). If you can't come on time, that's fine, we usually have a large group until 8:00 PM. If you want to come early, there are usually people there at 6:00. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* If you have SciFi/Fantasy Books or DVDs that you don't want anymore, feel free to bring them to the meetup and give them away (no sales, please). Be sure to take home anything that isn't claimed before you leave! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* There is no charge for this meetup, but the restaurant that hosts us greatly appreciates your business (and doesn't charge us a room rental fee), so please come hungry (or at least buy a drink).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

TRAVEL:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're taking the T, Harvard Square is on the Red Line, and Tommy Doyle's is a short walk south (just beside the Winthrop Square park). If you're familiar with Harvard Square, Tommy Doyle's is on the section of Winthrop Street that is closed to cars, but open to foot traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=96+Winthrop+Street+Cambridge,+MA&amp;amp;sll=42.566534,-71.539188&amp;amp;sspn=0.010019,0.013518&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=96+Winthrop+St,+Cambridge,+Massachusetts+02138&amp;amp;ll=42.373205,-71.120199&amp;amp;spn=0.002513,0.005423&amp;amp;z=18" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=96+Winthrop+Street+Cambridge,+MA&amp;amp;sll=42.566534,-71.539188&amp;amp;sspn=0.010019,0.013518&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=96+Winth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're driving in, there are several parking lots nearby:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a pay lot (Harvard Square Parking Garage) at 20 Eliot St, Cambridge, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Evening Rates Entering After 5 PM are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;-1/2 Hour or Less $4.00-1 Hour or Less $8.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;-1 1/2 Hours or Less $14.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;-1 1/2 Hours to Close $15.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;- Lost Ticket: $30.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;- $2.00 Validation When Stamped By Affiliated Vendors (Not sure if Tommy Doyle's validates or not)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is another pay lot at the Charles Hotel at One Bennett St. Cambridge, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$7.00 1 hour &lt;br /&gt;

 $16.00 2 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 $19.00 3 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 $21.00 6 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 $25.00 12 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 Daily Max: $34.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there is yet another pay lot at 124 Mount Auburn St, Cambridge, MA. Details for that lot are here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston.centralparking.com/Cambridge-124-Mount-Auburn-Street-Parking.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://boston.centralparking.com/Cambridge-124-Mount-Auburn-Street-Parking.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is metered parking in Harvard Square, but it usually goes very quickly. I personally park at the Alewife T stop (7 dollars a day) and take the Red Line to Harvard Square.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>All the way downstairs!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom "spot" Callaway</member_name><member_id>2590946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323635545000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320790060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Social Meetup 2011</name><id>40469462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323214200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/40469462/</event_url></item>