<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.353788</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fan Pier</name><city>Boston</city><id>706709</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.044905</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>49.2299995422</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Under the Grand Chapiteau, at Fan Pier &amp;amp; Pier 4, on Boston’s New Waterfront.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I will be at the entrance with a meetup sign from 7:00 to 7:15 to give you all your tickets. The Cirque people said I CANNOT put the tickets at the box office with your name on them if you show up too late.&lt;/b&gt; I don't want to miss any of the show, so if you don't show up by 7:15 to get your ticket from me you'll be out of luck. So come early, &amp;amp; hobnob with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cirquedusoleil.com/en/shows/ovo/" target="_blank"&gt;Cirque du Soleil OVO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I shelled out for a block of 20 of the cheapest tickets ($45 seats) on Sat Aug 21's evening show. We have the first 2 rows in the cheap seats. The deal was that they charged me a single $50 service charge, vs having every person pay $8 service charge (??$8 service charge!?!?). You must pay me to get your ticket. &lt;/b&gt; Amazon payments is getting a lil off the top as well, the price listed covers exactly why I paid out of pocket for 20 tickets, plus the amazon fee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the show starts at 8pm.&lt;br /&gt;we're meeting at 7pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OVO is a headlong rush into a colourful ecosystem teeming with life, where insects work, eat, crawl, flutter, play, fight and look for love in a non-stop riot of energy and movement. The insects' home is a world of biodiversity and beauty filled with noisy action and moments of quiet emotion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When a mysterious egg appears in their midst, the insects are awestruck and intensely curious about this iconic object that represents the enigma and cycles of their lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s love at first sight when a gawky, quirky insect arrives in this bustling community and a fabulous ladybug catches his eye – and the feeling is mutual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OVO is overflowing with contrasts. The hidden, secret world at our feet is revealed as tender and torrid, noisy and quiet, peaceful and chaotic. And as the sun rises on a bright new day the vibrant cycle of insect life begins anew.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Direction to site and parking info&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cirque du Soleil is presented under the Grand Chapiteau at&lt;br /&gt;Fan Pier on Boston’s New Waterfront.&lt;br /&gt;Fan Pier is located next to the ICA, &amp;amp; Pier 4.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM LOGAN INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT &amp;amp; ROUTE 1A:&lt;br /&gt;Follow the signs towards I-90 West/ Ted Williams Tunnel. Take the Ted Williams Tunnel to Exit 2 South Boston. At the top of the ramp, proceed straight onto B Street. Turn left onto Northern Avenue/Seaport Boulevard, the right onto Northern Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points North via I-93:&lt;br /&gt;Heading southbound of I-93 towards Boston, take Exit 23, Purchase Street, and get into the left lane. Take the first left onto Seaport Boulevard, crossing the Moakley Bridge. Turn left onto Northern Ave. (East Service Road will be on your right.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Point South via I-93:&lt;br /&gt;Heading northbound on I-93 towards Boston, take Exit 20, which will be immediately after Exit 18. Once on the exit ramp, follow signs for South Boston, staying in the right lane through the tunnel. At the first set of lights at the end of the off-ramp, proceed straight onto East Service Road. At the intersection of Seaport Boulevard, go straight onto Northern Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points West via the Massachusetts Turnpike/ I-90:&lt;br /&gt;Follow the Massachusetts Turnpike/ I-90 East to Exit 25, South Boston. At the top of the ramp, bear left torwards Seaport Boulevard. At the first set of lights, proceed straight onto East Service Road. At the next set of lights, go straight onto Northern Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Storrow Drive:&lt;br /&gt;Take Storrow Drive to Leverett Circle. Follow signs for interstate 93 South. Once on Interstate 93 South, follow the directions above, coming from the North via I-93.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available on site at a cost of 10$. Parking may be purchased in advance for more information click here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here for routes, schedules and other info.&lt;br /&gt;The Grand Chapiteau (Big Top)&lt;br /&gt;The Grand Chapiteau seats over 2,600 spectators per show, with an adjoining entrance tent. As in a Roman amphitheatre, the seats fan out through 270 degrees around a central, circular revolving stage.&lt;br /&gt;Duration&lt;br /&gt;2 hours 30 minutes, including a 30-minute intermission.&lt;br /&gt;Latecomers&lt;br /&gt;The show starts on time and latecomers are admitted only during a suitable break in the performance. Late-coming wheelchair-users can only be admitted at the intermission.&lt;br /&gt;Box Office Hours&lt;br /&gt;Open: 2 Hours prior to show&lt;br /&gt;Close: 1/2 hour after start of performance*&lt;br /&gt;*Box Office supervisors on duty for guests attending the show until after intermission&lt;br /&gt;Food &amp;amp; Beverages&lt;br /&gt;Concessions open one hour before the show.&lt;br /&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * The temperature inside the Grand Chapiteau is controlled.&lt;br /&gt;    * There is no cloakroom.&lt;br /&gt;    * Smoking is not permitted in the Grand Chapiteau.&lt;br /&gt;    * Mobile phones must be turned off during the show.&lt;br /&gt;    * Videotapes, cameras and tape recorders are prohibited.&lt;br /&gt;    * Animals are not allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1282522003000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272300046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cirque du Soleil OVO at the Fan Pier</name><id>13294790</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282431600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13294790/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/d/global_14653821.jpeg</photo_url></item>