<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>42 Maple St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01069</zip><lat>42.067919</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-587-8900</phone><name>Side Street Cafe</name><city>Florence</city><id>975469</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467995</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It's hard to believe that it's already been ONE YEAR since we had our very first EatUp! but it's true, and like the earth's journey around the sun, we are also returning to our original event site, the fabulous &lt;a href="http://www.sidestcafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;SIDE STREET CAFE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine and I just got off the phone earlier today with Patrick Shannon, chef and owner of this hidden treasure in Florence, (just off Rt 9) and he is excited to be hosting us for the evening. We had a GREAT time last year, and we expect to have an even better time now that we are a more cohesive bunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The price for the festivities will be $35.00 per person, which, as usual, includes a fabulous 4 course meal AND your tax and tip! Such a deal! Any beverages you consume that night will be given to you on a separate check that you will pay individually.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you click the registration link, you will be taken to the payment page where you can use a credit/debit card via paypal. If you would prefer to pay by check, please let me know and we can arrange for you to mail me a check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;For all you folks that were excited about the pig roast, no worries, we've just moved that event to July to give us a bit more time to work out the details. (date to be announced in the next few days) if you have already registered for that event, we will simply roll over your registration with no fee. Please re-register for this event separately.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;we look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;warmly,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jessica &amp;amp; Christine &amp;amp; Kirsten&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will be the ones laughing the loudest</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282497201000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275185003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Side Street Cafe-Our One Year Anniversary Celebration!</name><id>13636323</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277676000000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/13636323/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/5/global_8946469.jpeg</photo_url></item>