<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Burbank St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.599323</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Falulah Brook Park </name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>8890982</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.805466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us in this extremely picturesque hike thru Flat Rock Wildlife Sanctuary in Fitchburg where will we pass Overloook Reservoir then stop at a small cemetery. From there we'll hike along Falulah Brook where we will pass a scenic gorge, water falls and Fitchburg' s water supply. Near the end of the hike we'll stop for about an hour to hang out and play at the wadding pools and trek thru the brook (if you wish).. Falulah Brook is a Fitchburg public park that you have to hike to get there. Good for us as few people ever come here. An extensive trail system traverses the sanctuary and park, which leads you through a number of habitats including rocky ledges, hemlock groves, dry upland forest and wetlands. Look for signs of deer, fox and coyote along the trails. &lt;br /&gt;

Bring: a towel (to sit on), snack, at least one quart volume of a drink. And if you wish to go in the water: water shoes/old sneakers if you have them and swim trunks. &lt;br /&gt;

Difficulty: Moderate, total elevatn climb less than 300 ft. 98 percent of hike is shaded forest. Total distance is about 4 miles with the hike lasting about 2 hours then stopping at Falulah brook as described above. &lt;br /&gt;

Weather forecast for Sunday: sunny, 84 degrees. &lt;br /&gt;

Plan to arrive 15 minutes early unless you know the kiosk location described below. BEWARE: If traveling from the West on route 2 toward Fitchburg and exiting along Route 31, beware there are road blocks for construction. I recommend using the directions below. &lt;br /&gt;

No pets are allowed on the hike as they are prohibited in Flat Rock Bird Sanctuary. &lt;br /&gt;

Hike leader: Richard Fallon, Home is 978-400-5564.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from intersection of Rt. 2 and Rt. 12 in Leominster. &lt;br /&gt;

1.Head North toward Fitchburg on N Main St (Rt. 12), 1.5 mi. &lt;br /&gt;

2.Turn right onto Bemis Rd. 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;

3.Bear right to continue onto John Fitch Hwy 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;

4.At the traffic circle,take the 3rd exit onto Mechanic St 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;

5.Turn right onto Romes Way 299 ft &lt;br /&gt;

6.Turn right onto Miller Street 367 ft &lt;br /&gt;

7.Slight right onto Burbank Street 0.1 mi. Go past the Urgent Care Center(on Left) and past the two huge smoke stacks. &lt;br /&gt;

8.Continue straight (the road curves 90 degrees to the left) to the end of the parking lot to find the Flat Rock (Mass Audubon) kiosk (small wooden) at the start of the trail head. Park here. You are now located in the right rear parking lot of the Health Alliance Hospital Burbank Campus, 275 Nichols Rd, Fitchburg, MA (978) 343-5000.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Richard Fallon</member_name><member_id>10897888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346119336000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345847972000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flat Rock Hike,  Falulah Brook Trek</name><id>79235722</id><headcount>9</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346000400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/79235722/</event_url></item>