<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>NH 113A, Wonalancet</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03897</zip><lat>43.908970</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ferncroft Parking ARea</name><city>Wonalancet</city><id>410429</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353912</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Bob and Mark (aka Lawnsale) are planning on hiking to the summits of Mt Whiteface &amp;amp; Mt Passaconaway via Blueberry Ledge, Rollins, and Diceys Mill trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plan is to meet at 8:45 AM at the Ferncroft Road Parking area off of Rte 113A in Wonalancet and be on the trail at 9 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dogs are Welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike at or slightly faster than book time with plenty of short stops (in order to stay warm) for food and water. Plan on food/snacks that you can eat while moving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check your maps and AMC White Mountain Guide for a description of the trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance   11.9 miles &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain  3,800 feet &lt;br /&gt;Book Time  7:50 excluding stops &lt;br /&gt;Goal time  8:00 including stops&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anybody considering joining should be experienced in Winter hiking for longer distances, be comfortable hiking after dark, breaking trail in deep snow, bushwhacking around blowdowns, and be knowledgable in the proper Winter gear required for such an endeavor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for full Winter conditions - snowshoes, crampons, microspikes, goggles, extra gloves/clothes may all be needed - plan your hike accordingly based on your experiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions on equipement or the hike please ask before showing up for the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in a green Suburban with NH plates and ROT &amp; VFTT decals</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob &amp; Geri</member_name><member_id>4842806</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263736031000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263257016000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Whiteface &amp; Mt Passaconaway - Advanced</name><id>12292778</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263563100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12292778/</event_url></item>