<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The night before the 2010 Oscars, Come and See One of the Contenders!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit the 360 Screening Room for a showing of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inception&lt;/strong&gt; (2010 - "Action" - Rated PG-13)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1375666/"&gt;IMDB Description:&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;In a world where technology exists to enter the human mind through dream invasion, a highly skilled thief is given a final chance at redemption which involves executing his toughest job to date: Inception.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starring: Leonardo DiCaprio, Ellen Page, Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Tom Hardy, Ken Watanabe, Cillian Murphy, and appearances by&amp;nbsp;Michael Caine and Pete Postlethwaite&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AJ Notes: This was one of the biggest pictures of 2010, and one of my favorites.&amp;nbsp; With the Oscars coming up, I though some of us would like to check it out or see it again prior to finding out who wins the next night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Set the time for 7pm, but we will not start showing the movie until shortly after 7:30. Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Notes: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately I have to limit RSVP's to 18 for theater size. There are NO Maybe's allowed, please only respond Yes if you're sure you can make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're Coming, &lt;em&gt;I will need your full names&lt;/em&gt; if I don't already have (or remember) them &lt;em&gt;for the Concierge to let you in&lt;/em&gt;, and you may be asked for ID. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please either put your name in your RSVP or e-mail it to me&lt;/span&gt;. (If you live in the building just let me know that instead.)&amp;nbsp; If it's less than 24 hours before and we have a waiting list of people whom did send me the required info, well I'll just say I do not want to have to be mean here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list.&amp;nbsp; As the date aproaches you may automatically be added if someone backs out.&amp;nbsp; Just please still send me your name for the Concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Notes:&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are instructions near the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7 pm.&amp;nbsp; If you don't mind a longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evenings (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street Starting at 5). 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only at $5 Daily Max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday, the entrance is on State street just to the right of the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1298847277000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296179460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie: Inception</name><id>16337431</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298764800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/16337431/</event_url></item>