<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>The Shoppes at Blackstone Valley Mall</address_2><address_1>70 Worcester Providence Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01527</zip><lat>42.192432</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-853-4000</phone><name>Blackstone Valley Cinema 14</name><city>Millbury</city><id>479940</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.770540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;MOVIE STARTS AT 2:15 PM - LETS MEET INSIDE THE LOBBY BY THE PIANO AT 2 PM, PLEASE PURCHASE YOUR TICKET FIRST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; - A DEFINITE MOVIE FOR BOTH THE GUYS AND GIRLS TO ENJOY!  We can go to Uno's afterwards which is right there in the Blackstone Millbury Shoppes Mall................&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ali is a small-town girl with a big voice who escapes hardship and an uncertain future to follow her dreams to LA. After stumbling upon The Burlesque Lounge, a majestic but ailing theater that is home to an inspired musical revue, Ali lands a job as a cocktail waitress from Tess, the club's proprietor and headliner. Burlesque's outrageous costumes and bold choreography enrapture the young ingenue, who vows to perform there one day. Soon enough, Ali builds a friendship with a featured dancer, finds an enemy in a troubled, jealous performer, and garners the affection of Jack, a bartender and fellow musician. With the help of a sharp-witted stage manager and gender-bending host, Ali makes her way from the bar to the stage. Her spectacular voice restores The Burlesque Lounge to its former glory, though not before a charismatic entrepreneur arrives with an enticing proposal. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the movie lobby next to the piano.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291081418000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290039123000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BURLESQUE! This Sunday Millbury Shoppes Cinemas!</name><id>15482842</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290970800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/15482842/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/0/global_19712160.jpeg</photo_url></item>