<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come and visit three great state parks and we will see the wonderful colors of fall.  Hopefully the leaves will be near their peak.  Norfolk has three state parks, with a waterfall and two views of the Litchfield hills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First we will visit Campbell Falls on the Massachusetts border.  We will meet on the Connecticut side and walk to the falls.  If there has been some rain, there should be 100 feet of falling water in the narrow cleft.  This park was a gift of the White Memorial Foundation in 1924 to both states.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Second we will visit Haystack Mountain and hike to the lookout tower.  This is a 35 foot circular stone tower with 360 degrees of view, including Long Island Sound, the Berkshires, and New York.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Third we will visit Dennis Hill with its grand pavilion at the summit.  This park was a gift of Dr Frederick Dennis to the state in 1935.  The pavilion used to be a grand summer house, now with the insides removed.  We will have our lunch with a spectacular view.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be an easy walk of about 2 miles with a couple of short hills to climb.  Social walking pace.  We will be out for 2 to 3 hours.  I have not visited this place in many years, and I will be following the trail map.  Afterwards we will have a picnic lunch at Dennis Hill.  The walk will be rescheduled if there is a threat of rain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs and children are welcome as long as they are calm and well behaved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:  (approximate address, no mailbox there) 29 Spaulding Rd, Norfolk, CT.  Going north from Norfolk center, take a left at the first sign for Campbell Falls.  If you cross into Massachusetts you have gone too far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=29+Spaulding+Road,+Norfolk,+CT&amp;amp;sll=42.042154,-73.230743&amp;amp;sspn=0.009816,0.034161&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=Spaulding+Rd,+Norfolk,+Litchfield,+Connecticut+06058&amp;amp;ll=42.042026,-73.229113&amp;amp;spn=0.009816,0.034161&amp;amp;z=15" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry</member_name><member_id>8113327</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286803890000</updated><rating><average>3.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282513553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Norfolk Trio Walk, Norfolk, CT</name><id>14504776</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286634600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/14504776/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>