<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>96 Winthrop street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372280</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tommy Doyles</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1114814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>8:00 - 11 :00 Live Musician Showcase @ TOMMY DOYLES (The Historic HOUSE OF BLUES!): Hosted by Bill Brockmeyer &amp;amp; BROCK &amp;amp; ROLL REVIVAL, and featuring other local area talented musicians.  Upstairs in the Loft.  Free Entertainment - Come one come all....come celebrate the holidays with singing your favorite Motown and Christmas carols.  &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also, if you are a talented &amp;amp; seasoned musician or singer and would like to play or sing in the Showcase, come audition at the PA's Lounge Monday weekly Open Mic and rehearse, arrange your song selections.  There are also auditions &amp;amp; rehearsals on Sunday afternoons.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event combines 5 or more meetup groups.  Food: Half price appetizers with a drink purchase. Just mention &amp;quot;Social Fun&amp;quot; when ordering. This offer is not offered to the public so make sure your waitress/waiter knows you are with our group Before your place your order. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB AT ALL TIMES! There is no charge to attend this event. Please remember that in order to bring you half price appetizers with drink purchase ...a 20% gratuity will be automatically included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transportation and Parking: Parking is unrestricted on Sundays, however, leave plenty of time to find a spot. Easiest is to park at Alewife station take the T on the red line to Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replace this text with the first item of your list&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replace this text with the next item&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can add more items by adding lines that start with a &lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4" usually on keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292202818000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289810883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Musician Showcase @ Tommy Doyles (Harvard Square)</name><id>15450295</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292198400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/15450295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>