<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Geoff Bartley is a folk-blues guitar player, singer-songwriter, and harmonica player. His last two CDs went to No.1 on folk radio. The folk press has called him a world-class guitarist, a brilliant songwriter, and the prophet and spiritual godfather of the Boston folk scene. Several of Geoff's songs and co-writes have been recorded by other artists in New England, Canada, Ireland, and Nashville, and some are also included in the Smithsonian Folkways Recordings of the Fast Folk Musical Magazine collection in Washington, D.C. In the 1980s, Geoff won four guitars at the National Fingerpicking Championships in Winfield, Kansas with his precise, bluesy guitar style. Geoff also plays guitar and sings harmony for folk beacon Tom Paxton and was instrumental in bringing the Tom Paxton Signature Model Martin guitar into production in 2004. Geoff presents two nights of acoustic music every week at the Cantab Lounge in Cambridge, Massachusetts. Both nights have been voted Best of Boston. Geoff Bartley's website is &lt;a href="http://www.geoffbartley.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.geoffbartley.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Howie Tarnower is a multi-instrumentalist and singer who has played concert venues and festivals in the US, Canada, the UK, Western Europe and Japan including appearances with Hazel Dickens and on A Prairie Home Companion and Car Talk. He has appeared on dozens of bluegrass, newgrass, and jazzgrass recordings. His previous musical projects include Special Consensus Bluegrass, the Fiction Brothers and Country Cookin'.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marylou Ferrante was described by music critic and writer, Daniel Gewertz, in the Boston Herald, as the Bay State's finest female acoustic blues interpreter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marylou is an artist who performs pre-war blues from the 1920's &amp;amp; 30's. She covers major artists from the delta to east coast piedmont style players such as Robert Johnson, Charlie Patton, Blind Boy Fuller and Memphis Minnie along with mandolin players such as Yank Rachell. Her passionate expression of these old songs comes from a love of the music and the arrangements themselves, as well as what she says is an appreciation for "the history of these folks and the difficult circumstances they endured." She has honed her craft listening to the old recordings and learning from some of the great blues players today such as Paul Rishell, Guy Davis, Robert Jones and mandolin great Rich DelGrosso, and has taught at The Cellar Studio, Salem MA &lt;br /&gt;

* "Marylou is a killer. I have watched her grow, and now she's taking over. Blues lovers look out!"... GUY DAVIS &lt;br /&gt;

* "Marylou has the soul of a blues Woman" Detroit's Blues Man... ROBERT JONES ..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alan Kaufman, a multiple contest winner and author, is a veteran fiddler and leader of a weekly old-time jam in Waltham as well as the Boston Bluegrass Union’s monthly kids' jam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Johnny D’s, 17 Holland Street, Davis Square, Somerville, MA 02144 &lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.johnnyds.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Ages 10+, contact Johnny D’s to make arrangements for minors. &lt;br /&gt;

Tickets: $10 general admission; reserved seating / dinner packages also available at the box office or online - &lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/advance-tickets/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.johnnyds.com/advance-tickets/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Artists' websites ~ &lt;a href="http://www.geoffbartley.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.geoffbartley.com/&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MarylouFerrantemusic" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/MarylouFerrantemusic&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Lord Geoffrey website: &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/lordgeoffreypresents/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/lordgeoffreypresents/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Lord Geoffrey Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/LGPresents/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/LGPresents/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364439702000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363196181000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One Sock On (Geoff Bartley &amp; Howie Tarnower), Marylou Ferrante &amp; Alan Kaufman</name><id>109080932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364428800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/109080932/</event_url></item>