<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As tradition goes, Wedeln will be hosting a new guest weekend up at the Lodge over Thanksgiving weekend! This is your chance to get some pre-season turns in, as most mountains are scheduled to open on or before November 26th! Hiking and outlet, tax-free shopping are always options around the lodge too! &amp;nbsp;The main purpose of this weekend is to get first time guests up to the house before the ski season has fully kicked in so you can check it out and hopefully make the Wedeln Ski House part of your winter plans this season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Friday night, when you arrive at Wedeln, we'll have snacks and a &amp;nbsp;meet and greet - you will get to meet the Wedeln members and enjoy our beautiful, well-appointed lodge. We will definitely have a roaring fire warming the hearth as we socialize and discuss where we are skiing on Saturday! &amp;nbsp;This is a great opportunity to get to know more about the Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors club, whether you're interested in membership (racing or full) or interested in just visiting a couple of times as a guest during the ski season or at other times during the year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Saturday - Your call - Ski or ride with us or come on an adventure bus ride (more details on that later). In the afternoon and evening, there will be events held at other nearby ski clubs which we will be attending.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Sunday - Hit the mountain again or pack up and head home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Details and $$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Check the lodge out at &lt;a href="http://www.wedeln.com"&gt;www.wedeln.com&lt;/a&gt;. The lodge is located on the North Conway, NH / Bartlett NH town line and is 3 hours from Boston. Directions given to those who RSVP Yes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Guests will need to bring their own linens/pillow/sleeping bag, as well as their own towels, toiletries, and flip flops for the showers. Rooms are separated by gender and are dorm style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;- We have a full kitchen so you can bring up your breakfast/lunch stuff if you wish. There is a refrigerator available for you to store food and drink. There is a large supermarket (Shaw's) on the way to the lodge or stop somewhere for sandwiches (Kringles is a wonderful stop off on the way to Wildcat! &amp;nbsp;There are plenty of dining options in the Mount Washington Valley! Typically people collaborate on dinner, whether it's going out, staying in to cook or ordering take out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Regular guest fees are $20 per night.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;For new and repeat guests attending this weekend, we'll offer 2 for 1 guest fees!&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;That's just $20 total to stay with us two nights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- To RSVP - a $20 deposit is required. Please use the link above to make a payment through Amazon Payments. Sorry - No refunds for cancellations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions, and of course, please let us know if you plan to come up as soon as possible to help us in our planning!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Wedeln Ski House is always age 21+ only. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;THINK SNOW!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just come on in, and we'll either be by the fire or hanging out in the bar room!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chago</member_name><member_id>990941</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322956540000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320331557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Guests Weekend @ Wedeln Ski &amp; Outdoors Club!</name><id>39799262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322265600000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/39799262/</event_url></item>