<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt. Auburn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.371338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-699-1221 </phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>363595</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116469</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First off, Happy Thanksgiving to you all.  I hope you are all have a great day spending time with family, friends, food, and/or doing anything else that you might be up to today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A big full hearted gobble gobble thank you to all the members of the Incubator who have really made this group exist.  A special jello dessert shout out of course to all the assistant organizers for all the time they have put into the incubator as well.  Insert applause here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also a quick hello to you all from our creator and former leader Barbara who I chatted away with last night in person.  She misses the incubator and all of us greatly.  And let's admit it, we miss her too, esp the dance moves, lol.  (Barb you know you are awesome!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's keep rocking it out through the holidays and into the new year.  Forsee many things of the incubator in the future I do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With that, I'm going to get the Democracy Center for an incubator tomorrow night.  A bunch of you said you would be up for coming in the poll so I really hope an even bigger bunch of you can make it; Your faces, smiles, and company are all greatly missed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indulge yourselves with great food, great company, and warm thoughts for the rest of the day and have a great night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And most of all be thankful,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock Turkey on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Jedrusiak&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Cause I'll open the door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228093174000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227817641000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Thanksgiving Incubators!  Now let's work off all the turkey with laughter!</name><id>9240244</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227918600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/9240244/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>