<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Biotech Patents          &lt;br /&gt;When:              Tuesday, November 30 to Wednesday, December 01, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:             Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website:           &lt;a href="http://www.americanconference.com/pharma_bio_lifescience/BiotechPatents.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americanco...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The biotech industry is at an amazing crossroads right now- while practitioners are facing daunting challenges in the shape of conflicting case law and evolving legislation, there is also a unique possibility to maximize market share.  Biotech leaders must capitalize on this epic opportunity to get in on the ground floor of landmark Supreme and District case law and statutory law.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;At ACI’s 12th Advanced Forum on Biotech Patents, leading biotech counselors and lawmakers will share insights and best practices on topics such as:&lt;br /&gt;How generic companies will implement the now-approved follow-on biologic pathway, including what is patentable, exclusivity, and patent resolution; &lt;br /&gt;How to draft and protect claims going forward in light of the attacks on the patentability of genes and diagnostic methods in Bilski and Myriad; &lt;br /&gt;Advanced claim drafting strategies and how to incorporate both the written description and enablement requirements; &lt;br /&gt;Avoiding inequitable conduct- lessons from Therasense, Inc. v. Becton, Dickinson &amp;amp; Co.; &lt;br /&gt;How to work the PTO rules and the patent prosecution highway in order to streamline the patent approval process and extend actual patent life; and &lt;br /&gt;Developing global strategies for minimizing risk and maximizing profit while filing and protecting patents abroad&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291126941000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279550433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biotech Patents </name><id>14145370</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291122000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/14145370/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>