<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1374 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341682</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zenna Noodle Bar</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1526022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come to dinner where we will talk film (among other things) and stay for the film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For consideration of Zenna Noodle Bar, RSVPs close at 3:00 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please specify in your RSVP if you will not be joining us for both parts of the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, if your plans change,&amp;nbsp;be sure to update your RSVP accordingly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See You A The Movies, Betsey (&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;will be waving a red meetup card&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What reviewers and promoters have written . . .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(bold print bg's)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a bold new feature version of Jane Eyre, director Cary Joji Fukunaga (Sin Nombre) and screenwriter Moira Buffini (Tamara Drewe) infuse a contemporary immediacy into Charlotte Bront&amp;euml;&amp;rsquo;s timeless, classic story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mia Wasikowska [one of my favorite actresses, bg]&amp;nbsp;(Alice in Wonderland, [In Treatment and The Kids Are All Right, bg]) and Michael Fassbender (Inglourious Basterds) star in the iconic lead roles of the romantic drama, the heroine of which continues to inspire new generations of devoted readers and viewers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 19th Century-set story, Jane Eyre (Wasikowska) suddenly flees Thornfield Hall, the vast and isolated estate where she works as a governess for Ad&amp;egrave;le Varens, a child under the custody of Thornfield&amp;rsquo;s brooding master, Edward Rochester (Fassbender). The imposing residence &amp;ndash; and Rochester&amp;rsquo;s own imposing nature &amp;ndash; have sorely tested her resilience. With nowhere else to go, she is extended a helping hand by clergyman St. John Rivers (Jamie Bell) and his family. As she recuperates in the Rivers&amp;rsquo; Moor House and looks back upon the tumultuous events that led to her escape, Jane wonders if the past is ever truly past&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;from New York Times, A.O. Scott:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reader, I liked it&lt;/strong&gt;. This &amp;ldquo;Jane Eyre,&amp;rdquo; energetically directed by &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/person/432545/Cary-Fukunaga?inline=nyt-per"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #004276"&gt;Cary Joji Fukunaga&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (&amp;ldquo;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/451507/Sin-Nombre/overview"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #004276"&gt;Sin Nombre&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo;) from a smart, trim script by Moira Buffini (&amp;ldquo;Tamara Drewe&amp;rdquo;), is a splendid example of how to tackle the daunting duty of turning a beloved work of classic literature into a movie. Neither a radical updating nor a stiff exercise in middlebrow cultural respectability, Mr. Fukunaga&amp;rsquo;s film tells its venerable tale with lively vigor and an astute sense of emotional detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The director does not exactly make the task look easy, but the wild and misty moors, thanks to the painterly eye of the cinematographer, Adriano Goldman, certainly look beautiful, and Dario Marianelli&amp;rsquo;s music strikes all the right chords of dread, tenderness and longing. Bront&amp;euml;&amp;rsquo;s themes and moods &amp;mdash; the modulations of terror and wit, the matter-of-fact recitation of events giving way to feverish breathlessness &amp;mdash; are carefully preserved, though her narrative has been somewhat scrambled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;from Salon.com, Andrew O'Hehir:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adapting a Victorian classic definitely isn't the obvious choice for Fukunaga, a California native of half-Japanese ancestry whose acclaimed debut, &lt;a href="http://www.salon.com/entertainment/movies/beyond_the_multiplex/feature/2009/03/19/fukunaga"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;"Sin Nombre,"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; was a violent indie thriller, made entirely in Spanish and mostly shot in Mexico. &lt;strong&gt;But maybe it was time for "Jane Eyre" to be set free from an overdose of Englishness&lt;/strong&gt;, and on the evidence so far, we're talking about a young director with a tremendous gift for cinema and almost limitless range. Either way, this retelling is vivid, alive and loaded with a doomed passionate intensity that feels very Bront&amp;euml;-esque. Arguably Fassbender and Wasikowska are both too good-looking for these roles; Jane is meant to be a plain, Quakerish girl and Rochester to be brooding and ugly. About the best way I can explain it is that both are such physical actors, and so committed to these characters, that their prettiness never gets in the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Purchase tickets in advance of 5:00 pm Zenna Noodle Bar for 6;45 pm Jane Eyre at The Coolidge Corner Theatre</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300756847000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>5:00 pm Zenna Noodle for film discussion and dinner
6:45 pm Coolidge Corner Theatre, 290 Harvard Street, Brookline, MA, 617-734-2500</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300325653000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jane Eyre, Sunday, March 20, 5:00 pm Zenna, 6:45pm  for 7:00 pm Film/ Coolidge</name><id>16950784</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300654800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16950784/</event_url></item>