<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Summer is in full-swing and the night life is heating up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us this Friday night at one of Boston's best lounges, Excelsior!  This is a great place to meet new and current members in a low key and intimate setting, before heading out to one of the near-by clubs in the area.  This is a great event to meet new people and to get your groove on!  New and current members welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 8pm in the bar area at Excelsior.  This is a cozy bar lounge, so finding the group should not be difficult.  We will head over to one of the local clubs (to be determined - Mansion, Gypsy Bar, Liquor Store, etc.) around 9:30pm to beat the lines.  Please meet us at Excelsior, and get there early as to have time to meet folks and beat the lines later.  Cover:  None for Excelsior, but there will be a cover for the club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue.  If traveling by T, Boylston the closest T stop on the green line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214880142000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>It's a Friday night in the summer in Boston!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214286057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Downtown Boston Nightlife Mixer and Dancing This Friday, June 27!</name><id>8202867</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214611200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8202867/</event_url></item>