<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Yes, I am breaking up the Bonds.  I would like to do Bond and West Bond via Zealand and Zeacliff to do a little &amp;quot;exploring&amp;quot; and perhaps at another date hike Bondcliff /Bond via Bondcliff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will enter and exit the wilderness via the relatively flat Zealand Trail.  The  real hike begins at Zealand Hut, where we will take the Ethan Pond  trail to the steep and less-often-used Zeacliff trail to begin the  ascent.  Zeacliff provides the opportunity to view Carrigain Notch and  the Zeacliff outlook.  The Zeacliff trail will bring us to the  Twinway, which we will follow from Zealand over to Guyot.  On Guyot,  at the junction of the Twinway and Bondcliff, we will turn left onto Bondcliff and ascend Mt Bond.  On the return, we will bear left at the  junction with West Bond Spur and ascend West Bond.  We will then  follow the Twinway back to the Zealand Hut.  &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Book Time is  approximately 13hr 30 minutes&lt;/span&gt;.  I would like to do it a bit faster  than book time so please only sign up for this hike if you are  familiar with the terrain and can hike faster than book time along  some of the easier sections of this hike (Zealand Trail, Ethan Pond  and relatively moderate parts of the Twinway).&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Zealand Trailhead on Zealand Road at 7am.  Because this is a LONG hike, I expect that everyone will bring a flashlight and/or headlamp, just in case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone has done this and has comments or suggestions, please post them for everyone's benefit!&lt;br /&gt;-------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Partially Plagerized from my White Mountain Guide Book for your benefit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zealand Trail &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(Enter)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;2.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;1hr 40 minutes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mostly flat, following old railroad grade.  I just did this this week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ethan Pond Trail &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(We would do this SECTION of the trail IN REVERSE)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;40 min&lt;br /&gt;1.3 mi&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;....follows an old railroad grade on a gradual cruve into Zealand  Notch with its steep, fire-scarred walls.  As the trail crosses the talus slopes of Whitewall Mtn, it comes into the open with fine  views...in the middle of this section the Zeacliff Trail diverges..The  Ethan Pond Trail soon reenters the woods and continues on the remains  of the railroad grade (which is badly washed out in places) to the  junction with Zealand Trail and the Twinway.  For Zealand Falls Hut  turn sharp left onto the Twinway and follow it for .2 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zeacliff Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;1.4 miles&lt;br /&gt;1500 ft&lt;br /&gt;1hr 25 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail runs from the Ethan Pond Trail 1.3 miles south of its junction with Zealand Pond to the Twinway .1 mi west of the Zeacliff  outlook.  It is an attractive trail, much less frequently used than most trails in this area, &lt;b&gt;but extremely steep and rough in parts and  not recommended for hikers with heavy packs&lt;/b&gt;...The trail leaves the  Ethan Pond Trail and descends west over open talus, then drops very  steeply to cross Whitewall Brook at .2 mi.  It then climbs very steeply up an old slide at first.  The grade eases up at .6 miles and  soon the trail reaches the top of the ridge, where it ascends  gradually through a beautiful birch forest, then swings left and  angles up to a rock face at 1.1 miles.  The main trail turns right  here and ascends steeply to the right of the rock face, then swings  right, passes an outlook toward Carrigain Notch and rejoins the main  trail.  Above this point, the trail ascends steeply to the ridgecrest  and the Twinway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Twinway&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; (Ascent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;2.9 Miles&lt;br /&gt;2 hrs&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...The trail (at the junction with Zeacliff) then ascends over several  ledgy humps and crosses a sag at 1.9 miles, where a side path leads  off to the left and reaches the shore of Zeacliff Pond in .1 mile.   The main trail ascends a rather steep pitch with a ladder to a ledge  overlooking the pond, then continues along the crest of the ridge over several wooded knowbs.  At 3.1 miles, just after crossing the height-of-land on the last of these knobs, it reaches a small cairn marking a  side path on the right that runs nearly level .1 mi to the true summit of Zealand Mtn.  The main trail descends sharply to a col then climbs  moderately up the long ridge to Mt. Guyot, breaking into the open just as it reaches the summit.  It then descends a short distance over open rocks to the junction with the Bondcliff Trail on the left at 4.4 miles.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bondcliff &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(We would do this section of the trail IN REVERSE)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;1.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;55 minutes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...&amp;quot;summit of Mt. Bond which commands a magnificent unrestricted view  of the surrounding wilderness and mountains.  The trail descends  North, crossing a minor knob, then drops down rather steeply past the  spur path to West Bond...and leaves the Pemigewasset Wilderness.  It  reaches the Bond-Guyot col...where a spur path descends right...to  Guyot Campsite and its spring.  The Bondcliff Trail then ascends to  the bare south summit of Mt Guyot and continues in the open .2 miles  to its junction with the Twinway .1 miles west of the higher, but less  open, north summit of Guyot.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;West Bond Spur&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;200 ft&lt;br /&gt;20 minutes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This short path provides access to the sharp rocky summit of the West Peak of Mt. Bond, which is perched high above the deep valleys of an  extensive wilderness area, commanding magnificent views.  The entire  trail is in the Pemigewasset Wilderness.  It leaves the Bondcliff  trail .6 mi north of the summit of Mt. Bond and .3 mi south of the spur to Guyot Campsite, descends moderately for .3 mil to the col at the  foot of West Bond and ascends moderately for a short distances.  It  then climbs the steep cone to the summit, which is the most easterly  of several small peaks on a ridge running east and west.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Twinway &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(Descent)(We would do this section of the trail IN REVERSE)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;4.4 Miles&lt;br /&gt;2400'&lt;br /&gt;3hrs 25 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the junction of Zealand and Ethan Pond trails, the Twinway crosses  the outlet of Zealand Pond, then climbs steeply on rock steps to Zealand Falls Hut, passing a side path left to a viewpoint for Zealand  &lt;br /&gt;Falls.  it then ascends moderately, passing a junction on the right  with the Lend-A-Hand Trail just before it crosses two branches of Whitewall Brook on ledges, and continues to climb steadily through a  &lt;br /&gt;fine forest of birches toward the crest of Zealand Ridge.  At 1.4 miles, where the trail levels off and swings right, a loop side path continues straight ahead, passing over the magnificent Zeacliff outlook and rejoining the main trail 50 yards west of its point of departure.  The Twinway passes a junction with the Zeacliff Trail on the left, then ascends over several ledgy humps and crosses a sag at  1.9 miles, where a side path leads off to the left and reaches the  shore of Zeacliff Pond in .1 mile.  The main trail ascends a rather  &lt;br /&gt;steep pitch with a ladder to a ledge overlooking the pond, then  continues along the crest of the ridge over several wooded knowbs.  At  3.1 miles, just after crossing the height-of-land on the last of these  knobs, it reaches a small cairn marking a side path on the right that  runs nearly level .1 mi to the true summit of Zealand Mtn.  The main trail descends sharply to a col then climbs moderately up the long  ridge to Mt. Guyot, breaking into the open just as it reaches the summit.  It then descends a short distance over open rocks to the  junction with the Bondcliff Trail on the left at 4.4 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zealand Trail &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(Exit)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;2.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;1hr 40 minutes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mostly flat, following old railroad grade.  I just did this this week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282859783000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280892821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bond and West Bond ONLY</name><id>14313122</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282820400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14313122/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/4/5/global_17059861.jpeg</photo_url></item>