<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>254 Crown St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.306161</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-495-8924</phone><name>Bar</name><city>New Haven</city><id>772983</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.930206</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We've got the back room at Bar all to ourselves from 7 to 10 with martini specials, free pizza and doorprizes -- all for a donation of $10. Proceeds from this event will go to cancer research, as our very own Sandra is training her butt off for a triathlon to raise money for the Leukemia &amp;amp; Lymphoma Society. (For more info about Sandra's fundraising, click &lt;a href="http://www.active.com/donate/tntct/tntctSAbbott" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out and start your weekend with tasty beverages, free goodies and a warm fuzzy feeling from supporting a great cause. (Ok, maybe you'll owe that warm, fuzzy feeling to the tasty beverages as well.) And don't forget Thursday night is $1 drafts after 10 at Bar, so plan on sticking around to continue the evening in true NHC fashion.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The back room at BAR is huge so feel free to bring as many friends, family members and coworkers as you like!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**UPDATE**You're not gonna want to miss a chance to win all kinds of free stuff! Doorprizes include gift certificates from Barcelona, Caffe Bottega, Nikkita, Miya's Sushi, Kudeta, Pacifico, Koffee Too, Cristy's, and Libby's Pastries as well as T-shirts, free manicure and other goodies.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174870318000</updated><rating><average>4.84999990463</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172797571000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Loads of Great Doorprizes at Our Exclusive BAR Party</name><id>5527997</id><headcount>54</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174604400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5527997/</event_url></item>