<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>233 Western Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01929</zip><lat>42.621984</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978.290.8190</phone><name>The Farm Bar &amp; Grille</name><city>Essex</city><id>1232673</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.814240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Entrain at The Farm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;4.11.10 UPDATE: Janet and I have closed this event to new RSVP's seeing that The Farm/Brad is not holding tickets for us anymore.  I have called in the RSVP for dinner, if you didn't call in your RSVP for your ticket, please change your RSVP on the site.  We are looking forward to seeing you at this event! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come check out Entrain at The Farms first official &amp;quot;concert”. Entrain they will be performing on April 16th, tickets are $20 and this show is sure to sell out!  The Farm is only selling 100 tickets and as of today they are almost sold out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;b&gt;4.6.10 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; Brad said that he will extend the date that he is holding the tickets for us, the &lt;b&gt;new date is Friday 4/9&lt;/b&gt;.  You still have to call in and reserve and pay for your ticket, cause after Friday he will not be holding them for us and he will sell them!  Be prepared you will NOT be able to get a ticket at the door.  When you call in for your ticket please change your RSVP on the site to let us know that you are coming, and if you will be joining us for dinner.  If you have changed your mind and you will not be attending please change your RSVP on the site.  We have this on 3 of our meetup sites and we have approx 10-15 people that have already called in for their tickets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket information:&lt;br /&gt;The Farm/Brad will be holding 20 tickets for us and you only have until Monday 4/5/10 to call in your ticket, so if you want to go please call in your RSVP.  If you call after Monday then you can not be guaranteed a ticket.  You will be calling Brad’s cell phone: 978-290-8190, leave a message and he will call you back.  When you call tell him you are “RSVPing with the Meetup Group”.  The tickets will be held at the Farm for you in an envelope with either Meetup on it or your name.  &lt;b&gt;When you call Brad you can give him your credit card #, and he will process your payment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About The Farm:&lt;br /&gt;This is a great local hang out, with awesome menu selections.  Check out their current menu at:  &lt;a href="http://www.farmbargrille.com/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.farmbargri...&lt;/a&gt;  But on Thursday their spring menu comes out which will include: featuring Fish Tacos, pan seared Scallops, and much much more, so check back on or after Thursday.  I hear their Pulled Pork Nachos are awesome!!  Gonna have to check them out!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Entrain:&lt;br /&gt;Spend an unforgettable evening and dance the night away with Entrain they are back with drums blazing as furious as ever! You'll find it hard to sit still during this tour-de-force of percussive rock music from one of the longest running bands in the HGMN. Rhythms literally overwhelm you as this ensemble incorporates a worldwide litany of influences into a freight.  Entrain will go on approx 9:30-10:00.  Let’s get their early grab some dinner, relax and dance the rest of the night away.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner: &lt;br /&gt;I will be calling a reservation for us for dinner on Monday 4/5, make sure that you put on your RSVP that you will be coming for “Dinner and music.”  Or if you want to only come to dance/see Entrain.  Just put that you in your RSVP.  This will be very helpful so I give the correct count for the dinner reservation. IF your plans change please update the site as soon as you can.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where to meet:&lt;br /&gt;Come on in the restaurant and look for the Meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of parking in their parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late please call the Meetup phone at: 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271633988000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270000634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Entrain at The Farm</name><id>13043762</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271460600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/13043762/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/4/global_9199748.jpeg</photo_url></item>