<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Temple Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304665</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-498-2500</phone><name>Criterion Cinema</name><city>New Haven</city><id>827452</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928467</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(Note: Only minorly edited 5/13 to add pre-meetup drink, RSVP deadline) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The newest rendition of a very old Legend starts in theaters this Friday!  It's the newest version of &lt;u&gt;Robin Hood&lt;/u&gt;!  My current plan is to go see the official first showing at Midnight (Thursday going into Friday) at Criterion in New Haven, and I invite anyone interested to come along! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Criterion Cinema's is right in Downtown New Haven, on Temple Street right across from the Temple Street parking Garage.  I plan to be in the lobby approximately 20 minutes before show time and go in 15 min before or as soon as all &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's show up so we can try and get good seats.  If you're going to be late you can text or call me and I'll try to save you a seat, but I have no idea how popular this premier will be.  Also, once the lights are dimmed I will be shutting off my phone.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Addition:&lt;/b&gt; Some of us plan to grab a drink and or munchies before hand at a near by bar.  I will post the location of that below once it's determined.  As such I've put a 10pm deadline to RSVP, only so that I can check it before I go to the bar and know who (how many) to look for.  If one decides last minute they want to come you're still welcome, just if that's the case please RSVP by my cell phone so I know to look for you.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're each on our own for Tickets, which are on sale already ($11 last I checked, $12 if going through the Internet) and you should be able to order online if you wish here: &lt;a href="http://www.movietickets.com/house_detail.asp?house_id=9192&amp;amp;showdate=2&amp;amp;err=9b" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.movieticke...&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;I hope everyone present will be courteous to their fellow cinema goers (as well as NHC members) and keep talking or other distractions to a minimum during the show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Background:         &lt;br /&gt;Robin Hood was always a favorite story/movie of mine growing up.  It has been released in many different versions, all telling it a little differently.  But for those of you who whom some how have avoided this highly popular tale, this is the basics of most versions:  An expert Archer in 13th century England returns from the crusades and fights against the tyranny of current rulers while the true King is away at War.  First name always Robin, real last name varies by version, he becomes known as &amp;quot;Robin Hood&amp;quot; whom fights and robs the rich in order to give charity to the poor.  There is also a plot of romance with the lovely maid Marion whom is sought for courtship by one of the tyrannical rulers.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info on this movie, or to watch the trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.robinhoodthemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.robinhoodt...&lt;/a&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you probably have the same reaction as I first did when seeing just the title, which was to begin to roll my eye and say &amp;quot;Another one?&amp;quot;.  &lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;But then I saw that this was starring Russel Crowe, and directed by Sir Ridley Scott.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  This has been a winning combination in the past.  Some of you may even say, &amp;quot;Isn't this just 'Gladiator 2', but in 13th century England then?&amp;quot;, to which I say: yes, yes it might be, but I have no problem with that!   Now on top of that add the talents of Cate Blanchett as Marion, and William Hurt will be in it as well.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll serve as the contact for this event.  My cell number is: 315 345 9348, though I will shut off my phone once the lights go dim in the theater.         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apologies for the some what late notice of this post.  Believe it or not I had a hard time getting the Manger to even tell me if they were going to have it last week, and yet a few days later here they are with a midnight premier available none the less!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait in the lobby until either everyone who's RSVPed Yes has shown up, or 15 minutes before show time by my cell.  You could also text or call and I would attempt to save you a seat up until show time.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273882882000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273624291000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Midnight Movie:  Robin Hood !</name><id>13455535</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273808700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/13455535/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/9/global_14984361.jpeg</photo_url></item>