<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come on out and see the band STRETCH play a FREE SHOW at the Burren!&lt;br /&gt;Located in Davis Square in Somerville, MA. Parking is between Elm and Orchard st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;dq=the+burren+loc:+Somerville,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=247+Elm+Street,+Somerville,+MA+02144&amp;amp;geocode=3482735296082139167,42.395361,-71.121867&amp;amp;ll=42.395361,-71.121867&amp;amp;iwstate1=dir:to&amp;amp;iwloc=A&amp;amp;f=d" target="_blank"&gt;Get Directions/Map here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.burren.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.burren.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stretch is typically a 5 piece Jazz band playing a unique Jazz, Fusion and even Reggae mix. Dave is playing Horns, Paul and Mike on Guitars, George on Bass and their new Drummer Randy. &lt;br /&gt;Stretch does not play very often so catch them when you can, you won't regret it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/stretchinboston" target="_blank"&gt;Listen to STRETCH!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The band starts around 10pm and plays till 1am. They are playing in the back room at the Burren.&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested the Burren serves food till 9pm I believe, not a bad place to get a bite to eat before the show. There is also good indian food, and other dinning choices close by.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I usually get there around 9 to 9:30pm to get a good spot to sit, stay as late as you care to on a weeknight. Especially if you have to work in the morning as I do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I usually only get a couple days notice when they play, sorry if it wasn't enough notice for you all. I noticed Stretch is not listed on the Burren's Calendar, But I'm sure they will be there this Wednesday so will I.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to Meetup with some of you there.   &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;E-mail me if you have any questions...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There is usually a small crowd so there should be no trouble finding me at one of the tables right in front of the band. I may be doing some recording of the band as well. Stop over and say Hello!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg D</member_name><member_id>4879355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201364247000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This is one of the better progressive Jazz bands in the area, if you like Jazz you'll appreciate this FREE SHOW!</why><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201013103000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stretch (Jazz) at the Burren</name><id>7170454</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201143600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/7170454/</event_url></item>