<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Free Saturday Morning Outdoor Meditation Class With Energy Healer David Petero &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us on at the Wellness Center at 10:30am.&lt;br /&gt;We will all walk over to to the West Haven Green for a relaxing &lt;br /&gt;Morning Meditation sponsored by &lt;br /&gt;Look At Me Now, A Wellness Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional information please call (203)-933-2200 or &lt;br /&gt;click on the link below to learn more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lookatmenow22.com/EnergyTherapy.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://lookatmenow22....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;lookatmenow22.com/EnergyTherapy.html&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being from West Haven, I am aware of the parking &lt;br /&gt;Problems on Campbell Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;I am also aware of parking areas&lt;br /&gt;That others might not be aware of or use.&lt;br /&gt;Most of the time, I use the large parking area that is behind&lt;br /&gt;Loris store.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, turn into the side street&lt;br /&gt;Of Curtis Place next to&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony s Pizza Italian Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;(Restaurant has had a few different names over the years &lt;br /&gt;But this is its latest name.).&lt;br /&gt;There is a large parking area behind there.&lt;br /&gt;Going to Campbell Avenue, you can walk over towards&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony s.&lt;br /&gt;Then turn right on Campbell Avenue to Lori s store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I walk over toward the right from the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt; There is an alley between the buildings.  &lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, I turn left.  Loris store is a few stores in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a healthy and fun Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lori Larsen is UZ POC for this Event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216046481000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215268124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UZ Researches Morning Meditation Class W Energy Healer David Petero </name><id>8280591</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215873000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/8280591/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/f/global_2489375.jpeg</photo_url></item>