<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A restored masterpiece. I've never seen it, but the description and the story make it a compelling flm to see.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most fun you have this summer may be watching the new 35mm restoration of a little-seen masterpiece from England on the big (single) screen at Cinestudio! Based on a short story by Graham Greene, Went the Day Well? is winning critical raves in New York and London, as well as comparisons to Hitchcock and the classic Ealing studios&amp;rsquo; Kind Hearts and Coronets. It begins cozily enough as a portrait of a cheerful English village, but brilliantly changes tone into a wartime thriller as Nazis stage an invasion, inspiring everyone from the gossipy postmistress to the estate poacher to take up arms. Made in 1942 when victory over Germany was far from certain, Went the Day Well? Is a triumph of decency over brutality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;A conspiracy thriller, a black-comic nightmare, and a surrealist masterpiece!&amp;rdquo; The Guardian UK &amp;ldquo;ENGAGING AND SURPRISINGLY AFFECTING. Cavalcanti&amp;rsquo;s design sense serves him well, and the beautifully lit scenes and crisp editing look like something MGM could have been proud of. William Walton contributes a brief but suitably grand score.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Kristin Thompson &amp;ldquo;A RICH AND PROVOCATIVE FILM. Deserves to be celebrated more widely.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; David Cairns&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby til 7:30.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312158645000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311460793000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Went The Day Well</name><id>26797071</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312154100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/26797071/</event_url></item>