<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>690 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.287613</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 482-8898</phone><name>Empire Garden</name><city>Boston</city><id>669036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**PLEASE NOTE: I changed the time to 10.30 am. We will likely have to wait to be seated but this way, it's a bit more civilized than 9.30am, plus we can chat while we are waiting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After calling and searching without success for venues that could house a larger meetup, I received an email from one of our members, Huang, who suggested Dim Sum and tea at Empire Garden Restaurant in Chinatown. They serve tea (generally Oolong) with the Dim Sum. I cannot vouch for the quality of the tea except to say that most Chinese restaurants serve decent teas (though likely not top-grade). Nonetheless, it would be a good venue to meet members and get to know each other and there is no seating limit. I have set the time for 10.30 am because if we go any later, the waiting list will likely be 45 minutes or more. Once we meet and get to know each other, I hope to get more suggestions regarding meetup venues/events and we can also maybe have a real Chinese gongfu tea ceremony at a future meetup if enough people are interested. My intention for the group is to learn more about tea and to sample and track down high-grade/rare teas together, but this meetup will be a nice ice-breaker and 'getting to know you' session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please note that we will be dividing the cost of the tab between members of each table since it is very hard to separate the tab for individual diners for Dim Sum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP Yes, please make every effort to come as I will be making reservations based on the RSVP. Please respect other members by being on time, and not making them wait for you if you are not coming. Please note that if you change your RSVP to No at the last minute, we will likely not get that message until after the event and might end up waiting for you anyway.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the sign for Boston Tea Connoisseurs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>HS Loh</member_name><member_id>9828275</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256243806000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Tea Connoisseurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Connoisseurs</urlname><id>1479042</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Connoisseurs</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252167563000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tea and Dim Sum</name><id>11297014</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254061800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Connoisseurs/events/11297014/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/f/global_9325583.jpeg</photo_url></item>