<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>108.2 mile marker 1-93 Northbound lane</address_2><address_1>Trailhead Parking</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.142196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lafayette Place Parking Lot</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>239317</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.681663</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be hiking Mts Little Haystack, Mt. Lincoln and Mt. Lafayette loop. Please read the below hike description before deciding to sign up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is each and every individuals responsibility to read and agree to the liability/waiver posted on this site. It is also the responsibility of each and every individual to adhere to the hikers responsibility outlined on this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that we are meeting in the Northbound lane of the Lafayette Place Parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Lafayette, Mt. Lincoln, Little Haystack Mtn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mountains: Little Haystack Mtn. (4760'), Mt. Lincoln (5089'), Mt. Lafayette (5260')&lt;br /&gt;Trails: Falling Waters Trail, Franconia RidgeTrail, Greenleaf Trail, Old Bridle Path, Appalachian Trail&lt;br /&gt;Region: NH - Central East&lt;br /&gt;Franconia Notch State Park&lt;br /&gt;Location: Franconia, NH&lt;br /&gt;Rating: Difficult&lt;br /&gt;Features: Summits, views, cascades, hut, brook, 4000-footers, loop hike&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 8.8 miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain: 3860 feet (cumulative)&lt;br /&gt;Hiking Time: Actual: 7:30 Typical: 7:20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route Summary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a loop hike starting and ending at the Lafayette Place parking area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Start out on Falling Waters Trail (which for the first 0.2 mile is also the same trail as the Old Bridle Path).&lt;br /&gt;• After 0.2 mile, turn right to stay on Falling Waters Trail and follow that until its on Little Haystack Mountain, 3.2 miles from the parking area.&lt;br /&gt;• From the end of Falling Waters Trail, turn left onto Franconia Ridge Trail.&lt;br /&gt;• Follow Franconia Ridge Trail 0.7 mile up to the summit of Mt. Lincoln.&lt;br /&gt;• Continue on Franconia Ridge Trail, down the other side of Mt. Lincoln, for 0.9 which will put you on Mt. Lincoln's summit.&lt;br /&gt;• From Mt. Lincoln, turn left to descend on Greenleaf Trail.&lt;br /&gt;• Follow Greenleaf Trail for 1.1 miles until reaching Greenleaf Hut and Eagle Lakes.&lt;br /&gt;• Turn left to get on Old Bridle Path.&lt;br /&gt;• Follow Old Bridle Path for 2.9 miles all the way back to the parking lot (upon reaching the junction with Falling Waters Trail, turn right).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Falling Waters Trailhead (1780') 0.0 0.0 0:00 0:00&lt;br /&gt;Little Haystack Mtn. summit (4760') 3.2 3.2 3:00 3:00&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Lincoln summit (5089') 0.7 3.9&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Lafayette summit (5260') 0.9 4.8 1:00 4:00&lt;br /&gt;Greenleaf Hut/Eagle Lake (4220') 1.1 5.9&lt;br /&gt;Old Bridle Path trailhead (1780') 2.9 8.8 3:30 7:30&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michele</member_name><member_id>9237839</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274835264000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268949328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lincoln - Lafayette loop</name><id>12926855</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274529600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12926855/</event_url></item>