<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWEST STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're the lucky people who got in! Congrats! We have an enormous group (the biggest the FMM has ever seen, actually), so here's how I'll keep my sanity (things you can do for me and for your fellow members):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Save my cell phone number -- 508/308-4897&lt;/b&gt; -- to your phone. &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Now.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; So if you need to call me (if you get lost, stranded somewhere in the theater, etc.) you'll have it on you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make sure you &lt;b&gt;show up at 6:00&lt;/b&gt;. If you are a few minutes late or get stuck in traffic, that's okay. We'll be &lt;b&gt;heading into the theater between 6:10 and 6:15 SHARP!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;As people show up, &lt;b&gt;I'll be selling small popcorn and small soda vouchers for $3 each&lt;/b&gt; (they're cheaper through me than at the counter). You can buy your treats one by one and rejoin the group so that there's not a huge line at the snack counter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand, please, that there are &lt;b&gt;probably more vouchers given out to the public than there are seats in the theater&lt;/b&gt;. I think that 45 minutes before the movie starts will get us seats, but if I'm wrong, and we can't all sit down, &lt;u&gt;I apologize profusely ahead of time&lt;/u&gt;. Other than getting there early, I can't think of any way to avoid the possibility that the theater just may not have room for us. We're not the only people going to this movie, unlike other movies (Christmas Carol much?!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We may need to split up as a group in order to get seats. Again, I kinda hope I'm wrong about this and that 45 minutes will let us sit together, but &lt;b&gt;be open to the possibility that we'll just meet again out in front of the theater doors after the movie and regroup.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If we have to wait to get in the theater and I'm overestimating the time we need before the movie, I see this as the lesser of the 2 evils (vs. them running out of seats and us not getting to see the movie). The movie starts at 7:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will be going out afterwards to TGI Fridays&lt;/b&gt;, if you want to go. Friday's can usually handle big groups on short notice (as in, we show up, they seat us). If you don't want to go out after the movie, that's perfectly fine. We won't like you any less, and we hope to see you again for a movie soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you get &amp;quot;lost&amp;quot; or disconnected from the group at any time, feel free to call my cell -- 508/308-4897 -- and I'll help you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Okay, the admin stuff is over with. PHEW! Now let's have some fun! See you tomorrow night (Monday night) at 6:00 right inside the ticket lobby of the Framingham AMC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP up to date, especially if you have a last-minute cancellation. There are people from our group who want to come, but can't because I've run out of tickets. I've told them to stay tuned on Monday for further updates to see if a spot opens up. Help me help you and all that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you tomorrow night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEWER STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So all 15 slots have been taken. And I got the passes today in the mail. And -- lucky us!! -- it turns out she sent me 17 passes and that each of them is good for 2 people. Which means.... &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;we can take 34 people&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, not 15 (and definitely not 6)! So... if any of you wants to invite any friends, just include that in your RSVP and we can just use the tally there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, this is a &lt;b&gt;free&lt;/b&gt; sneak preview of the movie. No one else will get to see this movie until it opens on Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seeing as how there's lots more people invited to this shindig (not just our group, obv), I'm a bit afraid they'll run out of seats. So we're going to alter our plans a little and &lt;b&gt;head into the theater at 6:15 not 6:30.&lt;/b&gt; This will hopefully ensure that we get seats -- maybe even together! And if we have to chat for a while before the movie starts, all the better. There may even be a movie trivia game to keep the fun rolling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So &lt;b&gt;plan on getting to the theater around 6:00&lt;/b&gt; and if you're a few minutes late, then that's okay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So glad I can open this up to so many more people! Thanks for understanding (I'm assuming you're understanding!) about the earlier time. If you're definitely coming, but can't get there before 6:30, I think I can get a ticket/seat for you and just meet you in the lobby when you show up. But you have to be DEFINITELY coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on Monday for this exciting (and free!!) event! To clarify, &lt;u&gt;the &amp;quot;normal&amp;quot; $2/person/meetup fee does NOT apply to this movie. But the $3 vouchers for soda and/or popcorn does apply (that's just a deal I extend to you for the AMC theater).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-D&lt;br /&gt;508-308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OMG, so within like 30 mins of posting this, all 6 tickets were spoken for. I've requested more tickets from my contact, so now 13 ppl instead of 6 can come. Please, though, if you RSVP yes, be aware that you may be taking someone else's spot. So keep your RSVPs up to date. If you want to come, but we're full, please check back this weekend to see if a spot opened up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--D&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If someone says &amp;quot;Would you like to see a free movie?&amp;quot; I'm interested. When that movie is one I was going to take the group to anyway, I'm so there! Even if it is short notice...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810073583/details" target="_blank"&gt;It's Complicated&lt;/a&gt; stars Meryl Streep, Alec Baldwin, and Steve Martin. With a cast like that and with the previews I've been seeing, it looks like a really hysterical movie. So take a break from your shopping and baking and yadda yadda and come with us! This movie opens on Christmas Day, but select people and groups are being invited to see it early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jane is the mother of three grown kids, owns a thriving Santa Barbara bakery/restaurant and has - after a decade of divorce - an amicable relationship with her ex-husband, attorney Jake. But when Jane and Jake find themselves out of town for their son's college graduation, things start to get complicated. An innocent meal together turns into the unimaginable - an affair. With Jake remarried to the much younger Agness, Jane is now, of all things, the other woman. Caught in the middle of their renewed romance is Adam, an architect hired to remodel Jane's kitchen. Healing from a divorce of his own, Adam starts to fall for Jane, but soon realizes he's become part of a love triangle. Should Jane and Jake move on with their lives, or is love truly lovelier the second time around? It's--complicated.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is completely free. &lt;b&gt;I only have 6 passes&lt;/b&gt;, so it's first-come-first-served. It's also that way at the theater on Monday night, so we're meeting especially early so that we have a chance to sit together. We'll be heading into the theater at &lt;b&gt;6:30 sharp&lt;/b&gt;. Usually I'm not such a stickler, but I want us all to get seats. &lt;b&gt;If you're running late, please call me. If you don't call, I can't guarantee you'll have a seat when you get there.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, I'll have $3 vouchers for small popcorns and small sodas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I don't see you on Monday, Merry Christmas, everyone! (Even if you don't celebrate Christmas, I hope your day is wonderful!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on Monday for this super-special event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508-308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263071357000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261066482000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's Complicated</name><id>12103598</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261436400000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12103598/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>