<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>910 Broadway, Rte 1 North</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.470512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781.231.2221</phone><name>Midwest Grille</name><city>Saugus</city><id>1171437</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.024985</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets go out to the Brazilian Buffett for Meat, Meat and More Meat.  Ladies and Gentlemen its salads for a week before going out to this restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Midwest Grille has been rated by Boston's Best &amp;amp; Phantom Gourmet every year since 2003.  The Waitstaff bring meat on skewers right over to your table and there is also a buffet for accompanying the entree.  But don't stop there...the desserts are fabtabulous also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Midwest Grill is a Brazilian BBQ with two Massachusetts locations. One in Cambridge and one on Route 1 North bound in Saugus right after Kowloons, &lt;b&gt;we will be going to the Saugus location.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Atmosphere&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;entering the restaurant you are immediately greeted by a live band playing near the entrance. The band is comprised of two people, one playing guitar and the other singing. The music they play is  Brazilian folk music, it is pleasant to listen to and gives the restaurant an authentic atmosphere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Food&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like most Brazilian BBQ restaurants dinner is served “Churrassco a Rodizio.” This means you pay one flat fee for all you can eat food, this includes a buffet of salads and side dishes as well meat that is brought around to the table on swords. At the Midwest Grill there is one buffet counter in the back of the dining room. On one side it has salad with your standard salad veggies, a pasta salad and some cheeses. The salad is all standard fare, nothing extraordinary. On the other side of the buffet is a very tasty garlic bread with an oil based garlic/cheese dip.  There is also a handful of side dishes on the buffet. There is a yellow rice with some pork in it, plain jasmine rice, mashed potatoes, beans, steamed carrots and broccoli, chicken wings, and some other hot items . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price of the buffet is $23.95.  RESERVATIONS MUST BE MADE IN ADVANCE, WHICH THE ORGANIZERS WILL BE TAKING CARE OF BUT PLEASE KEEP YOUR RSVP UPDATED SO THAT WE CAN GET A FINAL COUNT IN A COUPLE DAYS PRIOR TO THIS EVENT.  IF YOUR PLANS CHANGE AFTER THE EVENT RSVP DEADLINE, PLEASE CONTACT ONE OF THE ORGANIZERS IMMEDIATELY. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU ARE A MEMBER OF OUR OTHER GROUPS PLEASE ONLY RSVP ON ONE IN ORDER TO KEEP SPACES OPEN FOR OTHERS.  IF YOU ARE RSVP'D ON MORE THAN ONE SITE THE ORGANIZERS RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REMOVE YOU FROM THE OTHER SITE FOR THIS EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Meetup Table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268694664000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264377266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Midwest Grille Brazilian Buffet</name><id>12411125</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268521200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/12411125/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/6/global_12779222.jpeg</photo_url></item>