<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 491 9400</phone><name>Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>730460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Surely nerds pine fondly for the times when intellectual snobs were all the rage around academia!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conversation topics might be: the applied philosophy of the couch potato, (based on GB Shaw!); does evolutionary theory imply that humans are the most advanced monkey? Isn't time travel not just possible, but already happening, since we go forth second-by-second? What ash-cloud disruption? Should humans be flying in the first place? And other FUN provocative ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU DON'T NEED TO BE AN INTELLECTUAL TO COME. Just bring your opinions or questions about matters of truth &amp;amp; consequence, and be willing to listen. (&amp;quot;Of consequence&amp;quot; here, would not include, say, whether Brittney Spears' magazine photos should be airbrushed or not).&lt;br /&gt;AND: YOU ARE WELCOME TO FAKE IT! a lot of people, including in academia, are really good at this, you just need to bring along an aloof attitude full of irony... for recommendations it helps to see ehow.com, &amp;quot;how to become a pseudo intellectual&amp;quot;. &amp;quot;FAKE MOUSTACHES WELCOME&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE MEET AT THE LEGAL SEAFOOD OUTDOOR BAR patio in front of the Charles Hotel in Harvard Sq; at that hour there is shade. Large-size round-table seating is usually not hard to accomplish, but if you arrive earlier please graciously try to help grab table space for later arrivals. There is little pressure to order food, anyway this is a reasonably priced light-fare raw bar menu, not a full restaurant. LOOK FOR A ROW OF ROUND TABLES AND A NERD FUN SIGN to identify this Meetup. &lt;br /&gt;IF IT IS RAINING we meet right nearby, just inside the Charles Hotel at the NOIR bar &amp;amp; go from there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Street parking in Cambridge on Sundays is &amp;quot;unrestricted&amp;quot;. Parking is also available at the Charles Hotel garage, ask Legal Seafood about validating your parking ticket for a discount.&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Square is easily T-accessible via the Red Line subway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to share your ideas please post your comments as Wall &amp;quot;discussions&amp;quot; for this Meetup! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>duncan </member_name><member_id>9836304</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1275313012000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272900244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intellectual Snob Revival Redux</name><id>13367404</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275255000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13367404/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/d/global_2910317.jpeg</photo_url></item>