<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Stanhope St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348377</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6175723311</phone><name>33 Restaurant and Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>669046</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Sept. 4 Topic: EFFECTIVE NETWORKING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How do you effectively &amp;quot;work&amp;quot; and room and introduce yourself to complete strangers?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Thursday, September 4, we will welcome Diane Darling, author of The Networking Survival Guide and Networking for Career Success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As principal consultant for Effective Networking, Inc., she founded the company on the premise that everyone can learn to network, they just need to find their own style.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Combining interactive training, strategic planning and an exploration of the natural fears of networking, Darling demystifies the process by providing techniques that can be immediately implemented. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has received rave reviews for her seminars and speeches and is increasingly sought after as an expert resource on the subject of networking. She has appeared on NBC Nightly News, in The Wall Street Journal, San Francisco Chronicle, and The Boston Globe. She is a member of the CEO Club, Commonwealth Institute, Word of Mouth Marketing Association (WOMMA), and National Association of Women Business Owners (NAWBO). Darling is also a monthly columnist for the Boston Business Journal. She also teaches in the MBA program at Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Professionals of Color Business and Social Networking Group presents,&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bi-Monthly Networking Events at 33 Restaurant &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This is an informal social event, where you can get to know &lt;br /&gt; people and build relationships. We plan to hold networking &lt;br /&gt; socials on the 1st &amp;amp; 3rd Thursdays of the month. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; We aim to create a positive, relaxed atmosphere, were people &lt;br /&gt; can meet new friends and business contacts. In the coming &lt;br /&gt; months we will also invite speakers who will help us hone our &lt;br /&gt; networking skil ls, learn the art of small talk and promote our &lt;br /&gt; professional skills in the workplace. Please bring ideas for &lt;br /&gt; future meeting topics and seminars. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This event is FREE. Door prizes will be given away. Must be &lt;br /&gt; present to win. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bring your business cards, your smile and your networking &lt;br /&gt; skills and meet great people.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Red "Hello, My Name Is (Qiana) " Name Badge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Qiana Christian</member_name><member_id>5933597</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221776253000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219417155000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PCBS Network Meeting - Effective Networking Seminar</name><id>8598456</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220565600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/8598456/</event_url></item>