<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>259 Atwells Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.823586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gallery Z</name><city>Providence</city><id>1549063</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.426453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span&gt;Rhode Island Treasures&lt;/span&gt;
by Mike Bryce &lt;br /&gt; Show Dates: March 3rd - April 2nd, 2011 &lt;br /&gt; Opening Receptions: Thursday, March 17th, 5 - 9pm

&lt;a href="http://www.galleryzprov.com/galleryzprov/images/Treasures/Waterfire,%20Summer%27s%20Eve.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.galleryzprov.com/galleryzprov/images/Treasures/thumbs/Waterfire,%20Summer%27s%20Eve.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I.&lt;span&gt;&amp;mdash;On Thursday, March 17th, the opening reception for an exhibition of paintings by Mike Bryce will be held from 5:00&amp;mdash;9:00PM at Gallery Z.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Mike Bryce, a Rhode Island based artist, presents &amp;ldquo;Rhode Island Treasures&amp;rdquo;, a series of work celebrating the beauty of Rhode Island. Bryce received his BFA in painting, printmaking, sculpture, and photography from the University of Rhode Island in 1994, and went on to receive his MFA in painting and illustration from Syracuse University in 1998.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bryce has taught various courses in art and design as a college level educator at a number of universities and locations in the Rhode Island area, including Salve Regina, University of Rhode Island, the Community College of Rhode Island, the Newport Art Museum and CityArts Providence. Bryce has also taught at the Massachusetts College of Art, the Art Institute of Boston and Syracuse University.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Rhode Island&amp;rsquo;s imagery fuels Bryce&amp;rsquo;s passion. With a love for observing his surroundings, Bryce creates his art while feeling as if he is a part of his environment. Memories of playing in Hope Street Park, summer trips to Narragansett beach, or ferry rides to Block Island awaken a nostalgic feeling of warmth. Through his paintings, Bryce hopes to share some of this sentiment.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The opening reception will be held on Thursday, March 17th, from 5 to 9PM, and the show will run from March 3rd, to April 2nd, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unfortunately, I'll be out of town at a conference on Thursday- so bummed to miss it! If you're going, please say so in your RSVP, so others will know you're going! If you'd like to host, please let me know!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300400188000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Our own Mike Bryce is having a solo show at Gallery Z! Thursday, March 17th 5-7pm - check it out!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299370531000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opening at Gallery Z - Mike Bryce's solo show RI Treasures!</name><id>16812458</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300395600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/16812458/</event_url></item>