<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clear Conscience Cafe/Harvest Co-Op Market</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>687911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We'll finish off the year from the polls, but next year we'll be pulling from brand new polls (here's your hint to send book titles my way :-)  A revamping is on the way (hopefully in the next few weeks!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But for now, we're heading backwards, way backwards to throw a classic into the mix:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.penguin.co.uk/nf/Book/BookDisplay/0,,9780141907819,00.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.penguin.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;At twenty-seven, Anne Elliot is no longer young and has few romantic prospects. Eight years earlier, she had been persuaded by her friend Lady Russell to break off her engagement to Frederick Wentworth, a handsome naval captain with neither fortunenor rank. What happens when they encounter each other again is movingly told in Jane Austen's last completed novel. Set in the fashionable societies of Lyme Regis and Bath, Persuasion is a brilliant satire of vanity and pretension, but, above all,it is a love story tinged with the heartache of missed opportunities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Head on down to the Clear Conscience Cafe in Central Square.  Please note, I'm gonna miss this one, and i apologize well in advance.  Heading out of town for a bit the next couple weeks, so have crammed too much work into this one:-)   If you don't see a group of folks around a table or on the couches with at least one &amp;quot;Persuasion&amp;quot; out to see, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; the Cafe is a mad house, consider checking across the street at Au Bon Pain (684 Mass Ave) just in case we've been relocated :-)  But hopefully everyone will find each other with the greatest of ease (and the help of the book as a prop :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have fun!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257552588000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254999244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: Persuasion by Jane Austin</name><id>11579114</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257379200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/11579114/</event_url></item>