<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>848 Park Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02910</zip><lat>41.778857</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.467.7275</phone><name>RI Center for Performing Arts (RICPA)</name><city>Cranston</city><id>1443575</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436432</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>31.25</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>For this Meet-up we will try two new concepts.  The first is a matinee.  We will meet at the theater at 2:30 on Sunday, January 23rd for the matinee performance.  The second is a new theater.  This will be our first visit to the Rhode Island Center for Performing Arts which is in the historic Park Theater in Cranston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the description of the play on RICPA's website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[iIrish Need not apply or testify&lt;br /&gt;A trial where Irish Catholics were banned from the jury and the judge instructed that the testimony of Irishmen not be taken over that of native born Americans? That was justice in 1843 when an immigrant Irishman was found guilty of murder and ultimately hanged. John Gordon became the last person to be executed in the state of Rhode Island. His story is dramatized in a new play written and directed by former Cranston resident Ken Dooley. The play establishes John Gordon’s innocence and also identifies the actual murderer.&lt;br /&gt;“We feel that the Park Theatre is the natural place for the play to open, since it is only a few miles from the Sprague Mansion, not far from the path where the murder took place,” Piyush Patel, co-producer with Paul Plourde, explained.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $31.25. which includes the Amazon Payments service charge. Seating is reserved.  I will purchase the tickets on Monday, January 3rd.  Refunds will be available up until I purchase the tickets.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;I will send an e-mail including my cell phone number to all who RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;. Please contact me if you are running late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the theater at 2:30 PM.  I'll have everyone's ticket with me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the theater&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions are available on the &lt;a href="http://www.parktheatreri.com/about/directions" target="_blank"&gt;RICPA's Website.&lt;/a&gt;  Please be sure to allow time for traffic and parking!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside front entrance </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295877061000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291503849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Murder Trial of John Gordon</name><id>15642985</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295811000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/15642985/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/3/global_6290483.jpeg</photo_url></item>