<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Because of the snow storm that is predicted for this weekend,&lt;br /&gt;This event has been changed to Saturday, Dec. 29.&lt;br /&gt;Please change your RSVP if necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CT Paranormal has invited Greater New Haven Unknown Zone to their&lt;br /&gt;CT PRI Christmas Eggnog Party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I have said before, we have a few CT Paranormal members in our &lt;br /&gt;Group.  If you RSVP Yes in CT Paranormal site, then you are&lt;br /&gt;Encouraged to RSVP Yes in Unknown Zone.&lt;br /&gt;We are aware of the count so you can say Yes in &lt;br /&gt;Both sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CT Paranormal is a Private Location.&lt;br /&gt;Their address will not be shown on line.&lt;br /&gt;Their location will be sent to individual members&lt;br /&gt;Via e-mail if they RSVP Yes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This quote is from CT Paranormal;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello investigators, it's our annual Christmas Party!!! &lt;br /&gt;It gives us all a chance to wish each other a wonderful &lt;br /&gt;Holiday and and a beautiful New Year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and enjoy the fun and the spirit of the Holidays!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a dish.&lt;br /&gt;I will make the Ham!!! &lt;br /&gt;or I could make a Turkey!!&lt;br /&gt;with stuffing take a vote let me know :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please post what side dish or desert you will be bringing.&lt;br /&gt;See you there I will bring the Eggnog :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;End of quote.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It should be lots of fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is bad weather, then I am assuming that this&lt;br /&gt;Event will be cancelled and rescheduled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybes will be allowed in this Unknown Zone Site.&lt;br /&gt;I will just leave the Maybes there instead of&lt;br /&gt;Changing them to No this time.&lt;br /&gt;I still consider Maybes the day of the event &lt;br /&gt;To be the same as a No.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ho Ho Ho&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy all holidays or whatever else they are called this time of year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Yule &amp;amp; Winter Solstice for any Wiccans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, there is also snow predicted for Thursday into&lt;br /&gt;Friday, so be careful this Thursday and Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B&lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199764380000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196781821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deck The Halls Christmas Eggnog Party-Date Change</name><id>6854023</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198974600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6854023/</event_url></item>