<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>119 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02364</zip><lat>41.987522</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 585-5464</phone><name>Persy's Place</name><city>Kingston</city><id>806598</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.712393</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Good morning, fellow diners!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is being written one day after a long and hard-fought national election, and there is both good news and bad to report on the dining front. The bad news is a trend that has largely escaped the attention of the mainstream media, but one which concerns every SSDOMG member personally: We haven't run a breakfast since last December, nearly a year ago!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help! Flapjack withdrawal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The good news is that we, each of us, are not dealing with this alone: Someone stands ready to lead us into a new morning of coffee, homefries and Eggs Benedict! To say nothing of cornbread...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, seriously: Mike has been wanting to host another breakfast for SSDOMG for at least a couple months, and it's finally happening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the challenges with bringing a group like ours to breakfast is that many breakfast restaurants are simply too small to accomodate the numbers that our events can draw. There are some notable exceptions, however. One of them is a South Shore institution called Persy's Place, which first opened in Kingston in 1982, and still remains a family-run business even though there are now six Persy's restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About three years ago, the first Persy's restaurant was gutted by a fire and closed. This past summer, after rebuilding in its original location, Persy's opened again in Kingston. With seating for 90 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, you read right. Persy's is pretty much the grandaddy of breakfast restaurants, and it has a menu to match: Huge! Unfortunately they don't have a website, so there is no online version, but expect to find ALL your old breakfast favorites, plus a few you never thought of. And they give you cornbread. Life is good...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join Mike there on Saturday, November 22nd to greet a new day, as well as some old and hopefully some new friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP DEADLINE: Friday, November 21 @ 5:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Persy's is located on Route 3A, just south of Exit 9 from Route 3. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3, take Exit 9 (Route 3A) and head South on route 3A. The area around the exit is a cluster of restaurants and other businesses, including Mama Mia's (Italian) and Cancun (Mexican). You will almost immediately pass between a Mobil gas station and a Shell gas station. As you pass the two gas stations, look for Persy's to appear on your left, across the street from the now-closed restaurant Bocatu and just before Light &amp;amp; Leisure and a Kentucky Fried Chicken on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN and WHERE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 22 @ 10:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;Persy's Place&lt;br /&gt;119 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Kingston, MA 02364&lt;br /&gt;(781) 585-5464&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; $2.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our table is reserved under "Mike" and "South Shore Meetup Group"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229041689000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225939279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast at "The Original"!</name><id>9103536</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227367800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9103536/</event_url></item>