<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Front St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.520508</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Lobster Shanty</name><city>Salem</city><id>3146641</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.894417</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Super rare, barrel aged Harpoon beer, half price (really good) food, and free Harpoon Glassware. I'm so there! More details below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harpoon is kicking off The Lobster Shanty's seasonal opening with a one-off beer - the Cab-beret, a beer that started life in Harpoon's Homebrew system as the Black Beret, then aged in a Cabernet barrel. IPA-like hoppiness, stout-like creamy, chocolately, espresso flavors, and who knows what from it's time in the barrel! I'm super excited to try (what I believe to be) the only barrel of this in existence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Lobster Shanty was&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4CqjOQoz2h4"&gt;featured on The Food Network's Diners, Drive-ins, and Dives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;., and will be offering half-price on any new foods on the menu, AND a free Harpoon Pint Glass. To get the deal you either have to be a Friends of Harpoon member, or just check-in on Facebook via the QR code once you're there. Easy peasy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find me with the Harpoon Rep, and I'll be wearing a back and white houndstooth hat! Check the RSVP list for the pictures of other folks attending to help us find each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Since it's in Salem, if people want to carpool, comment below!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich DiTieri</member_name><member_id>12427807</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364857629000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>beer buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CraftBeerCrew</urlname><id>1469154</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Craft Beer Crew</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363892391000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rare Barrel Aged Harpoon Beer at Lobster Shanty Opening</name><id>110388172</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364850000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CraftBeerCrew/events/110388172/</event_url></item>