<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join fellow Members (and possibly Guests as the event nears) of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a fun casual lunch @ Barefoot Bob’s at Nantasket Beach in Hull, the top voted Warm Weather Restaurant from our Discussion Thread!  This will be a great way to say sayonara to summer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what some fellow diners had to say about Barefoot Bob's on yelp.com. &lt;br /&gt;-Vivian W from Hingham Ma gives an overwhelming 5 star review: &amp;quot;I can't believe that so few folks have rated this place- it's the closest approximation to being on vacation in Key West around! As if the south shore weren't amazing, Bob's alone could keep me living in Hingham for the rest of my life. Very parrot-head and beachy with outdoor seating in the warmer months, this place is the destination for cold Coronas and appetizers. Friends can't live without the Quahogs, but I'm particularly partial to their BBQ Pork sandwich. It's absolutely massive and to-die-for.  Regulars are eclectic and entertaining and run the gamut with a smattering of good-natured bikers and Hull locals mixed in with college kids hanging out on Nantasket.  Watch the sunset, sip a mai tai (they make a darned good one) and order the nachos. If you don't already live in Hull, you'll be looking to relocate immediately.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;-Julie A in Canton says: &amp;quot;i. love. this. place. the ribs are so good, and i dont even like ribs ha ha. same thing as the BBQ pork sandwich! i suggest their POPCORN SHRIMP. sssooo good, also, i enjoy the clam strips as well, tho many people'd rather with bellys. oh my goodness, such a nice place to hang out, graba couple beers, and veg before hitting the beach again. one of my all time favorite beach joints!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;-To read more reviews go to yelp.com and type in &amp;quot;Barefoot Bob’s&amp;quot; in the Restaurant Search and &amp;quot;Hull, MA&amp;quot; in the City Information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yelp states the approximate cost for one meal including drink, tax and tip is approximately $11-$30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather cooperates we will dine outdoors and may be split into a couple of tables.  Otherwise, we will dine indoors and be seated at one large table or split into two big tables.  Either way, this will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy.  This will also be a good opportunity to discuss future Dining Out events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 27th @ 12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Barefoot Bob’s&lt;br /&gt;276 Nantasket Ave &lt;br /&gt;Hull, MA 02045 &lt;br /&gt;781-925-2007&lt;br /&gt;www.barefootbobsnantasketbeach.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: There is no Braintree Carpool due to lack of interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 6 people 72 hours in advance. Max of 16 people (changed on Tues. 9/23 due to RSVPs). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: None to start.  This may change about 2 weeks prior to the event. **Updated 9/9 to allow 1 Guest per Member!**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees: Annual Members - FREE, Group Members &amp;amp; Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 3pm on Friday, September 26th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: We will meet outside the main entrance.  If it is rainy, meet us inside.  If you arrive after we are seated, the reservation is under &amp;quot;Angela.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Posted on Barefoot Bob’s website.  Below are the directions from the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From  route 3A North:  Go around the Hingham rotary and take your second right up and overt the hill down on to The George Washington Boulevard. Follow into Hull and take the second right after the Carousel. Cross over Nantasket Ave. and Barefoot Bob's Beach Grill will be on your left.   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;From Route 3A South: Take a right on route 228 until you enter the town of Hull. Shortly you will see the ocean on your right. Follow Nantasket Ave. for 1 mile and Barefoot Bob's Beach Grill will be on your left.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;From the South: Take route 3 south to Exit 14 Rockland/Nantasket. Go right at the bottom of the ramp and follow over route 53 onto route 228. Follow for several miles and cross over route 3A. Continue on route 228 until you enter the town of Hull. Shortly you will see the ocean on your right. Follow Nantasket Ave. for 1 mile and Barefoot Bob's Beach Grill will be on your left.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;From The North:  Take route 3 south to Exit 14 Rockland/Nantasket. Go left at the bottom of the ramp and follow over route 53 onto route 228. Follow for several miles and cross over route 3A. Continue on route 228 until you enter the town of Hull. Shortly you will see the ocean on your right. Follow Nantasket Ave. for 1 mile and Barefoot Bob's Beach Grill will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet near the entrance.  Reservation under "Angela" for late arrivals.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223071460000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219791032000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sayonara Summer Luncheon</name><id>8627460</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222533000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8627460/</event_url></item>