<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa is hosting a showing of Moonrise Kingdom at the Kendall.  If that works better for you, please feel free to switch RSVP's!  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Please note the change in start time.&lt;/span&gt; Also, forecast is for heavy rain Saturday evening.  Please update RSVP, if necessary, in order to make our restaurant reservations as accurate as possible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A film for Wes Anderson fans, Moonrise Kingdom opened this year's Cannes Film Festival.  Rave reviews from American Fans of Anderson's films (Mount Rushmore, The Royal Tenenbaums, Fantastic Mr. Fox, The Darjeeling Limited, Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou), reserved praise from the French.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This new film by director Wes Anderson stars a panoply of indie stalwarts, including: Edward Norton, Bill Murray, Tilda Swinton, Bruce Willis, Harvey Keitel, Frances McDormand, Jason Schwartzman, and Bob Balaban.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 1960s on a New England island, young love blooms when Khaki Scout Sam (newcomer Jared Gilman) meets a girl from town, Suzy (also first-time actress Kara Hayward). Through a series of clandestine correspondence, the duo decide to run away together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Various factions of the town mobilize to search for them and the town is turned upside down in their attempt - which ultimately may not be such a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;IMDB:  8.0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;,  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;ROTTEN TOMATOES:  98% - 43 Fresh, 1 Rotten&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From AVClub: &lt;span&gt;That the Cannes Film Festival has kicked off with a winner only prolongs the agony.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moonrise Kingdom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;opens in the U.S. next week, so I don’t want to steal too much thunder from the A.V. Club’s forthcoming official review, but it’s hard to imagine any consistent fan of Anderson’s work not surrendering to its trademark amalgam of precision and melancholy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;" If you hate Wes Anderson, this movie won’t change your mind, but believers should be enchanted."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;We have a large-group reservation at Pho Lemongrass for discussion following the film.  Reservations are under my name (John) if you arrive early/late.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will meet folks at Panera Bread a half hour before the film, and gather folks in the lobby after close of credits, utilizing a Classic Meetup Sign to shepard the group to Pho Lemongrass</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338806747000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337821656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moonrise Kingdom</name><id>66092772</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338670800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/66092772/</event_url></item>