<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>302 Central St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01440</zip><lat>42.576371</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 632-4893</phone><name>Terrapin Traders</name><city>Gardner</city><id>690589</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.995016</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come learn to drum with Jimmy Clapham from 2:00- 4:00 pm at Terrapin Traders!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first Class was a great success, so we decided to do it again!! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what Jimmy had to say about his class:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey everyone, I will be doing a hand drum class for beginners. We will focus on the 5 basic positions on the drum's head and how to make simple rhythms that can bring the players into meditative states of mind. I want this class to be light hearted and fun as well as informative. you must have access to a drum. I look forward to passing on what I have learned and can't wait to jam. My forte has mostly been West African style of hand drumming having studied with Baba Olatungi. He brought this style of hand drums to the U.S.A in the fifties and influenced popular music greatly. If you have extra drums please bring them. Thanks Jimmy Clapham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a HAND drumming class, so participants will need a hand drum...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth has said, that if anyone wants to buy a drum from her, she will order one at COST, which there are 2 sizes: small $90 and large $120 plus shipping. If you would like to order a drum, put&lt;br /&gt;your order in NOW!! So it will get here in time for the class- If interested you can email me at:&lt;br /&gt;talawolf7@webtv.net and I will put the order in for you :)&lt;br /&gt;I personally have seen the drums, and they are very nice and I ordered the smaller size&lt;br /&gt;(which is just right) for myself :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be worksheets this time, to help you remember the different hand beats.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296039564000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292280826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drumming for Beginners</name><id>15724730</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295809200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/15724730/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/4/global_19866900.jpeg</photo_url></item>