<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Click on the link for details.  I've added a few here.  Google says it's 4.5 hours from Dover.  Hotel anyone?!?&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to get our reservations early so we can stay at one of the closer hotels.  Who's game?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sheepandwool.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Rhinebeck&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission $10.00 (2 Day Pass $15.00) &lt;br /&gt;(Shirts and Shoes Required - No Pets, Bottles or Cans, No Skateboards, Scooters, Bicycles, or Rollerblades) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET HERE?&lt;br /&gt;The physical address of the fairgounds is 6550 Spring Brook Ave., Rhinebeck, NY 12572.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Printable Directions&lt;br /&gt;Directions from the South to the NYS Sheep and Wool Festival at the Dutchess County Fairgrounds in Rhinebeck, NY &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Taconic Parkway: North on Taconic Parkway to Route 199 Exit (exit is approximately 1 hour from start of Taconic Parkway). Exit at Route 199 (Red Hook, Rhinebeck). Turn left onto Route 199, heading west. After 4 miles, Route 199 will bear right at a traffic light; go straight at that traffic light onto Route 308, continuing west. Route 308 will take you into Rhinebeck. At the traffic light in Rhinebeck, turn right onto Route 9, heading north. The entrance to the Fairgrounds is approximately 2 miles from that traffic light on the right (east).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From NYS Thruway (I87/I90): Travel north to Exit 19, Kingston. After paying toll, you will enter a traffic circle, take your first right off the traffic circle (Route 28). You will go through a traffic light and bear right on the exit for the Kingston-Rhinecliff Bridge, Route 209, heading east. Crossing the bridge, the road changes to Route 199. After the bridge, at the second traffic light, turn right, heading south, onto Route 9G. In approximately 1 mile, you will come to another traffic light and the intersection of Route 9. Turn right onto Route 9, heading south. The Fairgrounds are located approximately 2 miles on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions and details from locations other than the south refer to the interactive mapping service below.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steph</member_name><member_id>4872811</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224595251000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We had such a great time at the Webs Tent sale that another road trip was called for.</why><group><who>Seacoast Knitters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>seacoastknitters</urlname><id>642244</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Knitters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211065705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhinebeck:  NYS Sheep &amp; Wool</name><id>7958978</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224277200000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/seacoastknitters/events/7958978/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/9/global_4152809.jpeg</photo_url></item>