<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Palmer Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02540</zip><lat>41.570717</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Steamship Authority Palmer Ave Parking Lot</name><city>Falmouth</city><id>6580852</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.620567</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/1723755200050492932723/img/smileys/biggrin.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Please read the entire posting. If you send me a question and I don't respond - it's because the answer is contained in the posting.  I took the time to research and write up this event, please take the time to read it. I apologize if I sound fresh but you wouldn't believe the time I waste answering questions that are right in this post. That said don't be afraid to email for clarification or other questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mileage -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This will be &lt;span style="color : #213e6a"&gt;approximately a 35 mile&lt;/span&gt; run. If there is enough interest for a longer run we can work out  a route for that group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pricing -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #213e6a"&gt;$8 per person each way and $4 per bike - $24 total for per person with a bike / round trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Family Friendly?  - &lt;span style="color : #213e6a"&gt;Kids&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #213e6a"&gt;are always welcome on the trip just please be sure that they can handle a full day and 35 miles on a bike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Rest Stop in OB&lt;/span&gt; -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I will be staying in Oak Bluffs, right near the ferry for a week so I will have a place to change if anyone needs to... and a bathroom for the ladies. We can stop here after we get off the boat if anyone wants to leave a bag or change of clothes for later, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rain Date -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #213e6a"&gt;we'll figure it out then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falmouth Parking&lt;/strong&gt; -&lt;/span&gt; The last time we did this we parked near the Peter Pan terminal but it was a bummer getting back there after dark. This time I think it would be best to pay the $8 and park at the Palmer Ave Lot. We can still ride our bikes along the scenic Shinning sea bike path to Woods Hole. But on the way home take the "Bike Bus" from the ferry to the parking Lot. No matter where you park please be at the Palmer Ave lot by 830 am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GPS Address for Palmer Ave lot -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (1 Oakwood Ave, Falmouth MA is a good address for your GPS - It's right across the street from the parking lot)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ferry Home -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (The last ferry from Oak Bluffs leaves at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;6:15 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. If you miss this one you can take the bus to Vineyard Haven and  the last boat to Woods Hole leaves at &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9:30 pm.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Or camp on the porch of my cottage.&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/614102232183174521616/img/smileys/wink.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Everything?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; I think I thought of most issues but If I didn't let me know and I will update the listing for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So be at the &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Palmer Ave Lot by &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;7:45&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;AM&lt;/span&gt;...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; WE will be leaving the Palmer Ave lot shortly thereafter so we can stop at Pie in the Sky for yummy Coffees, Teas &amp;amp; Lattes before we board the Ferry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take the &lt;strong&gt;930 am&lt;/strong&gt; Steamship Authority Ferry to Oak Bluffs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm not 100% on the course but this is what I am thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Route&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; We will all ride together through Vineyard Haven out to West Tisbury. This leg of the journey is mostly on the road with vehicles so we must be extra careful. Then in West Tisbury we can pick up the paved bike trails and head towards Edgartown via the airport and South Beach. Last year we relaxed at South Beach for a while, then grabbed lunch at a great little restaurant at the airport. This route is approximately 25 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After which we will proceed to Oak Bluffs to lick our wounds and sooth are aching arse's  - 7 Miles from Edgartown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THIS ISN'T A RACE BUT IT CERTAINLY IS NOT FOR THE NOVICE RIDER.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please don't let this be your first ride of the year.!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get your bike tuned up, have a few rides.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will travel on bike paths for as much as we can. (about half the day) but much of our trip will be on regular roads. PLEASE WEAR HELMETS &amp;amp; OTHER SAFETY GEAR !!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cuz we will leave you for dead if you are woefully unprepared. (ok that was a joke but please be prepared)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucky for all of us. The vineyard public buses all have bike racks attached just in case of bike or the rider breaks down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring Plenty of Water and Snacks...and sunscreen&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/3250963246259337556533/img/smileys/cool.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year we ended the tour at Nancy's in Oak Bluffs with some live music and cool drinks. I hope many of you can join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NO-SHOWS ON THIS WILL NOT BE TAKEN LIGHTLY.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SO PLEASE UPDATE YOUR STATUS IF YOU CAN'T MAKE IT SO WE AREN'T WAITING FOR YOU.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Last year I mapped out a couple of routes - right now I am leaning towards the shorter ride. It will be about 25-35 miles. If we get a lot of interest or if some would like to make a longer run, below is a 2nd option&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Longer Optional Route (if there is enough interest)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; starts like route 1 from Oak Bluffs through bike trails to West Tisbury and then vear off to Menemsha via Chilmark, over the bike ferry then an optional ride to Gay Head Light. We will backtrack and go through Edgartown. The entire route will be about 45 miles and have some good hills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;TRAIL MAPS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Here is a link to the bike trail maps. I will try to remember to print some out before I go. But I suggest you download your own. &lt;a href="http://www.capecodbiketrails.com/Bike%20Trail%20Maps.htm"&gt;http://www.capecodbiketrails.com/Bike%20Trail%20Maps.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Afterwards we can meetup at Nancy's in Oak Bluffs for some libations, then figure out dinner. &lt;strong&gt;The last Oak Bluffs ferry leaves at 6:15 pm&lt;/strong&gt;. So we will need to bike to Vineyard Haven to catch a later ferry. If anyone wants to join for part of the day and leave earlier, you're more than welcome to do so.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;BRING WATER, SNACKS &amp;amp; SUNSCREEN !!!! There are places where you cannot buy any.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Enclosure in the middle of the parking area.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369056928000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365036407000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>35 Mile Bike Ride from Falmouth to the Vineyard &amp; around the island</name><id>112565532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368963900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/112565532/</event_url></item>