<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>James Ray, featured in &amp;quot;The Secret&amp;quot; and creator of &amp;quot;The Science of Success &amp;amp; Harmonic Wealth&amp;quot;, is in Boston ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;with his event &amp;quot; The Secret of Attracting the Life You Want&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;admission: FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Only 11 seats available as of 9/2/08&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;venue: Boston Marriott-Newton&lt;br /&gt;Grand Ballroom&lt;br /&gt;2345 Commonwealth Ave&lt;br /&gt;Newton, MA 02466&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; on our meetup that you are attending.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then YOU MUST GO HERE to register directly on Jame Ray's website:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;a href="http://jamesray.com/events/free-seminars.php?CD=CD4013" target="_blank"&gt;http://jamesray.com/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**It'll be great to have a HUGE group of our members be at the event sitting together, supporting each other and James Ray &amp;amp; letting other attendees know there's a LOA meetup in Boston for like-minded folks to connect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;==================&lt;br /&gt;Here's an email invite from James Ray:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would it be worth less than 2 hours of your time if I gave you a FREE GIFT guaranteed to change the rest of your life?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you want to be more successful? Create more wealth? Generate more happiness? Enjoy true peace of mind?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have the courage to believe that, given just a little help and direction, you could achieve much more than you currently are?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great news...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi. My name is James Ray and in The Secret of Attracting the Life You Want, I show you exactly how to create the life you really want...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And the best news of all is...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's ABSOLUTELY FREE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Yeah, I kinda experience the holiday spirit all year long.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look. There are lots of personal growth, self improvement, and success trainings, books, and courses out there. And they all promise to deliver wonderful, life-changing results. Some of them do; others don't.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But one thing most of them have in common is that they say &amp;quot;do this...&amp;quot; &amp;quot;do that...&amp;quot; &amp;quot;try this technique...&amp;quot; &amp;quot;practice this simple system.&amp;quot; They're almost all technique oriented. In other words, &amp;quot;Follow my magic formula and you'll magically become rich and all your problems will disappear.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What a mistake! They're on the right track, but they're getting off at the wrong station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sure, some success and wealth-building techniques are better than others, but lack of techniques is not what makes the difference between winners and losers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's how you use what you were born with that really makes the difference — the real secret is in how you use your own mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people, by the time they reach adulthood, have developed a whole host of self-limiting, self-sabotaging beliefs, habits, and ill-serving strategies which dictate the level of success (or lack of) that they'll achieve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They go along their merry way usually running on &amp;quot;autopilot,&amp;quot; not realizing that they are in charge of their own minds. The truth is, you can choose to think and believe what you want — and therefore generate the results you want.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the deal... I've spend 23 years studying, examining, and helping people create true wealth in their lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thing I can tell you for certain is that if you want to make dramatic positive changes in your life, you'll do it easier, quicker, and with much better long term results by mastering your own mind rather than looking for a &amp;quot;magic pill.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Secret of Attracting the Life You Want is completely different (and creates life-long results).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, if...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * You simply (and deeply) want to make more money and become more successful...&lt;br /&gt;    * You want to double, triple, even multiply by ten the size of your business...&lt;br /&gt;    * You've already achieved at least a modest level of success and want to use that as a               &lt;br /&gt;         springboard to greater things...&lt;br /&gt;    * You know you could do a lot better in life with just a little help...&lt;br /&gt;    * You realize that simply working harder can only get you so far, and you want more...&lt;br /&gt;    * You know (or at least suspect) that money alone can't buy true happiness...&lt;br /&gt;    * You've already made a ton of money but haven't been able to enjoy it like you always&lt;br /&gt;         thought you would...&lt;br /&gt;    * You suspect there's got to be something more to life...&lt;br /&gt;    * Your personal relationships can have a huge impact on your overall satisfaction with &lt;br /&gt;         life... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You owe it to yourself to invest 2 hours of your time on Wednesday, September 3 in Boston, MA to check out the insider secrets to truly live a life of power.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And remember it is TOTALLY FREE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simply visit this link:  to learn how to create the life you deserve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've got absolutely nothing to lose and a whole new life to gain, so register at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://jamesray.com/events/free-seminars.php?CD=CD4013" target="_blank"&gt;http://jamesray.com/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James Ray, President&lt;br /&gt;James Ray International&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222455788000</updated><rating><average>4.32000017166</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218499654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join us to hang out with James Ray LIVE </name><id>8524379</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220482800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/8524379/</event_url></item>