<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join other solo professionals, coaches and service providers in this short no cost online seminar to learn how to choose successful marketing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Register &lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/6091129733/sbsnmtp"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; or click the yellow Register Now button to reserve your spot.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/6091129733/sbsnmtp"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/b/e/event_171790942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; Tuesday, April 2, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 2pm Eastern Time &lt;br /&gt;

 (48 hour replay available if your schedule doesn't cooperate, but you must sign up before the program goes live).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://evbdn.eventbrite.com/s3-s3/eventlogos/42388876/howchooseeffectivemarketingstrategies.png" alt="event image" width="500" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About this event&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you choose marketing strategies, if you make bad choices it will cost you thousands of dollars in lost revenue, and possibly many sleepless nights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose wisely, and you’ll be in flow growing your business and enjoying your work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of advice going around saying you just need to get out there and promote yourself. Unfortunately, done incorrectly this can lead to your being perceived as a pushy salesman rather than the competent, helpful professional you are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Others insist you must their favorite strategy if you want to be successful. This often leads solo professoiinals to making poor choices, wasting money and overwhelm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news is using the right criteria, you can pick the strategies that will work best for you. There is no one size fits all approach that you must use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketing is like nutrition for your business. It’s necessary, and trying to use too many strategies is a recipe for failure.   You’ll do better by carefully selecting a few successful strategies that fit your business and your personality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us to learn how to easily evaluate and upgrade your marketing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;During this no cost 2 part program you will learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to choose and evaluate marketing strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why relationship marketing often fails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The criteria to evaluate if your marketing strategy sets you up to be able to charge more with ease.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to be seen as a trusted advisor, not a commodity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to make an impact despite your prospects highly distracted state of mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 criteria to evaluate how likely your marketing strategies are to be successful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Format&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During each part of this 2 part webinar we will discuss 3 of the 6 important criteria you need to consider when you choose and evaluate marketing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The session will last approximately 15-25 minutes plus time for Q&amp;amp;A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us to set yourself up for success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the presenter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://evbdn.eventbrite.com/s3-s3/eventlogos/42388876/markreinert.jpg" alt="Mark Reinert" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 1px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Mark Reinert is a multipreneur, business and relationship coach and innovative problem-solver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a business coach and marketing consultant, Mark help self-employed service profesionals, coaches and solopreneurs who want to make a good living while making a difference in the world. While he works with many types of professionals, he specializes in helping those doing transformational work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Participate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register &lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/6091129733/sbsnmtp"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or click the yellow Register Now button to reserve your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/6091129733/sbsnmtp"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/b/e/event_171790942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure to mark your calendar now&lt;/strong&gt; so you don't forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Got Questions?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can post your questions below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Reinert</member_name><member_id>7305695</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364937292000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364848042000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Choose Effective Marketing Strategies (Part 1)</name><id>112136052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364925600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/112136052/</event_url></item>