<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>at the door.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>**WE'RE DEFINITELY ON AND WE'RE STARTING THE PARTY EARLY! Join us at 6pm. Socializing and Justice don't take snow days.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then you shouldn't miss this event!  It only happens twice a year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/7/7/event_6802647.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/1/7/event_6801527.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;No program. No speaker. Just arrive and enjoy yourself.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Newcomers always welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word &lt;b&gt;bring flyers for the free lit table&lt;/b&gt; - and there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network while sharing cheap pitchers of beer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From our FAQs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;It's not very easy for me to meet new people and I'm not really one for small talk at bars.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hear you. That's why at SoJust events, in addition to traditional name tags, we have &amp;quot;Ask Me About&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Looking For&amp;quot; tags. That way you can slap whatever you're into lately up on your shirt and wait for fellow SoJusters to approach you. These seem to do the trick of moving past the basic &amp;quot;what do you do for work? where do you live?&amp;quot; questions to conversations that lead to more substantial connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;What actually happens at events?&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll always be greeted by friendly folks who can help get you socializing, introduce you to people, and chat with you about questions or wishes. It's likely a few people will be there promoting their campaigns and issues (&lt;i&gt;yes, SoJust welcomes that sort of behavior&lt;/i&gt;). At our bigger events, there's always a literature table to toss down flyers, postcards, and other paraphenalia about events around town. Most importantly, we can pretty much guarantee there will be someone there you've never met before. As one of our members said, &amp;quot;You are bringing together people who might never get together otherwise - if that ain't a step towards justice I don't know what is.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;. Learn about our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/pages/Annual_Membership_Fee_details/"&gt;Suggested Annual Membership Fee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hilary</member_name><member_id>3092728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>29</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235088138000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227595393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Putting the SOCIAL Back in Social Justice</name><id>9227426</id><headcount>71</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233183600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/9227426/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/f/global_2821823.jpeg</photo_url></item>