<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Brave is the latest Pixar film; you've probably already seen the ads and toys as the Disney marketing onslaught commences. On the toys, I will say Merida's red curly hair is just not as &lt;em&gt;fabulous&lt;/em&gt; as it is in the trailer. On the movie, I will say that it's a Pixar film. If you like Pixar films you will probably like this one. :-) Thanks to alert member Surey for suggesting this meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be seeing the 7:15 show, which is 3d. I am curious as to how well Pixar does 3d.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/2/8/event_130499432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span&gt;I will be at the lobby close&lt;/span&gt; to an hour before and I will be wearing a red trucker hat with the meetup logo. If the movie is upstairs, I will be waiting at the tables near the front windows. If the movie is downstairs, I will be across from the refreshment stand. We'll head into the theater 20 minutes before showtime. Yes I know that's awfully early when you add it to the 10 to 20 minutes of previews, but hey, it'll give you a chance to talk to your neighbor!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I strongly advise buying tickets ahead of time on fandango.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, we gather outside the theater showing the film after the film ends. And then we go out for a discussion 'n' food 'n' beer. Or wine, or cocktails, according to your preference. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Since ancient times, stories of epic battles and mystical legends have been passed through the generations across the rugged and mysterious Highlands of Scotland. In "Brave," a new tale joins the lore when the courageous Merida (voice of Kelly Macdonald) confronts tradition, destiny and the fiercest of beasts.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Merida is a skilled archer and impetuous daughter of King Fergus (voice of Billy Connolly) and Queen Elinor (voice of Emma Thompson). Determined to carve her own path in life, Merida defies an age-old custom sacred to the uproarious lords of the land: massive Lord MacGuffin (voice of Kevin McKidd), surly Lord Macintosh (voice of Craig Ferguson) and cantankerous Lord Dingwall (voice of Robbie Coltrane). Merida's actions inadvertently unleash chaos and fury in the kingdom, and when she turns to an eccentric old Wise Woman (voice of Julie Walters) for help, she is granted an ill-fated wish. The ensuing peril forces Merida to discover the meaning of true bravery in order to undo a beastly curse before it's too late.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Directed by Mark Andrews ("The Incredibles," "Ratatouille," "John Carter") and Brenda Chapman ("The Lion King," "Prince of Egypt"), and produced by Katherine Sarafian ("Lifted," "The Incredibles"), "Brave" is a grand adventure full of heart, memorable characters and the signature Pixar humor enjoyed by audiences of all ages. The film takes aim at theaters on June 22, 2012, and will be presented in Disney Digital 3D™ in select theaters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailers 'n' Stuff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.disney.com/brave" target="_blank"&gt;Disney.com/Brave&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See meetup description for how to find the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340594997000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339988068000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brave</name><id>69612072</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340490600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/69612072/</event_url></item>