<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for a late season hike of the Carter Range.  We will hit all three of the official 4000 foot peaks in the Carters.  This trip will involve a short car-spotting expedition.  To that end we will meet at Nineteen Mile Brook Trail parking lot off of Rt. 16 near Camp Dodge and take one or two cars to Imp Trail once everyone arrives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The total hike will be just under 14 miles so headlamps are a requirement given the fact that it will likely be dark by 4 pm in the shadow of the presidentials.  Microspikes or stablizers are very strongly encouraged as are hiking poles.  The trails aren't likely to be very snowy given the warmth of the last week, but they could very easily be covered in ice in places from frozen springs by the weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Otherwise use your common sense.  It will be cold and the pace will be moderately quick in order to make it down before dinner.  So pack plenty of food and water an wear layers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you don't have reasonably appropriate gear I may ask you not to hike with us, so if in doubt please email me.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in a silver mazda wagon.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258461874000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257971669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Carters</name><id>11852620</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258288200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11852620/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/f/global_5294319.jpeg</photo_url></item>