<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please note the change:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting to organize to Stop the Cameras has been rescheduled for Thursday, January 8.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an ACLU event, this posting does not endorse the ACLU.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you feel your views should be represented on this important issue I suggest you attend the planning meeting meeting and say your piece. - JK&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mon Jan 5, 6pm, ACLU office, Plan to STOP THE CAMERAS!&lt;br /&gt;Please share widely!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Planning Meeting at the ACLU office &lt;br /&gt;Monday Jan 5, 6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stopping Homeland Security Funded - Surveillance Cameras in Your Community&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Forming a Greater Boston Coalition to Stop the Cameras&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The new version of surveillance camera-- under the black part is a camera that can turn 360 degrees, pan and zoom, at instructions from someone at the police station. Once you know what they look like, you'll notice them all over... Homeland Security is funding cameras like this all over the county-- The images captured are digital, meaning that they can easily be sent anywhere, including to Homeland Security, very easily, over the net.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come hear Nancy Murray give a short introduction to the full dangers of a national Surveillance State, Fusion Centers, the Homeland Security initiative to fund and place surveillance cameras all over the country, and what we can do about it in the  Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Especially Encouraging activists from each of the affected communities to come, to help develop a strategy to work against the cameras in each community, including those that never had a chance to vote on it, and to give each other support as a Greater Boston Coalition to Stop the Surveillance Cameras!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info:&lt;br /&gt;amyh@texnology.com&lt;br /&gt;nancy@aclum.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ACLU of Massachusetts office is at 211 Congress&lt;br /&gt;St., 3rd floor (corner of Congress and High Streets, close to South&lt;br /&gt;Station and Post Office Square).&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231981360000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230493671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stop the Cameras! Organizing to keep Spy Cameras out of Boston </name><id>9397711</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231455600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9397711/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>