<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 Broad Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.357525</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nix's Mate</name><city>Boston</city><id>7464662</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053093</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join NetSAP Boston at our holiday Cocktails and Conversations Party next Saturday December 15 from 8pm!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are hosting our cocktail party with the latest social utility Bandwagon - where it’s not just deals anymore, but deals with friends. Join us at Nix’s Mate at the Boston Hilton Hotel on Broad Street on Dec 15th, Saturday at 8pm. There will be complimentary drinks, courtesy of Deep Eddy Vodka, and a live DJ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For free entry and a complementary drink, RSVP here and hop on to the Bandwagon: &lt;a href="https://www.hoponbandwagon.com/bandwagon/30" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.hoponbandwagon.com/bandwagon/30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Bandwagon all about?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you seen Skiing, Rafting, Sky-diving, Paintball, Rock-climbing, Yoga deals and wished you had friends or other like-minded people to join you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you want to try new cuisines/restaurants and buy those dinner for 4, 6 people deals then wished you had company?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or did you move to a new city and wanted to explore by finding new experiences that cost nada, zilch and make new friends?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If so, Bandwagon is for you. Check out the Deals &amp;amp; Experiences, score a deal, then create your Bandwagon activity whenever you want. Make it a private affair and invite only your friends or make it public if you want to meet other like-minded people. You can also check out other public Bandwagon activities and hop on them. When you sign up, we notify you when there are fun things to do in your vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bandwagon makes your life much more interesting and fun. Hop On at www.HopOnBandwagon.com and roll!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355630918000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355089016000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NetSAP Boston's December Cocktails &amp; Conversations Party next Saturday!</name><id>94720692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355619600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/94720692/</event_url></item>