<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer  Thursday  April 2nd  at Market Boston 130 Water St. Financial District &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Financial District 6:45-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All I am leaving Boston in a few weeks  for the bright lights of New York City! Thus,  please join me Thursday April 2nd as I have my final event for the Boston Nightlife Group. Its been great being an organizer  my 3 years in Boston, I have met some amazing people and made some friends for life. I would like to thank Charlie for making me a part of the best meetup group in Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MKT Boston is one of the premier afterwork spots in the Boston area. If you enjoy making new contacts and friends, while enjoying some of the best cocktails on a wonderful  evening then this is the event for you!! Also if you are new member and have not been to an afterwork mixer, or have only been to a few events, I highly encourage you to attend and meet many of our wonderful members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So what better way to come out Thurs April 2nd  and have a few cocktails with the group as we gear up for another festive weekend and celebrate new beginnings! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting details: Check out the venue website at &lt;a href="http://www.mktboston..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mktboston....&lt;/a&gt;. This will give you a better overall sense of the venue and provide pinpoint directions from your destination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the bar area . Like any event, when arriving please be sure to locate the organizer which for this event is &lt;b&gt;STEVE&lt;/b&gt;. Please do not hesitate to call or text me upon arrival if you are having trouble finding the group. My picture is on the site under the Assistant Organizer section so I should not be hard to find. &lt;br /&gt;To find the group with ease I highly ENCOURAGE you to attend early as possible. My phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Please email me if you have any questions. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;Green/Blue Line to Govt Center &lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to State St &lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Park st. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event cost: Free. (However please feel free to grab a beverage for your hard working organizers) &lt;br /&gt;**Note please see the message board regarding meetup/event etiquette**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**The event at Market may be over at 9:30, but the party does not stop!  For those in attendance ( and who can be late for work Fri morn!)after the event  we will head to a nearby club in the city for dancing!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you arrive like any event look for the Organizer</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247274998000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237861586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Steve's Final Afterwork Mixer  "This is no April Fools" </name><id>10021231</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238712300000</time><rsvp_limit>51</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/10021231/</event_url></item>