<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This seems like an interesting program and am listing here in case anyone in the group is interested in participating.  While You can use this trip listing to coordinate with other group members that may be attending, you need to follow the instructions described below to register. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration is now open for the 2011 Winter Becoming an Outdoors-Woman (BOW) workshop, a one-day program for women to learn outdoor skills for winter activities. This program is offered by the NH Fish and Game Department together with the NH Wildlife Federation  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Winter BOW workshop will be held on Saturday, February 19, 2011 (snow date Sunday, February 20), at the New Hampshire Fish and Game Department’s Owl Brook Hunter Education Center in Holderness, N.H. The workshop costs $55, which includes a box lunch and most equipment. Participants must be at least 18 years old. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW began as a course at the University of Wisconsin looking into the reasons more women don't participate in many outdoors activities. It was determined that women preferred to learn these skills in a non-competitive atmosphere along with other women. Winter BOW participants choose a single activity to explore during the workshop. They can learn how to ice-fish, gain winter outdoor survival skills, try snowshoeing and tracking, snowmobiling or ’Shoe and Shoot (combines snowshoeing and woodland target shooting).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register, download the registration forms and workshop brochure at &lt;a href="http://www.nhbow.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhbow.com...&lt;/a&gt;, email Lisa.M.Collins@wildlife.nh.gov, or call  603-271-3212 . Sign up soon, because BOW workshops fill up fast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New Hampshire Fish and Game Department is the guardian of the state’s fish, wildlife and marine resources and their habitats. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.WildNH.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.WildNH.com...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New Hampshire Wildlife Federation is a nonprofit group that advocates for the promotion and protection of hunting, fishing and trapping, as well as the conservation of fish and wildlife habitat. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.nhwf.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhwf.org...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298216371000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294716845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Becoming an Outdoors-Woman Winter Workshop</name><id>16003340</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298160000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/16003340/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/a/global_20506746.jpeg</photo_url></item>