<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Asbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.654526</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bradley Palmer State Park</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>329919</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.909149</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For anyone interested in focusing a bit of effort on their speed and pace line training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The route is designed such that a minimum of circuits can familiarize a rider with it's course. The idea is that subsequent weeks can be used to measure improvement on a known course while simultaneously, hopefully, fostering a bit of team building camaraderie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The route starts in Bradley Palmer State Park and warms up for 5 miles to the I-95 overpass then continues through Boxford, Georgetown and the Andovers before returning to I-95 almost exactly 20 miles later. A church parking lot at the end of the loop provides a place to regroup and assess performance before heading home or out for another iteration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want this to be a drop ride mostly because... I want to be dropped. Yeah.. you heard right.. I want to be left in the dust. I want to feel my legs pulsing and my chest about to burst from the effort of TRYING to keep up with faster riders. That is how one improves in my experience. That is the motivation here and the reason the course is short and repeatable and easy to memorize with easy access to facilities and supplies (2 miles from Topsfield center. Water, pizza etc.. )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A drop ride may seem to fly in the face of the ethos for this group but I hope there are some folks herein who share this desire and I KNOW there are folks who are faster than me. I ask for the help of those folks to improve my riding. I promise to do my best to improve that of others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yours,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://ridewithgps.com/routes/1256681" class="linkified"&gt;http://ridewithgps.com/routes/1256681&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan</member_name><member_id>11982073</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344095668000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342909063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pace Line Training - Drop me, please!!!</name><id>qhwjcdyqlbgb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344084300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/74339012/</event_url></item>