<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lincoln Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01601</zip><lat>42.272555</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 755-1200</phone><name>Maxwell Silverman's Toolhouse</name><city>Worcester</city><id>816472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.799026</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We have over 40 signed up, with a few more spots available, with less than a week to go. Sign up here very soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come celebrate the holidays with your fellow Humanist friends in Worcester! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be gathering at Maxwell Silverman's - it's a great place with good food and lots of holiday ambiance! &amp;nbsp;There's a lunch buffet with a choice of 3 entrees as well as sides and a desert, and the bar will be open if you're so inclined!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tables will be set up to sit with friends, and of course you can make the rounds and mingle with others. &amp;nbsp;There will be lots of happy faces and holiday festivities - come on, we Humanists know how to party!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to bring along non-members, friends, visiting family - you know they'll feel welcomed by the GWH community, and we're happy to have them along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will have a raffle with many cool items donated by members, including a new Kindle, as well as on-topic books and artwork. &amp;nbsp;We hope you'll take part and help us raise funds for the chapter!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to play an instrument or have a local band who would be willing to come out, please let us know - we'd love a live act! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'd like to get your RSVP in by November 30th, so please sign up as soon as you can! &amp;nbsp;You can sign up here, or let a Steering Committee member know you plan to attend. &amp;nbsp;You will have the option of paying at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324160769000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321118750000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Non-Denominational Festive Winter Bash</name><id>40916722</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323536400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/40916722/</event_url></item>