<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join me if you want, or join me on the next event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your chairs, sunscreen, beverage of choice, and Pirate Pot Luck Food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WEATHER: LOOKING PRETTY GOOD, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Sunny, with a high near 68. Northeast wind between 8 and 10 mph&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am ready to give it a GO if you are willing to go this SUNDAY.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHFD&amp;amp;state=CT"&gt;http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHFD&amp;amp;state=CT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This event's Feature is YOU and the desire to start the season.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;KAYAK Group &amp;nbsp;PLAY ON THE WATER DAY at Bolton Lake* - Pirate Pot Luck Barbie-Q @ Oak Grove Nature CTR After the Paddling is done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All are invited&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;WITH OR WITHOUT KAYAKS&lt;/strong&gt;, Its a Get To Meet Up Again event after the long winter or to meet us for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can see what kind of new or old &amp;nbsp;equipment we have and why we have it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sit in the sun, ask questions, &amp;nbsp;and socialize if not playing on the water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I most likely will only be in the water for a short time testing out the new Home Depot Boat and try a few self rescue practice things , &amp;nbsp;the rest of the time will be near shore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please wear some fast draining or drying clothes, ie Fleece, (chances are slim you will fall in but its possible, wet suit or dry suit if you intend on going in).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;-----------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting to the &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Boat Launch&lt;/span&gt; area:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;There is a easy to reach boat launch right off of rte 44 in Bolton that has plenty of parking and PortoPotties (they should be there by then if not , Pee in the water..) . Further to the east on the lake is a beach area that would be an excellent place to sit in the sun .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: to the boat launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use the apx address for your GPs to get you close enough #1050 Boston Tpk Bolton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 heading East to Bolton Notch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) ...rte 6 is to the right&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. (South street intersection)&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PLEASE LEAVE THE LAUNCHING CIRCLE OPEN after unloading AND PARK ON THE DESIGNATED SIDE AREAS, the DEP cops show up all the time it seems. They are looking to make some money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need help during unloading we will always help you -- but we always don't know if you need help, &amp;nbsp; so ask anyone to help you if you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THEN JOIN US FOR THE SOCIALIZATION TIME AFTER AT THE &amp;nbsp;POT LUCK BARBIE-Q NEARBY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember the air may be warm but the water is still really cold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aviod cotton cloths and opt for fast draining &amp;amp; wicking garments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I will do a Recreation Kayak vs Compartmentalized Kayak&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;demonstration so you will understand the need to be careful for this event and all of the seasons we will be paddling. Its mostly to illiustrate what to buy so your future will be safer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/9/0/event_10244944.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then its a POT LUCK BARBIE-Q NEARBY AT OAK GROVE NATURE CENTER BY THE COVERED BRIDGE AND WATER FALL, nearby in MANCHESTER,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, everyone will arrive @ the Covered Bridge&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;(locally/unofficially referred to as "Childrens Covered Bridge"&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;over Porter Brook) smoothly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS LOCATION CAN handle more cars but still IS nearby, There is parking on the road up by the dam and bridge too (this is where i have to park with the trailer) and room for about 6 more cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The location is just minutes from Highland Park Market (if you forgot or want something fresh) as a reference and very easy to caravan to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring some chairs, food, and your faviourite beverage for here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GPS apx 200 Oak Grove St, Manchester&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park at: Oak Grove Nature Center Parking Lot (please park in a way as to leave room for others)&amp;nbsp;if done properly it should hold 10-20 cars &lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Driving directions from Bolton Lake:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leave Bolton Lake boat ramp, take a right onto rte 44 going&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;WEST&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bear left onto 384 toward Hartford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the first exit off of 384 (exit # 4)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a left onto Highland St (if going to Highland Park Market take a right)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go apx 0.5 mile and take a right onto&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;AUTUMN&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;ST&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THEN AN IMMEDIATE RIGHT onto Oak Grove St&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the first parking lot area on the right is the place..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park tightly..use some of the areas off on the sides also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will walk up into the area a bit to a nice secluded spot near the covered bridge and water fall.&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the only Kayaks i will bring for playing in the water:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~&amp;gt; A (What ever is in the back yard)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~&amp;gt; B (the one with spiders in it)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Or the easiest 2 out of the basement)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~&amp;gt; And ~~~&amp;gt;*The Home Depot Plywood Special* (this boat needs to be tested for seaworthyness) !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;al-r&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my Kayak Trailer in the parking area, i most likely will be wearing my AL-Gaddafi Hat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304867982000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>This weekend is looking warmer and its not a Holiday weekend either so no complaining.</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303318946000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SUNDAY Bolton Lk *Play on the Water Day* &amp; Pirates Pot Luck @ Oak Grove Ntr Ctr</name><id>17373474</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304265600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/17373474/</event_url></item>