<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=56" target="_blank"&gt;Free Teleconference with 3 of the most successful real estate investors in the country!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It doesn't get any better than this...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson, Curtis Brooks and Steve Dillon will be giving a FREE one hour teleconference to get you ready for what they have in store for you in late March at the 3 Day Foreclosure Workshop!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve Dillon is an ex-loss mitigator who worked in the banking industry for several large lending institutions. Steve negotiated over 8,000 short sales while in the banking profession. He left loss mitigation to do real estate and has been helping hundreds of real estate investors negotiate bigger profits on short sales for several years now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Curtis Brooks has purchased over 750 houses on the court house steps in Florida over the past decade. Curtis knows how to negotiate better than anybody I know.  He will teach you how to get a seller to say ?YES? 9 out of 10 times. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't know who Robyn Thompson is, where have you been?  Robyn is one of the nations most successful real estate investors and she's from right here in CT!  She started off in real estate after getting laid off from IBM along with 250 other people.  Not letting this get the best of her, she saw the opportunity and dove head first into real estate.  She bought a unit that was being foreclosed on in her same neighborhood and the rest is history.  She has bought, rehabbed and sold over 235 homes since then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's just a short list of the content that will be covered:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Why this is the best time in history to invest in foreclosures and how foolish you?d be NOT to get involved.&lt;br /&gt;    * How to capture the huge tidal wave of preforeclosures over the next 12 months&lt;br /&gt;    * How to find GREAT deals every single time &amp;amp; where you can get other people's money to fund these deals&lt;br /&gt;    * The step by step process on negotiating huge profits on discounting mortgages&lt;br /&gt;    * What are the different types of loans to avoid&lt;br /&gt;    * All the insider secrets to negotiate the loss mitigator down&lt;br /&gt;    * The six critical steps that all rookies make when trying a short sale&lt;br /&gt;    * What the banks DON'T want real estate investors to know&lt;br /&gt;    * How to prepare all the necessary paperwork so your deal sails through for approval with no glitches&lt;br /&gt;    * How to complete a Hud-1, Net Sheets, Authorizations To Release &amp;amp; Financial Distress paperwork to build a case for a huge discount with the lender&lt;br /&gt;    * The 4 killer strategies to locate an avalanche of good deals&lt;br /&gt;    * The most effective negotiation strategies to handle all sell obligations&lt;br /&gt;    * How to seel short sales for huge profit in a down market&lt;br /&gt;    * The top 10 strategies to getting buyers to ring your phone off the hook in a buyers market&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be on this FREE conference call. Now is the time to be investing in foreclosures and Robyn, Curtis &amp;amp; Steve are three of the most experienced investors in the nation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feb 20th at 8PM EST Dial:&lt;br /&gt;Playback Number: (641) 715-3413&lt;br /&gt;Access Code: 720157#&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=56" target="_blank"&gt;Register for this FREE teleconference on CT REIA's website to get the connection info!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203734593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>These are three of the most successful real estate investors in the country.  They have the knowledge to get the jobs done and bring in some serious cash and they are willing to share this information with YOU!</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202981086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Teleconference with Robyn, Curtis &amp; Steve!</name><id>7329692</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203555600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/7329692/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/0/global_3224144.jpeg</photo_url></item>