<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Plum Island Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.799107</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-5753</phone><name>Parker River Rufuge Headquarters</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>879211</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847862</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>At Parker River National Wildlife Refuge, wildlife come first. Wildlife-dependent recreational and educational opportunities are available however. These opportunities, deemed appropriate and compatible with the refuge's primary objectives, include wildlife observation and photography, hunting, fishing, shellfishing, environmental education and interpretation. Additional information concerning these activities is included below. Refer to the map for the location of available facilities. &lt;br /&gt;Wildlife Observation and Photography&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE'LL MEET AT THE JOPPA FLATS EDUCATION CENTER on 1 Plum Island Tnpk. Newburyport.  We can park there and carpool to the refuge just a short drive away since there is a $5 fee for each car entering the refuge.Be sure to bring binoculars and cameras since there is plenty to see.&lt;br /&gt;Birding the refuge in May can result in an especially long list of migrants. &lt;br /&gt;The refuge is renowned for its wildlife observation and photography opportunities with facilities providing easy access. Pull-offs are available along the refuge road for your convenience. Observation towers and platforms afford commanding views of the refuge and surrounding lands and waters. Several miles of self-guiding foot trails meander through dune, shrub/thicket, marsh, and other refuge habitats. The Pines Trail, Salt Pannes Wildlife Observation Area, North Pool Overlook, and observation platforms overlooking the beach and ocean at parking lots 1 and 7 are wheelchair accessible. &lt;br /&gt;A checklist of refuge birds is available from refuge headquarters and the entrance gatehouse when staffed. In addition, a comprehensive listing of recent bird sightings is available online from the Newburyport Birders.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hunting&lt;br /&gt; Waterfowl hunting opportunities are available in designated salt marsh areas of the refuge during state seasons. Also, a controlled deer hunt may be conducted on the Plum Island portion of the refuge with hunters chosen by lottery. All refuge, federal, and state hunting regulations apply.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In cooperation with the League of Essex County Sportsmen's Clubs, the refuge conducts a Youth Waterfowler Training Program each fall. This program includes an all-day seminar and a supervised hunt on a reserved section of the refuge.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fishing and Shellfishing&lt;br /&gt; The refuge offers some of the area's finest surf fishing. In season you may catch striped bass, bluefish, and several other species. A state license is not required for fishing from the refuge beach. A refuge permit is required for night fishing and vehicle access to the beach. All refuge, federal, and state fishing regulations apply. &lt;br /&gt;The refuge tidal flats are open for &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Refuge headquarters is located at 6 Plum Island Turnpike, Newburyport , MA, right before the bridge to Plum Island. It is directly across the road from the Massachusetts Audubon building. The administrative office is open Monday through Friday from 8:30am-4pm, and the visitor center &amp;amp; exhibits are open 11am-4pm, 7 days a week. For more information, please call 978/465-5753.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions to the Refuge Distances approximate: the refuge is located 35 miles (56.3 kilometers) north of Boston near the City of Newburyport. From Route 95 take exit 57 and travel east on Route 113, then continue straight onto Route 1A South to the intersection with Rolfe’s Lane for a total of 3.5 miles (5.6 kilometers). Turn left onto Rolfe’s Lane and travel 0.5 miles (0.8 kilometers) to its end. Turn right onto the Plum Island Turnpike and travel 2.0 miles (3.2 kilometers) crossing the Sgt. Donald Wilkinson Bridge to Plum Island. Take your first right onto Sunset Drive and travel 0.5 miles (0.8 kilometers) to the refuge entrance. &lt;br /&gt;LUNCH will be at bobs Seafood after the walk.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240154500000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235257961000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHESTNUT HILL -PARKER RIVER REFUGE- PLUM ISLAND, NEWBURYPORT</name><id>9792270</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237734000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/9792270/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/4/9/global_7252425.jpeg</photo_url></item>