<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;ldquo;Humanism as a Source of Inspiration and Meaning&amp;rdquo; with&amp;nbsp;Dr. Lawrence Rifkin &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Can the humanist world view be inspirational? Can humanism appeal to our  emotions, as well as our intellects? Can a deep understanding of the  human within an evolutionary naturalistic world fill us with profound  wonder and provide a deep sense of meaning? &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; This talk will assert that the answer is &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo; to these questions.  Humanism has made impressive and worthy progress in its focus on social  action, political justice, and critical analysis. Still, there are  literally millions of people who label themselves &amp;ldquo;non-religious&amp;rdquo; who do  not identify as humanists. Why? For those who need or want a deeper  sense of meaning and understanding, humanism can provide a psychologically satisfying alternative to theological cosmologies, an  alternative that is both satisfying to our intellects and full of  emotional grandeur. Come join us to hear and discuss how humanism and  the scientific world view can provide a positive, inspiring vision of  our place in a naturalistic universe.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Lawrence Rifkin, a physician and writer, has been published by the  National Academy of Science, the Humanist, Contemporary Pediatrics, and  Medical Economics magazine, in which he was named the Grand Prize winner  of the Doctors&amp;rsquo; Writing Contest. He has written multiple essays for  Free Inquiry magazine exploring humanism and science as a source of  meaning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everyone is welcome! Please consider becoming a member of Greater Worcester Humanists. Membership allows us to do all of the great programs, lectures, meetups, etc. and it's only $30 a year. If you're not interested in membership just yet, please consider donating at the door.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This meeting is at the &amp;lt;a href="&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=90+holden+st,+worcester,+ma&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hnear=&amp;amp;cid=0,0,2161099317048081133&amp;amp;ei=iaJ4S82hOYT08Qbf3630CQ&amp;amp;ved=0CAgQnwIwAA&amp;amp;hq=90+holden+st,+worcester,+ma&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;iwloc=A" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=90+holden+st,+worcester,+ma&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hnear=&amp;amp;cid=0,0,2161099317048081133&amp;amp;ei=iaJ4S82hOYT08Qbf3630CQ&amp;amp;ved...&lt;/a&gt;"&amp;gt;UU Church of Worcester&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Feel free to show up at the church around 6:30pm if you would like to socialize or help set up.&amp;lt;hr /&amp;gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Through the front doors on the right.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306078221000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302814339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Can Humanism be a Source of Inspiration and Meaning?"</name><id>17307998</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305068400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/17307998/</event_url></item>