<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our very own Kelly Halldorson has organized a nationwide cleanup effort, details below. Just RSVP with the location you are cleaning up, then email Kelly with the results at the email below. She managed to get several local articles with her 38 mile walk. This could get us some great publicity nationwide, and the timing just prior to the NH debates is appropriate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Supporters! Let's clean up America for Ron Paul,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While others are relaxing at barbeques with family and friends this Labor Day weekend let's clean up America for Ron Paul! You can work one day or all three it's entirely up to you. Pick up one bag or twenty, it's all good. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During my 38 mile walk from my home to my state (NH) capital I saw a lot of trash on the side of the road. It occurred to me that, like the walk, a clean-up effort might be a positive way to get some attention to the campaign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My vision is that Ron Paul supporters all over the country organize their own efforts. You can clean up the sides of roads, parks or even beaches. My suggestion would be to at least go where there are lots of people. Bring some signs to stick in the ground (while you are cleaning), wear your favorite Ron Paul t-shirt and don't forget to bring some literature to hand out to people that are curious about Ron Paul.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please video your efforts if at all possible and take lots of photos. I'm going to put together a press release and contact the national (and my local) media before and after the event. I want to get a tally of all the trash collected over the weekend so PLEASE send me your results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don't have to be in a meet-up group to participate. This is something you can just do as family if you like. Take your kids to a park and clean up the park with them or the beach. Any effort is appreciated and will add to our total trash count. :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone that plans on participating please email me your name, email, and where (and which day and time) you plan on cleaning and I'll work on getting some press for your efforts. This is your event so handle your state/city/beach clean-up however you'd like. If you would just send me info on what you're doing so I can put together an impressive list for the national media that would be fantastic. I'd also love to get a head count and/or list of names. So, contact me with that info too...first names are fine if you prefer. I'd just like to be able to tell the press how many supporters participated and how many bags of trash we collected. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get this on EVERY national and local television station out there! Let's make this clean-up HUGE and get the Paul campaign lots of press all while we are doing some good for our communities!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are participating please send me your info and/or updates to cleanup@halldorson.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WOO HOO!! Go Ron Paul, &lt;br /&gt;Kelly Halldorson&lt;br /&gt;www.halldorson.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542002000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187812999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nation-wide Cleanup for Paul</name><id>6226156</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188828000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6226156/</event_url></item>