<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Overnight road trip to the Long Island wine region for a tasting extravaganza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan is to gather in Hudson and leave at 8am Sat, Sept 24 to catch the 10am New London ferry to LI which arrives at 11:30am. Most wineries open at 11am.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I'm still researching hotels and a restaurant for dinner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Return is 3pm ferry on Sunday, Sept 25.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Of course, you can make other arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We can and should car pool to reduce car and ferry costs. A parking garage is available at the ferry. We could also gather in New London and take only a few cars over.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please sign-up only if you definitely want to attend.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;I suggest each person bring a picnic lunch(for sat and sun), instead of searching for places to eat. This way, we can picnic at a winery, buy wine and also have more time to visit other wineries! Wineries close around 5pm, so we would arrive in Riverhead around 5:30. Check into hotel, drive to restaurant, cocktails, dinner at ~7pm. Leave at 10am Sunday morning, arrive first winery by ~11am(or 10:30). &amp;nbsp;I need to be home by 7pm so my last winery is Old Fields at 1:45pm, leaving by 2:15 to catch ferry at 3pm. Of course, if we have more than 1 car,&amp;nbsp; others can catch a later ferry. You could also reserve a later ferry and possibly get stand-by, if you decide to leave earlier. Hotels apparently are in short supply due to many weddings. However, I found a Budget East End in Riverhead for $129. Its located at 30 East Moriches Road, Riverhead, NY. They have a 48 hour cancellation policy. I'll search for restaurants and offer a few suggestions for consideration. &amp;nbsp;Mostly using TripAdvisor: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurants-g48502-Riverhead_Long_Island_New_York.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurants-g48502-Riverhead_Long_Island_New_York.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I'm making a ferry reservation for myself and 1 car. I can take 3 people comfortably (and I'm not drinking). So if you're taking your car, you'll need to do make reservations. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The drivers need to know who is car pooling, so they can add the passengers to their reservation. You can also make a reservation just as a passenger.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.longislandferry.com/Reservation/Departure.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.longislandferry.com/Reservation/Departure.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ** This is a fair weather trip **&amp;nbsp; That is, the weather should be mostly fair. But if the forecast is rain all weekend, its not much fun. You'll need $$ for wine tastings. Here's a map of the LI wineries. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.liwines.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.liwines.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp; and &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.liwineguide.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.liwineguide.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Please let me know if you have any questions. I've traveled this route often and can probably answer any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Blake</member_name><member_id>748860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317769074000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>White Wine Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-MetroWest-White-Wine-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1441608</id><group_lat>42.5900001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The MetroWest White Wine Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315579522000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Long Island Wine Tasting Road Trip</name><id>32886972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316865600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-MetroWest-White-Wine-Meetup-Group/events/32886972/</event_url></item>