<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>While Tom and some other meet-up members are off watching a 7 hour Hungarian film at the Harvard Film Archive, I thought it would be fun to continue our recent Asian film bent with Linda Linda Linda. Also, after all the violence in Curse of the Golden Flower, I think we're due for a fun film :). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2005) dir dir Nobuhiro Yamashita w/Dun-na Bae, Aki Maeda, Yu Kashii, Shiori Sekine [114 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fun, flirty and irrevocably for the young and young-at-heart, LINDA LINDA LINDA takes its title from an almost unbearably catchy '80s pop song by the Japanese punk group The Blue Hearts (&amp;quot;the Japanese Ramones&amp;quot;). It's also one of three Blue Hearts tunes that four Japanese female high school students are determined to play at their school's annual rock festival. But when their vocalist drops out unexpectedly, drummer Kyoto, guitarist Kei, and bassist Nozumi choose a girl at random and their choice ends up being a Korean exchange student, Son, whose grasp on Japanese is a little rough. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Imagine downing Jarmusch and Kaurismaki's entire output in one sugary gulp and you'll get an idea of what bliss awaits you&amp;quot; -- Time Out New York&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;That song, simple and simply irresistible, which neither meditation nor surgery has been able to remove from my head since I saw the movie last year at the Toronto Film Festival. Everybody: Linda Linda! Linda Linda! Lin-da-ah-ah!&amp;quot; -- Richard Corliss, Time Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of this year's most unexpected pleasures.&amp;quot; -- Jeannette Catsoulis, The New York Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I (Nicole) will be standing at the front of the theater after the film ends with a meet-up sign so we can go off to a nearby place (Au Bon Pain or Boloco maybe?) to discuss the film. Looking forward to seeing group members again, both old and new.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1169059497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168364834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Linda Linda Linda</name><id>5378726</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168713000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5378726/</event_url></item>