<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 Powers Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.540779</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Witches Woods</name><city>Westford</city><id>3989282</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.442612</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.34000003338</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VERY IMPORTANT: Be sure to READ the details at the bottom of this listing!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/WitchesWoods.png" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, October 28th, we're going to &lt;strong&gt;Witches Woods&lt;/strong&gt; in Westford Mass to have the most Halloween fun as possible! Check this out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Many people are unaware that deep in "The Woods" of Nashoba Valley, exists a dark and terrifying secret! According to an ancient legend, a coven of witches met secretly each October to practice their powerful magic. Their one sacred task was to guard an ancient "gateway" that held back the dreaded creatures of the night. Despite the coven's best efforts, the evil presence has inevitably grown too strong. The Supernatural creatures now roam the woods freely in search of helpless prey to drag into the night. The authorities were called in, but not a single trace of their bodies was ever found.  Are you brave enough to take “The Haunted Hayride” to discover the legend of Witch’s Woods… or will you just be another victim?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your single admission ticket includes unlimited access to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.witchswoods.com/images/jackolantern_jamboree.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Come see hundreds of professionally carved pumpkins, brought to life in this spectacular display. Jack O'Lanterns are stacked high with bright lights illuminating their faces. The carvings feature famous horror movie characters, and other Halloween icons. Classic faces and silluoutes of Halloween creatures fill the rows in this unique jack o'lantern display. All visitors, even those without admission tickets, are welcome to walk the rows of carved pumpkins and admire these beautiful works of art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/pumpkin-patch.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.witchswoods.com/images/horrorwood_chamber.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;A terrifying new walk-through highlights past and present horror movie icons with a surprising twist. Come explore the scenes with characters from your favorite Halloween and horror movies. All visitors, even those without admission tickets, are welcome to visit this attraction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/dracula.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your ticket will also grant you one ride on our Haunted Hayride, and one entry into each of our haunted houses including Castle Morbid, Nightmare Mansion, and the 3D Keeper's Crypt.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.witchswoods.com/images/hayride09.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;The woods at Nashoba Valley Ski Area have been taken over by the souls of the dead. As you board your hayride, you will notice that your driver sits in the center of the tractor, far away from the sides where guests are vulnerable to attacks. When the wagon pulls into the woods, you might see a witch or two darting in the trees. Although they are overwhelmed by the growing numbers of ghouls, the witches still watch guard over the woods and our guests. Deeper into the woods, you will hear werewolves howling at the moon, and maybe even see one near the hayride, attracted by the scent of human flesh. Zombies are never far behind, and struggle to keep up to your wagon, lured by the tasty feet dangling off the sides. Spirits of dead lumberjacks haunt the woods, ready to cut through anything, including the wooden wagonload of visitors. Unknown creatures crawl in the dark, barely visible but surely advancing on you. You won't be alone in these woods, will you enter? * This attraction uses strobe lights for effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/foggy.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.witchswoods.com/images/castle_morbid.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Will you enter the dark gates of castle morbid? The spirits living in the castle walls have grown in strength and can cast confusion spells on you. Only the strong will survive this medieval journey. Entering the castle, the younger sprites sense your presence and pass through the walls to get near you. Screaming to alert the others, they chase you and each other through the winding halls that fill the castle. The oldest spirits live deep within the castle's keep, eager for fresh flesh which they will inhabit soon. This castle was once used to keep intruders out, but now the castle serves a different purpose. With the defenses turned in on the spirits of the dead, will you be able to get out alive?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1castle.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.witchswoods.com/images/nightmare_mansion.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Enter Nightmare Mansion if you dare! Some ghosts inside are older than the legend of the house itself. This large house once belonged to a single family with a loving father who wanted to give everything to his many children. In desperation, he sold his soul to the devil in exchange for a larger house and for his children to live long lives. The house grew larger, but became entangled with vines and overgrowth. The halls are twisted with secrets passages, and the floors are scattered with giant holes leading to the depths of hell. His children have lived for nearly 200 years, unable to die even as the leathery flesh drapes off of their withering bones. Years of their torturous existence in the mansion has made them upset with anyone who steps foot into the house. If nosy people aren't scared by their painful wails or wall banging, the aging children will take more drastic measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1mansion.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.witchswoods.com/images/keepers_crypt.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Enter a whole new dimension in terror. Pass through the wrought-iron gates into a three-dimensional land of the living dead! The dead have awakened, and straining to leave their weakened corpses they have crossed into the third dimension. Rotting flesh tears and bones crack apart as the living dead scramble after young bodies. You may even feel them flying into your eye sockets as they jump towards you, eager to posess your body with their weary soul. The walls seem like they are shifting in, the zombies numbers multiply, and you'll have to pass through a gauntlet of animated cadavers to leave these terrifiying grounds. * This attraction uses strobe lights for effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/ghost-scare.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carnival Rides and Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;A choice of twirling, spinning, and whimsical rides that are sure to be a big thrill. Rides will only be available on the 3rd, 4th, and 5th weekends in October.  Test your luck at The Carnival Games and win fun prizes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1rides.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Witch's Woods Killer Thriller Stage Show Live Performances &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(Hourly-60 minute shows)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Hosts: DJ Aether, MC Byron, and Vincent Priceless— will host a fun, entertaining and fright filled hourly stage show with audience participation to win prizes, including skiing and tubing tickets.  The Monster Dating Game and The Air Guitar Competition are some of the participants favorites.  Be sure to stay to the final show act, where participants will pay homage to the King of Pop, Witch’s Woods "Killer Thriller" style, for more fun prizes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1stageshow.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Freakshow Firestarter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;The Legendary Jonathan Damon will be juggling fire and riding a unicycle around the Screampark.  Freak Show leads off the Stage Show each night, juggling fire, knives and chickens.  BBQ Anyone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;¬ David Statik&lt;/strong&gt; – Fire Poi with a Flare! David swirls and spins Fire Poi in a dazzling, on the edge show.  All of our Fire Poi Performers will demonstrate awesome Feats with Fire!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;¬ Cirque de Light&lt;/strong&gt; – Fire Poi Performers, Andrew Lindsay and Elizabeth Knights will amaze the audience with a death defying display of twirling and juggling fire, while intertwined together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1firestarters.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch This!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;xobject height="264" width="470"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/tStUilXJaM4?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_US" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;--- THE IMPORTANT DETAILS ---&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hey folks! This is going to be an awesome event at a great place! Here's how it works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. RSVP&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - You need to be on the RSVP list before Sunday, the 28th at 2:00 PM when the list closes. NO EXCEPTIONS! I need to give them our list ahead of time. $1 to RSVP. You NEED to be on the RSVP list to get the group rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Use The Code Word&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - On the day of the event, there's a Code Word you need to know to get our special group rate when you buy your ticket. I will email this out to the RSVP's on the DAY OF THE EVENT. Remember to check your email for this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Purchase Your Tickets &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; - When you to Witches Woods, you will visit the WILL CALL window. There, you will use the Code Word to get our group discount. Tickets are $25 each (reg $30). &lt;br /&gt;

 - This price on the combo ticket includes the Witch’s Woods Ticket at $22 per ticket and $8.00 of Carnival Food. (We actually give you the value $12 in coupons to spend at the concession stands.)  The food served on the Midway includes: hotdogs, burgers, sausages, steak and cheese sandwiches, BBQ chicken sandwiches, fried mozzarella sticks, turkey drum sticks, chicken fingers, french fries, candy and caramel apples, fried dough, corn dogs, cotton candy, popcorn, soda, hot apple cider, coffee and hot cocoa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Meet Up!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - We will meet up near the entrance to The Outlook Restaurant between 6:30 and 7:00 PM. From there we'll split off into groups. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;- Don't worry if you can't make it by 7:00 pm, you can get your tickets up until 10:30.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 -  &lt;span&gt;If people would like to meet earlier and get dinner or drinks from the Outlook, let&lt;/span&gt; me tell you the food and drinks are TOP-NOTCH! I was out there the other day getting this event organized and we had dinner and drinks and let me just tell you, everything was AMAZING!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Have Fun! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; - The park stops letting people in at 10:30 and it closes whenever the last person has gone through the park, whatever time that is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Late Dinner? &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; - Anyone want to get a late dinner? Leave a comment and let me know! The Outlook closes at midnight, so plenty of time for us to get food and another drink or two before we head home again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Outlook Restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : justify"&gt;The Outlook Restaurant and Lounge is a year round establishment at Nashoba Valley Ski Area which&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="text-align : justify"&gt;features savory steaks, fresh seafood, and pastas in a rustic setting with a view. The menu and specialty&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="text-align : justify"&gt;drinks change with the seasons and compliment the lifestyle of our customers. The restaurant will have some&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="text-align : justify"&gt;life-size, custom made horror movie characters displayed throughout the venue and every night the staff is dressed up in costume for Halloween.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1outlook.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Looking forward to having you all on Sunday, October 28th!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~Matt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Code Word will be sent via email on the day of the event. Remember to look for this email! :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Adams</member_name><member_id>13654210</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351478452000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350617041000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup Night At Witches Woods!</name><id>87642052</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351463400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/87642052/</event_url></item>