<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;UPDATE 7/8/11: The current roster is 10 men and 10 women. If you would like to be on the waitlist in case someone cancels, signup information is below (please include a phone number with your information).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a QK doubles event, which is a friendship tournament event meetup. The event will consist of reverse coed doubles matches played in a King-Queen format, meaning that you will be playing with and against different people during pool play. Top players after pool play will compete in a playoff format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a friendship tournament format, meaning call your own faults, as there are no referees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be using the ruleset listed in the first post on the following: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The events will start at 10:30 AM and will likely last at least until the mid afternoon (~3:30 PM). If you would like to play in this event you must commit to staying at least through the end of pool play. Remember to bring snacks/food and water/beverages, as this event will involve a significant amount of volleyball play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is intended for players with experience playing reverse coed doubles format. Signup for these events is a little different. To sign up for one or more of these events, please send me an email using the following link on meetup: &lt;a href="http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=4774008" class="linkified"&gt;http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=4774008&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the email, provide the following information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Name
 &lt;br /&gt; Gender
 &lt;br /&gt; Event date(s) that you would like to sign up for
 &lt;br /&gt; Outdoor rating (AA/A/BB/B), if you have one; otherwise, short description of reverse coed doubles experience
 &lt;br /&gt; Confirm that you have read the ruleset at the link above and that you agree to play by those rules.
 &lt;br /&gt; Confirm that you can commit to play from 10:30 AM to 3:30 PM.
 &lt;br /&gt; Signup partner name (if you have a signup partner)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preferably, each player in a signup pair should send an email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this event we will have a nominal cap of 20 players (10 men, 10 women) to simplify the event management. Preference is given to AA/A/BB players who sign up in male/female pairs, although some single signups will be allowed. Note that sending an email does not guarantee a spot to play; spots are only guaranteed if you are assigned a Yes RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Lee</member_name><member_id>4774008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310527464000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305953381000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Outdoor (Grass) QK RevCoed Doubles Volleyball</name><id>19170911</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310221800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/19170911/</event_url></item>