<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;starting at Mount Osceola Trailhead&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;hike 3.20 mi/2 hr 41 min/+2016 ft on the Mount Osceola Trail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;The trail leaves Tripoli Rd. and climbs moderately with somewhat rocky footing, going east across the south slope of Breadtray Ridge. It begins to climb by switchbacks toward the ridge top, and the footing improves. A ledge on the left offers a view of Sandwich Mountain, and it crosses a small brook (unreliable). The trail resumes its switchbacks, gains the summit ridge and turns right, and soon reaches the summit ledge, with excellent views. A good outlook to the north can be obtained from a small ledge on a short side path, which begins at the older fire tower site that is located in the woods just to the west of the open ledge.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;to Mt Osceola&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;hike 1.00 mi/40 min/-150 ft on the Mount Osceola Trail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;The trail then turns left and descends from the summit, alternating flat stretches with steep, rocky descents. Just before reaching the main pass between Osceola and East Osceola, it descends a steep chimney, which can be avoided by a detour to the left (north). The trail crosses the pass and climbs moderately with steep pitches past a fine outlook on the left, reaching the summit of East Osceola (marked by a small cairn).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;to East Osceola&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Totals&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Distance 4.20 mi&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Time 3 hr 21 min&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Elev Gain +2526 ft&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Elev Loss -660 ft&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Elev Change +1866 ft&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Difficulty/hike rating:  moderate    {easy paced but have mountain trail experience  1 mph pace if elevation is steep}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;. We will meet together and&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;identify the pace groups so everyone hikes at a comfortable pace.  The summit is an option. All hikers are welcome to hike. Your group can enjoy a great hike with a shorter turn around option. Slower hikers might want to start earlier to finish at a reasonable time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A weather advisory will cancel this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A minimum of 4 hikers will be required. While we will hike at a comfortable pace, no one should hike alone.  Proper "Hikesafe" clothing and gear required. Know your equipment and how to pack your gear, review the weather conditions before you arrive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition to the standard lists, remember to pack "gatorade" drinks or gels to replace your electrolytes. This is advised for any high endurance exercise that lasts for over one hour.&lt;a href="http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1"&gt;http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/7/event_10322999.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet 7:30 at the exit 23 carpool  or 9am trailhead. restrooms, Dunkin Donuts and Subway are just past the park and ride that is patroled.  phone/text so we have real plans to meet you for the meetup, and no question of if your in the right location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338256174000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330396932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT Osceola and East Osceola Casual paced 4000ft</name><id>dgmrlcyqhbkc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338123600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/54119282/</event_url></item>