<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We`ll be starting off our Ladies &amp;amp; Gents Night Out with a quaint and intimate wine and cheese reception for our members. Show up after work for a laid back get together of about 30-40 members ages 25-45.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ADMISSION INCLUDES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Private Store rental&lt;br /&gt;LIMITED Open Wine Bar - will not be like the Art &amp;amp; Wine Socials. Expect 1 glass per person.&lt;br /&gt;Cheeses/Chocolates&lt;br /&gt;Shopping!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$15 for one person&lt;br /&gt;$10 for groups of 3 or More&lt;br /&gt;PREPAY HERE: &lt;a href="http://bostonmoxieinthecity.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonmoxieint...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLUS..FOR THE LADIES ONLY...SIGN UP FOR THIS EVENT AND SAVE $10 OFF THE BJ CLASS BEING HELD THE SAME NIGHT!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8:15, if you choose, you can leave this social mixer and head a half a block down to our &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/moxieinthecityboston/calendar/12725076/"&gt;Women Only Sex Ed Salon/BJ Class being held at Boston Common Coffee Shop at 8:30.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT SHAKE THE TREE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amidst the bustle of Boston`s North End, Shake the Tree is one of the neighborhood`s newer eclectic and trendy boutiques. It features a wide range of stylish contemporary clothing, leather handbags, mixed-media jewelry, unique gifts, cool home decor, ribbon-wrapped soaps, scented candles and cute things for babies. Shoppers will find the latest clothing collections from designers including Ella Moss, Susana Monaco, Velvet, Johnny Was and Splendid plus amazing bags and wallets by Hobo, Tano, Linea Pelle, Latico &amp;amp; Highway! There is also a wide showing of jewelry by local artisans.&lt;br /&gt;A treasure chest of contemporary and vintage groove looks, Shake the Tree is the perfect spot to find that hard-to-find gift.  Voted `Best Neighborhood Shopping` by Boston Magazine; `Best Hidden Gem` by the Improper Bostonian and `Best Jewelry` by The Weekly Dig, we are open later on weekends to catch the dinner crowds!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shakethetreeboston.com/index.html"&gt;http://www.shakethetr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Show up and expect to mingle with 15-20 other women ages 23-45. We`ll set up a small open wine bar for you to pour your own wine and set up a table full of nibbles like cheeses and chocolates.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910704</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272841404000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New Residents</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-666</urlname><id>375609</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston New In Town Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269902680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chocolate &amp; Wine Networking Social</name><id>13030063</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272668400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-666/events/13030063/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/2/global_14012002.jpeg</photo_url></item>