<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/a/event_92582842.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;People, I am told, talk about our cooking club at other Meetups and amongst their outside friends. To me, people comment on how other than the common or normal our group is. It is difficult to classify, full of friendly loud people who embrace the shy members, made of all ages and backgrounds of people, singles couples, people with dogs and people with cats. We have people who just throw things in a pot and hope for the best, and we have people who check their recipe after every ingredient addition. We are a drinking club with a cooking problem which has a fair number of nondrinkers as active members. From the beginning, this group has been an anomaly and about consumption so this month&amp;rsquo;s theme seems almost as if it should have been one of the nominees for our group&amp;rsquo;s name last year. There is certainly a fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interesting thing about gastronomy is that many folk think this means food but it is actually about eating, not about the creation of food or the food itself. This is about the science and the art of eating. Food takes its place in gastronomic focuses when it transcends it role as nutrient, goes beyond taste and becomes the full sensory experience sought by the true gourmand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is eaten must appeal to the eye in both its own embodiment and in its presentation; there are no paper plates or plastic sporks in gourmand. It must appeal to our nose long before it is tasted or even seen. The feel of the bite on one&amp;rsquo;s teeth and one&amp;rsquo;s tongue must ask your palate to sing with joy. Choruses of MMMMMMMMMMMMMmmmmmmmmm, would suggest success with this piece. Nomnomnnom. Taste of course, and the lingering of the high point after taste is key, of course, but all the&amp;nbsp;senses&amp;nbsp;must be employed for a true gastronomic experience. The crunch of the piece of toast perfectly buttered, the pop of the skin on a grape, the crackle of crispy crust broken through to allow the steam to escape, food sounds shape our experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These sounds can include the clatter or the silverware, the smacking of lips, the happy conversational hum of the diners, the clink of wine glasses, and the sizzle of the grill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a gourmand is allowed the full sensual experience of the dish before her the desire to interact with the experience deepens. Gourmands write about food, they photograph and create images of food; their dreams have flavors. They seek out environments in which food is center stage and everything complements its existence and its demise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In many ways, this month&amp;rsquo;s theme is the mirror twin of last month&amp;rsquo;s theme. This month calls for searching out the finest ingredients, creating the perfect presentation, considering the complementary environment, and careful combinations of beauty for each sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The anomaly for any other group would be if this &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; work, for our group the anomaly would be if it &lt;em&gt;did not&lt;/em&gt;. As individuals preparing our offering, however, challenging the norm comes naturally, blazing new trails of ingredients and taste, these are where you excel. I am very excited to see what gastronomic anomalies you have in store for the Fabulous Foodies' collective plates and palates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;And a little known but favorite (of mine) alternative rock band provides our theme song for this month&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XwCn0p2x_zU"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XwCn0p2x_zU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/f/c/event_92584092.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVPs open 30 days prior to the event and these dinners fill up quickly. Remember there are no rules. Caryl will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time.&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Address will be sent via email the Wednesday before the dinner</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331738258000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328766034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gastronomic Anomaly</name><id>qxhmlcyqfbmb</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331337600000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/51661132/</event_url></item>