<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>524 Main Street (Route 6a)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02638</zip><lat>33.498581</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-385-3434</phone><name>Borsari Gallery</name><city>Dennis</city><id>1360305</id><country>us</country><lon>-88.402388</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be reading the book:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Three Cups of Tea: One Man’s Mission to Promote Peace . . . One School at a Time , Greg Mortenson, and journalist David Oliver Relin, recount the journey that led Mortenson from a failed 1993 attempt to climb Pakistan’s K2, the world’s second highest mountain, to successfully establish schools in some of the most remote regions of Afghanistan and Pakistan. By replacing guns with pencils, rhetoric with reading, Mortenson combines his unique background with his intimate knowledge of the third-world to promote peace with books, not bombs, and successfully bring education and hope to remote communities in central Asia. Three Cups of Tea is at once an unforgettable adventure and the inspiring true story of how one man really is changing the world—one school at a time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us at the beautiful Borsari Gallery to view the artwork and for tea and light lunch to discuss the book (as well as our usual girl talk!) We will be trying to get the private diningroom for this event (Thank you, Nichole!)...it should be a special afternoon to discuss a special book with special friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****Attire should be afternoon chic! No jeans or TShirts please!****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With groups of 10+ the tea room likes to offer 3 choices each &lt;br /&gt;for $21 all include Tip and taxes.  This makes it very easy for &lt;br /&gt;everyone to pay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Borsari Afternoon Tea--Scone, 8 finger sandwiches 4 tea &lt;br /&gt;desserts and a pot of tea&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soup de Jour and Sandwich of the day--Bowl of Soup,Chicken &lt;br /&gt;Salad with Cranberries and Walnuts, 2 tea desserts  and a pot &lt;br /&gt;of tea&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quiche of the Day with Salad--Quiche of the Day, a side salad 2 &lt;br /&gt;tea desserts  and a pot of tea.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara </member_name><member_id>7313867</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286405866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283041755000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club and Tea Luncheon at Borsari Gallery...UPDATE! 9/3/10 Please read all!</name><id>14575674</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286121600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/14575674/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>