<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Providence, RI</address_2><address_1>103 Point St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.816340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 831-6666</phone><name>Olga's Cup and Saucer</name><city>Providence</city><id>146379</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.407760</lon></venue><fee><label>Optional donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hey Gang,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's officially spring now, traditionally a season of birth and renewal. We're just a month away from the 1-year anniversary of our group's formation, so I thought we'd head back to our very first Meetup location at Olga's Cup and Saucer to indulge in their fine culinary offerings and hopefully enjoy some fresh air on their outdoor patio. If you plan on ordering food there, you may want to show up early as they can get pretty busy at lunch time. I'm going to head over early to snag some table space, so please be sure to RSVP yay or nay so I know how many seats we'll need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for discussion topics, it will be open format as usual. I was in San Francisco last month for the O'Reilly Web 2.0 Expo and Conference and I'd be happy to share my notes if anyone is interested. Feel free to suggest any other topics on our new mailing list: &lt;a href="mailto:webdesign-410@meetup.com" target="_blank"&gt;webdesign-410@meetup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in attending this event, consider making a donation towards the monthly cost of running the group website. All donations are optional and there is no required fee for any of our monthly events. You can submit your donation via PayPal or to me directly at the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Shearer</member_name><member_id>1529786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178985979000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Web Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>webdesign-410</urlname><id>272511</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Providence Web Development Lunch Hour Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176386658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence Web Development Lunch Hour May Meetup</name><id>5662944</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178812800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/webdesign-410/events/5662944/</event_url></item>