<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chace Center // RISD Museum</name><city>Providence</city><id>846995</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408308</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check out Design the Night: You Are Here - at the RISD Museum!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last Design the Night: Trends in August was such a success that the museum decided to do it again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Where are you? Navigate ideas and artworks related to place, space, and time. Explore online and public spaces, as well as traditional and surprising representations of landscapes in paintings and photographs. Artists along with RISD and Brown faculty, students and alumni are your guides in this evening of personal inquiry and discovery. Free, all welcome.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be checking out the Artist Lab and the Magic Lantern Performances/Experience. All are welcome to join me or participate in whatever you like, and come and go as you please. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is NOT an organized meetup, but an FYI instead, since its a large space and everyone may have different activities they would like to experience. However, please RSVP so we know who is coming and can look for you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food is somewhat limited at the event, so you may want to go earlier and hit up Harry's Burger Bar or XO Cafe before hand (or after if you prefer). The &lt;span&gt;Mijos Taco Truck and Providence Coffee Roasters Mobile Cafe will be on hand in the plaza and there is a cash bar. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The schedule of the evening's events are below:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Magic Lantern Performances/Experience &lt;br /&gt;

 6-8 pm &lt;br /&gt;

An early optical device used for the projection of images for mass audiences, the magic lantern reached the height of its popularity as a Victorian parlor amusement, educating and entertaining audiences through playful illustrated lectures. In conjunction with the Wonder Show, the Museum recreates a contemporary interpretation of this 19th century popular art form, taking visitors on a visual tour through scenes of historic landscapes. &lt;br /&gt;

 Showcasing the historic photographs of Northwestern photographer Asahel Curtis, the event will feature storyteller Laura Brown-Lavoie and musician Ben Cosgrove. For more information, check out: &lt;a href="http://thewondershow.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://thewondershow.org/&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Artist's Lab &lt;br /&gt;

 5–7 pm | Fain Gallery, 3rd fl &lt;br /&gt;

 Join an artist for an experimental drop-in lab that invites participants to co-conspire, experiment and create. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Refreshments &lt;br /&gt;

 5:30-9 pm | Chace Plaza, North Main St &lt;br /&gt;

 The Mijos Taco Truck and Providence Coffee Roasters Mobile Cafe will be selling food and coffee to keep you going! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Music + Cash Bar &lt;br /&gt;

 5:30-9:30 pm | Grand Gallery, 5th fl &lt;br /&gt;

 Enjoy a drink from our cash bar and listen to music provided by a local DJ. Mark your hometown on world, United States or Rhode Island maps - see where our evening's visitors hail. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Double Take Gallery Talk &lt;br /&gt;

 'Landscape with Tree Trunks' &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30-7:15 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Join specialists from various fields as they offer differing views on landscapes, stimulate thinking about social context, artistic interpretation, and ever-evolving meanings. RISD Professor of Illustration Fritz Drury and Neal Overstrom, Director of RISD’s Edna W. Lawrence Nature Lab, consider the representation of the sublime in Thomas Cole’s majestic painting. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Gallery Talk: Art Shots &lt;br /&gt;

 7-7:30 pm | Meet at Babylonian Lion, 5th fl &lt;br /&gt;

 Explore art and design through this gallery talk spanning centuries and cultures from the perspective of student artists and art historians. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Work in Process &lt;br /&gt;

 7:30-9 pm | Asian Textile Gallery, 6th fl &lt;br /&gt;

 Join RISD students for an on-going conversation about the processes and techniques used to create their art in relation to historical examples on view. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Artists on Art &lt;br /&gt;

 Artists, designers, and experts share perspectives on their own works, art processes, and the future of art in lively, invigorating discussions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Alone in Public &lt;br /&gt;

 7:30-8:15 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Artist Wendy Richmond (Navigating the Personal Bubble) discusses her work exploring public privacy through personal technology with Mark Tribe, Assistant Professor of Modern Culture and Media at Brown University. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Artists on Art: Photo Futures &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30-9:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 FlakPhoto.com creator Andy Adams and Jörg M. Colberg, publisher of the website Conscientious, explore the intersection of online publishing, social media, and community collaboration in this discussion of photography in the Internet era. &lt;br /&gt;

 --- &lt;br /&gt;

 Mix, match, and custom-tailor your Museum experience. Dynamic evenings offer ways to connect with art and one another. Lively discussions with artists and designers, hands-on art-making, a Magic Lantern show, live music and more — come design your night!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is posted as an FYI - I will probably be going wearing the usual blue and white gradated scarf. Look for me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348812708000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347572107000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI - Design the Night:YOU ARE HERE at the RISD Museum!</name><id>82282392</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348779600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/82282392/</event_url></item>