<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/5/8/event_225796472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Difficulty: Difficult&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 7-8 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duration: 2.25hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read the entire write up before signing up for this hike / walk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by signing up for this hike you ( and your guest if applicable) agree to the terms of the liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We will walk  at a very brisk pace for about 7-8 miles before sunset. We will start walking North on the path and on the return trip we will try and time it to see the sun set on the water @ Larisa Park or Sabins Point Park. When we did this last week we averaged over 3.5 MPH. The East Bay Bike Path is a flat ribbon of former rail tracks that goes from the Providence/ East Providence line down to Bristol. It is about 28 miles round trip. We will be starting at the Loof Carousel in Riverside and heading North for a bit before returning to try and catch the sunset on the Narragansett Bay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Headlamp is a good idea for PM walks. As always bring snacks and water. I think the forecast is for warmer temps in the daytime. Make sure you bring a wind layer or fleece  for when temps start to drop..See you in the parking next to Blount Clam Shack. Again FASTER PACED WALK. If you are unsure of pace contact me and if I don't know you I will contact you to be sure you are on the same page as far as pace goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>parking lot in front of the Blount Clam Shack  next to carousel</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370399342000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1370293823000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fast paced Power Walk on The  East Bay Bike Path</name><id>122749792</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370381400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/122749792/</event_url></item>