<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday at The Beehive Bar &amp;amp; Bistro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's South End neighborhood. 6:30-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday  April 10th.  This time we are taking the party to the brand new Beehive Bar &amp;amp; Bistro located in Boston's trendy South End neighborhood. The Beehive is one of the &amp;quot;hidden gems &amp;quot; among the Boston nightlife scene and is known for its great live Jazz music and amazing cocktails! If you enjoy a great laid back but lively atmosphere with good music and people then this is an event you do not want to miss!   So what better way to come out this Thurs and have a few cocktails with the group as we gear up for another  festive weekend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting details: The address is 541 Tremont st.  I highly recommend going online (google) to get a better idea for directions. Also check out the venue website for Beehive at &lt;a href="http://www.beehiveboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beehivebos...&lt;/a&gt;.  This will give you a better overall sense of the venue and provide pinpoint directions from your destination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inside, we will meet at the LOWER level bar area . Like any event, when arriving please be sure to locate the organizer.   Please do not hesitate to call or text me upon arrival if you are having trouble finding the group. My picture is on the site under the Assistant Organizer section so I should not be hard to find. The  Beehive is one of the most lively and packed venues on Thurs nites so I highly ENCOURAGE you to attend early as possible. My phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line to Copley&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to Back Bay&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note please see the message board regarding meetup/event  etiquette**&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please call or text my cell when ariving at the Beehive</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208040050000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>A great way to start the weekend!!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207535211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thirsty Thursdays Afterwork Mixer Returns  The Beehive!!!</name><id>7688524</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207866600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/7688524/</event_url></item>