<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Directions below&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chill out, watch a movie, socialize, eat pizza, yummy chocolates, and more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat will supply the pizza. You bring what you want to drink, a side dish or your favorite chocolates to share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie TBD at a later date by consensus (I promise, not a &amp;quot;chick&amp;quot; flick). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's enjoy each other's company and make new friends&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions will be sent out as the date gets closer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joint event with &amp;quot;Spice of Life too short&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Pat's house in Belchertown&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 9 from Amherst: &lt;br /&gt;Go thru lights at Mobil stations and stay on 9 east &lt;br /&gt;Take a left at the blinking yellow light (Old Enfield Road) &lt;br /&gt;Take a left at Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;2nd house on the left - #15 Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 9 from Ware: &lt;br /&gt;Make a right at the blinking yellow light onto Old Enfield Road &lt;br /&gt;Take a left at Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;2nd house on the left - #15 Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 202 south of Belchertown: &lt;br /&gt;Follow 202 to the center of Belchertown &lt;br /&gt;Go straight thru the lights at the common &lt;br /&gt;At the bottom of the hill, make a left at Route 9 West &lt;br /&gt;Go to blinking red light &lt;br /&gt;Go thru intersection onto Old Enfield Road &lt;br /&gt;Take a left at Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;2nd house on the left - #15 Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 181 from Palmer: &lt;br /&gt;When you get to common in Belchertown, make a right and go down the hill &lt;br /&gt;At the bottom of the hill, make a left at Route 9 West &lt;br /&gt;Go to blinking red light &lt;br /&gt;Go thru intersection onto Old Enfield Road &lt;br /&gt;Take a left at Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;2nd house on the left - #15 Allen Road &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you get lost, call Pat's cell phone: 413-374-3289.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237332534000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1514</urlname><id>824401</id><group_lat>42.0999984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5899963379</group_lon><name>Single Mingle Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233179722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie - Social - Pizza - Chocolates - at Pat's house in Belchertown</name><id>9622088</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234656000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1514/events/9622088/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/e/global_3300622.jpeg</photo_url></item>