<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Valley Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.608825</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-777-1245 </phone><name>Connors Farm</name><city>Danvers</city><id>750154</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.937395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/2/2/event_156403042.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/a/4/event_156403172.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Let's go out to the &lt;strong&gt;singles night event at Connors Farm in Danvers&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have done this event in the past and it has always been fun lets go check out what they have and what they have added this year.  Seeing that it is "Singles Night" there will be other Meetup groups plus other singles groups, there are always a ton of people to meet and talk to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Things you MUST know:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather:&lt;/strong&gt; Bad weather will cancel this event but a light rain &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;will not&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to meetup:&lt;/strong&gt; We will meet outside the Farmstand to the right as you are going in the farm stand.  If you haven't been to any of this group Meetup's events then take a look at my picture or look at the other members coming to the event so you will be looking for the right group(s), some other group may also be waiting there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; I will tell you from past experiences, this can be tough.  If you are able to get there and park in the lot, then you are lucky if not then find a spot on the road, be careful!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; $15.00 (Actually the real price is $20.00, but they are running a special for us singles when you have a party of 15 people then cost is only $15.00 each.  I know my 2 groups we will hit over 15 peeps. So I am putting the cost in as the special price.  &lt;strong&gt;NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; When you get to the register tell the person which group you have signed up on and you will get the discount) I am putting this on my 2 groups, Our Circle of Friends and Connections &amp;amp; friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price includes:&lt;/strong&gt; Haunted cornfield, flashlight maze, private hayride, campfire, hot or cold apple cider, and apple cider donuts. You are more than welcome to bring stick's, marshmallow's to toast at the fire pit.  In the maize we may stay together or split up into groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the Meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811. This phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not paid your dues, this event would be a good opportunity to do so.  Thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/54916378942021045586710/img/smileys/shock.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet outside the Farmstand to the right as you are going in the farm stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349625865000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346978754000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Night at the Corn Maize</name><id>81230672</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349559900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/81230672/</event_url></item>