<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>so it occured to me the other day that it might be cool to have an old-fashioned pub crawl (this time of year makes me mindful of the passage of time...you may be able to guess why) but then i got to thinking, &amp;quot;what the hell is an old-fashioned pub crawl&amp;quot;? did they do that, say, 100 years ago? i'm willing to bet that they did, and very little would have changed, which is actually kind of cool when you think about it: just a group of people going from one watering hole to another, enjoying the unique charms of each establishment and, more importantly, each other's company. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;of course, a truly old-fashioned pub crawl would try to follow in the footsteps of our alcoholic forebears...which is where good old New Haven comes in. New Haven, you see, is a pretty old town (as least as far as we Yankees reckon; Europeans may beg to differ). so i propose to hit up some of the Elm City's more seasoned establishments. the preliminary itinerary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Playwright (9:00ish - 10:00ish)&lt;br /&gt;ok, ok, so it's not an &amp;quot;old&amp;quot; place, strictly speaking. but i've heard that in building it they actually imported and used pieces of churches and old buildings from Ireland and other parts of Europe. so it kinda counts. besides, it kind of feels like you're drinking in church (albeit one with a sixty-inch screen on the wall), and that never gets old (at least for &lt;br /&gt;me).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** UPDATE ** Robyn's former co-worker's band, 'Out Cold', is playing at Playwright and is supposed to start around 10, so it's possible the Crawle will hang out there for a while after 10 before meandering on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from there we stumble over to...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Richter's (10:00ish - 11:00ish) &lt;br /&gt;calls itself the oldest bar in New Haven, and may very well be. after all, it served as the bar area of the Taft, a 19th-century hotel (the ballroom is now Hot Tomatoes)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from there we stagger over to...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rudy's (11:00ish - close)&lt;br /&gt;dates to the end of Prohibition as the Lynwood Grill, but became Rudy's after Rudy Conte bought the place a few years later. history, ambiance, and frites. enough said.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;of course this isn't written in stone, and i'd be open to different and better suggestions. i only put up three, because frankly, when it's 20 degrees out, i prefer more pub than crawl. also, as you can see, the times are intentionally approximate (most of us have to keep to a schedule at work...why be a slave to the clock in our free time as well?). but feel free to drop me (Ben) a buzz to see where we are: 203-554-5144&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so...won't you come pickle your liver with me?&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197252282000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196705488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ye Olde Pub Crawle</name><id>6848250</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197079200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6848250/</event_url></item>