<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>From Mass Ave to Melnea Cass Blvd (South End)</address_2><address_1>Columbus Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02120</zip><lat>42.331464</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beantown Jazz Outdoor Festival</name><city>Boston</city><id>1031868</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.beantownjazz.org/schedule.html"&gt;Berklee Beantown Jazz Festival's&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;eleventh anniversary. It has become an event tens of thousands look forward to attending each year. The music is outstanding, there is a variety of delicious ethnic cuisine sold from vendor tables, numerous items for sale such as clothing, jewelry, and various novelties in addition to business and non profit informational tables from which you can get many giveaways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;September 20th and 23rd through 25th there are free events as well as paid shows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday September 24th the festival celebrates Global Music and Nature, featuring musical styles and artists from around the globe in an outdoor setting with performances on stages along Columbus Ave in the South End of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public transportation is strongly recommended because it will be extremely difficult to find parking nearby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MBTA:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to plan your route.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ten (10) minute walk from:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruggles Station - Orange Line&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mass Ave Staion - Orange Line&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;five (5) minute walk from:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;# 1 Mass Ave bus&amp;nbsp;(Mass Ave and Columbus Street stop)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Check out the schedule then comment on which performances interest you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Saturday September 25, 2011 (Free)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Performance Schedule:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Columbus Ave - taking it to the street performing among the crowd from Mass Ave to Melnea Cass Blvd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1:00PM-4:00PM Marcus Santos &amp;amp; Bloco AfroBrazil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10334.png" alt="10334" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil's goal is to preserve, promote, and spread the Afro-Brazilian culture, in all its aspects: music, dance, religion, and culinary arts. Their primary focus is on music and dance, through different music entities: BatukAx&amp;eacute; drum and dance ensemble playing samba reggae and other batucada style grooves. Banda Jil&amp;oacute; playing Forro music from northeastern Brazil. Aguid&amp;aacute; plays Ax&amp;eacute; music, the most contemporary music style from Salvador. Mangal&amp;ocirc; a modern interpretation of traditional Brazilian grooves. Our goals are to create an annual event fully dedicated to the Afro-Brazilian culture and to organize an annual trip to Bahia to spread the knowledge of Afro-Brazilian culture in the U.S. by exposing people to the lifestyle of Bahia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1:00PM-4:00PM Berklee BeanTown Traditional Jazz Band&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Berklee BeanTown Traditional Jazz Band, is a dixieland style octet comprised mostly Berklee College of Music Faculty Members. &amp;nbsp;Of the eight of them,&amp;nbsp;Charlie Lewis,&amp;nbsp;Harry Skoler,&amp;nbsp;John Pierce,&amp;nbsp;Bill Thompson,&amp;nbsp;John Marasco,&amp;nbsp;Jon Hazilla, and&amp;nbsp;Bob Tamagni all currently teach at Berklee and are known for their prestige in the U.S. music scene.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This year&amp;nbsp;Stu Gunn will be joining the group on tuba. The Berklee BeanTown Traditional Jazz Band will be seen throughout the day all over Columbus Avenue, giving Dixieland-style small band pe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Subaru of New England Stage (by Burke St.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;12:00PM-12:45PM Berklee Global Jazz Institute Ensemble&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10320.png" alt="10320" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Berklee Global Jazz Institute Ensemble&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The members of the ensemble are all enrolled in the Berklee Global Jazz Institute (BGJI), a unique focused area of study at the college designed to foster creativity and musicianship through various musical disciplines. World-renowned pianist Danilo P&amp;eacute;rez serves as its artistic director.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The program's directed study classes and seminars are designed to help the students build a community of creativity. Classes include Introduction to Global Jazz, focusing on the development of jazz from Africa to Europe and the Americas; Global Jazz Workshop Assembly, offering a forum for artists-in-residence and presentations from the Liberal Arts, Music Therapy, and Composition departments; and Creative Improvisation Through Interdisciplinary Collaboration, exploring the creative process and the connection between jazz and performing and visual arts, including painting and dance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experiential and service learning are also be integral to the program. Explained Marco Pignataro, managing director for the BGJI, "They've been given this great musical talent. We'll teach that as artists, they are responsible to positively affect their communities." In addition to playing with and being mentored by jazz masters, the students travel together to play at festivals in Panama, Puerto Rico, and other places, and record original material in the studio. They give back to the community by working with children, and teaching music locally through Berklee's City Music program and in other cities during institute performance trips. Students develop the skills needed to become role models for a new generation of musicians and inspire leadership in others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1:00PM-2:00PM Louis Hayes Cannonball Legacy Band&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10321.png" alt="10321" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Louis Hayes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hard bop drummer Louis Hayes has been a force in jazz since the mid-1950s when he began working-as a teenager-with Yusef Lateef, Curtis Fuller, and other artists hailing from his home of Detroit. Later he played with legends such as John Coltrane, Sonny Rollins, and Wes Montgomery. He has released nearly two dozen albums as a leader.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hayes's main influence during his formative years was Philly Joe Jones. His work with three groups in particular is what he is perhaps best known for: Horace Silver's&amp;nbsp;Quintet (1956-1959), the Cannonball Adderly&amp;nbsp;Quintet (1959-1965), and the Oscar Peterson&amp;nbsp;Trio (1965-1967). Hayes often teamed up with Sam Jones, both with Adderley and Peterson, and in freelance settings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;2:15PM-3:15PM The Cello/Piano Project with Eugene Friesen and Tim Ray&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10713.png" alt="10713" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Eugene Friesen and Tim Ray&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Musical passion, sweeping melody, and rocking rhythm mark the one-of-a-kind performances of the Cello/Piano Project. Contemporary jazz, Brazilian classics, and American folk tunes are the soil from which the duo's joyful interplay blooms, and chamber music is changed forever.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As featured players with the likes of Paul Winter, Lyle Lovett, Bonnie Raitt, and others, both Eugene Friesen and Tim Ray have cultivated unique styles of accompanying and soloing. At their duo concerts, audiences are treated to the full range of their remarkable abilities in living color.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The melodic and emotional facets of Eugene Friesen's cello have been well documented on hundreds of commercial CDs and film scores. Less known are his unbridled improvisations featuring an almost percussive use of the cello, or his unique pizzicato techniques derived from African folk traditions. Friesen's use of his voice, doubling his cello lines in perfect intonation and nuance, is another distinctive sonic signature.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ray has appeared on Jay Leno, and has been featured on national tours with Lyle Lovett. Fluent and brilliant in a myriad of American pop, folk, and swing styles, he is also highly regarded as a jazz performer and composer. Though a dazzling soloist, Ray is equally creative as an accompanist and producer and has served as musical director for singer-songwriters Jane Siberry and Victoria Williams on the road and in the recording studio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Playing jazz as well as innovative compositions by both Friesen and Ray, the Cello/Piano Project&amp;nbsp;traces a wideranging musical gamut in a program which is simultaneously imaginative, immediate, and original.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;3:30PM-4:30PM Rafael Zaldivar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10319.png" alt="10319" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Rafael Zald&amp;iacute;var&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rafael Zaldivar was born in Camag&amp;uuml;ey, Cuba. Growing up in a family of musicians, he began playing percussion and piano at the age of 10 and went on to pursue his musical education at Havana's Superior Institute of Arts. The great Cuban pianist Chucho Vald&amp;egrave;s awarded him second prize in Cuba's prestigious Jo-Jazz competition on two different occasions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the age of 22, he moved to Canada in order to broaden his musical horizons and perfect his art. He rapidly earned both a bachelor's degree from Universit&amp;eacute; de Montr&amp;eacute;al and a master's degree from McGill University. His undeniable talent did not go unnoticed among his teachers and the jazz community as a whole. In 2009, he won the prestigious Jazz en Rafale New Talent Contest presented at Espace Dell'Arte. First prize consisted of a professional recording, and in November of that year he recorded&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Life Directions&lt;/em&gt;, accompanied by Nicolas B&amp;eacute;dard and Kevin Warren.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He has been invited to every major jazz event held in Qu&amp;eacute;bec this year, including the Montreal&amp;nbsp;International Jazz Festival, OFF Festival, FestiJazz de Rimouski, Festival de Jazz de Qu&amp;eacute;bec, and Festival de Jazz de Mont-Tremblant. Later this year, Zaldivar will go to Paris to participate in the prestigious Martial Solal Jazz Piano Competition, followed by his first tour of Italy, Spain, France, and Belgium.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the course of his musical career, Zaldivar has performed with Terri lyne Carrington, Steve Coleman, Tony Coleman, James Cammack, Francisco Mela, Steve Turre, and Oliver Jones. His teachers have included Barry Harris, Kenny Barron, Danilo P&amp;eacute;rez, Greg Osby, and Francisco Mela.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;4:45PM-6:00PM Neal Smith Quintet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10317.png" alt="10317" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Neil Smith&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Drummer Neal Smith&amp;mdash;an associate professor of percussion at Berklee&amp;mdash;has performed with artists such as Geri Allen, Anita Baker, Tom Harrell, Donald Harrison, and Frank Morgan. He has recorded several albums as a leader and has produced several projects for various artists on the NASMusic label.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Born and raised in Cleveland Heights, Ohio, Smith has been playing drums since the age of 5. By the time he completed high school he had achieved a remarkable list of performance accomplishments and earned an impressive array of awards, scholarships, and honors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With the support of his family, Smith continued his studies at the Oberlin Conservatory of Music where he received a bachelor of music degree in jazz studies and performance, the first African-American to earn a degree in jazz studies from Oberlin.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He performs regularly with internationally recognized artists and has shared the stage with the likes of Tom Harrell, Anita Baker, Geri Allen, Donald Byrd, Kenny Burrell, Sonny Fortune, Jimmy Owens, Eddie Harris, Isaac Hayes, Gary Bartz, Benny Golson, Donald Harrison, Frank Morgan, Brian Lynch, Benny Green, Cyrus Chestnut, Frank Foster, Dewey Redman, Mark Whitfield, Ronnie Mathews, Rufus Reid, Wendel Logan, James Moody, Marlena Shaw, and Vanessa Rubin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Smithl has recorded several albums as a leader and has produced several projects for various artists on the NASMusic label. He performs regularly in clubs and concert halls, at colleges and universities, and at U.S. and international jazz festivals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Natixis Global Asset Management Stage (Carter Playground&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;12:00PM-12:45PM Music Clubhouse Youth Showcase&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Boston's network of neighborhood-based youth music education programs sponsored by Berklee, the Music and Youth Initiative, and eight youth agencies will showcase rising stars from the Blue Hill Boys and Girls Club, Sociedad Latina, Hyde Square Task Force, and the Boys and Girls Clubs of Dorchester.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1:00-1:30PM Shea Rose&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10567.png" alt="10567" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Shea Rose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Aspiring recording artist and singer-songwriter Shea Rose is a Boston native and Berklee alumna. Rose, who majored in professional music, describes her sound and style as the female Lenny Kravitz meets Lauryn Hill with a splash of Betty Davis. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In her article "Raw Rocking Soul,"&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Performer&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Magazine&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;writer Noelle Janka describes her as, "Equal parts soul, hip-hop, and rock 'n' roll," and says that Shea's stage presence calls to mind the raw energy of Rage Against the Machine's Zack de la Rocha.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1:45-2:45PM Bernie Worrell &amp;amp; SociaLybrium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10622.png" alt="10622" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Bernie Worrell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bernie Worrell first came to prominence as a founding member and musical director of Parliament-Funkadelic. While this massively influential supergroup was radically altering the course of music, Worrell was radically charting the course of emerging keyboard technology during the golden age of analog synthesis. Among the key ingredients in his sonic stew were perfect pitch and a well-honed facility with the classical canon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A child prodigy who began studying piano at the tender age of 3 and gave his first public performance just a year later, Worrell wrote his first concerto at 8 and performed with the Washington Symphony Orchestra at 10. His classical studies would continue throughout his adolescence, including private lessons at the Juilliard School of Music, before he entered the New England Conservatory of Music. ??Upon leaving the conservatory, Worrell served for several years as musical director for Maxine Brown before joining George Clinton's Parliament-Funkadelic crew. Worrell then proceeded to provide this freewheeling collective with a structural foundation which, while occasionally implied, was ever-present. At the same time, he explored and expanded his own musical ideas in every conceivable direction with a brazenness which was both revolutionary and evolutionary. From fanciful forays on clavinet, which leaped without warning, to guttural gulps to squiggly squeals to liquid Minimoog bass lines,&amp;nbsp;which herded listeners to the dance floor, it all represented new musical language. All the while, his rapid advancements of the synthesizer's potential were actually traceable to his classical foundation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The hits were many: "Flashlight," "Atomic Dog," "Aqua Boogie," "Cosmic Slop" and "Red Hot Mama" are only a few of the Parliament-Funkadelic classics which Worrell cowrote, played, and coproduced, on dozens of albums&amp;mdash;not to mention his years of wild P-Funk performances, which quickly became the stuff of lore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After departing Parliament/Funkadelic, Worrell resurfaced with the revamped Talking Heads lineup for several albums, including&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Name of This Band Is Talking Heads&lt;/em&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Speaking in Tongues&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and Jonathan Demme's dazzling concert film,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Stop Making Sense&lt;/em&gt;. Worrell's ominous colorings, this time delivered via new digital keyboards such as the Prophet 5, were central to the recasting of group leader David Byrne's musical ideas through African rhythms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the years since he left Talking Heads, Worrell has been a phenomenally prolific studio musician, serving as a primary change-agent in the many experimental works of producer Bill Laswell while contributing his singular flair to projects by the likes of Keith Richards, the Pretenders, Jack Bruce, Deee-Lite,&amp;nbsp;and Bootsy's New Rubber Band. At the same time, he has been among the most sampled musicians ever, with Digital Underground, De La Soul, Dr. Dre, Snoop Dogg, Ice Cube, DMX, and countless others having acknowledged his timeless grooves by building their tunes around his signature riffs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Worrell also released a series of critically acclaimed solo efforts, including&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Funk of Ages, Blacktronic Science, Pieces of WOO/The Other Side&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Free Agent: A Spaced Odyssey&lt;/em&gt;. And he has become quite a sensation on the jam band circuit, playing with groups ranging from Warren Haynes' Gov't Mule to Laswell's Material, Method of Defiance and Praxis conglomerations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In 1997, Worrell was inducted into the&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Rock and Roll Hall of Fame&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;along with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Parliament/Funkadelic&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Talking Heads would follow five years later). That same year, he launched his own group, Bernie Worrell and the WOO Warriors, which has performed all over the US and abroad to rave reviews. The in-concert energy of this ensemble has twice been captured on live albums:&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Bernie Worrell and the WOO Warriors Live&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;(1998) and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;True DAT&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(2002).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Worrell's work has also continued to surface in other places. In 1993, when David Letterman moved his program to CBS, Worrell helped launch the CBS Orchestra with Paul Shaffer. He cowrote the score for the cult classic,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Car 54, Where Are You?&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and other films, including the Ice Cube vehicle,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Friday&lt;/em&gt;. In 2003, his music was featured in the NBC television mini-series,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Kingpin&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The "Wizard of WOO" continues to wear many hats as effortlessly as he mixes musical forms, performing with both Mos Def's Black Jack Johnson band and Colonel Claypool's Bucket of Bernie Brains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;2005 saw the release of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Stranger: Bernie Worrell on Earth&lt;/em&gt;, a documentary film on the life of this master musician. And, between 2009 and 2010, Worrell assembled his latest musical project, SociaLybrium.&amp;nbsp;SociaLybrium is features Worrell on keyboards, Melvin Gibbs on bass, Ronny Drayton on guitar, and JT Lewis on drums&amp;mdash;a rock/funk/jazz fusion feast. To finish off 2010 with a bang, Worrell has just recently debuted another collaboration with guitar prodigy Wes Santo called&amp;nbsp;WesN'Worrell.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;3:00-4:00PM Berklee P-Funk Ensemble&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;(special guest Bernie Worrell)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;The Berklee P-Funk Ensemble is a group that honors the music and tradition of George Clinton and Parliament-Funkadelic. It is a Berklee class directed by the funky faculty Lenny Stallworth. This event will feature Bernie Worrell, one of Parliament-Funkadelic's founding members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;4:15-4:55PM Jeff Ramsey/Darcel Wilson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10324.png" alt="10324" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Jeff Ramsey and Darcel Wilson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vocalist&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Jeff Ramsey&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;has toured the world over with such artists as Lalah Hathaway, Al Jarreau, Tina Arena, Patrice Rushen, and Maxwell. He can also be heard on recordings by artists such as Celine Dion, Whitney Houston, Diana Ross, and Barbra Streisand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ramsey has performed on radio and television commercials for Burger King, Levi's, Dryel, Mountain Dew, and Michelob. He has also done solo work on a range of projects, including&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Everybody On the Bus,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;a CD by Tower of Power bassist Rocco Prestia and James Day's EP&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Remember When&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and CD&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Better Days,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;with the latter two featuring the UK hit "Don't Waste the Pretty&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;" &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He is a Berklee alumnus and member of the Voice Department faculty.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Darcel Wilson&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is an engaging, powerful, and expressive vocalist who has worked with Branford Marsalis, Paul Simon, Mark (Marky Mark) Wahlberg, Walter Beasley, Fatwall Jack, Brad Delp,&amp;nbsp;Armsted Christian, Keith Robinson (with Metropolis,) and producer Dan Serafini.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A member of the Berklee faculty since 2006, Wilson has served as lead session singer and vocal arranger for the Broadway show&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Brooklyn: the Musical,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;with writers Mark Schoenfeld and Barri McPherson.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;5:00-6:00PM Oleta Adams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10325.png" alt="10325" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Oleta Adams&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Oleta Adams has inspired a growing legion of fans in the U.S. and Europe with journeys of the heart via songs that draw deeply from her roots in gospel, while crossing effortlessly into the realms of soul, R&amp;amp;B, urban, and popular music.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Adams's 1990 debut album&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Circle of One&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(which went platinum), and the impassioned hit single "Get Here"&amp;mdash;the Brenda Russell composition that became an unofficial anthem of the 1991 Gulf War&amp;mdash;built her fan base. Her success, nurtured by worldwide tours with Tears for Fears, Phil Collins, Michael Bolton, and Luther Vandross, has been solidified by four Grammy nominations and a seemingly bottomless well of creative energy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Berklee Stage (Mass Ave)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;12:00PM-12:50PM Pablo Ablanedo Octet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10326.png" alt="10326" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Pablo Ablanedo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Argentina-born Pablo Ablanedo '96 is a pianist, composer, bandleader, and teacher who has lived in the United States since 1993, when he began his jazz composition studies at Berklee.&amp;nbsp;At Berklee, he studied with Herb Pomeroy, Jeff Friedman, and Greg Hopkins, and received the John Dankworth Award for Jazz Composition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;From 1997 through 2001 Ablanedo was an invited member of the BMI Jazz Composers Workshop in New York City, directed by Jim McLean and Manny Albam. His arrangements were recorded by the Marcelo Gutfraind Jazz Sextet for its&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Rio Abajo&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;disc. He has written music for the television production&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The 500 Miles of the Rio de la Plata&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and for the tango group Amacord. He received an honorable mention in the 2000 Jazz Composers Alliance Julius Hemphill Composition Awards. He also leads the Pablo Ablanedo Octet with which he has recorded two albums:&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;From Down There&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Alegr&amp;iacute;a.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;12:50PM-1:00PM Chief Joseph Chatoyer Garifuna Folkloric Ballet of NY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/11147.png" alt="11147" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Chief Joseph Chatoyer Garifuna Folkloric Ballet of NY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This dance company was named Chief Joseph Chatoyer to honor the legacy of a brave Garifuna man who fought fiercely against the Europeans' influence in defense of the Garifunas' territories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It was founded by Felix Gamboa in December 2008. Gamboa was born in Honduras and came to the United States at the age of 16. Gamboa never disconnected himself from his culture and traditions, and, to help others do the same, he welcomes everyone and anyone who's interested to deepen their knowledge about who they are.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Garifuna are a combination of West African, Indian Arawaks, and Carib natives that were exiled from their motherland of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines on March 11, 1797, to the Island of Roatan, Honduras, where they arrived on April 12 of the same year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Despite the experience of intense physical hardship and strong acculturation pressures, the Garifuna maintain a distinct identity embodied in their unique language, religion, and tradition. They have been able to maintain their language, their identity as Garinagu (plural for Garifuna), and most of all their infectious and mesmerizing music, which Gamboa proudly exposes to all eyes and ears&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1:05PM-2:00PM Rajdulari&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10328.png" alt="10328" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Rajdulari&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The lead voice for many of New England's eclectic world, jazz, and funk groups, Rajdulari hails from Boston and is a 10-year veteran of the local performance scene. Her credits include such venues as jazz clubs Regattabar, Ryles, and Scullers as well as the Emerson Majestic Theater, Hynes Convention Center, and the Isabella Stuart Gardner Museum.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rajdulari, a Berklee alumna, has worked with composers Walter Robinson, David Zoffer, and James Stewardson, and&amp;nbsp;is featured on many compilations along such performers as award-winning pianist George W. Russell.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rajdulari has performed as a member of the eight-piece, all-female world music band Zili Misk, the David Zoffer Differential, Guy Mendilow, and currently with her own band, the Rajdulari Jazz Project.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;2:15PM-3:15PM The Jazz Urbane featuring Joey Blake, Directed by Bill Banfield, Special Guest Grace Kelly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10329.png" alt="10329" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;The Jazz Urbane&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Award-winning guitarist and composer Banfield&amp;mdash;a Berklee professor and director of the college's Africana Studies program&amp;mdash;performs contemporary jazz with his band.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jazz Urbane is a contemporary music movement that infuses jazz with great R&amp;amp;B songwriting, melodies, grooves, and style. It's not really a "new movement," but a new configuration of a mindset: mature, sophisticated, and creative artistry that provides a groove&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;anyone&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;can feel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;3:30PM-4:30PM Andrea Capozzoli&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10434.png" alt="10434" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrea Capozzoli&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vocalist, trumpet player, songwriter, and producer Andrea Capozzoli is a force to be reckoned with on the modern music scene. Named 2004 Female R&amp;amp;B Artist of the Year at the New York International Music Festival, the Berklee faculty member has gained great acclaim for her powerful energetic performances.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Originally from Pittsburgh, Capozzoli got an early start as a professional musician, studying vocals with the likes of Cheryl Bentyne (Manhattan Transfer), Kevin Mahogany, and Maureen Budway.&amp;nbsp;She has opened for the likes of Steely Dan, Sister Sledge, and Jessica Simpson, and shared the stage with Slide Hampton, Bernard Purdie, and Eric Kloss, among many others. She recently had the honor of performing for President Barack Obama.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;5:00PM-6:00PM Dave Samuels and the Caribbean Jazz Project&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.berklee.edu/images/events/10333.png" alt="10333" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Dave Samuels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For over a decade, Dave Samuels has been performing and recording with his group the Caribbean Jazz Project whose most recent CD,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Afro Bop Alliance&lt;/em&gt;,&amp;nbsp;serves notice that the CJP is among the most thoroughly inventive Latin jazz ensembles of this or any era. The album received a Latin Grammy and was also nominated for a Grammy. Previous CDs&amp;mdash;&lt;em&gt;Her and Now&amp;mdash;Live in Concert&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Birds of a Feather&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;were nominated for Best Latin Jazz Recording. Their recording&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Gathering&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;won the Grammy in 2003 for Best Latin Jazz Recording. Some of his other recording projects include&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Remembrances&lt;/em&gt;, a percussion recording that features a commissioned marimba concerto for chamber orchestra and soloist composed by Jeff Beal, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Tjaderized&amp;mdash;A Tribute to Cal Tjader&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Verve) that features contributions from some of Cal's former bandmates Chick Corea, Eddie Palmieri, Clare Fischer, Ray Barretto, Michael Wolff, and Karl Perazzo as well as performances by Dave Valentin and David Sanchez.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;David Samuels will perform with&amp;nbsp;Alain Mallet, Mark Walker, and Lincoln Goines at the Berklee BeanTown Jazz Festival.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the entrance of Song Cleaners 607 Columbus Avenue, which is directly across from Darryl's Corner Bar &amp; Kitchen, When you find me I will have a peace symbol sticker for you to wear so we can find each other.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316988791000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316664459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Berklee Beantown Jazz Outdoor Festival September 24th</name><id>34514482</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316880000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/34514482/</event_url></item>