<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;EDITED TO ADD:  I checked the RAW website, and it says that the movie (which is very short) wil run repeatedly on Thursday evening.  So it may be hard to coordinate which showing to see.  If this means that you can go and see it at a later showing, by all means do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you love jazz you know about the photograph - this one-hour documentary tells the story behind it, in the words of the people in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Real Art Ways website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Great Day in Harlem Thursday, May 17, 2012 | FREE with admission to Creative Cocktail Hour&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/great_day_in_harlem/trailers/" target="_blank"&gt;[watch the trailer]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art Kane, now deceased, coordinated a group photograph of all the top jazz musicians in NYC in the year 1958, for a piece in Esquire magazine. Just about every jazz musician at the time showed up for the photo shoot which took place in front of a brownstone near the 125th street station. The documentary compiles interviews of many of the musicians in the photograph to talk about the day of the photograph, and it shows film footage taken that day by Milt Hinton and his wife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(USA, 60 mins, English)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If you wanted to introduce someone to what jazz is all about, this would be an ideal place to start." -&lt;a href="http://www.chicagoreader.com/chicago/a-great-day-in-harlem/Film?oid=1052871" target="_blank"&gt;Jonathan Rosenbaum, &lt;em&gt;Chicago Reader&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's a funny and moving film whose swinging rhythms and informal tone capture a feeling for the music, the people who make it and the affection and respect they feel for each other and the art form." -&lt;a href="http://www.sfgate.com/cgi-bin/article.cgi?f=/c/a/1995/07/14/DD40123.DTL" target="_blank"&gt;Jesse Hamlin, &lt;em&gt;San Francisco Chronicle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE:  Since it is part of their monthly Creative Cocktail Hour, the place will be JAMMED.  I will try to get confirmation of the time the film will be shown, but we may not find out until we arrive.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The movie is playing repeatedly - see it when you can.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337355318000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335617494000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"A Great Day in Harlem" @ Real Art Ways</name><id>62502692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337293800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/62502692/</event_url></item>