<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Every behavior, at its core, has a positive intention.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;-NLP presupposition.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Come watch a demonstration of how various NLP techniques can be used to bring about clarity, focus, and - in combination with Law-of-Attraction &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;concepts &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- a mindset of financial success. This &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;also &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;will be a good opportunity to get&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;answers &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; related questions &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;you may have. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;If you plan to eat, please arrive by 6:30 pm to order&lt;/strong&gt;; otherwise, by 7 pm will be fine. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;There is no specified purchase minimum for refreshments,  but participants are encouraged to order &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt;thing to support the  business, in appreciation of Management's permission to meet in their space.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Please be advised: Commercial eating establishments generally do &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt; permit &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;on-site &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;consumption of refreshments brought in from elsewhere, due  to liability concerns, so please be considerate&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 pm- Order dinner/refreshment if you plan to eat- $2.45 (for a soda) and upward&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 pm- Intro to neurolinguistic programming (NLP)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 pm- Roots of clutter: Cluttered thinking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30 pm&amp;ndash; Time Line and How It's Used&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:45 pm - Demonstration&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 pm- Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:45 pm- Wrap-up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kevin Martin&lt;/strong&gt;, a practicing certified hypnotherapist and   neurolinguistic programming (NLP) Practitioner, will offer us frameworks  for QUICKLY (on a  scale of MINUTES- not months or years ...  practically magic, rather like a "Gestalt  switch") living beyond  cluttered thinking- particularly regarding finances. As organizer  of  several Boston-area NLP Meetups, Kevin originally envisioned these  groups would help people learn self-help tools. He often looks for   resources, tools, and groups outside the fields of hypnosis and NLP to   mesh with that vision -and fortunately, our group does!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Calendar to schedule Action Items (next steps), and a notepad &amp;amp; pen  or other note-taking device. Dress in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in  case the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer) and comfortably, as  Kevin might have us all do some NLP exercises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Come join us!&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; (Or specify a better time and place for you to do so--)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;NOTES: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meeting is being offered on short notice because:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1) Our February 2011 venue was so noisy and distracting that I embarked on a whirlwind &lt;em&gt;Quest for &lt;strong&gt;More Suitable Venues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, welcoming input- the sooner the better!&amp;nbsp; Our venue for this meeting is quite close to the MBTA- a short walk  from the Red Line's Central and Kendall Square stations. Parking  on-street or in a *city lot* nearby (e.g., lots accessible from Norfolk  Street and Bishop Richard Allen Drive beside the Harvest Co-op in  Central Square ... Cambridge Traffic, Parking &amp;amp; Transportation Dept.  says these city lots are closest to our venue) is FREE AFTER 6 PM. The  restaurant has been very quiet when I've checked its noise level during  our usual meeting time on a Monday or Tuesday, and staff members have  seemed accommodating. I've been told we can probably meet in the  semi-private back room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2) This program is experimental: Kevin is developing NLP methods to help people address financial issues, and one or  two demonstrations during our program will contribute to his research. Kevin will provide handouts highlighting major points covered,  and says participants will take away enough to be a good value exchange for our time and  monetary investments- I know that &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; certainly learned much from Kevin's February  program at Alewife, as did that program's two demo subjects, judging from the feedback they provided; in fact, I continue to glean insights from that program, so I hope that &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;, too, can be part of this upcoming program ... perhaps as a subject for a demo?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;The   $10-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal or in cash at the  event) helps to compensate the organizer and any presenter for their training and specialized knowledge shared,  also for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt; their time spent &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;planning, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;coordinating,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;administering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727 ; font-size : 12px"&gt; the event, and to defray Meetup.com's charge assessed organizers to   serve members each month, e.g., by hosting this web site and offering  marketing tools. If you are late and/or miss a pre-paid event, pls note there  will be NO REFUND. Please plan on being early, and allow for possible  travel delays.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READINGS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Bandler, &lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation &lt;/em&gt;- EXCERPTS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...there is a magic moment when it all comes together, without effort."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...if you learned to do something one way, you can learn how to do  it totally different and better. Learning is the way to personal  freedom. Hypnosis and NLP are tools to make this easy and fun."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;em&gt;See more quotes and links to sample NLP/EFT video clips&lt;/em&gt; appended to our event posting for Thursday, February 24, 2011:&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; "DECLUTTER YOUR THINKING *FAST*: Moving Beyond Clutter with NLP &amp;amp; EFT!"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a red &amp; white Meetup sign at our table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300888997000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Opportunity to meet in a new, quiet location to "reframe" and learn other neurolinguistic programming (NLP) techniques.  Come experience NLP in Action!</why><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300153577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Living CLEAR: Clearing What's in Your Way to Financial Success</name><id>16923671</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300833000000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/16923671/</event_url></item>