<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This time we will be viewing and discussing a 90 minute video by Valya Boutenko, called "Reversing the Irreversible".  This shows the immense curative power of doing nothing more than switching to a healthy diet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This truly inspiring video includes interviews with 37 different people who  cured themselves of a variety of serious medical conditions by simply making dietary changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These fundamentals are important to understand as we prepare for a future where conventional medicine may no longer be accessible.  Furthermore, it is important to understand NOW that the most sensible approach is PREVENTATIVE "medicine", which is simply learning how to properly nourish our bodies by sensible eating, as well as developing good life-style habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Periodically, additional meetup topics will include specific holistic modalities that we can all learn to incorporate into our "tool kit", such as what kinds of herbs and homeopathic remedies to stock up on, how to use safe and effective forms of SELF-healing, why it is best to avoid going to any practitioner who offers any form of "energy healing" etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although our usual meeting place is the Celery Stick Cafe area at the Concord Cooperative Market, Meetups with topics requiring use of an overhead projector with screen, or DVD and TV capabilities will be conducted at the ULCS Clinic, just 3 miles from exit 22 off I-93.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means you must bring your own refreshments. Please go up the first driveway with the Meetup sign at the end, NOT the second driveway with the ULCS Clinic sign.  Enter through the front door, which has another Meetup sign.  No need to knock.  Just go on down the stairs if you arrive early.  Your host will come down to join you at 6:00 PM.  This Meetup adjourns promptly at 9:00 PM.  Thank you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on for some interesting links, as why this information deserves your attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;                                 ******&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extremely challenging times may soon be upon us, due to several situations which have reached a critical threshold. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To better understand why our very survival depends upon personal preparedness steps we  take now, please view the following links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Three E's:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eidQTDjQ5gw"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eidQTDjQ5gw&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Resources &amp;amp; Monetary Systems:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nI-BIVWlc7A"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nI-BIVWlc7A&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2012 Cosmic Energies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm"&gt;http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign on one of the tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336019964000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Co-Creative Planetary Stewards</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Back-to-Basics</urlname><id>1438479</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Back to Basics: Sustainable Self-Sufficient Healthy Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317001219000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Immense Curative Power of Simply Eating NATURALLY!</name><id>qsbwccyqcbhb</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335909600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Back-to-Basics/events/34941942/</event_url></item>