<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>February tends to be a lot of our least favorite month's of the year...bitter cold, nothing to do....our precious Pugs HATE going out even to do wee wee, so we thought we would do a REALLY special &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Valentine's Pug Meetup&lt;/span&gt; to keep everyone's spirits high!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday February 27th at 1pm....save the date and RSVP early as space WILL BE LIMITED!!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be exchanging Valentine's so I'd say bring enough for 20-30 pugs! Kelly and I will be providing little &amp;quot;mailboxes&amp;quot; for everyone to bring home their Valentine's and of course we will also be making some wonderful sweet treats for both pugs and their people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADDITIONALLY we will be have not one, but TWO VERY special guests join us. Well renowned Pug Portrait Artist, Mary Beth and her very special pug &amp;quot;Mr P&amp;quot; who will be flying around Gibson Kennel in his wheelchair!! We will have order forms on site for you to place your orders. Your one of a kind pug portrait will be mastered on a 8X10 canvas and proceeds go to Curly Tail Pug Rescue. Each portrait is only $47 which is unheard of! DOn't miss this opportunity! &lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;Bring CASH&lt;/span&gt; or check with you that day, OR we will have my laptop available for you to make a payment through Paypal.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.curlytailpugrescue.org/Home/pug-portraits" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.curlytailp...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly and I truly enjoy being the Organizers of the Grafton pug Meetup. We hope that we have met each of you individually, and if we have not, please come up and introduce yourself at the next one. We are constantly trying to come up with new treats for our precious pugs, and ideas to keep it informative and interesting. We welcome all suggestions. It seems to be very personal and we all have tons of fun.  We always welcome new members to come join in the fun and excitement at watching our little puggie friends romp and play in the spacious room at the Gibson Kennel in Grafton. Note: &lt;b&gt;this is a PUG Meetup&lt;/b&gt;...as not all breeds play well together.  There are other small breed Meetups, but this is for PUGS ONLY!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******A receipt of current vaccinations must be brought with you in order to enter the play area (kennel rules)*********  (this has not been strictly enforced at the Meetups but, it's better safe then sorry since the owner of the kennel did request we have this on-hand)    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will ask for a $5 fee per family for each Meetup&lt;/b&gt; to cover Meetup costs and any leftover money will be donated to the Curly Tail Pug Rescue as well as other animal related charity that we all agree on as a group. These donations go toward paying the monthly dues, snacks and to keep this website going so we can all see when the next Meetup is taking place.  We will also do special events from time to time to keep it fun and interesting!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all and I look forward to playing again with all you pug lovers out there and your pups! =)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will introduce ourselves...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erin maguire</member_name><member_id>3828727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269708620000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Puggy Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pug-569</urlname><id>252667</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6900024414</group_lon><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>43</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264878359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grafton Pug February Meetup</name><id>krppcyndbkc</id><headcount>47</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267293600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pug-569/events/12468218/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/b/global_10981051.jpeg</photo_url></item>