<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE SEPTEMBER MEETUP IS THE SECOND SUNDAY IN SEPTEMBER!&lt;br /&gt;HALLOWEEN'S COMING SOON - START PUTTING TOGETHER PUGGIE COSTUMES!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the September meetup, we're giving Buford a break and moving the operation to King Clovis's backyard in Brockton!  The yard isn't as big as Buford's and my kiddie pool is just an old black rubber horse tub, but there's plenty of shade and water, and enough room to run around in.  Your organizer is short on lawn chairs, so unless you intend to sit on the  grass, please remember to bring your own lawn chair!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know.  We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GET READY FOR HALLOWEEN!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to be back in Carver the second Sunday in October for Halloween, and we're going to have a costume contest with PRIZES, ribbons for the proud owners and toys for the dogs!  Best costume and runners up 2-4. plus prizes for best puppy costume, best home made costume, most creative costume.  This year, we're going to have CONTESTS, more prizes and toys! - pug races by sex, and by age, best trick, cutest pug,  best tail wagger, oldest pug, youngest pug, and my all time favorite - FATTEST pug.  No fair stuffing your pug for this one!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need people to bring Halloween snacks to this one, and if you bring homebaked snacks for the pugs, make sure they are soft snacks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR LAST MEETUP?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite an early afternoon downpour, which was just winding down at 2:00, three dozen Pug lovers and almost as many Pugs came to Carver for the August meetup, and everyone had a wonderful time, especially the little black puppy girl who was absolutely beside herself with excitement.  There were quite a few new faces at this meetup, but we have quite a few old timers too - hard to believe that some people have been coming to the Pug Sunday Socials for the past two and a half years!  Miraculously, the sun came out, everybody dried off, and the pugs kept playing.  Thanks to the rain, it was lovely weather, not too hot for pugs!  Thanks again to Sharon and Ron for opening their home to this puggy crowd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again, we had quite a few new folks at the meetup, and we certainly hope they had a good time!  Be sure to let us know if it's your first time attending, and we will be happy to introduce you to the rest of the gang.  All family members are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Thank you to the folks who brought the goodies for the meetup. Even though our monthly host provides the soft drinks and the paperware, we depend on our members to bring the snacks for all the pugaholics attending.  They haven't failed us yet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be soft drinks and something to snack on for the people attending!  If you bring treats for the Pugs, please ONLY hand out treats around the central table where everyone can keep an eye on the dogs, DON'T FEED CLOVIS, and PLEASE BE SURE that nothing gets dropped - your organizer has a Pug (yes, that would be Clovis...) who has brain damage which makes it very difficult for him to swallow.  I don't want Clovis to choke to death on a stolen treat, and I'm sure no one else does either..  Thank you for your consideration!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. We want everyone to have fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups and the South of Boston Small Breed Dogs Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend.  Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis, Cletus and Stoney's faces when Puggie Sunday rolls around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222542512000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218395489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug September Meetup</name><id>8515909</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221415200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/8515909/</event_url></item>