<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>719 Cherry Valley Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03249</zip><lat>43.551804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gunstock Mountain Resort</name><city>GILFORD</city><id>7910162</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360077</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note that you must go to the Gunstock Website and get your tickets prior to signing up (see instructions below.)  There is only a total of 25 spaces available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dianne and I did the Aerial Treetop Adventure at Gunstock Mountain Resort last weekend and had a great time!! &lt;br /&gt;

It is the best course of this nature we have been on and thought it would make for a great meetup. &lt;br /&gt;

It is a challenging course, that in my opinion requires more mental and determination than physical. It is also a great way to help overcome a fear of heights. &lt;br /&gt;

Please go to the Gunstock Mountain Resort and follow the information to sign up. Also, I have included a brief description. &lt;br /&gt;

All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website &lt;br /&gt;

Built within the trees along Gunstock's pond, Aerial Treetop Adventure is New England's Largest Aerial Obstacle Course. Explore Gunstock from a birds eye view. &lt;br /&gt;

91 different challenges are securely suspended within the trees in 8 courses, including the Explorer Course just for kids. Some of the features include log ladders, bridges, swings, seesaws, foot bridges and, of course, lots of zip lines. &lt;br /&gt;

Adult Aerial Treetop Adventure Course &lt;br /&gt;

The Adult Adventure begins with a training course where our Adventure Park Guides will show you how to use the equipment to ensure that you understand and can demonstrate that you can safely navigate the courses. You begin on the Green course which is the easiest and has the lowest games, which are 10’ to 15’ off the ground. Each course gets more challenging and the elevations get higher. If you make it all the way through, you'll finish on the Black course where you will be upwards of 100’ off the ground, crossing a 165 foot long, irregularly spaced foot bridge. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Every participant must complete a Liability Release&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the office where you pick up your harness and sign the release.  Please be there by 9:00 AM</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341498777000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340711705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Aerial Treetop Adventure at Gunstock Mountain Resort</name><id>70784322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341408600000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/70784322/</event_url></item>