<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002060"&gt;We just did this for the Boston Law of Attraction meetup group and the people there LOVED it! Powerful experiences and shifts happened right then and there!&amp;nbsp; Be sure to take advantage of this opportunity! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can make the vision boards; you can diligently take all the actions and follow all the formulas... yet if you &lt;em&gt;are not&lt;/em&gt; at one with your Greater Self, you might have a harder time creating the success and the joy that you &lt;em&gt;truly&lt;/em&gt; want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who YOU are is far, far more than your physical self. It's the self that is your Spirit-Self .... Source Energy...Higher Self....deeper wisdom.&amp;nbsp; It's the greater part of who you truly are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Many of us know this as a concept &amp;amp; even believe in it; yet it's still "out there", in an &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;abstract way, versus truly experiencing &amp;amp; feeling it &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;from within. &amp;nbsp;When you are &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;feeling &lt;/span&gt;the oneness with your greatest, highest self, everything flows easily to you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So how do you transcend the "smaller you" &amp;amp; physical "reality"?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight we'll be focusing on the spirituality that is the foundation of law of attraction and helping you to move beyond it as just a concept to being more able to feel it and BE it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;We will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;guide you to &lt;em&gt;feel&lt;/em&gt; the connection &amp;amp; oneness with Spirit/Source, to BE at one with your TRUE YOU. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;share ways for you to &lt;em&gt;access&lt;/em&gt; your TRUE YOU whenever you are stuck, feeling alone &amp;amp; separate, or feel like you have to &lt;em&gt;make &lt;/em&gt;things happen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the surest "way" to get clarity of &lt;em&gt;true&lt;/em&gt; purpose, &lt;em&gt;true&lt;/em&gt; happiness &amp;amp; is the &lt;em&gt;speediest&lt;/em&gt; way to manifest more of what you truly desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're sure there will be lots and lots and great discussion, and, of course, we'll guide you into the experience, as well!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We're so excited about this!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;"Ann and Mark are so incredibly uplifting. Another great evening that was filled with creativity and inspirational ideas that got me into the "vortex." It's so nice being surrounded with people that are all on the path to positive changes and open to learning about the Law of Attraction. Thank you again!"&amp;nbsp; Amy &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thank you so much to those of you who have RSVP'd "yes" and showed up! PLEASE, PLEASE be considerate of our efforts and &lt;em&gt;let us know if your plans change&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp; We set up our space, and prepare handouts accordingly.&amp;nbsp; Help us reach our goal of 100% attendance for those who rsvp "yes"!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun! Please join us and stay "connected" by participating in our community's message board discussions and receiving our e-mails (which will include our "Good Vibrations" tips and news). To be able to do so, go to your account, and under "Your Groups", each one has an "Edit email settings". Set your preferences there. Hope to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Wings studio on the first floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299978771000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Come to experience yourself as creative Source Energy.</why><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288469515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Way of Enlightenment - Experiencing yourself as Spirit!</name><id>fvzspypfbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299974400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/16063676/</event_url></item>