<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>219.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=50" target="_blank"&gt;The Tsunami of Foreclosures is Flooding The Real Estate Market- Are You Taking Advantage?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Mini Crash Course for 144 students with the nation?s leading short sales experts, Curtis Brooks &amp;amp; Steve Dillon in Windsor Locks, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve Dillon is an ex-loss mitigator who worked in the banking industry for several large lending institutions. Steve negotiated over 8,000 short sales while in the banking profession. He left loss mitigation to do real estate and has been helping hundreds of real estate investors negotiate bigger profits on short sales for several years now. Curtis Brooks has purchased over 750 houses on the court house steps in Florida over the past decade. Curtis knows how to negotiate better than anybody I know.  He will teach you how to get a seller to say ?YES? 9 out of 10 times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's just a short list of the content that will be covered:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Why this is the best time in history to invest in foreclosures and how foolish you?d be NOT to get involved.&lt;br /&gt;    * How to capture the huge tidal wave of preforeclosures over the next 12 months&lt;br /&gt;    * How to find GREAT deals every single time &amp;amp; where you can get other people's money to fund these deals&lt;br /&gt;    * The step by step process on negotiating huge profits on discounting mortgages&lt;br /&gt;    * What are the different types of loans to avoid&lt;br /&gt;    * All the insider secrets to negotiate the loss mitigator down&lt;br /&gt;    * The six critical steps that all rookies make when trying a short sale&lt;br /&gt;    * What the banks DON'T want real estate investors to know&lt;br /&gt;    * How to prepare all the necessary paperwork so your deal sails through for approval with no glitches&lt;br /&gt;    * How to complete a Hud-1, Net Sheets, Authorizations To Release &amp;amp; Financial Distress paperwork to build a case for a huge discount with the lender&lt;br /&gt;    * The 4 killer strategies to locate an avalanche of good deals&lt;br /&gt;    * The most effective negotiation strategies to handle all sell obligations&lt;br /&gt;    * How to sell short sales for huge profit in a down market&lt;br /&gt;    * The top 10 strategies to getting buyers to ring your phone off the hook in a buyers market&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This action packed three day training is only $219 and is limited to 144 seats.  All students will receive $499 worth of education materials, classroom seating, and a complimentary dinner with Curtis, Steve and Robyn on Friday evening. To take advantage of this great weekend of learning, register now or call our office to register at 860-265-4414!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=50" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to learn more and register!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206918493000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202459990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3 Day Foreclosure Workshop :: Buying &amp; Selling in Today's Market </name><id>7289428</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206745200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/7289428/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/3/d/global_3167693.jpeg</photo_url></item>