<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>i just copied and pasted this listing. here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop the Wars - Oct 11 - Boston Common&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear Friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March, 2008 ushered in the sixth year of war and occupation &amp;quot;without end&amp;quot; on Iraq . In an act of arrogance and impunity, Congress in a bipartisan vote approved another $162 billion in funding for the wars on Iraq and Afghanistan . The stepping up of threats against Iran and the increased likelihood of a U.S. troop &amp;quot;surge&amp;quot; into Afghanistan point to an imperative for action and an independent voice from the peace and justice movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Boston , the October 11 Mobilizing Committee has been formed to organize a mass demonstration on Boston Common around the following demands/slogans:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;E STAND UP FOR PEACE IN THE MIDDLE EAST.&lt;br /&gt;E STOP THE WARS AND OCCUPATIONS IN IRAQ AND AFGHANISTAN .&lt;br /&gt;E BRING THE TROOPS HOME NOW.&lt;br /&gt;E MONEY FOR JOBS, EDUCATION, HEALTHCARE AND HOUSING ...NOT FOR WAR AND OCCUPATION.&lt;br /&gt;E NO SANCTIONS OR ATTACK ON IRAN .&lt;br /&gt;E STOP THE RACIST SCAPEGOATING OF ARABS AND MUSLIMS.&lt;br /&gt;E STOP THE ASSAULT ON HUMAN RIGHTS AND CIVIL LIBERTIES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was on October 11, 2002 that Congress approved the &amp;quot;Iraq War Resolution&amp;quot; granting the Bush administration authorization to invade Iraq . The weeks ahead will continue to be filled with debate as the election campaigns gear up. Instead of being spectators who watch the media pundits put their spin on the political pronouncements of the candidates, we will be actively engaged in injecting our agenda, the antiwar agenda, into the intensifying debate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organization can help:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Endorse the Action! &lt;br /&gt;Get your organization and allies to endorse the October 11 action; simply reply to info@oct11boston.org if you can endorse or if you have any questions or comments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Plan the Action!&lt;br /&gt;Participate in the next planning and organizing meeting that will take place September 20, 3:00 PM at the Democracy Center in Cambridge ( 45 Mt. Auburn St. - Harvard stop on T).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Support the Movement!&lt;br /&gt;Help by providing human resources (including volunteer time), funds, logistical support, and artistic ideas for building the action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Network with Results!&lt;br /&gt;Help reach out to other organizations, groups and individuals to support the action and add more voices to this movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Educate the Public!&lt;br /&gt;Hold teach-ins, film screenings and other events in the run up to the action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Build Grassroots Outreach!&lt;br /&gt;Leaflet, flyer, and poster in your neighborhood, campus, workplace, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, of course... MOBILIZE EVERYONE YOU KNOW to SHOW the WORLD that the ANTIWAR MOVEMENT has the POWER to BUILD, SPREAD and turn millions more against this war and ultimately STOP THE WARS of the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, please visit www.oct11boston.org or reply to info@oct11boston.org with your phone number and a good time to call, and we will be in touch soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Peace and Solidarity,&lt;br /&gt;October 11 Mobilizing Committee&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223914289000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221511834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bring 911 Truth @ Stop the Wars - Oct 11 - Boston Common</name><id>8763386</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223740800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/8763386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>