<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A few years ago this Meetp group put on a Trash the Dress event - it was so popular that we've decide to bring it back again this year! Rain or Shine...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So what is Trash the Dress?&lt;br /&gt;Trash the dress, fearless bridal, and rock the frock - refers to photography that contrasts elegant clothing with an environment in which it is completely out of place. Usually brides decide to have pictures taken on the beach, but possibilities are endless. City streets, rooftops, garbage dumps, fields, and abandoned buildings are only few examples of trash the dress session locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A model often wears a ball gown, prom dress or wedding dress, and may effectively ruin the dress in the process by getting it wet, dirty or in extreme circumstances tearing or destroying the garment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It may also be done as an additional shoot after the wedding, almost as a declaration that the wedding is done and the dress will not be used again. It is seen as an alternative to storing the dress away, never to be seen again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And this is exactly what we are going to do... Gather models - both Male and Female- to come to Oakland Beach in RI and Trash some Dresses and other clothing- while us photographers create images of it all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have volunteers to help with day- thank God!- Because this was huge last time- and it take a lot of work to organize. So here is the break down...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa Davenock (and her dress committee of Donna and Deb) have agreed to be point person on all things clothing related - Dresses and Suit coats for the models. So if you have a model that wants to participate - you need to get Lisa their dress/suit size. She will be working on getting clothing for folks. Or if your Model has a dress they want to use - be sure to let Lisa know!&lt;br /&gt;She can be reached at : info@lisadavenock.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dana Lane and Steve I have agreed to be point people on all things related to Models. They will be recruting and courting models for this shoot. They will take care of the model releases and any and all information about the day concerning the models needs to follow through them. So if you have a model that wants to participate - can commit to the day and times - you should get all their info over to Dana or Steve I.&lt;br /&gt;Dana can be reached at : dana@danalanephoto.com&lt;br /&gt;Steve I: stevei@steveiadarolaphotography.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Walker, (and his prop committee of Jeff Baker and Alan K) have agreed to be point people on all things related to Props. They will be gathering flowers, bouquets, tiaras, jewelry, chairs, seats, anything that can be utilized as a prop for the photos. Please be creative and pitch in your ideas and props! Please donate and please share...&lt;br /&gt;Tom can be reached at : tom@tomslens.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I still need a volenteer for organizing three tents-(hopefully 10x10) two need to have sides so they can be used as changing rooms. The bathrooms at this beach are not great or large. So we need to come up our own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I need another person to bring/organize coolers, chairs, tables, and blankets - to set gear out on. The Sand is not your friend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are currently looking for Stylists - both hair and makeup as well as a clothing stylist.... the more we have the better the event will be!! So please send out your search parties and see what you can gather for this area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;New info!!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;There is a cost to participate in the event. It is $25.00 per person.&lt;/b&gt; It goes toward dresses we purchase, drinks for the day, paperwork that needs to be printed and the list goes on and on... Models and photographers will need to pay. We all benefit from these kinds of events and we see it as a portfolio building exercise for all involved... money must be given to me ASAP, or by August 1st. Methods of payment- Paypal, check mailed to me, or cash... or you will not be able to participate that day.&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/crying.gif' border='0' alt='crying' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers- here is the DEAL! So that means you have to give each model you photograph a min of 3-5 images for their portfolios. Fully retouched and useable for their promotional uses. They are not allowed to resell the images to anyone - only for promo use. You have one month to get images to Donna to share with them. That means by Sept 8th, 2009. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One month - no exceptions!! I will hunt you down!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW- I am also going to work on getting us some press for this event. So if you have any contacts in the media please send them to me and I'll be sure they hear about the event... Again- good for all of us!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We meet in the parking lot to car pool and get organized...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1250290735000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246486649000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trash the Dress Photography and Model Event of the Year!</name><id>10782514</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249740000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10782514/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/6/global_9453206.jpeg</photo_url></item>