<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Part 2 – &amp;quot;Chicago Style&amp;quot; SteppingIQ Workshop with Larry Collins &amp;amp; Kammal Smith of The Steady Steppers (Detroit).&lt;br /&gt;All Levels&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1:15pm – 3:15pm. Doors will open at 1pm for admittance to this workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The SteppingIQ Workshop, will use the learnings' from Part 1 to enhance and ignite the couples dance.  Part 2 will take good follow techniques and good lead techniques and transition these techniques to good dance techniques e.g. the couples’ ability to harmoniously flow smoothly on the dance floor.  Combinations and movements will be introduced to the ‘addict’ dancer for the ‘club’ and ‘competition’ dance floor that include styling techniques and footwork for both the male and female.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a natural transition and will build upon techniques learned in Part 1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free Parking. Cash Bar. &lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Please purchase all beverages (water &amp;amp; soda) from the bar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Early bird pricing from workshop Part 2 is $30 p/p, (cash/check), Advance Payment and RSVP Required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(doors will open at 1pm for this workshop)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See Lady Tracey or Gentleman Scott to make your cash or check purchase to reserve your place in the workshops. Or purchase this workshop via PayPal using your credit card.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;PayPal payments should be sent to &amp;quot;  &lt;a href="http://www.paypal.com" target="_blank"&gt;steppersboston06@aol.com&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE STEADY STEPPERS:&lt;br /&gt;The Steady Steppers Dance Institute, based in Detroit, Michigan, was found in 2003 by Larry Collins and Kammal Smith.  Since 2003 they have produced six (6) Chicago “Style” Stepping instructional DVD’s; provide an average 8 - 10 Chicago “Style” Stepping instructional workshops per year across the nation; instruct weekly Chicago “Style” Stepping instructional classes on Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday in the Detroit (MI) area where they have taught over 500 classes to unknown hundreds of interested dancers; and they have a chapter in Las Vegas, Nevada.  Finally, The Steady Steppers host an annual October dance convention where all styles of dance are experienced in Las Vegas, Nevada.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Steady Steppers were voted the 2009 nations #2 Stepping Promoter of the Year on ChiSteppers.com and in 2008, the nation’s #2 Stepping Organization of the Year.  Additionally in 2004 and 2005, The Steady Steppers were proud Spirit of Detroit Award recipient’s from the Detroit City Council in recognition of their exceptional achievement, outstanding leadership and dedication to improving the quality of life in Metropolitan Detroit through dance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gentleman Scott</member_name><member_id>4548946</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracey </member_name><member_id>5014779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295804548000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Original Steppers of Boston</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Steppers-of-Boston</urlname><id>1340809</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Original Steppers of Boston Inc. 2006</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268198938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Part 2 -   Exclusive SteppingIQ Workshop 1:15pm -3:15pm</name><id>12836506</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278782100000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Steppers-of-Boston/events/12836506/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/6/global_13569670.jpeg</photo_url></item>