<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>132 Butler Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01057</zip><lat>42.049118</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Peaked Mountain Tract Parking Area</name><city>Monson</city><id>7624262</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.352090</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/2/event_125883042.jpeg" width="315" height="202" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/1/6/event_125891542.jpeg" width="317" height="199" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peaked Mountain (pronounced pea-kid mountain) is part of a land trust maintained by a group called "The Trustees Of Reservations". Below is the website www.thetrustees.org and the specific page for this place. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/pioneer-valley/peaked-mountain.html"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/pioneer-valley/peaked-mountain.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more details about this place including trail maps.  I put the trail maps for both the Miller Forest and Peaked Mountain Tracts in the Files section under the More tab. &lt;br /&gt;

A brief excerpt from the website states, "Explore woods roads through a former working forest and trek to a summit that rewards with panoramic views from Mount Wachusett to Vermont’s Green Mountains."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a fantastic hike. For the more adventurous, the Peaked Mountain Tract is at address 132 Butler Road (Lat 42.049 Lon -72.352). This has the larger parking area. The trails on this road lead uphill to a wonderful view. It is a more strenuous hike but the trail roads a very well marked and wide. &lt;br /&gt;

For the more laid back types, the Miller Forest Tract is at 21 Butler Road (same road) (Lat 42.062154 Lon -72.350115). This area has trails that loop around a pond great for the dogs to go swimming. The trails are also well marked and wide/flat. &lt;br /&gt;

There are places to picnic and rest at. Let's meet up at the larger parking area at 132 Butler Road and we can decide what we want to do first. I have an idea that we check out the great view while the temperature is not maxed out yet and then head to Miller Forest for some relaxing time and the dogs can go swimming.  But I am open to suggestions and you can decide to do any part you want. &lt;br /&gt;

Bring a lunch or snack. Bring water for you and the dogs if you plan on doing the Peaked Mountain View hike as there is no stream. Beware that these trails are also used by others exercising their horses. Check out the pics from the previous meetup when a few of us went to Peaked Mountain. &lt;br /&gt;

Directions are to take route 32 South into Monson. Just before the soldier statue in Monson turn right onto High St. Take immediate left onto Ely Rd. Proceed 1 mi., then go straight at stop sign onto Lower Hampden Rd for 2 mi. Turn left onto Butler Rd. AFTER you pass a small parking lot on the right, which is for the Miller Forest Tract entrance, conitnue on and  go 1.2 mi. to main entrance and parking (20+ cars) is on the left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340997447000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339211072000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peaked Mountain Tract/Miller Forest Tract</name><id>68408852</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340542800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/68408852/</event_url></item>