<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>280 Berkeley Street</address_2><address_1>Back Bay Events Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349699</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John Hancock Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>1401448</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072321</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;2010 Event Descriptions&lt;br /&gt;From Page to Screen&lt;br /&gt;1:30pm John Hancock Hall at the Back Bay Events Center 180 Berkeley Street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What’s it like to see your words, characters and ideas translated to the screen? Do you get a say in who plays the lead? Is being on-scene fascinating or infuriating or somewhere in between? Find out from Dennis Lehane (Mystic River, Gone Baby Gone, Shutter Island), A. M. Homes  (Jack, The Safety of Objects) and Tom Perrotta (Election, Little Children), seasoned veterans of the transition from page to screen. Hosted by Boston Globe movie critic Ty Burr. Sponsored by The Boston Globe.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great way to spend a Saturday afternoon in the Back Bay.   Last year these events were very well attended so saving seats may not be allowed, but we generally know who we are.   If we don't meet outside or find seats together we will meet outside the main entrance on Berkeley Street after the event for discussion, drinks, coffee, etc.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New people are always welcome.  Look for a woman with a red pocketbook waving a red card up in the air.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be holding a red card up in the air outside the main entrance on Berkeley Street at 12:30.  I'll do the same thing inside and also outside  the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286939289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>From Page to Screen at theBoston Book Festival</name><id>15092332</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287246600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15092332/</event_url></item>