<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>East hartford CT</address_2><address_1>East River Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06074</zip><lat>41.899734</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great River Park</name><city>South Windsor</city><id>550405</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.662590</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Bring picnic food to share and chairs and off.  Come and enjoy the music.  Enjoy the Hartford Pops, featuring the Hartford Pops Band, a 38-piece professional concert band featuring wind, brass and percussion instruments lead by energetic conductor Gary Partridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North of Hartford, take I-91 South to Exit 30, I-4 East to East Hartford and Glastonbury. Take Exit 53, East River Dr / Rt 44 and follow the exit ramp signs for East River Dr. At the end of ramp, turn right onto East River Dr. The park entrance is on your right.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From South of Hartford, take I-91 North to Exit 29, Rt 5 / 15 &amp;amp; I-84 to East Hartford and Manchester across the Charter Oak Bridge. Take Exit 90 and bear right at the ramp split following the signs for East River Dr / Rt 2 West. Take Exit 4 off Rt 2 onto East River Dr. At the end of the ramp, turn left onto East River Dr and pass under the highway. The park entrance is on your left.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From East of Hartford, take I-84 West to Exit 54, Downtown Hartford. Take the Darlin St. exit before crossing the Founders Bridge. At the end of the ramp, turn right onto Darlin St. At the end of Darlin St, turn right onto Pitkin St. At the end of Pitkin St, turn left onto East River Dr. The park entrance is on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From West of Hartford, take I-84 East to Exit 53, East River Dr / Rt 44 and follow the exit ramp signs to East River Dr. At the end of the ramp, turn right onto East River Dr. The park entrance is on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited free public parking is available within the park. During special events, other parking arrangements will be announced.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We can do a picnic in the park  I'll get theres early and hava a sign on my chair.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214260327000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Because we  are fun. and some one needs to bring the off.</why><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206072310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hartford Pops Olmstead Summer Concert Series</name><id>7574643</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214087400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/7574643/</event_url></item>