<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've got a great group forming (about 30 people) to attend Terry's Evening with us!  If you have not signed up yet, please do so soon!  We invited Terry here for you!  This topic was created with you in mind....so the discussions should be really rich!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Theme:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many conscious individuals feel called, vocationally, by something far beyond the common cultural mind of our time. These two words, &amp;quot;Integral&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Evolutionary&amp;quot; each describe key aspects of a new sensibility that has begun to spontaneously emerge at the leading edge of consciousness and culture. Our world has entered a crisis that calls for something truly new, and it calls each of us, personally. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry will examine what's currently emerging in each of these (interrelated but sometimes distinct) movements - the &amp;quot;Evolutionary&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Integral&amp;quot; movements. He will engage a group process in which we can connect with that which is most pure, essential, and alive in both of them. We'll connect with what includes and transcends them, and how that can guide and inspire us to live authentically and effectively, grounded in both prior oneness and clear discernment, in service of our highest personal and collective possibilities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Terry Patten&lt;/b&gt; serves internationally as a thinking partner and catalyst to cultural leaders and activists, and he is a leading voice in the emerging fields of Integral and Evolutionary leadership and spirituality.  He worked with Ken Wilber and a core team at Integral Institute to develop Integral Life Practice, which distills ancient and modern practices into an intelligent, contemporary, transformational lifestyle. As an entrepreneur, consultant, and communicator he has worked for thirty years to help leaders bring higher consciousness into practical actions that transform complex human systems. Terry currently teaches in the Integral Executive Education program at the University of Notre Dame and is the author of four books.&lt;/i&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="http://www.integralheart.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.integralhe...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please register online for this event: &lt;a href="https://clients.mindbodyonline.com/asp/home.asp" target="_blank"&gt;https://clients.mindb...&lt;/a&gt;.  This is a special event, and Terry is an amazing speaker!  I hope to see you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Love, &lt;br /&gt;Ted &amp;amp; Nicole &amp;amp; the Samadhi Tribe!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267743196000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262826436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening with Terry Patten: Evolutionary vs. Integral</name><id>12246423</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265758200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/12246423/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>