<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>466 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02359</zip><lat>42.083229</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Christina's</name><city>Pembroke</city><id>6001602</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.785339</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, March 20th is the first day of spring - Hard to believe when winter just started! But, as members of SSDOMG, we learn that the passing of time and the turning of the seasons are inevitable, with each new season bringing new adventures around new tables with new friends (and, of course, some old ones).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christina's in Pembroke is an Italian restaurant on a sleepy stretch of Route 53. It's the kind of area where you&amp;nbsp;might not&amp;nbsp;expect much to be happening, whatever the time of year.&amp;nbsp;However, owner Christina Cataldi and her staff are definitely doing things here, and quite a few of them are right. Perhaps the best evidence we can offer is this short review by the &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H_OeeF4yyDA"&gt;Phantom Gourmet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope you'll join us at 7:00 pm on this first evening of spring, as we endeavor to hold back the remnants of winter's chill with the warmth and laughter emanating from our table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Christina's Restaurant&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Tuesday,&amp;nbsp;March 20th, 2012 @&amp;nbsp;7:00 PM&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

466 Washington Street &lt;br /&gt;

Pembroke, MA &lt;br /&gt;

(781)&amp;nbsp;829-9001&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer:&lt;/strong&gt; Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. Two per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact Mike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/strong&gt; Minimum of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;three&lt;/strong&gt; by Sunday, March 18th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Range:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Christina's doesn't seem to have its own website, but I did find an online menu showing almost all of their entrees below $20.00. Have a look: &lt;a href="http://www.menupix.com/menudirectory/menu_link.php?mxresto_id=2102877"&gt;Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; Current Annual Members - None, Group Members - $2.00, Guests - $2.00; $12 to become a 2012 Annual Member (Definitely worth it, especially if you plan to attend at least 5 more events this year.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over five years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Monday,&amp;nbsp;March 19th&amp;nbsp;@ 7:00 pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer. Changes to "No" after the deadline will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us Pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Christina's is located on Washington Street (Route 53) in Pembroke. It's just a short drive south&amp;nbsp;from Orta and the British Beer Company; two restaurants which the group has visited. If you're travelling south on Route 53, Christina's will be on your left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332347148000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330827060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Italian Spring!</name><id>54860572</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332284400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/54860572/</event_url></item>