<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;This is a location that has a few interesting ponds and river areas that are perfect for recreational kayaks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The pond portion has interssting big and little birds, the river porting is pretty interesting too... &lt;br /&gt;A little bit of everything in a area that would be much larger elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok i have a limited amount of kayaks..&lt;br /&gt;some are already reserved..&lt;br /&gt;but I have a OLD CANOE..its long and heavy..plastic type..&lt;br /&gt;its been behind the garage for 15 or so years..looks water worthy..&lt;br /&gt;I cant carry this monster...and it wont fit on the trailer very well...&lt;br /&gt;Roof top..not on my car...it will go throug the moon roof LOL&lt;br /&gt;SO....if you got some vehicle that can carry some 16 or 18 foot..canoe..then we can use it...&lt;br /&gt;other wise it stays as a lawn ornament...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there: &lt;br /&gt;From Hartford: take I 84 east to exit 59 onto I 384 east.... When I 384 ends at rte 6 and 44..take the left split = rte 44 east.... for 7.8 miles and turn right onto rte 32 (Stafford Rd) go apx 1.8 miles then take a right on to rte 275 (South Eagleville Road) at the boat launch sign... &lt;br /&gt;The access is on the right in apx .3 miles just after the dam/bridge on the right at the beginning of Pine Lake Drive...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS, or others..use 38 Pine Lake Drive, Coventry, CT to get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It only takes a few hours to see a lot here...we will think of something for food..thats a discussion for there on the water... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR we cook it up right there..and make a good time of the day...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183484073000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182954970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recreational/Social Paddling and Pot luck meal at Eagleve dam in Coventry CT</name><id>5942618</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183311000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5942618/</event_url></item>