<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Roger's Campground Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03584</zip><lat>44.468908</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Roger's Campground</name><city>Lancaster</city><id>1251859</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.545445</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://porcfest.com/"&gt;http://porcfest.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://porcfest.com/news/who-what-when-where-why-how"&gt;http://porcfest.com/news/who-what-when-where-why-how&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone that wants to come, but particularly those that love freedom  and indiviudal liberty, and more specifically those that have signed the  Free State Project&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://freestateproject.org/soi"&gt;statement of intent&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;WHAT:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Free State Project for the entire week, from Monday, June 20,  2011 through Sunday, June 26, 2011. Feel free to arrive any time during  that week and explore the Free State.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest is a week full of fun and excitement for freedom lovers of  all ages.As previous PorcFest attendees have said, there&amp;rsquo;s simply not  enough time to do every fun activity&amp;hellip; you&amp;rsquo;ll just have to come back next  year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest will feature an entire section of the campground dedicated  to kids and family fun!&amp;nbsp; Learn about homeschooling, do some arts and  crafts, participate in family hikes and sports, enjoy a pool party, and  go on field trips!&amp;nbsp; The fun filled week will culminate in a kids  carnival, complete with a dunk tank which will raise funds for some  great liberty oriented causes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest has a full array of firearms events for seasoned gun geeks  and newbie shooters alike: there will be an Appleseed marksman&amp;rsquo;s  training, basic firearms etiquette and safety classes, seminars about  firearms and the law, and even ammunition reloading for more experienced  shooters!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest features the famous Soapbox Idol, a contest where  participants can perform their own unique rants on whatever topic they  deem worth ranting about!&amp;nbsp; You, the audience, can help judge whose rant  rocks the hardest.&amp;nbsp; PorcFest even has its own poetry jam!&amp;nbsp; Start  thinking of rhymes now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and shake your groove thing on the dance floor at Buzz&amp;rsquo;s Bigger  Gay Dance Party!&amp;nbsp; It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;bigger&amp;rdquo; because last year it was called the Big  Gay Dance Party, but this year it&amp;rsquo;s expanded and promises to be better  than ever.&amp;nbsp; Freedom lovers of all orientations are welcome, as long as  they like to dance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best speakers in the liberty movement will be lending their ideas  to PorcFest attendees all day.&amp;nbsp; Ever wanted to see superstars like  Stefan Molyneaux, Robert Murphy, J. Neil Shulman, Brett Veinotte, and  Evan Nappen &amp;amp; Brian Aitken?&amp;nbsp; PorcFest is your chance to see them all  in one place!&amp;nbsp; And of course, live Music will rock PorcFest each and  every night, with a lineup of musical artists that you won&amp;rsquo;t want to  miss.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the highlights of PorcFest will be the amazing Agora Valley,  where vendors will serve the needs of PorcFest attendees in a radically  free-market way!&amp;nbsp; Buy, sell, trade, and learn about agorism &amp;ndash; all while  having a blast at PorcFest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While you're being catered to by all of the great Agora Valley  vendors, be sure not to eat too much. &amp;nbsp;You'll want to sample the dozens  of dishes at the&amp;nbsp;Liberty Ladies&amp;rsquo; 5th Annual One Pot Cook-off! &amp;nbsp;Maybe  you&amp;rsquo;d like to enter &amp;ndash; there will be prizes for the best dish &amp;ndash; but  equally rewarding is being a One Pot Cook-off judge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch different regions of New Hampshire compete for YOU, the  prospective mover, with guided virtual and real-life tours of different  activist hot spots around New Hampshire, and regionally sponsored  activities like the famous FreeKeene Karaoke!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dozens of other activities include: a pig roast featuring hogs from a  Free Stater homestead, the Humans vs. Zombies tag game, a pirate themed  costume party, and many, many more!&amp;nbsp;You won't want to miss this  celebration of individualism, individuality, and individual freedom!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;WHEN:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;June 20-26th, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;WHERE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roger's Campground in Lancaster, NH&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;WHY:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Free State has been chosen and each year the Porcupines of the  Free State Project meet there to show our spines. ALL who support the  FSP and our goals should come to meet, mingle, befriend, and plan!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;HOW:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any way you can. Just get there. Scrounge, bum a ride from any of the  many convoys, or make some crafts or food to sell and even make your  trip profitable! However you can manage to make it happen, and make it  hot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Registration:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://freestateproject.org/registration/porcfest/2011"&gt;http://freestateproject.org/registration/porcfest/2011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dreepa</member_name><member_id>4145573</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308576114000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302022031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Porc Fest 2011</name><id>17192226</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308571200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/17192226/</event_url></item>