<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;One of the finest singer/songwriters Brazil has produced, Fernando Holz is in a class with Caetano Veloso, Ivan Lins, Djavan and Jobim. His voice is poignant, playful, caressing and his songs come from the soul. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;$10 cover; tickets available in advance on line.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;abracos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jon Simmons &lt;/strong&gt;on  trombone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jason Davis &lt;/strong&gt;on  bass&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Rose &lt;/strong&gt;on  drums&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Molly Flannery &lt;/strong&gt;on  piano&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fernando Holz &lt;/strong&gt;on  voice and guitar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;For more info visit &lt;a href="http://www.fernandoholz.com/"&gt;www.FernandoHolz.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.rylesjazz.com/"&gt;www.RylesJazz.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"In addition to being an excellent singer, Holz is  a composer of great sensibility... beautiful and provocative melodic  lines. But the most significant part of his work as a composer is  represented by his lyrics." - Martin Pillsbury, Ritmo Brasileiro.On his  new release Minh' Alma Nua (My Nude Soul), Fernando Holz sings and  orchestrates original Brazilian pop-jazz music that makes the listener  feel that he or she is being spoken to personally. The Boston-based  musician from the south of Brazil by way of Europe melds happiness and  sadness in superior material with an uncommon ease. Poetry is achieved  through his sensitive and careful employment of mood, tempo, melody, and  harmony. Never stilted or weak in sentiment, the music makes  connections with that of the master, Tom Jobim. A native of Rio Grande  do Sul,Brazil, Holz first made a favorable impression on the New England  music scene as the vocalist with the popular quintet Gandaya, which  created "Brazilian music with a great deal of heart and soul, and not  afraid to take a chance or two," - Jeff Turton, WFNX-Radio. He appeared  at the Boston-area's premier jazz rooms Scullers and Regattabar as well  as at the Hartford Jazz Festival before disbanding in the '90s. He's  also displayed his sizable musical talent with the Rio Show Band, with  Banda Aue, and with Duo Bossa Rio. Outside of the Greater Boston area,  Holz has earned a following in New York City by performing at prominent  venues like the Zinc Bar, SOB's, and the Queens Theatre. The Fernando  Holz Quintet, whose repertoire includes sambas and bossa novas from the  songbooks of Djavan and Jobim along with originals and gems from the  Great American Songbook, consists of the bandleader, pianist Molly  Flannery, John Funkhouser, drummer Steve Rose and trombonist Jon  Simmons. Holz also keeps busy as a vocal coach when not performing with  his band or making special appearances at Brazilian music shows held at  MIT, the University of Massachusetts, Berklee College of Music, the  Brazilian Cultural Center of New England, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Em Portugu&amp;ecirc;s &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; FERNANDO HOLZ - Cantor/Compositor &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ga&amp;uacute;cho de Novo Hamburgo,RS -  Brasil, Fernando Holz vem se destacando  como um m&amp;uacute;sico extremamente competente nas linhas de MPB e Jazz  Brasileiro na regi&amp;atilde;o da Nova Inglaterra, EUA. No seu novo release Minh&amp;rsquo;  Alma Nua (My Nude Soul), Fernando Holz canta m&amp;uacute;sicas originais de sua  autoria que fazem com que o ouvinte sinta se na intimidade de sua sala  de estar ouvindo o artista cantar e tocar. Fernando mistura alegria e  tristeza num material de alt&amp;iacute;ssima qualidade de uma forma completamente  natural e genu&amp;iacute;na.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/f/4/event_11858132.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt; equate this music with the sultry ambiance and fire of a Sarasota sun  off shore just as the peaceful blanket of nightfall enter ones  life.(Karl Stober)   Minh'alma Nua (My Nude Soul)  The music of Minh'  Alma Nua opens up vistas of beauty with colors and textures resulting  from Holz's smooth singing, a string section, Romero Lubambo's guitars,  Gilson Schachnik's and Rebecca Cline's pianos, Jose Pienasola's bass and  Paulo Braga's drums. With complete command of phrasing and timbre, Holz  works through hard sorrow on Freud Explica (Freud Explains) and  projects both vulnerability and determination during Segredos De  Laetitia (Laetitia's Secrets). His voice radiates a poignant tension  amidst the surprising blend of rambunctious drums and sweet strings on  Outro Outono (Another Autumn). The joy-plus-ache that his vocals carry  on the infectious, melodious number Diaspora Brasileira (Brazilian  Diaspora) makes for a perfect fit emotionally with the guitar  expositions. These and all of Holz's other song performances are at once  pristine and sensual. Radiant innocence often masks harsh reality in  his arresting prose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aos compatriotas Brasileiros e nossos irm&amp;atilde;os de lingua portuguesa que  visitam minha website, agrade&amp;ccedil;o pela paci&amp;ecirc;ncia, pois estou come&amp;ccedil;ando o  processo de incluir informa&amp;ccedil;&amp;otilde;es em Portugu&amp;ecirc;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obrigado,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fernando Holz&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will reserve a table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301745699000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>A great opportunity to see this amazing group! If like me you love bossa-nova you are on for a treat! We are so lucky to have an artist of this caliber that live in the Boston area.</why><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299679101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fernando Holz (Soulful Brazilian Music)</name><id>16856972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301533200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/16856972/</event_url></item>