<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In looking at the weather, its JUST RIGHT .. abit of waves and a bitof wind just right for this kind of trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday...Sunny. about 77*F&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Variable winds less than 5 kt becoming S 5 to 10 kt in the morning. Mostly sunny. Seas around 1 ft.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;For a general map of the area will be paddling - i am using someone else's map. (CT Coastal Kayaking) so if you miss my event please look them up for the tour or other things they offer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctcoastalkayaking.com/files/mystictourallramps.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctcoastalkayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING WATER AND A PORTABLE LUNCH or  WHATEVER for the actual paddling part of the day. We will land on one of the far islands beach if the tide is favorable (if not any beach is good).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIDES: It sort of dosent matter, we are going anyway.. the bridge for Mason's island is first anyway..then we head around it and a few islands..etc..return is on the other side and then tour the Mystic Harbor.&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOAT LAUNCH SITE DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Launch Site:     Under I-95 Bridge Launch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Initial Directions: THERE ARE A FEW WAYS TO GET HERE..ONE IS 9 SOUTH TO 95 NORTH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;USE YOUR SPECIFIC DIRECTIONS FROM YOU LOCATION OR JUST USE YOUR GPS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following directions are just a guide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE WAY I WILL TAKE IS RT 2 SOUTH TO rte 11 SOUTH..GO TO END TAKE LEFT on to rte 82 then take a right (south) onto rte 85, go under rte 395 ...  pass by THE MALL,  AND GET ONTO 95 NORTH TILL THE # 89 EXIT AND FOLLOW THE REST OF THE DIRECTIONS BELOW..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(MIGHT EVEN TAKE 395 TO 32..ETC..NOT SURE YET.) depends on traffic, etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;its apx  1 hour from hartford..so plan ahead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;From the West: Take I-95 North to exit # 89.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at exit end:&lt;br /&gt;Make a right to go onto Allyn Street. &lt;br /&gt;Then take a left on Sandy Hollow Road. &lt;br /&gt;Continue until the end of Sandy Hollow Road at which you will make a left onto ( Cow Hill Rd) or High Street. (i have seen both names)...Just go left here,&lt;br /&gt;Then go a short distance to the first right turn onto Bindloss Ave, following to its end.  &lt;br /&gt;( this is a side street with a boat launch sign as best i can remember)  --  &lt;br /&gt;make a left turn onto River Road  -- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Once on River Road continue on a short distance and just after you go under I- 95 Bridge, the boat launch/Parking area is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;Pick any spot to park and carry down the yaks..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS ADDRESS: APX  604 RIVER ROAD, MYSTIC, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;AFTER PARTY DRIVING DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Please Read and print these directions further down if you dont have a GPS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DINNER / BARBIE-Q     BUGG JUICE, FIRE PIT..ETC.. it is not on the Mystic Site LOCATION,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I suggest Gardner Lake (off to the right of the boat launch out of everyones way) its on the way home for most all of us anyway, the lake is right off i sect 82 and 85 (right before we approach rte 11 entrance ramp)..to the EAST a mile or 2.&lt;br /&gt;look at you maps...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;But remember we can skip the after party or even have it somewhere else&lt;/span&gt;..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GARDNER LAKE after party location:&lt;br /&gt;ON THE RETURN TRIP....take a right on rte 82 = Norwitch Rd for apx 2.6 mi, then take a left onto rte 354 = Old Colchester Rd, passs Lake View Rd on right, next right should be Boat Launch Access Rd.. should still be a sign near by..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS users use 145 Old Colchester Rd, Salem CT to get you real close.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING SOME FOOD AND BUGG JUICE FOR THIS PART OF THE EVENT..&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;This trip is ok for most recreational and all sea kayaks, we will watch out for you and help if needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But i will not let the trip go on if the wind is above 10 mph or seas are more than 2 feet mostly that for short rec kayaks, you may get swamped and/or get tired fighting the wind..etc..and none of us really likes bad weather anyway especially at this distance..&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancells the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the weather as we get closer to the event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simple stuff to have is a sponge, pfd and whistle, pump and paddlefloat..&lt;br /&gt;If you dont have this, dont worry, most of us have this on our own boats so there should be enough..but if you can get these items, they are cheapo life insurance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle &amp;amp; Leash,   Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dougnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any wide yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a yes and by persons i have some familiarity with..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybee's obviously can't reserve any yaks and if ya reserve one and don't show up ya won't ever get a second chance to again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer. They get stolen too easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF USING MY YAKS YOU CANT LOOK LIKE A BONEHEADED BEGINNER AND STEP INTO THEM VIA THE FLOOR OR DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. Only Novices in cheap plastic boats do that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way and you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro and impress the others who don't know how. Or you may laugh at the ones that fall in who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: always get out parallel to shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes and paddling  style, and tight fit adjusted...if you have your own please bring it..&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths and types of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some cheap ones for that.)-&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourtie Yak Pad optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer, Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with Novice and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR TRICE ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro, Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;---  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--RESERVED for AL-R---.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest and smallest cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR MARY----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Modified), Yellow, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR DEB BRAULT.---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model and larger cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; ----RESERVED BY MARK K.  ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guillemot Night Heron&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with beginner/intermediate and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (45 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-------&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR  ALEX -- --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Orange Hunting Hat.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281308803000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280853331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> KAYAK The Mystic River - Mystic Seaport - Mason Island- &amp; Islands</name><id>14305029</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281195000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14305029/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/3/global_4970051.jpeg</photo_url></item>