<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Waking up at 6 am to trek to Portsmouth not your thing, but you still want to discuss film with the Boston Arthouse and International Film meetup crew? Did you want to see either My Best Friend or Boss of it All, but couldn't make it?  This is the meetup event for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brattle is screening both films this Sunday as part of a Double Feature. You can go to one or both, but we'll be meeting after the Boss of it All which begins at 5:30. This event will be hosted by Nicole, who will be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater so we can head off to a Thai restaurant for food and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Descriptions of both films are below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My Best Friend&lt;br /&gt;(2006) dir Patrice Leconte w/Daniel Auteuil, Dany Boon, Julie Gayet [94 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;François (Auteuil) is a successful antique dealer who is shocked to find that those who he considers his close friends don?t actually like him. In fact, they don?t believe that he even knows the meaning of friendship. François? business partner, Catherine, wagers that he can?t produce his best friend and challenges him to introduce them. Determined to win the bet, François enlists a friendly cabbie, Bruno, to pose as his friend and help him learn how to be a likeable person. This witty, erudite comedy is a wonderful film from one of France?s leading filmmakers and one of its most beloved stars. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boss Of It All&lt;br /&gt;(2006) dir Lars Von Trier w/Jens Albinus, Fridrik Thor Fridriksson, Peter Gantzler, Benedikt Erlingsson, Iben Hjejle [99 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An entirely unexpected office comedy from Danish director Lars von Trier, THE BOSS OF IT ALL marks von Trier's first Danish film since 1998's The Idiots. Ravn (Gantzler), the owner of an I.T. company, attributes all of his company's executive decisions to a fictional ?Boss Of It All.? Conveniently the fictional boss lives in the United States and communicates solely via e-mail. However, when a potential buyer demands to meet the company's boss he must hire Kristoffer (Albinus), an out-of-work actor to masquerade as the loathed CEO. What follows is a hilarious comedy of errors as Kristoffer is confronted with the chaos and confusion of meeting the company's staff; all of whom have been given contrasting information about their fabled boss. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190748849000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190140195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>In Case You Missed It: My Best Friend and Boss of It All at the Brattle</name><id>6382875</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190575800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6382875/</event_url></item>