<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;My Dearest Goddess SoulSisters!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such a pivotal sacred time we are living in! This lifetime has taught me many lessons - many of the jam packed into this past year! I am happy to share that not only have I survived but I have reached new heights beyond my imagination of my abilities to heal, transform and love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Real *majik* available for us all when we open ourselves to tap into its inherent potential! I am offering this ritual as a reminder to re-membering who we really are and who we came here to be when we set aside the conditioned traps of cultural programming, past wounds, injury and betrayal. It is time to instill a new IMPRINT! What kind of life do you want to live?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I invite you to come celebrate with me on this powerful day - FULL MOON SOLAR ECLIPSE - to release aspects of relating with others that are no longer serving you or the planet's highest good. You are FREE to let it all go and claim your birth right!&amp;nbsp; Together we will welcome in this new paradigm of being in relationship based in integrity, possibility, authenticity and the highest love ever!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adorn your beautiful Goddess self - bring any items you would like to add to the alter, words you would like to share, relationship patterns you would like to release, dreams of what is possible and an organic dish to share for our feast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Birth As We Know It film with Elena Tonetti will be shown at 6pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;followed by a community meal &amp;amp; our ritual&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308185169000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306934213000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Solar Eclipse Release Ritual ~ for women only</name><id>20503601</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308180600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/20503601/</event_url></item>