<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>53.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello All- We need to raise some bucks for Jeff Baker who has been great about letting us use his studio for our meetings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hence us introducing a Fundraising Lighting Workshop- a whole day of learning about light and photography. So here's your chance to participate in not one- not two - but yes three mini sessions each focusing on a distinctive light source. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt; Studio Lighting for Fun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Erb will show you how to use the lights in the studio. From one light set up ~ to two lights  ~ to a grand finally of three lights! Maybe for your amusement we’ll have a little fun playing with Hair Light, Main Light, Fill Light, Back ground Light… Split lighting and dramatic single light portraits! Oh My!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt; Beyond On-Camera Flash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lou Swinand will teach you all about using flash! This workshop looks at using single and multiple portable flash units off the camera. It will cover types of flash units, TTL flash, uses and limitations of portable flash, lighting characteristics of flash units, flash ratios, guide numbers, bounce flash, remote triggers, and the use of flash accessories and modifiers (such as umbrellas, reflectors, Omni bounce, Gary Fong units, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt; Using Natural Light&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teya Rutherford will lead you on an extraordinary visual journey into using only the light that surrounds you! She’ll chat a bit about positioning your subjects for unsurpassed compositions and how to use reflectors. Capture folks using natural light and create stunning fun portraits! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt; Details! Each session will have 10 folks in it and last aprox 1.5 hours each. After your 1.5 hours of fun – you’ll switch to the next group and a new light situation. So at the end of the day you’ll have learned a bit about each type of light. Models will be used in each session. So bring your cameras! We’ll take a break for Lunch and Socializing and get back to the two afternoon sessions. We’ll be wrapped up around 5PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;All this for the low price of $50.00 per person (53.00 if paying online through paypal)! Space is limited so please sign up ASAP!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions? Comments? Email us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt; We will accept pay pal payments of 53.00 (including the up charge) Just click below to get to the paypal site. Hit the send money button and enter Scott's email address. scott@erbphoto.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or you can mail a check to me. Once I get the check I will RSVP you to the event here online. My mailing address is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Dufault&lt;br /&gt;380 Bridle Path &lt;br /&gt;Worcester MA 01604&lt;br /&gt;50.00 - make check out to Scott Erb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basic Agenda for the day...&lt;br /&gt; 9:00 AM - 9:30 AM Check in time&lt;br /&gt; 9:30 AM - 10:00 AM Group Assignments&lt;br /&gt;10:00 AM - 11:30 AM Session 1&lt;br /&gt;11:30 PM - 1:00 PM Lunch&lt;br /&gt;1:00 PM - 2:30 PM Session 2&lt;br /&gt;3:00 PM - 4:30 PM Session 3&lt;br /&gt;4:30 PM - 5:00 PM Feed back, Clean Up, and Chillin'&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check in with me at the Door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225412416000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222883476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baker Fundraiser- Photography is all about Light!</name><id>8873438</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225027800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8873438/</event_url></item>