<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kearsarge Valley Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03287</zip><lat>43.390446</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Winslow State Park</name><city>Wilmot</city><id>8171302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.868680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer&lt;/strong&gt; - Larry Peck (978)853-5481 &lt;br /&gt;

 =========================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a spur of the moment hike that my wife and I will be doing. I thought I'd post this as a meetup if anyone would like to join us. My wife(Kelly) is a beginner hiker who hikes at a beginner pace with lots of breaks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we'll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be starting in the parking area at Winslow state park, hiking the Winslow trail to the lookout tower, having a bite to eat, and hiking the Barlow trail back to the parking lot. The overall hike is about a 3 mile loop. I don't expect this hike to be more than 4 hours in duration, chances are it might be less depending on how much time is spent at the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The forecast for Saturday is mostly sunny and hot (90 degrees), make sure you bring plenty of water. This is a 15% chance of a thunder shower so a rain shell might not be a bad idea to bring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is will be at a slow paced hike catering to beginner hikers. The goal is to tag a 52wav peak and enjoy the scenery at the top without killing ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to know what you are expected to have, review the following list:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail map can be found &lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/KearsargeHikingMap_Web.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Route 93 north &lt;br /&gt;

 - Route 89 northwest to Exit 10 &lt;br /&gt;

 - Route 11 east &lt;br /&gt;

 - Kearsarge Valley Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for the 2012 Black Subaru Outback &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email me your questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Peck</member_name><member_id>10414539</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342920678000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342104813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>52wav: Kearsarge (Winslow State Park) EASY PACE</name><id>73044302</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342274400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/73044302/</event_url></item>