<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Ferry Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01835</zip><lat>42.772040</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-374-9683</phone><name>Crescent Yacht Club</name><city>Bradford</city><id>1120809</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073668</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Don't Call Me Shirley (DCMS) is at The Crescent Yacht Club in Bradford, lets go out and listen to the great music they play, do some dancing and socializing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have followed DCMS at various venues and absolutely love this band. Although they have lost a band member, they are still awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The band goes on at 9pm but lets get to The&amp;nbsp;yacht club&amp;nbsp;at 830pm in order to reserve our table,&amp;nbsp; and socialize before the music starts.&amp;nbsp; The Yacht club does not serve food but will allow you to bring in munchies, if anyone is interested you can bring munchies but they MUST BE NUTFREE.&amp;nbsp; You will be asked at the door if your snack is nutfree as the bartender is HIGHLY allergic to nuts (not the human kind).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover charge at the yacht club, but you must sign in as a non-member.&amp;nbsp; The parking can be a little tight so make sure you get there early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to take the Meetup cell number in case you get lost, are running late or need to cancel at the last minute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Haven't paid your dues yet this year? Please be prepared to pay your yearly dues at this event. Yearly dues goes to the cost of maintaining the Meetup Site, event costs and incidentals. Please make sure you stay current with your yearly dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So grab those dancing shoes and come on down to The Yacht Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you all there  &lt;br /&gt;Janet &amp;amp; Donna&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup Table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303777272000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We always have a great time at a DCMS event</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299937761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DCMS at The Crescent Yacht Club in Bradford</name><id>16893556</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303518600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/16893556/</event_url></item>