<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>540 Forest Ave</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04102</zip><lat>43.668230</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(207) 772-0300</phone><name>The Great Lost Bear</name><city>Portland</city><id>669824</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.280266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Team,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This was a hard decision but I am going to have to reschedule this week's meeting to next Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to personal issues, I have neither read everyone's story nor completed my own.  And it is not at all fair for me to show up to the group unprepared which is why I'm rescheduling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet Wednesday, March 3rd @ 6:30PM where I will be fully prepared to discuss all our stories.  Mine will be up by Saturday at the latest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I appreciate your understanding and will see you next week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Chang&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February Homework Assignment&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Team Rocketship Unicorn!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have had a revelation.  And this is that we need to break into a new paradigm – or something like that (I’ve been drinking wine).  So, with this in mind, Rudi, you are released from your homework.  And this is so the rest of us can individually do homework assignments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is your homework for the next meeting:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will write a 2,500 word story or beginning of a story using the elements I supply you with below. .  It cannot be tongue in cheek.  It must be serious.  Failure to complete this means you must pay for the meal &amp;amp; drinks of the person to your left at the next meeting.  Failure to show up for the next meeting (unless in the case of medical or personal emergency) means you must write 5,000 words and pay for the meal and drinks of the persons to your left and right.  No shit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, here are your assignments:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIM – You must write a science fiction story about cybernetic beagles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHRIS – You must write a fantasy story about a dragon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JAMIE – You must write a steampunk story about Queen Victoria and her servant Robert Brown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CINDY – You must write a cyberpunk story involving the Ark of The Covenant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RUDI – You must write a golden age sci-fi story about Amazon women in a crisis.  You must also suggest a topic for me to write on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone else new to the group who wants to come to this meeting should email me and get a topic to write on.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy your writing, folks!  See you in February!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- CHANG&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chang Terhune</member_name><member_id>8087033</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267832223000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Science Fiction Writers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Science-Fiction-Writers-Group</urlname><id>1313705</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>ROCKETSHIP UNICORN</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264044443000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ROCKETSHIP UNICORN:  LOVE IN THE TIME OF OH MY GOD THEY'RE ALL VC!!!</name><id>12379121</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267659000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Science-Fiction-Writers-Group/events/12379121/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/b/global_9582795.jpeg</photo_url></item>