<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you know how to turn olive oil into fuel? &amp;nbsp;Can you assemble a chicken coop in less than a minute? &amp;nbsp;Do you have a trick to create flawless knitting stitches each time? &amp;nbsp;Ok, so my examples are a little extravagant (read: impossible) but we all have learned some clever tricks and skills in our areas of expertise, be them cooking, gardening, construction, wilderness survival or politics. &amp;nbsp;Today is a day where you can show off.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this afternoon, consider this to be an "open mic night." &amp;nbsp;Come demonstrate something in under 15 minutes for the group and see what others have mastered. &amp;nbsp;This will be educational and fun, I promise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other things you can expect this afternoon:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are a new member, come on over and do a little meet and greet to see your neighbors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm some projects we could tackle and try to schedule some of our awesome ideas posted into actual meetups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share information about resources in our area so that we can maintain a strong sense of community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm hosting this at a location at the intersection of Route 1 and Route 95, a convenient location for all points north shore. (It is a housing complex, so don't park in any numbered spaces) &amp;nbsp;I'll provide some light refreshments but please feel free to show off a favorite snack or recipe of yours!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Shore Vitality events are designed to remind ourselves of all the cool people that make up our local community, what our talents are and what we can do to bring ecological vitality to our lives and neighborhoods. Together, we can show that the North Shore is quite impressive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will definitely wrap up by 6pm as I have another engagement to attend to this day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks! :-) Happy Permaculturing!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302981612000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>we want to motivate each other and stay connected</why><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299691783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northshore Vitality - Demo Day</name><id>16859430</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302976800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/16859430/</event_url></item>