<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Prior to the 2nd Annual Bully Parade, and continuing into the afternoon if there are attendees who can't make the loop (older, disabled dogs or people or those who want to attend but can't do the 3 mile loop), CGC (Canine Good Citizen) Testing will be conducted beginning at 8:00a at 182 Hayden Rowe Street, Hopkinton, MA. ~~~ This is a ten-step test, an award earned through the American Kennel Club which handlers like to attain for various reasons including, but not limited to: a prerequisite to therapy work, to exempt your dog from some town's Breed Specific Legislation (yuck!), to obtain or keep home owners insurance, for a BREAK on insurance, as a symbol of accomplishment between you and your dog and to be one more person with a Canine Good Citizen-certified bully breed dog! ~~~ You can learn more about the CGC and its steps here: &lt;a href="http://www.akc.org/events/cgc/program.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.akc.org/ev...&lt;/a&gt;. ~~~ The cost will be $15 per dog, and will benefit the MA Canine Professionals Club (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/dog-trainers-group/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;) as well as a few other organizations to be determined. ~~~ Dogs must be on a flat collar, and a 4-6 foot leash (NO FLEXI/EXTENDABLE LEASHES), and handlers may not use treats, toys or other incentives to pass the test. ~~~ Special thanks to Peter Grobel, founder of the MA Canine Professionals Club, Kelli Leahy, who does therapy work with her two Labrador retrievers, and Alicia Seguin, who owns X, the only Search &amp;amp; Rescue pit bull in RI, featured on &lt;a href="http://stubbydog.org/"&gt;http://stubbydog.org/...&lt;/a&gt;. ~~~ Hope to see many of you come out and give it a try! Feel free to email me direct at justcassie101@gmail.com with any questions or concerns.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337559712000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329335091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canine Good Citizen Tests beginning at 8:00a before the 2nd Annual Bully Parade</name><id>52480452</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337428800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/52480452/</event_url></item>