<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Plan is to meet at the Carter Moriah trailhead off Route 2 near Gorham.  We will ascend by Stony Brook Trail and return by Carter Moriah Trail.  To avoid a road walk we will begin by leaving one or two cars at the Carter Moriah Trail head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohamed Ellozy's description of the hike is:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are two routes up Mt. Moriah. One is the fairly gentle climb up the Carter-Moriah trail from Gorham (rt: 9.0 miles, 3,550 feet, 6:15). The other, by the Stony Brook and Carter-Moriah trails (rt: 10.0 miles, 3,150 feet, 6:35) includes a steep section. Both offer great views (and blueberries in season) from open ledges, and the views from the summit are excellent. They can be combined as a loop ascending by Stony Brook (lp: 9.5 miles, 3,300 feet, 6:25), this requires a second car or a road walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stony Brook Trail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:  3.6 miles, 2200 ft velevation gain - 2 hr 55 minutes book time&lt;br /&gt;Carter Moriah Trail to Mt. Moriah Summit&lt;/span&gt;:  1.4  miles, 950 ft elevation gain - 1 hr 10 minutes &lt;br /&gt;Carter Moriah Trail to Bangor Rd via Mt. Surprise.&lt;/span&gt;:  4.5  miles, 150 ft elevation gain - 2 hr 20 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate totals:  8.5  miles, 3300 elevation gain, 6 hr 25 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Weather forecast&lt;/span&gt;:  Mostly Sunny - looking good.  Highs around 57 at peak, 67 in the valley.&lt;br /&gt; Check for updates at: &lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.34152959888481&amp;amp;lon=-71.12960815429688&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;smap=1&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text" target="_blank"&gt;http://forecast.weath...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pace: Moderate.  I start with the notion of doing the trip within an hour of book time (allowing for one long break and a number of smaller ones). I'm fine with going a faster, especially if late afternoon thundershowers are forecast or a little slower if that's the pace the group is comfortable with.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: This is challenging hike.  We will be going above treeline, so you must come prepared for bad weather.   Weather in the mountains is unpredictable.  People have died from exposure hiking in the White Mountains in summer, so there are risks even in early autumn. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necessary equipment:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Headlamp (or flashlight) with spare batteries, or a second headlamp/flashlight. &lt;br /&gt;• Clothing: Light-weight to mid-weight synthetic shirt/pants - no jeans or cotton. Cotton does not insulate well when wet. Windy ridge conditions can compound this. &lt;br /&gt;• Outerwear: Light-weight to mid-weight waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and something (even a fleece vest) to wear for extra insulation if needed. &lt;br /&gt;• Food and Water: High-energy snacks and at least two quarts of water.&lt;br /&gt;• Other Gear: Sunscreen and insect repellent. &lt;br /&gt;• Trail hardy Footwear. &lt;br /&gt;* Anything else your experience, judgment or research tells you that you need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information please look for the list of 10 essentials, other gear and the Hiker Responsibility Code at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.c..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Car Pooling –   Lets save some gas money and shrink our carbon footprint! If you have a ride to offer or need a ride please post your needs or availability on your RSVP.  Please note your interest in giving or getting a ride and contact hikers directly if their posts or profiles indicate it might be convenient to share rides with them.  It looks like my car is close to full (I will be taking a dog and two other hikers), but could probably squeeze in another and I'll likely have more room for the return trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs:   Well behaved dogs are welcome, I'm bringing mine.  Please mention your dog in your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Please allow plenty of time and let me know ASAP if you are running late as cell phone coverage is not reliable.  Having been burned by no shows a few times, I will not keep people waiting unless I am sure you are coming. &lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions:    (pasted from a website):  End of Bangor Street in Gorham, elevation about 800 feet &lt;br /&gt;44.3824°N, 71.1695°W (WGS84) &lt;br /&gt;This is a narrow street and parking at the end is limited to a couple of spaces on the opposite side from the houses.   Park only on the left, opposite the houses.   No WMNF parking pass is required. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93 exit 35 N of Franconia Notch, take US Route 3 N about 13 miles to NH Route 115. Turn R on NH Route 115 and follow it about 10 miles to its end at US Route 2. Turn R on US Route 2 and follow it 15 miles through Gorham (.5 miles past Gorham town common with railroad station), turn sharp R just beyond railroad tracks on Bangor Street and proceed .4 miles to the end. Park on the opposite side from the houses as signs allow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;MY DISCLAIMER: MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no).  I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.   HOPEFULLY WE'LL ALL HAVE SOME FUN AND ENJOY A GREAT HIKE IN GOOD COMPANY.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be there with a shaggy black dog </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David (Ped Xing)</member_name><member_id>4566112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285639525000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285359540000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mounts Moriah and Surprise via Stony Brook return by Carter Moriah Trail</name><id>14885205</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285594200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14885205/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>