<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Do you have a membership for the &lt;b&gt;Museum of Science&lt;/b&gt;? If not, get one! :) With a $75.00 &amp;quot;Basic 2&amp;quot; membership for the Museum of Science &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/members/buy_a_membership" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/me...&lt;/a&gt; you and a guest get to explore the Museum of Science as many times as you want to view free science lectures happening daily inside the exhibition halls, two free one-time-use passes for the Omni Theater and two for the Planetareum. Bring a friend along just onece, use up the free passes they give you, and you basically have broke even. Museum of Science Membership also provides you opportunities to see events such as ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harry Potter™: The Exhibition&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/members/events_and_promotions/member_events?d=3850" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/me...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Be among the first to step inside the magical world of the most famous boy-wizard! Enjoy an up-close look at the amazing craftsmanship of more than 200 props and costumes from the Harry Potter films, all displayed in settings inspired by the film sets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Fee&lt;/b&gt;: $5 per member. Entrance is limited to the number of Exhibit Halls admissions permitted with your membership level. Be sure to bring your current membership card with you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Admission by timed ticket only. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advance purchase is strongly recommended&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; . Audio guides available: add $5 (adult), $4 (senior, child, member). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Exhibit opens to the public Sunday, October 25. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Purchase Tickets&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="https://store.mos.org/?action=showevent;event_id=530" target="_blank"&gt;https://store.mos.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Event details: 617-589-0180, 617-589-0417 (TTY), 9:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m. daily&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was thinking that we could grab a few big tables in the food court of the Museum of Science starting at 10:00 am. I'll throw a few red MEETUP table tents on the table we grab so people could find us. It seems like tickets are selling out fast for this day. For example, as of 9/8/2009 from 10:00 am to 11:00 am slot only the 10:20 am, 10:25 am, 10:40 am, and 10:50 am and 10:55 am slot is open. We could hang out briefly and group up with the people in the same time slot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They say it should take an hour or so to browse the entire show. With so many people split up into different groups, it might be difficult to plan anything after. Let's see what happens...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. He managed to get the 10:45 am timeslot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about the Harry Potter exhibition:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We want you to get the most out of your experience in the exhibit, so please be aware of the following restrictions when planning your visit: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* When ordering tickets, keep in mind that there are no refunds or exchanges. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Photography, filming, or recording of any kind are not permitted in the exhibit. Like all of our exhibits, food or beverages are not permitted. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Step inside the famous boy-wizard's magical world through Harry Potter: The Exhibition, a new exhibit featuring more than 200 authentic costumes and props from the Harry Potter films, all displayed in settings inspired by the film sets. View iconic items such as Harry's original wand and eyeglasses, the Marauder's Map, and even pull your own Mandrake. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Nonmember admission includes an Exhibit Halls voucher for use on the day of your visit or within six months. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Also available: Harry Potter: The Exhibition Audio Tour -- Listen to behind-the-scenes stories from the creators of the films and delve deeper into Harry Potter's magical world. Advance purchase is strongly recommended; supplies are limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It is recommended that visitors allow approximately one hour to go through the exhibit&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Can't make it to the event on this particular day, but still want to see the exhibit? Write to Heather the Organizer for Assistant Organizer permissions, and schedule a meetup event on the Nerd Fun calendar when you can make it!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256743584000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252425297000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harry Potter the Exhibition: Sneak peek for members of Museum of Science </name><id>11318008</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256392800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11318008/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/c/8/global_10606808.jpeg</photo_url></item>