<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Edgehill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.331053</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgerton Park</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1057313</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.917214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;RSVP's for this event will be closed by 9 pm Friday night August 31. Info on how to find us at the park will be sent by 9 am Saturday morning Sept 1.  : )&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for outdoor theater in New Haven's historic Edgerton Park. Performances are free but with a suggested donation of $20 for adults and $10 for students. Bring a blanket or chair. Picnics encouraged! BYOB. Find more information at &lt;a href="http://www.elmshakespeare.org"&gt;www.elmshakespeare.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Christine will Host this meetup.  If you have any questions, please e-mail her &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/message/?recipientId=6235505"&gt;Here!&lt;/a&gt; She'll provide contact information to the "Yes" RSVP's the day before the event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elm Shakespeare Company kicks off its 17th season with a production of Macbeth featuring James Andreassi as Macbeth and Marianna Bassham as Lady Macbeth. This not-for-profit theater group's has become a summer staple in New Haven and not to be missed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Authentically set and clothed in the Scotland of its setting, the play includes combat scenes with broad swordplay. The set and the costumes are spectacular aiming at a ‘Game of Thrones’ look and feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1995, The Elm Shakespeare Company is a professional, multicultural theatre company committed to establishing a discourse with Connecticut communities and schools through the medium of Shakespeare’s plays. Since then, audiences have grown to over 30,000 attending performances throughout the month of August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact information and instructions on how to find us will be emailed to Yes RSVP's the day before the event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Christine will provide Contact Information to the YES RSVP's the Day before the Event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346597589000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345299791000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shakespeare in the Park</name><id>78284672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346542200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/78284672/</event_url></item>