<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>530 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02482</zip><lat>42.297070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-235-1610</phone><name>Wellelsey Hills Library</name><city>Wellesley </city><id>788653</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.290911</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The new Child Support Guidelines scheduled to take effect January 1, 2009 contain radical increases in child support for some people—doubling an even tripling of the order. Very few people will escape with less than a fifteen percent increase. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I urge you to attend our next General Membership meeting on Tuesday evening, November 18 at the Wellesley Free Library, beginning at 7 PM. We will present the Guidelines, calculate your individual support order (if you wish), discuss our response, and begin our action plan for 2009. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you demand change that matters, come to this meeting. Also, BRING A NEW SUPPORTER WITH YOU. A bigger army means a faster victory. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free refreshments will be served. The meeting is free and open to the public. We begin at 7 PM and finish around 9 PM, but you can arrive or leave whenever you wish. Directions are found below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Wellesley Free Library, 530 Washington St, Wellesley, MA 02482:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE NORTH AND SOUTH&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 128, to Exit 20B (Route 9 West).  Proceed through the SECOND set of lights (Oakland Street intersection), start down hill and take off-ramp (on your RIGHT) to Route 16 (if you go under bridge, you've gone too far).  At interestion with Route 16 (Washington Street), take a LEFT and proceed through five sets of lights (as a landmark, there is a MOBIL gas station at the fourth set of lights).  Immediately after the fifth set of lights, the driveway to the Library will be on your LEFT, AFTER THE BUILDING.  Parking is either below or in back of the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE EAST (via Route 9)&lt;br /&gt;Once you enter Wellesley, you will see signs for Route 128 North and South.  Proceed through the second set of lights (Oakland Street intersection), start down hill and take off ramp (on your RIGHT) to Route 16 ( if you go under bridge, you've gone too far).  At intersection with Route 16 (Washington Street), take a left and proceed through five sets of lights (as a landmark, there is a MOBIL gas station at the fourth set of lights).  Immediately after the fifth set of lights, the driveway to the  Library will be on your LEFT, AFTER THE BUILDING.  Parking is either below or in back of the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE EAST (via the MassPike)&lt;br /&gt;Proceed on Mass Pike West to the Route 16 exit to West Newton/Wellesley.  Keep RIGHT at the fork in the ramp and merge onto Route 16 West.  You will proceed past Newton Wellesley Hospital (on your LEFT) and travel over Route 128.  Once you pass over Route 128, you will proceed through seven sets of lights (as a landmark, there is a MOBIL gas station at the sixth set of lights).  Immediately after the seventh set of lights, the driveway to the Library will be on your LEFT, AFTER THE BUILDING.  Parking is either below or in back of the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE WEST (via the Mass Pike)&lt;br /&gt;Take the MassPike East to Exit 13 heading toward Natick.  At first set of lights after leaving off ramp take a RIGHT onto Speen Street. Proceed to Route 9 East.  Ramp is on LEFT and merge onto Route 9 East.  Go through two sets of lights, and proceed to the Weston Road exit.  At bottom of exit ramp, take a RIGHT onto Weston Road.  Proceed approximately one mile to Central Street (you will see Wellesley College in front of you).  Take a LEFT onto Central Street; go through one set of lights.  Before second set of lights light, the driveway to the Library will be on your RIGHT.  Parking is below or in back of the building.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ned Holstein, M.D., M.S.</member_name><member_id>3335203</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256206051000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fathers' Rights Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fathersrights-210</urlname><id>676727</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Fathers' Rights Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226937101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>General Membership Meeting</name><id>9178510</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227052800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fathersrights-210/events/9178510/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/7/global_2531783.jpeg</photo_url></item>