<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ford Hall Forum&lt;br /&gt;at Suffolk University&lt;br /&gt;presents&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Election 2008:&lt;br /&gt;Review and Forecast&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;with&lt;br /&gt;Congressman Barney Frank&lt;br /&gt;Chairman, House Financial Services Committee&lt;br /&gt;(Democrat, 4th Congressional District of Massachusetts)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;joined by&lt;br /&gt;Emily Rooney&lt;br /&gt;Host and Executive Editor of Greater Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, November 13, at 6:30-8:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Old South Meeting House&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Boston, MA) Ford Hall Forum presents “Election 2008: Review and Forecast” with Congressman Barney Frank, joined by Emily Rooney. Thursday, November 13, at 6:30-8:30 pm.  Admission is free and open to all. Old South Meeting House, 310 Washington Street (corner of Milk St.), Boston, MA. Wheelchair accessible and conveniently located near the State St. and Downtown Crossing stops on the MBTA. For more information, call the Ford Hall Forum at 617-557-2007 or visit www.fordhallforum.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obama. McCain. Who will be sitting in the Oval Office on January 21, 2009? What does it mean for the future of our country? The economy. Supreme Court justices. Foreign policy. Global warming. Nuclear proliferation. Abortion. Energy security. Join us as Congressman Barney Frank speaks with Greater Boston host Emily Rooney to unravel the deciding factors that led one candidate into the winner's circle -- and then look forward to its impact on the coming years for our nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Background information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Congressman Barney Frank has been in Congress since 1981. He is the Chairman of the Financial Services Committee. Previously he was a Massachusetts State Representative and an assistant to the Mayor of Boston. He has also taught at several Boston area universities.  (&lt;a href="http://www.house.gov/frank/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.house.gov/...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emily Rooney has been host and executive editor of Greater Boston, WGBH’s local issues and public affairs program, since its debut in January 1997. Greater Boston airs Monday through Friday at 7pm on WGBH 2 and at midnight on WGBH 44, providing viewers with a fresh approach to and in-depth analysis of timely news, politics, and public affairs issues of local interest. The series has been honored with numerous New England Emmys, Associated Press and Edward R. Murrow Awards for Best Public Affairs Program, and excellence in writing and commentary. She has also received the Dennis Kauff Award for Excellence in Reporting, the Yankee Quill Award from the American Newspaper Society and the Reporter of the Year Award from the Mass Bar Association.  (&lt;a href="http://www.wgbh.org/gb/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wgbh.org/g...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ford Hall Forum is the nation’s oldest free public lecture series. The Forum promotes freedom of speech and fosters an informed and effective citizenry through the public presentation of lectures, debates, and discussions. Its events illuminate the key issues facing our society by bringing to its podium knowledgeable and thought-provoking speakers, including some of the most controversial opinion leaders of our times. These speakers are presented in person, for free, and in settings, which facilitate frank and open debate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Forum began in 1908 as a series of Sunday evening public meetings held at the Ford Hall, which once stood on Beacon Hill in Boston. While the original building no longer exists, the public conversations have continued throughout the Greater Boston area with the generous support of foundations, corporations, academic institutions, and individuals. As the Forum marks its 100th Anniversary, it is embarking on a new partnership with the Suffolk University College of Arts &amp;amp; Sciences. Suffolk is now housing the Forum’s administrative offices just a block away from where the original Ford Hall once stood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ford Hall Forum programs are made possible through the generous contributions from individual members as well as corporations and foundations, including The Boston Foundation, The Boston Public Library, Citizens Bank, Boston Private Bank &amp;amp; Trust Company, CBT Architects, The Fred and Marty Corneel Fund, Fidelity Investments, Helen Rees Literary Agency, Houghton Chemical Corporation, Jackson &amp;amp; Company, Levine, Katz, Nannis + Solomon, PC, The Lowell Institute, Massachusetts Cultural Council, Nellie Mae Education Foundation, The Old South Meeting House, The Pfizer Foundation, Plymouth Rock Assurance Corporation, Prince, Lobel, Glovksy, and Tye, LLP, The WAND Education Foundation, WBUR, WGBH, William Gallagher Associates.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226792013000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225085290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Truth Squad: Congressman Barney Frank @ Ford Hall Forum: Election 2008</name><id>9038302</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226619000000</time><rsvp_limit>992</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9038302/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>