<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Conscious Movie:  &lt;b&gt;The Chorus&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, December 12th • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It’s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An inspirational story in the rich tradition of MUSIC OF THE HEART and MR. HOLLAND'S OPUS, THE CHORUS has moved critics everywhere to declare it one of the year's very best films! When he takes a job teaching music at a school for troubled boys, Clément Mathieu is unprepared for its harsh discipline and depressing atmosphere. But with passion and unconventional teaching methods, he's able to spark his students' interest in music and bring them a newfound joy! It also puts him at odds with the school's overbearing headmaster, however, locking Mathieu in a battle between politics and the determination to change his pupils' lives!&lt;br /&gt;Snacks will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're just around the corner from the Stony Brook T-stop on the Orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229469265000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223571605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie:  The Chorus</name><id>8930740</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229128200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/8930740/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/6/9/global_5805177.jpeg</photo_url></item>