<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT E51-145</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>212199</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Feature Presentation&lt;br /&gt;Title: USING ROBOTIC TRADING TO TRADE STOCKS by ERIC EKLOF from Vermont&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: Eric Eklof will  show how he uses Robotic Trading to trade stocks. Eric uses &amp;quot;Cool-Trade&amp;quot; fully-automated stock trading software that intelligently filters &amp;amp; trades stocks on it's own while you are at work or on vacation. Cool-Trades &amp;quot;Auto Trader&amp;quot; executes your strategies 100% on its own and trades your logic, applies your rules and thus removes emotions. Eric suggests you check-out the Cool-Trade website prior to the meeting. Find it at: &lt;a href="https://www.cool-trade.com/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.cool-trad...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Eric Eklof has been attending our meeting for nine months. Over that period we have all gotten to know him as an upbeat, knowledgeable short-term trader. He is not afraid to volunteer his knowledge and opinion, often pointing out the positive contributions of others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting's agenda will have the following agenda:&lt;br /&gt;- 6:00-7:00 In addition to his feature presentation, Eric Eklof will do a primer on general robotic trading during the premeeting period. This is optional. Open to all.&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Meeting Begins:&lt;br /&gt;- Group discussion led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;- Agenda setting for the fall led by Doug&lt;br /&gt;- Technical Analysis update by Harlan&lt;br /&gt;- Stockpicks section&lt;br /&gt;- Feature Presentation by Eric Eklof (see above)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members value open discussion highly. We try to pack as much open discussion as possible. Expressing ideas and sharing knowledge is paramount to our members.&lt;br /&gt;All levels of expertise are welcome. No question is too simple - as a matter of fact the simplest question often evokes the best discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have friends that you talk stocks with then bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Location: MIT Building E51. MIT, 70 Memorial Drive, Cambridge, MA, USA.&lt;br /&gt;This building is on the far eastern side of the MIT campus, about a ten minute walk from the main entrance, and about two minutes from the Kendall Square 'T' stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free meeting. There is no membership required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186701086000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184342506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors Business Daily Tuesday Meetup</name><id>6019085</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186527600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/6019085/</event_url></item>