<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's June Baby! My favorite month of the year. Time to chat about all the cool stuff we want to get out and photograph this Summer! Click and Shoot planning is top priority- so please think about where you want to go and we'll start planning to make it happen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The big click and shoot for this summer....Trash the Dress! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can learn about the last event we did - check out the photos in the photo section of the site. It was huge and it was fun! We got 17 models, 20 photographers, 3 makeup artists, and a stylist and converged on Oakland Beach in RI. We ate lunch first getting to know one another and then went out to photograph. So...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd like to plan a huge Trash the Dress event in August/Sept.&lt;br /&gt;We are looking for volenteers to help plan it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the things we need to get help with are:&lt;br /&gt;Location - where do we want to shoot- Picking either a City or Beach location?&lt;br /&gt;Dresses- Chatting with Bridal Places, going to Salvation Army, and Thrift shops&lt;br /&gt;Props- flowers, veils, jewelry&lt;br /&gt;Models - Male and Female&lt;br /&gt;Paper work- model releases, permits, File sharing of images&lt;br /&gt;Costs- what to charge for all expenses&lt;br /&gt;Press- Last time we got a lot of press- but they want to be there the day we are shooting to &amp;quot;cover&amp;quot; the event... good for all of us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get organized!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scotty&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Scott and I are always to try to greet everyone who comes to the meetups. We'll</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246146015000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243557545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Worcester Photography June Meetup</name><id>10518840</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245972600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10518840/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/d/3/global_7856515.jpeg</photo_url></item>