<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>347 Gilead Street</address_2><address_1>Route 85</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06248</zip><lat>41.697037</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hebron Lions Fairgrounds</name><city>Hebron</city><id>398960</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.362680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;10/1/11 Update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOMETHING WICKED THIS WAY COMES...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="text-align : justify ; color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : justify ; color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;img src="http://ctfaire.com/images/pumpkin_glow.jpg" width="178" height="181" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Get ready for a special Halloween event like nothing you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen before as the Pumpkin King joins King Arthur for an extended-hours event. Beginning at 5:30pm the Faire slowly transitions from happy harvest festival to haunting Halloween fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the village zombies wander the streets looking for opportunities to pose for fun photos; there are costume contests for kids and adults; a chance to have your picture taken with the Pumpkin King; fire shows light up the night and dazzle audiences; jack o&amp;rsquo; lanterns cast an eerie glow upon the streets as crowds shuffle back and forth to see the shows leading up to the &amp;ldquo;Joust to the Undeath&amp;rdquo;; hot mulled cider, pumpkin pie, shopping, and fun for all awaits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the bell tolls seven, mortals are invited to watch the Witch Queen and a Death Knight take to the field of shadows where they joust upon Nightmares for the right to escape Limbo. The victor will gather souls for the dark one for a year&amp;rsquo;s time. The Headless Horseman, Jack of the Lantern, joins the battle in a contest where there can be only one. Magic will scorch the air, fiery lances will shatter in the night with unholy vengeance, and flaming swords will cut to bone. Bring your friends, your family, and even your enemies&amp;hellip; nobody wants to die alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ghoulishly fun event begins in the evening toward the Faire&amp;rsquo;s regular close time and is included with your admission! This is a MUST SEE event because there is no other Halloween event ANYWHERE like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I experienced this last year and it was fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;End of 10/1 update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something came up so that I am rescheduling the event to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;October 8th, the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you cannot make it that week then please change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;your RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go back in time to 1525.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entering the Village of Caer Leon in the presence of King Arthur,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His Knights of the Round Table &amp;amp; Camelot. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Hebron Lions Fairgrounds &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Route 85 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

347 Gilead Street &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Hebron, CT 06248 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

A &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.ctfaire.com/connecticut_renaissance_festival/index.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ctfaire.com/connecticut_renaissance_festival/index.php&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

www.ctfaire.com/connecticut_renaissance_festival/index.php &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

B &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://hebronharvestfair.org/History.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://hebronharvestfair.org/History.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

hebronharvestfair.org/History.html &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

C &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.renaissancefestival.com/viewEvent.asp?eventID=221" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.renaissancefestival.com/viewEvent.asp?eventID=221&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

www.renaissancefestival.com/viewEvent.asp?eventID=221 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Reminders &amp;amp; more information closer to the event date. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Attendance Fee is $15. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FROM HARTFORD Take I 84 E towards East Hartford. Cross Conn River, take exit number 55, Rte 2 East towards Norwich/New London. Take exit number 13 (Rte 66). Turn LEFT Rte 66 &amp;amp; follow to the light several miles down the road. At the light take a left onto Rte 85. Lions Fairgrounds will be on the LEFT. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FROM NEW HAVEN Take I- 91 Nth towards Hartford. Take EXIT 25, merging onto Rte 3 N towards Glastonbury. Merge onto Rte 2 East towards Colchester/Norwich. Take exit number 13 (Rte 66). Turn LEFT Rte 66 and follow to the light several miles down the road. At the light take a left onto Rte 85. Lions Fairgrounds will be on the LEFT. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FROM NEW LONDON Take Rte 85 Nth towards Hartford. Turn LEFT onto Rte 82/East Haddam Rd. Take Rte 11 North towards Hartford/ Colchester. Merge with Rte 2 West. Take the Rte 16 exit, exit number 18, towards Colchester / Middletown. Take a RIGHT onto Rte 16 East. Take a LEFT onto Rte 85 North. Follow Rte 85 Nth across Rte 85 and Rte 66 intersection. Lions Fairgrounds will be on the LEFT. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FROM PUTNAM Take I 395 Sth to Exit 91 (Rte 6 W). Follow Rte 6 W to Rte 66 W (Willimantic). Follow Rte 66 W to Hebron CT. Turn right on 66 W to Rte 85. Follow signs to Hebron Fairgrounds on Left about 3 miles down road. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For more about Renaissance Faires: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.renfaire.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.renfaire.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

www.renfaire.com/ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

And &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.renaissancemagazine.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.renaissancemagazine.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

www.renaissancemagazine.com/ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This magazine can be purchased at such locations as Barnes &amp;amp; Noble and Other Bookstores. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.ctfaire.com/fall/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=57&amp;amp;Itemid=64" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ctfaire.com/fall/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=57&amp;amp;Itemid=64&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

www.ctfaire.com/fall/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=57&amp;amp;Itemid=64 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For those who ask what kind of Coffee Will Be At The Meet Up?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I usually drink Coffee at restaurants on the way to the MU, not there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do not remember seeing coffee at this MU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be other Coffee MU in September and October before this MU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike B&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee Talk Organizer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have purple backpack.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318865847000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Coffee Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>coffee-397</urlname><id>570343</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Coffee Talk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314069288000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CTattends as King Arthur visits Hebron Renaissance Faire</name><id>30525781</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318095000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/coffee-397/events/30525781/</event_url></item>