<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Prospect Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366140</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>617-576-1253</phone><name>Improv Boston Cabaret</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>536120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103380</lon></venue><fee><label>Ticket for Adults</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come one come all to Improv Boston where you organizers: Sandy, Ben, Barbara and maybe Jason?? will be trying their hand, (making their debut) in the forum of Sketchprov.  As the name  gives away it is a combination of Improv and Sketch Comedy.  No we've never done it before.  Yes, we thrilled. We'd be happier if you were in the audience.  &lt;a href="http://www.improvboston.com/webcalendar/view_entry.php?id=96" target="_blank"&gt;Link to SketchHaus &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the T&lt;br /&gt;ImprovBoston is conveniently located just a few hundred feet from the&lt;br /&gt;Central Square T station. Take the Red Line to Central Square Station.&lt;br /&gt;Walk north on Prospect Street past the Starbucks and The Field (an&lt;br /&gt;Irish Pub). ImprovBoston is about 200 feet from the corner of Prospect&lt;br /&gt;St. and Mass Ave. on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 93 Northbound/Southbound&lt;br /&gt;Take the Storrow Drive exit towards Cambridge. Continue on Storrow&lt;br /&gt;Drive to Mass Ave. Make a right on Mass Ave (the only way you can go)&lt;br /&gt;and drive across the bridge into Cambridge. Go past MIT and through&lt;br /&gt;Central Square to Prospect St. Make a right on Propsect St.&lt;br /&gt;ImprovBoston is about 200 feet from the intersection of Mass Ave. and&lt;br /&gt;Prospect St. on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Mass Pike (Rte. 90)&lt;br /&gt;Take the Cambridge/Allston exit. Stay to the right as you exit and&lt;br /&gt;follow the road over the bridge into Cambridge. Continue straight on&lt;br /&gt;River Street through Central Square (crossing Mass Ave.). River Street&lt;br /&gt;now becomes Prospect Street. ImprovBoston about 200 feet from the&lt;br /&gt;intersection of Mass Ave. and Prospect St. on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Central Square has ample parking (metered spaces, public lots, a City&lt;br /&gt;garage), but can get congested, especially on weekends, so leave&lt;br /&gt;yourself 20-30 minutes to find a space. There is metered parking&lt;br /&gt;($0.25 / half hour until 6 PM Monday - Saturday) on most of the&lt;br /&gt;streets surrounding ImprovBoston. Do NOT park in residential spaces&lt;br /&gt;(except on Sundays) or you will be certainly ticketed and possibly&lt;br /&gt;towed. There are three public lots (metered parking at $0.25 / half&lt;br /&gt;hour until 6 PM Monday - Saturday) accessible from Bishop Allen Dr.&lt;br /&gt;The lot near Douglass St. is the largest. The Green Street Garage has&lt;br /&gt;the largest number of spaces and offers very reasonable rates (open 24&lt;br /&gt;hours, $1 / hour, daily maximum $13, $5 night rate).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the stage performing :-) If you are in the audience then I hope you'll be able to find us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy Blackman</member_name><member_id>4979909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206492696000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Watch you organizers at work in a venue other then the 4th floor of the porter exchange, as we attempt to make you laugh.</why><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204866933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SketchProv @ SketchHaus 3/7</name><id>7482791</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204936200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/7482791/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/6/global_1667606.jpeg</photo_url></item>