<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please note that this month our meeting has been moved out by one week to April 22. I will be away the week of April 12-18, and asked the Library to schedule us for the following week. Please mark your calendars accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to think everyone is trading successfully right now, but I know that is not the case. The market is full of fear and high anxiety right now. There's a lack of confidence in our economy and much concern about what will/will not happen next. It's during times like these that we need to be most alert and very reactive on our feet in order to minimize the losses and stay in the game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With that in mind, I'd like each attendee to bring some thoughts to the meeting regarding things that make them comfortable or uncomfortable in this market environment. What areas of your trading give you the most difficulty? Which areas do you feel most comfortable with and why? What do feel are your weakest and/or strongest points in trading? Where do you feel you could benefit most from some mentoring and/or group discussion? Do you have (and do you use) an entry strategy, exit strategy, prtocective strategy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have just returned from a 5-day Trading Convention/Cruise in the Western Caribbean, and will highlight a few bits and pieces learned from that. Beyond that, my thoughts are to conduct an impromtu discussion regarding some ways one might profit from today's market environment, and to address any issues individual members might like to open for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this meeting is after-hours, we are free to use the Library's parking lot. Our meeting room is downstairs and just to the right of the staircase (the Peace Dale Room).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newcomers are certainly welcome, so  if you know of others who might be interested in joining us, please refer them to this site or just bring them along to the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there! &lt;br /&gt;Ray&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy working the laptop &amp; projector set up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Dreczko</member_name><member_id>4521820</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242859227000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>IBD Enthusiasts and Traders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ibd-739</urlname><id>559772</id><group_lat>41.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237418095000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum April Meetup</name><id>9983857</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240437600000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ibd-739/events/9983857/</event_url></item>