<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On Labor Day (Monday Sep 6) there will be an outdoor volleyball QK doubles event. This is a friendship tournament event meetup that consists of reverse coed doubles matches played in a King-Queen format, meaning that you will be playing with and against different people during pool play. Top players after pool play will compete in a playoff format.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a friendship tournament format, meaning call your own faults, as there are no referees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be using the ruleset listed in the first post on the following URL: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/messages/boards/thread/8548572?thread=8548572"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The events will start at 10:30 AM and will likely last at least until the mid afternoon (~3 PM). If you would like to play in this event you must commit to staying at least through the end of pool play. Remember to bring snacks/food and water/beverages, as this event will involve a significant amount of volleyball play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is intended for players with experience playing reverse coed doubles format. Signup for these events is a little different. To sign up, please send me an email using the following link on meetup: &lt;a href="http://volleyball.meetup.com/122/message/?recipientId=4774008"&gt;http://volleyball.mee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the email, provide the following information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Name&lt;br /&gt;Gender&lt;br /&gt;Email address&lt;br /&gt;Cell phone number&lt;br /&gt;Outdoor rating (AA/A/BB/B), if you have one; otherwise, short description of reverse coed doubles experience&lt;br /&gt;Confirm that you have read the ruleset at the link above and that you agree to play by those rules.&lt;br /&gt;Confirm that you can commit to play from 10:30 AM to 3 PM.&lt;br /&gt;Signup partner name (if you have a signup partner)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Preferably, each player in a signup pair should send an email. Preference is given to AA/A players who sign up in male/female pairs, although some single signups will be allowed.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Lee</member_name><member_id>4774008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283865824000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283126048000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Outdoor Doubles (QK)</name><id>14584316</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283783400000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/14584316/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/3/global_1997523.jpeg</photo_url></item>