<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>409 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.355735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Pierce Boathouse</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>964616</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I just discovered that there is an Azorean Portuguese Whaleboat Regatta on the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;This should be a very pleasant event especially if the weather is nice.&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet at MIT Pierce Boathouse at 2pm and watch the whale boats. Then we can walk a bit along the river and for those who would like to continue the outing, we go out to eat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if anyone would like to meet before the event. &lt;br /&gt;I would be willing to meet people before at a coffee shop or after the regatta for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;___________________________________&lt;br /&gt;One of the most outstanding events of the Festival is back with keen crews and at least as much enthusiasm as in previous years. &lt;br /&gt;The Azorean Whaleboats Regatta on the Charles River will be hosted by the Azorean Maritime Heritage Society - owner of the whaling boats that will be used - in conjunction with the MIT Rowing Club and the MIT Dept of Athletics, Physical Education &amp;amp; Recreation. &lt;br /&gt;It will bring together whaleboat rowing crews from New Bedford, Hudson, Lowell, Gloucester, Peabody and other MA communities, as well as the MIT Rowing Crews.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will also be an opportunity for the public to learn more about Azorean-Portuguese history, its centuries-old ties with New England whaling, and one of the most remarkable boat designs of the Northern Atlantic. &lt;br /&gt;These sea-going boats have a complete sailing rig, of great visual effect, used in the whaling days for longer distances in order to quietly get to the proximity of the groups of whales, and were then rowed for the final approximation. &lt;br /&gt;They are extremely efficient due to their slim cross section (for a sea-faring craft), and are rowed by a crew of 6 plus skipper.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The first New England whaler to stop at the Azores did so about 1730, and by 1750 Azorean crews were being taken. This went on for 175 years ending in 1921 when the last whaler appeared. In 1780, as many as 200 whaling ships could be found in the Azores picking up crew members. Not only did the ships stop at the Azores for crews, they also collected supplies, and repairs were made. Some would deposit the whale oil and bones for shipment to New Bedford. Once an Azorean sailor arrived in Massachusetts, he would often find work in the local area. Some would travel to California either by land or on another whaling ship. Sometimes the Azorean would return home to the islands for a visit or to bring his wife and children back to the United States. Those who stayed in the New Bedford area, could find jobs on shore in many of the whaling-related industries. There were whale oil refineries, cooper shops, toolworks, and processing plants. Soon Southern New England became populated with Azoreans, and they could be found living in Nantucket, Martha’s Vineyard, Cape Cod, Gloucester, Boston, and Providence to name a few locations.” (Robert L. Santos, In Azorean and New England Whaling and Fishing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions and practical information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The regatta takes place to the west of Harvard Bridge (Mass. Ave), between the bridge and the MIT Pierce Boathouse (*), running along Memorial Dr. (see interactive map below). The best vantage point to enjoy the regatta is the Boathouse, which is freely accessible on the day. The Cambridge end of Harvard Bridge affords good close-up views of the race starting area. The event is usually completed with a sailing demonstration using the whaleboats’s spectacular full sailing rig. This takes place west of the bridge, between the boathouse and the south bank (Boston side).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonportuguesefestival.org/bpf/2009/04/04/azorean-whaleboats/" target="_blank"&gt;(*) not to be mistaken with the MIT Wood Sailing Pavillion (bldg.51), which is located to the east of Mass.Ave.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonportuguesefestival.org/bpf/2009/04/04/azorean-whaleboats/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonportugue...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244940114000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242878451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Azorean Whaleboat Regatta </name><id>10460563</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244397600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/10460563/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/5/global_8731077.jpeg</photo_url></item>