<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 William Day Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>venuecity444</zip><lat>42.329948</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Carson Beach</name><city>South Boston</city><id>703507</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.044823</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Exactly one year later we're back at Carson Beach for more outdoor SoJust fun.  We'll be there from 11am-2pm(ish), so stop by anytime.  We'll be the gaggle of folks having fun and wearing nametags!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us and you'll get the chance to meet our new intern, Monica. She and SoJust regulars will be on hand to meet newcomers.  Plan ahead and bring snacks or get something at the snack bar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is definitely a family-friendly beach and dogs are welcome too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Never been to Carson? &lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborwalk.com/placestogo/location.php?nid=6&amp;amp;sid=45" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;* Subway: Take the Red Line to JFK/UMass.  Exit the station to your right.  Take the second exit of the rotary (or go straight through) and walk towards the beach.&lt;br /&gt;* Public Parking: Free public parking is available.&lt;br /&gt;* Bus: Take MBTA Route 5, 8, 11, 16, or 41.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the website - just click '&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/"&gt;Messages&lt;/a&gt;'.  The &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/calendar"&gt;SoJust Calendar&lt;/a&gt; is packed with social justice-related events held throughout Greater Boston.  Help us keep it filled - tell us about events you hear about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From our FAQs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;It's not very easy for me to meet new people and I'm not really one for small talk.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hear you. That's why at SoJust events, in addition to traditional name tags, we have &amp;quot;Ask Me About&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Looking For&amp;quot; tags. That way you can slap whatever you're into lately up on your shirt and wait for fellow SoJusters to approach you. These seem to do the trick of moving past the basic &amp;quot;what do you do for work? where do you live?&amp;quot; questions to conversations that lead to more substantial connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;What actually happens at events?&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll always be greeted by friendly folks who can help get you socializing, introduce you to people, and chat with you about questions or wishes. It's likely a few people will be there promoting their campaigns and issues (&lt;i&gt;yes, SoJust welcomes that sort of behavior&lt;/i&gt;). At our bigger events, there's always a literature table to toss down flyers, postcards, and other paraphenalia about events around town. Most importantly, we can pretty much guarantee there will be someone there you've never met before. As one of our members said, &amp;quot;You are bringing together people who might never get together otherwise - if that ain't a step towards justice I don't know what is.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt;  and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248026054000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245895374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beaching for Justice</name><id>10730468</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247410800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/10730468/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/a/global_9330954.jpeg</photo_url></item>