<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for another beautiful night of shirts and skins frisbee.  We'll be meeting at 8PM at the Cambridge Common baseball diamond which is located a couple blocks north of Harvard Square. We generally play from 8-10PM and then go out for food and drinks. Before attending our events, please review our &lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/350/about/"&gt;About Us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd recommend you bring a light-colored shirt for visibility's sake and a change of clothes. We supply all of the equipment necessary so there's really nothing else you need to bring besides your smiling face.  Which should look like this &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/crying.gif' border='0' alt='crying' /&gt; now that I'm leaving.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Organizers pay out of pocket for the frisbees, lanyards, glowsticks, field cones and first aid kits. Please consider bringing a couple bucks or visiting our &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/IRMLHWE8OGKZ"&gt;Amazon Wishlist&lt;/a&gt; to support our equipment costs. Our group is free and will always be that way but your optional donations are certainly appreciated! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP as space is very limited at Cambridge Commons. We're anticipating a lot of players now that the weather is nice and it's extremely helpful for us to know how many players to expect.  For now, we'd prefer not to enforce any sort of &amp;quot;you can't play if you don't RSVP&amp;quot; rule--but such a thing may be on the horizon. Our top two priorities are safety and fun, and neither is served well if 90 players show up when we expected 25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=10+garden+st+cambridge+ma&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=33.626896,81.738281&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.376807,-71.119566&amp;amp;spn=0.007656,0.019956&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;Cambridge Commons Map&lt;/a&gt;. Parking at Cambridge Common's is tricky and we highly recommend you take the &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; to Harvard Square. If you have any questions about our group, please don't hesitate to contact our Organizers!  Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Chea</member_name><member_id>4415505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Baz</member_name><member_id>4845259</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209431926000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><why>Because we'll be playing shirts and skins.</why><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208629108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jim's Ultimate Last Stand - Cambridge Commons</name><id>7770250</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208908800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7770250/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/c/global_3460060.jpeg</photo_url></item>