<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Lets enjoy the beauty of the seashore before it gets too crowded, and while horses and dogs are still allowed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.5 miles of trails traverse dunes and track the beachfront on both the Ipswich Bay and Essex River Estuary sides of the Castle Neck peninsula.  Moderate hiking. These trails are part of the Bay Circuit Trail. Some of the trails are on boardwalks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a $7 per car fee for non-members (of the Trustees) at this time of year, so carpooling is a good idea.  Use your rsvp to arrange carpoolong or to ask for a ride if you need one. Expect to be leaving Ipswich at 2:30 or 3 for the ride home after lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet near the Crane Beach bathhouses. From Route 128 north (towards Gloucester), take exit 20A (Route 1A north) and follow for 8 miles to Ipswich. Turn right onto Route 133 east and follow for 1.5 miles. Turn left onto Northgate Road and follow for .5 mi. Turn right onto Argilla Road and follow for 2.5 miles to Crane Beach gatehouse at end of paved road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the area:&lt;br /&gt;Along with Castle Hill and the Crane Wildlife Refuge, Crane Beach was once part of the vast early 20th-century summer estate of Chicago industrialist Richard T. Crane, Jr. The white sands of Crane Beach stretch for miles along both sides of Castle Neck, forming one of the most picturesque swimming beaches in all of New England. Crane Beach also provides important habitat for myriad wildlife and is an important natural barrier that protects the Essex River Estuary and its inland communities.&lt;br /&gt;More than 1,200 acres of beachfront, dunes, and maritime forest are managed for both recreation and conservation. Elevated boardwalks, vegetation management programs, and fencing protect the dunes. More than five miles of designated trails traverse an extensive dune complex featuring swales that support amphibians and invertebrates. Cranberries and insect-eating carnivorous plants, such as sundews, also grow in these interdunal swales. Castle Neck is the site of the North Shore's largest maritime pitch pine forest.&lt;br /&gt;Crane Beach is among the world's most important nesting sites for the threatened piping plover, a once- common bird that was nearly hunted to extinction in the nineteenth century for its eggs and its feathers. Recent surveys place the piping plover population at only 1,300 pairs. Crane Beach has been nationally recognized for its successful shorebird protection program. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Dog walking is permitted October 1 to March 31. Dogs must be on leash at all times and walk only on beachfront below the high tide line. &lt;br /&gt;*** Horseback riding is permitted October 1 to March 31.&lt;br /&gt;*** For the off-season there are portable toilets located outside the bathhouses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map showing the bathhouses is available at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/pages/294_crane_beach.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Telephone:&lt;br /&gt;978-356-4354 &lt;br /&gt;E-mail:&lt;br /&gt;castlehill@ttor.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will have lunch at the Choate Bridge Pub.&lt;br /&gt;3 South Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Ipswich 01938&lt;br /&gt;978-356-2931&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ipswichma.com/choatepub/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ipswichma....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175374901000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173298404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crane Beach walk</name><id>5546422</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174748400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5546422/</event_url></item>