<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What: A reading of the letters of John and Abigail Adams by Senator and Mrs. Ted Kennedy and Governor and Mrs. Deval Patrick&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Monday, November 19, 2007 at 7 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Faneuil Hall, Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.masshist.org/welcome/" target="_blank"&gt;Massachusetts Historical Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: CMF members; meet at 6:30 at the door to reserve the best seats available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Massachusetts Historical Society will celebrate the publication by Harvard University Press of My Dearest Friend: Letters of Abigail and John Adams, a new edition of this important correspondence, the original manuscripts of which are housed at the Historical Society. To mark the occasion they have reserved Faneuil Hall for a free public event: a reading of selected Adams letters hosted by Mary Richardson, WCVB-TV5. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several contemporary couples who understand the challenges and sacrifices of public service, including Senator and Mrs. Edward Kennedy, Governor and Mrs. Deval Patrick, and former Governor and Mrs. Michael Dukakis will be on hand to read the extraordinarily moving words about the founding of our nation and John and Abigail's lifelong devotion to one another. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the days before the telegraph, telephone, or Internet, the only way John and Abigail Adams could keep in touch was through letters, and the immediacy of their correspondence makes this history at its most engaging and authentic. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the first collection of their letters that is selected from the entire forty years span of their correspondence (which coincides with the most important period in American history) and includes several letters never before published.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1774 John Adams recognized that they lived &amp;quot;in an age of tryal&amp;quot; and asked Abigail Adams  &amp;quot;to take part with me in the struggle.&amp;quot; She as always responded with support and encouragement &amp;quot;I long impatiently to have you upon the stage of action.&amp;quot;  The letters printed in this book and the readings selected for this event reveal, not only the quarter century JA devoted to public service, but the important and intimate relationship with AA that sustained him during the era of revolution and nation building in which he participated. The letters also reveal the domestic side of the relationship that is unique among the records of the founding generation. In short these are the letters of the best-known husband and wife partnership in American history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: The event is free and open to the public&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195690231000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194559634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading: The letters of John and Abigail Adams </name><id>6704612</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195516800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/6704612/</event_url></item>