<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Atheneum Square north</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.764014</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>871547</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.673404</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For those interested-&lt;br /&gt;While not a German-language event, this is posted for those who might be interested.  It is free and should be very interesting.&lt;br /&gt;Those who want to can go out for ein Bier after at nearby pub!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;LECTURE and FILM: Looted European Art: The Hermann Goering Collection&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday Apr 7, 09 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Docent Memorial Lecture: Looted European Art: The Hermann Goering Collection, by Nancy Yeide, Head, Department of Curatorial Records, National Gallery of Art&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lecture at 6:00 pm, followed by screening of the film, The Rape of Europa in the Aetna Theater&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Docent Council of the Wadsworth Atheneum Museum of Art&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among the Nazi elite, the art collection of Hermann Goering was second in importance only to that assembled for Hitler. Yeide will give an overview of Goering’s collecting within the context of Nazi art looting, describe the nature of the collection and its post-war disposition, and discuss provenance issues in museums today. The lecture will be followed by a screening of the 2007 film, The Rape of Europa, about the theft, destruction, and miraculous survival of many of Europe’s artistic treasures during World War II.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in downstairs lobby- look for Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239923818000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Deutsch speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>german-425</urlname><id>438488</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford German Kaffeeklatsch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233892158000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wadsworth Atheneum lecture &amp; free film</name><id>9685007</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239141600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/german-425/events/9685007/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/b/b/global_3413819.jpeg</photo_url></item>