<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 110</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.561600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kimball's Farm</name><city>Westford</city><id>325218</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431396</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What more could you ask for??? :-)&lt;br /&gt;    Let's go to Cruise Night at Kimball's Farm in Westford!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Kimball's hosts Cruise Night, with as many as 350 cars ranging from Corvettes to Model A's. The now famous &amp;quot;Ultimate Cruise Night&amp;quot; offers the additional excitement of live local band entertainment, the delicious Kimball Farm BBQ grill, and the Legendary Ice Cream Buffet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    On this evening the John Penny Band will be playing from 5-9 PM.&lt;br /&gt;    Voted Best Country Band by MA Country Music Association in 1995, 1996, 1997 and 1998.&lt;br /&gt;    The John Penny Band is a five piece country band with two guitars, bass, keyboards, and drums. All five members sing lead and backup vocals. Their repertoire consists of contemporary and traditional country music plus some pop standards and some oldies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Come on...dust off your cowboy hat, bring a beach chair, (maybe some bug spray) and let's just laugh and have some fun together! What better way is there to spend a Summer evening. Admission for the general public is $3.00 for adults. If enough people respond I will be sure to come up with a creative way for you to find us!!! If it rains I will post an alternate meeting place that afternoon, so...Say YES!!!! Awe, come on...just do it!&lt;br /&gt;    ;0)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185661861000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184711812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BBQ, Ice Cream, Old Cars, Country Music and Great Company!!!</name><id>6038034</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185489000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/6038034/</event_url></item>