<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A Social Fun favorite! Let’s go back to Brother’s Kouzina in Peabody MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located just 15 minutes from Boston on Route 1 North in Peabody, Brother’s Kouzina offers traditional Greek dishes as well as a wide array of Mediterranean food. Menu selections are prepared with ingredients that exemplify freshness and flavor. Brother’s Kouzina offers an elegant yet relaxed setting for our guests to enjoy their meals. Our family has created a comfortable atmosphere that will make our guests seem as if they are members of our family. The authentic Greek recipes that we’ve applied, has allowed us to serve exceptional food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy, who is the original founder of the Brother’s Deli Restaurants, has been preparing classic Greek dishes for over 40 years. At the age of 18 he opened his first restaurant in his hometown of Kalamata Greece. He has a long history of serving traditional Greek food in the Boston area since his first American based restaurant in 1972. The number one goal for Jimmy and the rest of the Christopher family, has always been to serve the best quality food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner menu: &lt;a href="http://www.brotherskouzina.com/dinner.htm"&gt;http://www.brotherskouzina.com/dinner.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the website at:&lt;a href="http://www.brotherskouzina.com/index.htm"&gt;http://www.brotherskouzina.com/index.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very easy to get to off Route 1 in Peabody.(Route 1 North) 25 Newbury Street Peabody, MA. Everyone is in charge of their own bill/tip and I will try to arrange that we have separate checks. I am limiting this one to 15 people since that was what we had the last time and it made it easier to talk/get to know each other. Please do not take up a spot unless you know you can attend. I will have a waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snow cancels this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Driving only: Not T accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Hostess station</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Phaedra</member_name><member_id>3140926</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1355224476000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352661289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Dinner: Brother’s Kouzina in Peabody MA</name><id>90944172</id><headcount>14</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355182200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/90944172/</event_url></item>