<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>75.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ever considered rock climbing? Well this is your chance! Join other Wedelns and plenty of friends for a weekend at the Wedeln Ski House and a day of fun at one of the local climbing hot spots (chosen by our guides from EMS)! This event is geared for all levels of climbers. If you have never strapped on a harness before, that's fine, we have beginner-level guides ready to teach you the basics. If you're already at a 5.9 level, that's fine too, we have multi-pitch climbs accessible as well. There's something for everyone and no one will be left out! Even advanced climbers enjoy the easy stuff every now and again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weekend will look something like this: We'll gather together Friday night to hang out, then head out early Saturday morning for a full-day of rock climbing in the White Mountains. After swinging from ropes and using muscles we din't even know we had, we'll head back to the Wedeln house for dinner, drinks and socializing. If the weather permits, we'll build a bonfire outside and relax. OR, we might be able to head down the street and enjoy a live band at one of our sister clubs! Sunday will be a day of choice, with options for hikes, bike rides or just checking out the local area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Schedule:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday:&lt;/b&gt; Arrive at the Wedeln Ski House anytime after 7:00pm. Beer and wine available while socializing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfast provided at Wedeln. Head out at 8:00am to arrive at EMS by 8:30. Rock climb all day, arriving home around 4:30ish. Dinner Saturday night will begin around 5:30 or 6. Beer and wine will be included. Bonfire or live band at the Makusue Ski Club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfast at Wedeln followed by hiking, exploring, etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pricing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Food:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfasts = $5, Dinner Saturday night = $15 (includes beer and wine at dinner only)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Climbing:&lt;/b&gt; The ratio of climbers to guides if 5:1 for top-roping (beginner) and 3:1 for multi-pitch (intermediate). Each guide costs $350 regardless of how many climbers we have out of that 5, so pricing will vary depending on how many people we get. I would estimate that we will certainly be able to reach full capacity, so climbing costs will be somewhere in the area of $70, and upwards from there depending on number of people and if other wants to do multi-pitch climbing ($117 per person).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lodging:&lt;/b&gt; $20 per night.  21+, no kids, no pets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Band Party:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; This will be $20. This includes both the band for the night and beer, wine and hard alcohol. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My name is Audra and I am a member of the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club. I joined the club after attending the rock climbing weekend two years ago... and I hope you will too!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the girl behind the bar checking everyone in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Audra</member_name><member_id>5480374</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254869804000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251460663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wedeln Rock Climbing Weekend</name><id>11223198</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254571200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/11223198/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_10437793.jpeg</photo_url></item>