<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Typical coffee tab</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Latest iteration of the Dire Literary Series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Riippi was born in Seattle and lives in New York City, where he is getting his MFA at City College. His essays and stories have appeared in The Brooklyn Rail, New Delta Review, Salamander, Soon Quarterly, The Bitter Oleander, and others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Darcie Dennigan was a 2007 Discovery/The Nation winner. Her first poetry collection, Corinna A-Maying the Apocalypse, will be published in February 2008. She lives in Los Angeles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hannah Baker-Siroty has studied writing at The University of Wisconsin, Madison (B.A.) and Sarah Lawrence College (M.F.A.). She has worked for DoubleTake Magazine and was an editor of The Madison Review. A former emerging writer fellow at The Writers' Room of Boston her poetry has appeared in Lumina ,the anthology Earshot: the First Offenders, and online at RantArt.com and stopbuyingstuffmagazine.com. She is currently working on her first collection of poems and teaches writing at Pine Manor College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Gager is the author of eight books of fiction and poetry. His latest, Treating a Sick Animal, Flash and Micro Fictions, was released by Cervena Barva Press.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265591019000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262999025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Riippi, Dennigan, Baker-Siroty, and Gager at Out of the Blue Gallery</name><id>jnhtyndbhb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265418000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/12265706/</event_url></item>