<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bear Mountain State Park</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10911</zip><lat>41.310000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>845-786-2701</phone><name>Bear Mountain Inn</name><city>Bear Mountain</city><id>1363141</id><country>us</country><lon>-74.000000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a full day trip to hike 6 beautiful miles of moderate to higher effort (steep) on Bear Mountain in Bear Mountain State Park in southern New York. This state park is along the Hudson River in Rockland County, NY. Carpool leaves 7 AM, E. Windsor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pack a hearty trail lunch and a quart of water for this trip. Hiking boots are required as well as warm layered clothing so layers can be removed as you warm up on the hike. A pack is strongly advised to store your lunch and layers removed. Your hands need to be free for the hike. Carpool (limited capacity) from Hartford area leaves 7 AM, group for hike meets at park at 9:30 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The view is dramatic starting with the Hudson River valley as we approach the park. The valley is a fjord at this point, deepened by glaciers long ago. The mountains on either side of the river are over 1,000 feet in altitude and they rise about that much above the river. We cross Bear Mountain Bridge over the Hudson with our vehicles and the view is wonderful up and down the valley from such a high path. We'll park at the Bear Mountain Inn (closed for renovation though) and wait for the gathering of hike participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll hike a small portion of the Appalachian Trail from the Inn up to the peak of Bear Mtn. The gain in altitude is roughly a respectable 1,100 feet in 1.75 miles of hiking. Generous time has been allotted for the ascent (up to 2 hours) and it is not recommended for those with heart or breathing issues. At the peak we'll temporarily pass the Perkins Memorial Tower to reach the true peak of the mountain a little further on. We then backtrack to eat our packed in lunch at a picnic area. After lunch we backtrack a little more to the tower to check it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We then start out decent, still on the Appalachian Trail until we intersect with a Red blazed trail in a small valley and start heading southeast. We'll intersect a Yellow blazed trail and take that around a swampy area and up a couple hundred feet on a shoulder of Bear Mountain as we make our way northeast. Once over the shoulder we descend and intersect a portion of the Appalachian Trail we used for the ascent and return to the Inn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many interesting amenities and views in the area of the Inn we'll have about an hour of free time to check out (see below). We will stop to get something to eat after the hike on the way hime. Please bring enough cash to facilitate paying the check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you carpool, please chip in a fair share for the ride. Parking fee, if in effect, is $6/car. Bridge toll to leave the park (to east) is $1/car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:&lt;br /&gt;+ 1,100 ft total gain in altitude to peek (160 ft at start - 1,284 feet at peak).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 AM Carpool leaves E. Windsor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 9:30 AM Arrive and park at the Bear Mtn. Inn parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 10:00 AM Start hike up Bear Mtn. via AT trail (alt 160 ft)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 12:15 PM Reach actual peak (alt 1,284 ft), have lunch, and check out tower&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 1:00 PM Hike down on AT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 1:45 PM Intersection with Red trail, take it to SE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 2:10 PM Intersection with Yellow trail, take it to NE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 3:15 PM Back to start by Inn (6 mi, alt 160 ft). Suggestions: Outdoor Skating Rink; Marry-Go-round ($1 ride); Zoo &amp;amp; small museum; Inn, lake, buildings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 4:30 PM Assembled for dinner trip (we could head home at this time)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 5:30 PM Start back to CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 8:00 PM Arrive back at carpool start in CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions via MapQuest (entrance actually off of Seven Lakes Dr., zoom in to see, look at arial view):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/Bear+Mountain+NY/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MORE INFORMATION:&lt;br /&gt;Bear Mountain State Park:&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://www.hudsonriver.com/bearmtn.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hudsonrive...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://www.friendsofpalisades.org/content.php?mode=parks&amp;amp;object_id=5" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.friendsofp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://3dparks.wr.usgs.gov/nyc/parks/loc9.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://3dparks.wr.usg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor **leaving** at a 7 AM for those interested. There will be a blue Dodge Grandcaravan Sport. Return at about 8 PM. It is advised to call Kevin (number in RSVP) so he knows you plan to carpool. Approximate location/directions for the carpool meet-up can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/69+Prospect+Hill+Rd+East+Windsor+CT+06088-3600/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location or at the carpool location in E. Windsor, CT (call Kevin S cell in his RSVP if you want to carpool ASAP or e-mail by midnight tonight 3/20/08 -see below).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206270789000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Let's get out of CT to see another beautiful area of mountains! A great view of the Hudson River and surrounding mountains too! To top it off, a zoo, museum, carousel, and outdoor skating rink.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206016724000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Bear Mountain State Park, NY</name><id>7569036</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206097200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7569036/</event_url></item>