<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This only meetup in Boston that brings together nonprofits and businesses to work on collaboration and partnerships in an informative and fun format. We will be having a short presentation followed by discussion on how it can benefit your organization. Every month we bring one local nonprofit into the spotlight and all the donations go directly to the organization. The spotlight nonprofit will be Boxxout (&lt;a href="http://www.boxxout.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boxxout.or...&lt;/a&gt;) for our next meetup. Vlora has also provided a special menu for the group. Look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12-12:30pm - Networking with food and drink&lt;br /&gt;12:30;1:45pm - Short introductions, Boxxout (&lt;a href="http://www.boxxout.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boxxout.or...&lt;/a&gt;) will be our monthly nonprofit spotlight, followed by a presentation on cause marketing by Joe Waters and Joanna MacDonald.&lt;br /&gt;1:45-2pm - More Networking and collaborating&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Waters and Joanna MacDonald started the cause marketing program at Boston Medical Center in 2004. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe and Joanna has developed and executed cause marketing programs with many local and national companies, including iParty, Staples, Shaw`s Supermarkets, H. P. Hood, Zipcar, Fuddruckers, Virgin America, Fidelity Investments, National Amusements, Finagle A Bagel, Boston Bruins, Papa Gino's, Ocean State Job Lots, Tedeschi Food Shops, Valvoline Instant Oil Change and Pepsi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With iParty, Joe and Joanna were part of the original team that founded BMC's Halloween Town. In 2009, Halloween Town had 38 corporate sponsors and 14,000 attendees at the two-day event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A well known speaker on the intersection of business, philanthropy and marketing, Joe spoke most recently at the annual Run, Walk, Ride conference in Dallas, TX on &amp;quot;Selling Local Sponsorships.&amp;quot; He has also spoken at Cause Marketing Forum's annual conference on &amp;quot;The Power of Pinups,&amp;quot; which covered developing a lucrative point-of-sale cause marketing program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe blogs on cause marketing at &lt;a href="http://www.Selfishgiving.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Selfishgiv...&lt;/a&gt;. He and Joanna are the founders of &lt;a href="http://www.Sixfigurecausemarketing.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Sixfigurec...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PS. Remember to bring your own name tag this will help brand your organization more effectively.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsors of the event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Nonprofit Career Coach a division of Jobs In Nonprofits (&lt;a href="http://www.thenonprofitcareercoach.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thenonprof...&lt;/a&gt;) and Vlora Restaurant (www.vloraboston.com)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a name tag - Bring your own name tag please!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark McCurdy, NGO Career Coach</member_name><member_id>4242482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260468939000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Impact Community</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Social-Impact-Community</urlname><id>1383232</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Social Impact Success Community Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256749600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Impact Circle December Meetup</name><id>qcxqlymqblb</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260295200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Social-Impact-Community/events/11733250/</event_url></item>