<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1080 Chapel Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.308068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-432-2800</phone><name>Yale Center ForThe British Arts</name><city>New Haven</city><id>869091</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.930590</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt; Seeing Double: Portraits, Copies, and Exhibitions in 1820s London&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Yale Center For the British Arts&lt;br /&gt;Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1829, the young artist John Scarlett Davis sought to make a splash on the London art scene with his painting, Interior of the British Institution. An image of an art exhibition, the painting is also an elaborate visual puzzle. Seeing Double: Portraits, Copies and Exhibitions in 1820s London invites viewers to decode this puzzle and in the process explore the relationship between display and replication in early nineteenth-century Britain. Davis's painting has long been recognized as a valuable record of an early nineteenth-century exhibition venue, representing in miniature works by Sir Joshua Reynolds and Thomas Gainsborough, among others. What has less often been recognized is that the figures who chat amiably or stoop to examine canvases are themselves replicas of paintings: Davis copied the figures from pre-existing portraits, notably by Sir Thomas Lawrence. By examining this practice, the exhibition reveals hitherto unknown connections between works in the Center's collection. Seeing Double has been organized by the Yale Center for British Art and curated by Catherine Roach, Postdoctoral Associate, Department of the History of Art, Cornell University. The organizing curator at the Center is Cassandra Albinson, Associate Curator of Paintings and Sculpture. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited spaces are available for a small fee at the centers parking lot across from the Chapel York Garage. Metered street parking and public garages near the museum offer additional spots.There is also indoor paid parking at the Chapel-York Garage on York Stree&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Krista in the lobby at 2:00</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Krista</member_name><member_id>8471076</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283813021000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283218758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Seeing Double</name><id>14598957</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283623200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14598957/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/c/global_17609340.jpeg</photo_url></item>