<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Only rush seats are still available for this film.
We'll get in line early 4:00 - 4:30, depending on the weather and hope for the best.
'Sorry for the uncertainty surrounding this event.&amp;nbsp; It's the best we could do!
SYATM, Betsey
Promo from IFF Boston website:
What do you do when you get your dream job, only to lose it six months later? If you&amp;rsquo;re Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien, you get angry for a while&amp;hellip;and then you go to work. As he is contractually forbidden to be funny on TV, he mounts a live variety show and takes it on the road. The success of the venture is by no means guaranteed; after years of seeing him onscreen for free, will people pay to see him in the flesh?  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Anyone who was lucky enough to catch the tour when it hit the Wang Center last fall knows the answer to that question. But the Conan who emerges in this documentary is a surprising one indeed. Onstage, we see the familiar public figure: affable, quick witted, self-deprecating, wildly energetic, and intelligent. More revealing are the offstage scenes, which show the entertainer&amp;rsquo;s vulnerable side as he wrestles with the insecurity and exhaustion that a lengthy tour can induce. The flip side of the public&amp;rsquo;s adulation is that they are never satisfied, and the more thinly Conan is stretched, the further his patience is eroded.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;However, offstage or on, Conan&amp;rsquo;s mind is constantly working: he never misses an opportunity to squeeze a laugh from his audience, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a sold-out theater or just a handful of his trusted staff. And Rodman Flender&amp;rsquo;s camera catches it all.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It is impossible to not be inspired by O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s work ethic. He is a dervish, constantly striving to improve his performance. By providing unique insight into this critical transition point, CONAN O&amp;rsquo;BRIEN CAN&amp;rsquo;T STOP reminds us that endings are opportunities for new beginnings. It also is a side-splittingly funny documentary about one of the most hilarious and hard-working people in the industry.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;A portion of the ticket proceeds from this screening will benefit the Cardiology Clinical Research Fund at Boston Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.&lt;/em&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me in the ticket line holding our place.  After I get my ticket.  I'll wait in front of Simon's Shoes.   After purchasing tickets (or not) we'll decide where to celebrate or cry!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304544099000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>This is the last night of the IFF Boston and should be a fun way to end the festival whether or not you've seen other films or only (try to) see this one.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304386104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conan O'Brien Can't Stop Rush Tickets Line before 5:00 pm</name><id>17519674</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304539200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/17519674/</event_url></item>