<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Caps Ridge Trailhead (The south end of Jefferson Notch Rd. is located directly opposite Mt. Clinton Rd. at a crossroads on Base Rd. (the road that runs from US 302 to the Cog Railway)).&amp;nbsp; We will shuttle cars to the Valley Way Trailhead and start there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as possible. Criteria: NO WHINING, COMPLAINING, ETC. All hikers must be able to maintain a minimum pace of three miles an hour for a minimum of four hours. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;starting at Air Line Trailhead (Appalachia) and Valley Way Trailhead (Appalachia) Back to here hike 0.03 mi/1 min/+15 ft on the Air Line The Air Line and Valley Way Trails begin together at Appalachia and cross the Presidential Range Rail Trail to a fork near the edge of the power-line clearing, where the Air Line leads right and Valley Way left. to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+15 ft on the Air Line In 40 yd., just after the Air Line enters the woods, the Link diverges right. to the junction of The Amphibrach and The Link hike 0.15 mi/6 min/+58 ft on the Air Line The Air Line crosses the Sylvan Way. to the junction of Sylvan Way hike 0.40 mi/21 min/+300 ft on the Air Line The Air Line crosses the Beechwood Way and Beechwood Brook. to the junction of Beechwood Way hike 0.20 mi/11 min/+178 ft on the Beechwood Way Then the path crosses the Air Line at and ends at the Valley Way. to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+25 ft on the Valley Way The Valley Way leads nearer Snyder Brook and is soon joined from the right by the Beechwood Way. to the junction of The Brookside hike 0.03 mi/1 min/+13 ft on the The Brookside The Brookside leaves the Valley Way about 30 yd. above the Valley Way&amp;#146;s junction with the Beechwood Way, continuing straight where the Valley Way turns uphill to the right. to the junction of Randolph Path hike 0.01 mi/1 min/0 ft on the The Brookside The Brookside and the Randolph Path cross the brook together on large stepping-stones (the former bridge at this crossing was washed out in 2005 and will not be replaced). to the junction of Inlook Trail and Randolph Path hike 1.16 mi/1 hr 3 min/+871 ft on the The Brookside The Brookside recrosses the brook and climbs along the west bank at a moderate grade with good footing, rising well above the brook through a fine birch forest, with occasional views through the trees to cliffs on the valley wall on the other side of the brook. Returning gradually to brook level, it comes to the junction with the Kelton Trail, which enters from the left. to the junction of Kelton Trail hike 0.50 mi/30 min/+506 ft on the The Brookside Above this point, the Brookside becomes steeper and rougher (though recent intensive trail work has significantly improved the footing), and again runs close to the brook, passing Salmacis Fall (limited view north from the top). It continues along a wild and beautiful part of the brook, with cascades and mossy rocks in a fine forest. It then climbs away from the brook and finally ascends sharply to the Watson Path a short distance north of Bruin Rock. to the junction of Watson Path hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+9 ft on the Watson Path In another 80 yd., the Lower Bruin branches to the right toward the Valley Way, and the Watson Path crosses the brook at the foot of Duck Fall. to the junction of Lower Bruin entering alpine zone hike 0.90 mi/1 hr 17 min/+1637 ft on the Watson Path The trail soon attacks the steep flank of Gordon Ridge on a very steep and rough footway. to the junction of Pine Link hike 0.30 mi/21 min/+410 ft on the Watson Path The trail emerges from the scrub onto the grassy, stony back of the ridge, crosses the Pine Link, and ascends to the summit of Mt. Madison over rough and shelving stones. to Mt Madison Totals Distance 3.82 mi Time 3 hr 58 min Elev Gain +4135 ft Elev Loss -97 ft Elev Change +4038 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.48 mi/14 min/-546 ft on the Osgood Trail The Osgood Trail then follows the crest of the ridge past several large cairns, drops off to the left (south), and continues to descend westward just below the ridge crest and above the steep slopes falling off into Madison Gulf on the left. Soon it crosses to the north side of the ridge and descends steeply, to the junction of Pine Link hike 0.02 mi/1 min/-13 ft on the Osgood Trail Then, 30 yd. before the trail reaches Madison Hut, the Pine Link joins on the right. to AMC Madison Spring Hut hike 0.02 mi/1 min/-13 ft on the Gulfside Trail The trail begins about 30 yd. from Madison Hut at a junction with the Valley Way and Star Lake Trail and leads southwest through a patch of scrub. to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.30 mi/20 min/+357 ft on the Gulfside Trail The Gulfside then aims to the right (north) of Mt. Quincy Adams and ascends its steep, open north slope. At the top of this slope, on the high plateau between King Ravine and Mt. Quincy Adams, it is joined from the right by the Air Line, which has just been joined by the King Ravine Trail. to the junction of Air Line hike 0.06 mi/2 min/+10 ft on the Gulfside Trail The Gulfside and Air Line coincide for less than 100 yd., then the Air Line branches left toward the summit of Mt. Adams. to the junction of Air Line hike 0.54 mi/36 min/+641 ft on the Air Line After coinciding with the Gulfside Trail for 70 yd., on the high plateau at the head of the ravine, the Air Line diverges to the left (southwest), passing northwest of Mt. Quincy Adams, up a rough way over large, angular stones to the summit of Mt. Adams, where it meets Lowe&amp;#146;s Path and the Star Lake Trail. to Mt Adams Totals Distance 5.24 mi Time 5 hr 12 min Elev Gain +5169 ft Elev Loss -696 ft Elev Change +4473 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.20 mi/12 min/-210 ft on the Lowe's Path From the summit of Mt. Adams, at the junction with Air Line and Star Lake Trail, the Path descends almost due west. to the junction of Israel Ridge Path hike 0.10 mi/6 min/-100 ft on the Israel Ridge Path The Israel Ridge Path leaves the summit of Mt. Adams on Lowe&amp;#146;s Path, descending down the rocky west side. Lowe&amp;#146;s path veers off to the right (to Thunderstorm Junction) and the Israel Ridge Path veers to the left (to the Gulfside Trail). The cairns between the Gulfside Trail and Lowe&amp;#146;s Path are rather sketchy, so in poor visibility it might be better to follow Lowe&amp;#146;s Path from the summit to Thunderstorm Junction. Israel Ridge Path then joins the Gulfside trail, turning left. to the junction of Gulfside Trail hike 0.50 mi/17 min/-225 ft on the Israel Ridge Path The Gulfside Trail and Israel Ridge Path coincide, passing Peabody Spring (unreliable) just to the right in a small, grassy flat; more-reliable water is located a short distance beyond at the base of a conspicuous boulder just to the left of the path. Soon the trail climbs easily across a small ridge, where the Israel Ridge Path diverges. to the junction of Gulfside Trail hike 0.70 mi/22 min/-312 ft on the Gulfside Trail Near this junction in wet weather there is a small pool called Storm Lake. The Gulfside bears a bit left toward the edge of Jefferson Ravine, and, always leading toward Mt. Jefferson, descends southwest along the narrow ridge that divides Jefferson Ravine from Castle Ravine, near the edge of the southeast cliffs, from which there are fine views into the Great Gulf. This part of the Gulfside was never graded. At the end of this descent, the trail reaches Edmands Col. to Edmands Col hike 0.20 mi/14 min/+249 ft on the Gulfside Trail South of Edmands col, the Gulfside Trail ascends steeply over rough rocks, with Jefferson Ravine on the left. It passes flat-topped Dingmaul Rock, from which there is a good view down the ravine, with Mt. Adams on the left. This rock is named for a legendary alpine beast to which it is reputed to bear a remarkable resemblance&amp;#151;the more remarkable because there has never been a verified sighting of the beast. About 100 yd. beyond, the Mt. Jefferson Loop branches right and leads to the summit of Mt. Jefferson (5,716 ft.). The views from the summit are excellent, and the Mt. Jefferson Loop is only slightly longer than the parallel section of the Gulfside, though it requires about 300 ft. of extra climbing and about 10 min. more hiking time. to the junction of Mt Jefferson Loop hike 0.33 mi/23 min/+423 ft on the Mt Jefferson Loop This trail provides access to the summit of Mt. Jefferson from the Gulfside Trail. to the junction of Six Husbands Trail hike 0.06 mi/4 min/+72 ft on the Mt Jefferson Loop The trail diverges right (west) from the Gulfside, south of Edmands Col, and climbs steeply almost straight up the slope. to the junction of Castle Trail hike 0.01 mi/1 min/+4 ft on the Mt Jefferson Loop Just below the summit, the Six Husbands Trail enters on the left, then the Castle Trail enters on the right. to the junction of Caps Ridge Trail hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+21 ft on the Caps Ridge Trail The Caps Ridge Trail starts 40 yd. from the summit of Mt. Jefferson, at the base of a small conical crag. At the summit, the trail meets at a junction with the Castle and Six Husbands trails. to Mt Jefferson Totals Distance 7.36 mi Time 6 hr 52 min Elev Gain +6049 ft Elev Loss -1655 ft Elev Change +4394 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.40 mi/32 min/-663 ft on the Caps Ridge Trail From the summit, the trail descends west, keeping just south of the crest of the ridge. The Cornice enters left, providing an easy shortcut to Monticello Lawn and points to the south then diverges right in 20 yd. providing a very rough route to the Castle Trail and Edmands Col. to the junction of The Cornice hike 1.00 mi/1 hr 7 min/-1245 ft on the Caps Ridge Trail The trail descends very steeply down the ridge as the summit mass blends into the ridge, eventually arriving at the highest Cap. The trail reaches the lowest Cap after steep scrambles down ledges, with frequent views. The Caps Ridge Trail follows the narrow crest of the ridge, getting a bit easier as it climbs down to the scrub. The Link leaves to the right, providing a nearly level but rough path that runs to the Castle Trail just below the Castles, making possible a very scenic though strenuous loop over the Caps and Castles. to the junction of The Link leaving alpine zone hike 1.10 mi/58 min/-792 ft on the Caps Ridge Trail There is an outcrop of granite on the left that provides a fine view, particularly of the summit of Jefferson and the Caps Ridge ahead. There are several potholes in this outcrop; such potholes are normally formed only by torrential streams, and such streams occur on high ridges like the Ridge of the Caps only during the melting of a glacier, so these potholes indicate to geologists that the continental ice sheet once covered this area. The trail descends the lower part of the ridge steadily, crossing a wet section on log bridges very near the bottom. The trail terminates at the parking lot. to Caps Ridge Trailhead Totals Distance 9.86 mi Time 9 hr 29 min Elev Gain +6079 ft Elev Loss -4385 ft Elev Change +1694 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER FOUR DOOR SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1310217592000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309197391000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT MADISON, ADAMS AND JEFFERSON</name><id>23693811</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310212800000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/23693811/</event_url></item>