<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Location: Omni Parker House, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us on Thursday, January 27 for what has proven to be the must–attend event of the year for policy makers, biotechnology, life sciences, healthcare and business leaders - The 2011 MassBio Policy Leadership Breakfast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In recent years, MassBio has successfully assembled the right mix of speakers and attendees to discuss the year ahead on both Beacon and Capitol Hill. This year will be no different, as we will hear from MassBio leadership—President and CEO Robert Coughlin and Chairman Dr. Geoffrey Cox—on the upcoming initiatives we plan to undertake and the challenges we face. We have invited Governor Patrick to provide welcoming remarks, and to introduce our keynote speaker, who will present a look into healthcare reform implementation from the Obama Administration’s standpoint.  Further details on the keynote speaker will be available soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have a panel discussion entitled Healthcare Reform: Successful Implementation without Killing Innovation, which proves to be lively and informative. This year’s program is still in formation, but the content will center on what healthcare reform implementation means to our industry.  We will have a highly energized and knowledgeable moderator with four panelist discussing four high priorities impacting our industry: Payment Reform, including Medicare and Medicaid, Essential Benefits Packages at the state level, as well as Comparative Effectiveness Research and Biosimilars – two issues on which MassBio has worked diligently over the last few years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So please mark your calendar for January 27 at 7:45 a.m. at the Omni Parker House in Boston to learn more, have your voice be heard and network with a group of who’s who in state and federal politics, healthcare and life sciences. We expect to have a packed room once again to lay the groundwork for what’s to come in 2011 and beyond. Don’t miss it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve a seat today by emailing policy@massbio.org or calling 617-674-5100.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296138060000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292991358000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MassBio Policy Leadership Breakfast</name><id>15796279</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296133200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15796279/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>