<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>near Arlington T Station</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351852</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Boston Public Gardens</name><city>Boston</city><id>272992</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hanami means flower viewing. Specifically, it means to view the cherry blossoms (sakura). Hanami is thought to have started during the Nara period. Usually, people gather under the cherry trees and have a party, and we will too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start at one pm and go until three. If you are interested, there may be soccer or Frisbee afterwards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP so we know how much food to buy. Please bring a donation of $5 OR food to share. When you RSVP, if you are bringing food please mention what you are bringing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can &lt;b&gt;learn more about Hanami here&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hanami" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt; [English]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://greggman.com/japan/hanami/hanami.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://greggman.com/j...&lt;/a&gt; [English, one man's blog about his first hanami]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E8%8A%B1%E8%A6%8B" target="_blank"&gt;http://ja.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt; [Japanese]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2a/Castle_Himeji_sakura02.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://upload.wikimed...&lt;/a&gt; [a picture]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are &lt;b&gt;pictures and descriptions of last years hanami&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://japanese.meetup.com/27/calendar/5703382/"&gt;http://japanese.meetu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get off at the Arlington T stop on the green line. Make sure to use the exit that leaves you on Arlington street-- it is through a bit of a tunnel.&lt;br /&gt;On the corner of Arlington and Boylston you will see a church that has a lot of construction going on. Walk on Arlington street in the direction of the church until you get to Commonwealth Avenue. &lt;br /&gt;Enter the Public Gardens: You will see a statue of George Washington on a horse. &lt;br /&gt;When you get to the bridge, do not cross the pond, but instead take the path to the left that follows the pond. When you see the stone Chinese lantern, we will be right by the cherry tree.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is a dry location. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here is a map&lt;/b&gt; - please notice that there are two optional meeting locations near the bridge.  We chose meeting place 2 last year, but I don't know which we will choose this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mit.edu/~rschuman/www/boston_publ_gardens_map.jpg"&gt;http://mit.edu/~rschu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weather:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with any outdoor event, there is a chance that we will have to cancel the event if it rains.  If we do have to cancel on April 26, we will hold the Ohanami event on May 3.  Also, if we do cancel, we will instead have our normal Prudential Meetup from 4-6 PM.  If the weather looks bad that morning, please check your e-mail - we will send you our decision by 10 AM.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a sign by the tree nearby the stone Chinese latern
We will be wearing name tags.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209563338000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>We will have food.</why><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208563859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ohanami -- MUST RSVP -- New Map Added :)</name><id>7766910</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209229200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/7766910/</event_url></item>