<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;With some calendar rearranging, a movie-themed Meetup is back on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In celebration of the Academy Awards on Sunday, let's have a movie game night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll get the popcorn popping and have out some movie games like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cinemaplexity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scene-It&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Movie Title Celebrity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any other film-themed games, please bring them. Whether you're a cinemaphile or you just like playing games, we look forward to seeing you. We welcome new players with open arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to bring a favorite snack for the evening. We'll have popcorn and plenty to drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You should know that we are a household with a cat who will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to two small children who will be in bed during the event, but either one may pop their head in if they wake up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*If there is a snow emergency, this event will be cancelled. Should it look like we'll receive snow that evening, we will be in contact via e-mail. Otherwise, you are always welcome to call to verify.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362107777000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359941157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oscar Weekend Movie Game Night</name><id>102871922</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361667600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/102871922/</event_url></item>