<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1656 Worcester Road (Rt. 9)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.269367</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Acapulco's Mexican Restaurant and Cantina</name><city>Framingham</city><id>588263</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.200455</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Alright, to be fair my ancestry is about as Northern European as you can get, but who can say no to the deliciousness of food smothered in cheese.  And I am all for celebrating a little Mexican independence if it's an excuse to eat all kinds of yummy food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be descending upon Acapulco's in Framingham for dinner.  Be advised, so will the rest of suburban Boston.  They aren't actually taking reservations b/c it's typically so busy, so be prepped to enjoy some quality meet and greet time in the Cantina before being seated.  It's going to be packed fully of happy celebrating people, so bring your most festive ole' and be ready to cheer and chow down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To gain a little Mexican history prior to the event, check out the website: &lt;a href="http://www.vivacincodemayo.org/history.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vivacincod...&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Acapulco website with directions to the Framinham location is: &lt;a href="http://www.acapulcos.net/locations.php?pageid=location_framingham" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.acapulcos....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For now, we'll plan to meet out front, assuming fair weather is our friend.  I'll send updates to the yes's if this changes with extra details on how to find me.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm still limiting numbers or we'll never get seated, so please do be fair and keep your RSVPs accurate.  If you've got a huge craving but we're all full number-wise, make a note in your no's and we'll see what we can do.  We're closed to maybe's at this point (4 pm Sunday), but have one spot open to be filled.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to it!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210726824000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Well, it IS Cinco de Mayo.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209063795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cinco de Mayo! Mexican anyone?</name><id>7804916</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210028400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/7804916/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/2/global_2186386.jpeg</photo_url></item>