<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ferncroft Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03897</zip><lat>43.913185</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ferncroft Road Parking lot</name><city>Wonalancet</city><id>9632262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Foliage should be spectacular and this is the best day of the weekend, so why not start it a little early!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whiteface and Passaconaway via Blueberry Ledge, Rollins Trail, Dicey Mills Trail. 11.7 miles, 8 hours book time, 4383' elevation gain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ferncroft Rd. parking area. Ferncroft Rd. leaves NH 113A at Wonalancet Village, at a right-angle turn in the main highway; at 0.5 mi. from NH 113A, a &lt;br /&gt;

 gravel road (FR 337) turns right and reaches a parking area and kiosk in 0.1 mi. No parking is permitted on Ferncroft Rd. beyond this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a trained guide or medical person. I am just a hiker looking for others to join me on the trail. By signing up for this hike, you agree that you will be responsible for your own safety, and will hold me harmless for any injury or death that occurs in relation to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please only sign up if you know you can hike this kind of distance and elevation gain at least at book time speed. The days are shorter now, so we don't have a lot of extra time to make it out before dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drive should be about 1.75 hours from Concord, NH. Let's plan on getting on the trail by 8am.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349485001000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349375651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's going to be a beautiful day! Let's hike Whiteface and Passaconaway!</name><id>85513832</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>28800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349438400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/85513832/</event_url></item>