<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 4</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.644600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mickey's</name><city>Enfield</city><id>5937912</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.141914</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet Mickey's restaurant Enfield NH (Rte 4 on R just past Methodist church) 9 AM for breakfast. Sign up with trip leader before 5 PM Sat for reserved seat; non-signups still welcome but YOYO for seating. Carpool to winter parking 0.8 mi below summer trailhead (roadwalk is good warmup for the hike. We'll snowshoe 1.8 mi to treeline, then decide if we bag summit or stay lower depending on weather at the time. Either way, plenty of time to cruise the snowfields, picnic, enjoy views out to 55 miles if weather is clear. Midafternoon descend back to cars. Total length up to 5 miles, climb not over 1400'. Hiking speed 1 mph. Leader may refuse persons w/inadequate gear, see gear list on www.hikesafe.com. Required gear: windbreaker, hat, mittens, windproof shell/raincoat, sunglasses, winter boots, snowshoes. Lots of food and at least 2 qts water: drink at trailhead, leave that in car, take 1 for hike, empty it, have some back at car. Poles recommended. Blue jeans, cotton shirts forbidden: wear polypro, fleece, wool. Temps in 20s and 30s mean we'll be wet from snow and perspiration, and cotton will suck warmth from you and help you freeze. Hypothermia can kill you. We want no preventable medical emergencies. We'll stop on request to layer/unlayer, eat and drink. We'll stay fed, watered, and warm. Aside from the beauty of our very own local alpine zone, if we are lucky the wind will have shaped the snowdrifts into fantastically beautiful shapes. Bring cameras!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331071608000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330525178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snowshoe Mt Cardigan Sunday 4 March</name><id>54329402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330869600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/54329402/</event_url></item>