<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Brattle will be unable to screen BRINGING UP BABY as originally scheduled for Sun 2/10 at 1:30 - HIS GIRL FRIDAY will show in its place.  Please update your RSVP if this change affects your plans.  Thank you!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me at the Brattle for two outstanding comedies: HIS GIRL FRIDAY and ADAM'S RIB are part of the &amp;quot;Great Romances&amp;quot; repertory series in which the Brattle &amp;quot;celebrates classic, quirky, and occasionally bizarre cinematic romances.&amp;quot;  We'll meet and discuss after ADAM'S RIB.  As this is a double-feature, I highly recommend you make an afternoon of it and catch the 1:30 PM screening of BRINGING UP BABY as well.  Please indicate your intentions when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HIS GIRL FRIDAY (screens at 1:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This typically fast-paced comedy by Hawks, features Grant, at his snarky finest as a tabloid editor, and Russell, as his ace crime reporter and ex-wife. She's re-engaged to another guy but puts her impending marriage on hold to cover a hot murder story, and Cary takes full advantage of the situation ? but is it revenge or still-smoldering love?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Double Feature w/ADAM'S RIB - Showing in place of BRINGING UP BABY &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADAM'S RIB (screens at 3:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nominated for Best Story and Screenplay at the 1950 Academy Awards, ADAM'S RIB is a peerless comedy predicated on the double standard.  The romantic legend of Katharine Hepburn and Spencer Tracy's real-life affair sometimes overshadows the actual work they did together -- and that's a shame -- for the films the pair made together are almost uniformly excellent.  Their onscreen chemistry (not surprisingly) is so powerful that it's impossible not to see them as two soul mates bantering.  In this, one of their best-known collaborations, they play rival attorneys on opposite sides of an attempted murder case . . . that just happen to be married to each other.  The fact that the case revolves around a woman who tried to kill her loutish husband doesn't help their marital relations much.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read the original NY Times review at: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/review?res=9E02E5DC1F3BE23BBC4E51DFB4678382659EDE" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it's off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199768080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>His Girl Friday &amp; Adam's Rib</name><id>7060359</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202668200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7060359/</event_url></item>