<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWER STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 3:40, so let's meet at 3:10 right inside the ticket lobby doors. Then I'll buy our tickets and we can get snacks and head in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're going to be late, need directions or have to change your RSVP after 1:00 p.m. tomorrow, give me a call (508/308-4897).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow for Invictus!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The holidays are over (sniff, sniff) and some of us got some things that are going directly into the regift basket. Bring in any gift you've gotten (under about a $20 value) and we can swap our unwanted gifts for ones we actually want. After all, one man's trash is another man's treasure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only those who bring a swapable item can participate in the swap. (Bring one item, get one item. Bring 2, take 2, etc.) Stay tuned for more swap days in the future!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please indicate in your Yes RSVP if you'll be bringing something and how many something's you'll bring so we know how many people can swap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ooo. A Saturday movie! Not only that -- a Saturday afternoon movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Morgan Freeman and Matt Damon are apparently phenomenal in &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810073710/details" target="_blank"&gt;Invictus&lt;/a&gt;. We must see it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The true story of how Nelson Mandela joined forces with the captain of South Africa's rugby team, Francois Pienaar, to help unite their country. Newly elected President Mandela knows his nation remains racially and economically divided in the wake of apartheid. Believing he can bring his people together through the universal language of sport, Mandela rallies South Africa's underdog rugby team as they make an unlikely run to the 1995 World Cup Championship match.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right the theater ticket lobby and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Invictus!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263515131000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262390867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Invictus</name><id>12193023</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263067200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12193023/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>