<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Camille &amp;amp; Craig, has open up there home to celebrate there harvest and take us for a evening get away to "Paris" We are blessed to have such wonderful music to accompany this wonderful evening of Wine, Food, &amp;amp; Meetup friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine (no boxed wine or 1.75MLs please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food, hors d'oeuvres or desert. Please indicate what food item you want to bring when you sign up. If you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is $15 or more ( 750 ml) with your dish. Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $30 or more depending on the quantity of people in the group, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste. Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reds - Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whites - sav blanc, chards, reisling, pinot grigio, etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a person's spot if you do not show up. If you must cancel, the earlier the better if there is a waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event if you don't have it already to all the "yes" RSVPs, due to this being a private residence. It should go without saying to Drink Responsibly. I will have water and coffee too.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We Will E-Mail Directions</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Camille</member_name><member_id>6528452</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307405891000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><why>A party to enjoy all the fruits of spring - With Wine, and music provided by "Darlene Wow" and our very own "Tom &amp; Craig" our theme is Paris so bring "French Wine &amp; Appetizer, desert" the most creative dish will win a bottle of wine :-)</why><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>43</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302790547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"SPRING TIME IN PARIS" WINE PARTY" COME LET US SALUTE THE SUN</name><id>17303187</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307228400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/17303187/</event_url></item>