<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;all kayaks have been loaded as below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It seems MYSTIC wins out over Bluff Point.&lt;br /&gt;Those of you who want to hike with Steve T, please see his listing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Now that most of you have been on the ocean with this group or another group and 8 foot waves are just a bump .. that means you are ready to take on the BIG SHIPS in the harbour..LOL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Today: A chance of showers and thunderstorms. Patchy dense fog before 9am. Otherwise, mostly cloudy, with a high near 77. Northwest wind between 3 and 10 mph. Chance of precipitation is 40%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight: Mostly clear, with a low around 60. West wind around 6 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  TODAY&lt;br /&gt; W WINDS 5 TO 10 KT...INCREASING TO 10 TO 15 KT WITH GUSTS&lt;br /&gt; UP TO 20 KT LATE. SEAS 1 TO 2 FT. PATCHY FOG EARLY THIS MORNING.&lt;br /&gt; A CHANCE OF SHOWERS AND TSTMS UNTIL LATE AFTERNOON...THEN A SLIGHT&lt;br /&gt; CHANCE OF SHOWERS AND TSTMS LATE. VSBY 1 NM OR LESS EARLY THIS&lt;br /&gt; MORNING.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK SOME WAVES FOR YOU&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  03:57 EDT   0.20 feet  Low Tide&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  05:58 EDT   Sunrise&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  09:47 EDT   2.73 feet  High Tide&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  16:05 EDT   0.40 feet  Low Tide&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  17:18 EDT   Full Moon&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  19:41 EDT   Moonrise&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  19:45 EDT   Sunset&lt;br /&gt;2008-08-16  21:56 EDT   3.15 feet  High Tide.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEE MY LISTING UPDATES &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://kayaking.meetup.com/119/"&gt;http://kayaking.meetu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR     kayaking.meetup.com/119/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Read and print these directions further down if you dont have a GPS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING WATER AND A PORTABLE LUNCH... GRINDERS, WHATEVER...for the actual paddling part of the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DINNER / BARBIE-Q     BUGG JUICE, FIRE PIT..ETC.. IS LATER IN A DIFFERENT LOCATION,&lt;br /&gt;I suggest Gardner Lake (off to the right of the boat launch out of everyones way) its on the way home for most all of us anyway, the lake is right off i sect 82 and 85 (right before we approach rte 11 entrance ramp)..to the EAST a mile or 2.&lt;br /&gt;look at you maps...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GARDNER LAKE after party location:&lt;br /&gt;ON THE RETURN TRIP....take a right on rte 82 = Norwitch Rd for apx 2.6 mi, then take a left onto rte 354 = Old Colchester Rd, passs Lake View Rd on right, next right should be Boat Launch Access Rd.. should still be a sign near by..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS users use 145 Old Colchester Rd, Salem CT to get you real close.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING SOME FOOD AND BUGG JUICE FOR THIS PART OF THE EVENT..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip is ok for most recreational and all sea kayaks, we will watch out for you and help if needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But i will not let the trip go on if the wind is above 10 mph or seas are more than 2 feet mostly that for short rec kayaks, you may get swamped and/or get tired fighting the wind..etc..and none of us really likes bad weather anyway especially at this distance..&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancells the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the weather as we get closer to the event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simple stuff to have is a sponge, pfd and whistle, pump and paddlefloat..&lt;br /&gt;If you dont have this, dont worry, most of us have this on our own boats so there should be enough..but if you can get these items, they are cheapo life insurance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Launch Site:     Under I-95 Bridge Launch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Initial Directions: THERE ARE A FEW WAYS TO GET HERE..ONE IS 9 SOUTH TO 95 NORTH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE WAY I WILL TAKE IS RT 2 SOUTH TO rte 11 SOUTH..GO TO END TAKE LEFT on to rte 82 then take a right (south) onto rte 85, go under rte 395 ...  pass by THE MALL,  AND GET ONTO 95 NORTH TILL THE # 89 EXIT AND FOLLOW THE REST OF THE DIRECTIONS BELOW..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;its apx  1 hour from hartford..so plan ahead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take I-95 North to exit 89. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at exit end:&lt;br /&gt;Make a right to go onto Allyn Street. &lt;br /&gt;Then take a left on Sandy Hollow Road. &lt;br /&gt;Continue until the end of Sandy Hollow Road at which you will make a left onto ( Cow Hill Rd) or High Street. (i have seen both names)...Just go left here,&lt;br /&gt;Then go a short distance to the first right turn onto Bindloss Ave, following to its end.  &lt;br /&gt;( this is a side street with a boat launch sign as best i can remember)  --  &lt;br /&gt;make a left turn onto River Road  -- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Once on River Road continue on a short distance and just after you go under I- 95 Bridge, the boat launch/Parking area is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;Pick any spot to park and carry down the yaks..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS ADDRESS: APX  604 RIVER ROAD, MYSTIC, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Homless Persons Bathtub= Pungo 12' with F/R floataion bags installed= JANICE&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper &amp;amp; Dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= home&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna Snake= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', =  ALEX&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= JiLL&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= AL_r&lt;br /&gt;Lisa's boat loaded also. Thats it no more changes for today&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 10 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why only 10 bucks ?&lt;br /&gt;Thats the amount it costs me to cover all the holes and gashes with new duct tape and additional roofing nails for the wood structure repair slats each time they go out in the ocean. NON HAVE SUNKEN YET...LOL&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Toyota Avalon/w yak trailer &amp; Traffic Cone on ROOF, BLUE SHIRT-</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219075768000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217985027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>KAYAK-Mystic River- Mystic Seaport- Mason Island(s) Recreational and Sea Kayaks </name><id>8485899</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218902400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8485899/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/3/global_4970051.jpeg</photo_url></item>