<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>January 12, 2011&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;HI! My friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;GOOD EVENING AND HAPPY NEW YEAR!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is truly a new beginning for our Interfaith Book Club... I apologize to each of you, if after my return from Italy, I was unable to get in touch with you. In the last months, my time has been taken up by an increased number of activities and among these the restructuing of our house in Holliston took up a lot of my time. For those of you who have followed this &amp;quot;saga&amp;quot;, I can tell you that upon my return I found the house project in the same way I had left it months before. In addition we had to look for a new contractor, which forced up to reapply for all the permits with the town. The last permit came through the day before Thanksgiving. The work began the first week of December and God willing we are going to see the light at the end of the tunnel by the end of February. Keep us in your prayers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, I hope this note of mine finds you well, with peace and joy in your heart. I pray you had a SEASON blessed with peace and joy. I hope this 2011, notwithstanding the tragedy that took place in Tucson (AZ) remains for us a great gift from God and a great opportunity for further committment in the area of reconciliation and dialogue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, on Sunday January 30th at 4:00pm we are staring once again our Interfaith Book Club meetings. During this meeting I hope we are going to choose our next reading material. As we did in the past, if you have any book or any suggesiton bring it along and then together we decide which book to take up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Personally, I would suggest a couple of books for the new beginning. These as you notice are the same books I suggested before the end of the summer:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;1) God is not One: The eight rival religions that run the world and why their differences matter, by Stephen Prothero.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;2) A History of God: The 4000 year quest of Judaism, Christianity and Islam, by Karen Armstrong.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;These are only my suggesitons. I hope to see a lot of books and materials being offered at our next meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark your calendar and hope you can make our upcoming meeting:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;TIME: January 30th at 4:00PM&lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;See you soon. Blessings on you and yours. As we continue to move into the New Year may we walk with the Divine in peace and reconciliation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144&lt;br /&gt;pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296493181000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294872896000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WELCOME TO THE INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB</name><id>16027385</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296421200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/16027385/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/global_4353546.jpeg</photo_url></item>