<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10253922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Game is less than one week away. Please Update your RSVP and call Laurie's to finalize your reservation. An additional phone number has been included below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Super Bowl Party option is for those who live in the suburbs north of Boston and can not make it into our primary party at North Star in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Patriots are out but many of us are still looking forward to a good Super Bowl between the Baltimore Ravens and San Francisco Forty Niners!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives will be teaming with Wakefield Week Nights and other suburban groups for this event.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a private party as Laurie's will be closed to the public. You must have a reservation. The Party Includes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.Pick your guaranteed seat at the Penny Lane Bar, Raw Bar or at a table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.Pasta and Raw Bar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.Rotating Appetizers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.Carving Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.Half Time Raffle Prizes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.Watch on 4 Big Screen HDTVs &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.$3.00 per Draft Beer All Game&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8.$5.00 Super Bowl Punch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TO RESERVE: Call Bob or Laurie at Laurie's to make the credit card reservation and pick your reserved seat. All food and reserved picked seat is included in the $40.00 price. Call 781-246-1909. Or call Bob at 781-223-7168. Your RSVP on the Natives Meetup means nothing until you call and reserve with Laurie's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited and this will sell out. Reserve early and pick the best seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/7/6/event_189763382.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;For information on the venue go to &lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;http://www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive any time after 5:00pm to claim your reserved pre-paid seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GAME TIME is 6:30pm. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this will be your first time meeting the Red Sox Natives or Wakefield Week Nights Crew check out the photos of those who RSVP Yes so you can find us.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay as you order and tip your servers. However, if you sit at a group table a group bill may be provided so please communicate with your servers. Credit Cards are held by the servers at Laurie's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participating Groups Include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.Wakefield Week Nights (Melody)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.Red Sox Natives (Frank)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.Single Professionals, Nerds &amp;amp; Geeks (Alison)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.Boston Happy Hour (Tonya)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar is Wakefield's newest restaurant and Bar with live entertainment several nights per week and Tuesday night Trivia with Morgan White Jr. from WBZ Radio. Laurie's is located at the Wakefield Commuter Rail Train Station in Wakefield. The Reading and Haverhill Commuter Rail trains stop at Laurie's. Laurie's is easily accessible within 10 minutes from Routes 128, 93, 28 and 1. Free parking is available in two lots on Tuttle Street and on street. Check out the MBTA or Hop Stop for additional public transit options including the less reliable/frequent 136 and 137 bus lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Say hello to Laurie and Bob when you visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the "Penny Lane" Bar, the 9:09 and Beatles references.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information at http://&lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives have organized weekly Patriots Viewing parties over the last two seasons with guests from other invited groups attending. We have had a blast with up to 85 people attending at various Boston, Woburn and Wakefield locations. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call Laurie's to pick and reserve your seat at one of 2 bars or at a table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob MacFadgen</member_name><member_id>70176472</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360293008000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358799465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Bowl Party at Laurie's 909 in Wakefield Includes Seating, Food &amp; More</name><id>100698452</id><headcount>23</headcount><duration>19800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359928800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/100698452/</event_url></item>