<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A memoir about a boy’s love for the magic of movies, set in a small town in Italy following WWII. Poignant performance by Philippe Noiret as the town’s projectionist and the boy’s mentor. (1988) 2h35m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cinema Paradiso&lt;/u&gt; is the story of a famous Italian film director who returns home to a Sicilian village for the first time after almost 30 years away. At home he is re-connected with he life and people he once knew and revisits the poignant memories formed in childhood. For him, the journey brings back the highlights and tragedies that shaped his life and inspired him to pursue his dream. --&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When &amp;quot;Cinema Paradiso&amp;quot; won the Academy Award as best foreign film in 1990, it was an open secret that the movie the voters loved was not quite the same as the one director Giuseppe Tornatore made. Reports had it that Harvey Weinstein, the boss at Miramax, had trimmed not just a shot here or there, but a full 51 minutes from the film. Audiences loved the result, however, and the movie is consistently voted among the 100 best movies of all time at the Internet Movie Database.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now comes a theatrical release of &amp;quot;Cinema Paradiso: The New Version,&amp;quot; with an ad campaign that promises, &amp;quot;Discover what really happened to the love of a lifetime.&amp;quot; Considering that it was Miramax that made it impossible for us to discover this in the 1988 version, the ad is sublime chutzpah. And the movie is now so much longer, and covers so much more detail, that it almost plays as its own sequel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll gather before the film at &lt;b&gt;The Upper Crust&lt;/b&gt;, an appropriate Italian Pizza place next to The Coolidge Corner Theater.  Come as early as 6 for pizza and conversation, or meetup with us at 6:45 as we head to the theater so that we can sit together and lose ourselves in the paradise of cinema.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the Upper Crust at 6:00 eating pizza at a table with a Meetup Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241375030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cinema Paradiso</name><id>10326695</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242687600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10326695/</event_url></item>