<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 McNamara Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05757</zip><lat>43.480888</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forget-Me-Not Farm</name><city>Tinmouth</city><id>8156662</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.076073</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As the Northeast's premier energy and music festival, SolarFest blends art, education, and community outreach to inspire the conservation of Earth's limited resources, to promote renewable energy, and to support the creation of sustainable communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since its inception in 1995, SolarFest has built a strong foundation for promoting artistic excellence and community-building while providing both general and detailed information on a wide range of sustainable living topics. We raise more than a few eyebrows when we explain how our entire weekend festival, including the sound and lights on our main stage, runs on renewable energy, primarily solar with a bit of wind in the mix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SolarFest's reputation as New England's most entertaining energy and music festival is growing just as it should: reasonably and sustainably. We combine superb family entertainment with presentations by some of the region's most knowledgeable Renewable Energy experts. We thicken the mix with how-to and hands-on workshops on green building, sustainable agriculture and thriving locally. We even offer a track of workshops designed especially for young people, entitled The Solar Generation. We offer a special children's activity area (Kids Korner), and a wide variety of food, craft, renewable energy and sustainable living vendors. Our featured performers represent a far-ranging spectrum of styles and traditions from around the world. We provide plenty of space throughout the weekend for serendipitous encounters, conversation, dancing, hiking, camping, relaxation, and an overall celebration of our planet's beauty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.solarfest.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.solarfest.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leora Mallach</member_name><member_id>11642426</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342815383000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342030930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SolarFest</name><id>72919752</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342803600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/72919752/</event_url></item>