<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>State Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.689293</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Mt Grace State Forest</name><city>Warwick</city><id>957167</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.341130</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;This is a pret&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/e/a/event_125212202.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;ty, moderate hike. I am scheduling it for a Tuesday for now and will likely repeat this hike later in the summer on a weekend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt Grace is situated in Warwick State Forest. We will park at Olsen Field across from the Warwick Highway garage on Route 78 (Warwick Road if I remember correctly). While there is a more direct route to the summit, by following the Round the Mountain trail and joining the M+M Trail it stretches this hike to 6+ miles round trip. Once we reach the Fire Tower, we can decide to take the direct route down, shaving off a couple miles, or meander along M+M over Little Grace and work our way back to our starting point. I am keeping in mind that this group has a Watatic hike scheduled for the 4th, so I don't intend on wearing anyone out on this hike! I hiked the 6+ mile route in good sneakers Wednesday and was able to hike another 9.6 mile loop around Long Pond Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/e/e/event_125212462.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;For those who have never hiked this route, it begins with a downhill hike for about a mile. You'll walk through forested areas and fern filled paths while passing an old ski area tow rope.  Once you connect to the M+M Trail, the hiking becomes more moderate. Shortly after starting up the M+M Trail you'll encounter a lean-to shelter with stone fire pit and picnic table. Inside the lean-to there is a journal in a plastic bag for people to sign and date.  Staying on the M+M Trail will bring you to the summit. The Fire Tower is normally not manned unless conditions dictate, but there is no gate keeping you from climbing to the locked structure on top.  THIS is where you'll get views of the surrounding area, because the base of the tower is surrounded by trees!  The tower isn't too wobbly, by the way!  There is a nice picnic table here as well to stop and grab a bite.  Once you leave the Fire Tower, if you continue on the M+M Trail you will climb over Little Grace which affords "some" views to the West. At the bottom of Little Grace the trail meets up with the Round the Mountain Trail once more. Following this trail brings you back to the gravel road to the Fire Tower and eventually back to Olsen Field.  Not all the trails are well marked, but if you can follow a map, this hike isn't difficult at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Grace is named after Grace (Sarah) Rowlandson, the daughter of &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mary_Rowlandson"&gt;Mary Rowlandson&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Puritan"&gt;puritan&lt;/a&gt; colonist of Massachusetts. Grace died after she and her mother were captured by &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Native_Americans_%28United_States%29"&gt;Native Americans&lt;/a&gt; of the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Narragansett_%28tribe%29"&gt;Narragansett Tribe&lt;/a&gt; during &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/King_Phillip%27s_War"&gt;King Phillip's War&lt;/a&gt; in 1676. She was reportedly buried at the foot of the mountain.                                                                                                     Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming from Rte 2 East, take exit 15 (should be the exit to Rte 122). At the end of the ramp, bear right heading north on South Main Street (also Rte 122) into the center of Orange. At the second set of lights, turn left and head west on Rte 2A for maybe 2 miles. Turn right onto Rte 78 and drive 6 miles give or take until you drive through Warwick center (don't blink!) Olsen Field is about a third of a mile past the center of town, just past a school on your right. The field which we will start from is on your left.  I drive a silver Toyota Corolla and will be parked at the northern end of the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341432646000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338599628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Grace via Round the Mountain and M+M Trails</name><id>67361652</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341320400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/67361652/</event_url></item>