<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Bring a bag lunch and join us for a day looking at Micro and Mini cars at the Larz Anderson auto museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is cross posted with CityScoots&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From their site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event: Micro Mini Car Day&lt;br /&gt;Event Type: Lawn Event&lt;br /&gt;Date: Jul 12, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1:00:PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: This is the Largest Truly Exotic Car Meet in the United States! Join us from 1PM-4PM on Saturday July 12th. Nearly everyone has seen a Ferrari, but when was the last time you set your eyes on the sensuous curves of a Messerschmitt, a Peel Trident, or a Kleinschnittger F125 Roadster? This 360 pound all aluminum roadster car can propel its two occupants to a maximum speed of 28 mph by the force generated by its one cylinder, 3 ½ horse power, 125 cc engine. These are not toy cars, but rather serious transportation solutions designed by some of the world?s best aircraft engineers, to place a war torn, poverty stricken Europe back on its wheels. The ?clean sheet of paper? approach to engineering achieved some really fresh, unique and eccentric designs such as BMW?s egg shaped Isetta with the single ?refrigerator? door in the front which resembles a fighter plane which has had its wings ?clipped.? Built by the Messerschmitt aircraft company from 1953 to 1964, it features tandem seating, acrylic cockpit dome and a steering ?yoke? right off the fighter plane. Its two stroke engine is stopped and started in a reverse direction in order to select one of four available reverse gears. These microcars were manufactured primarily in the 1950?s and 1960?s, and constitute a really unique chapter in the history of the automobile. The vast majority of Microcars are European, and include such marques as Goggomobile, Zundapp, Isetta, Messerschmitt, Vespa, Heinkle Trojan, and Fiat. There are some American and Japanese examples such as Crosley, King Midget, Fuji, Daihatsu, Honda and Subaru. Most are powered by 1 or 2 cylinder, 2 stroke motorscooter engines. Many are 3-wheel configurations with enclosed chain drive, and all of them are absurdly whimsical in their appearance, design and function. HIGHLIGHTS This is the most unusual, unique and fun automotive event you will ever attend. Unlike many classic car shows where you are asked not to touch the finish of the showcars, which are parked for static display only, this day will be buzzing with activity. You will hear the sounds, and smell the scents as sixty to one hundred of these tiny little vehicles buzz around the museum grounds to the delight of everyone. Showcar owners will offer rides to spectators who will have an opportunity to ride in as many different marques as they wish. Saturday, JULY 12, 2008 Larz Anderson Museum of Transportation, 15 Newton Street, Brookline, Massachusetts (617) 522-6547 Registration Fee: $20 per car (includes two Museum admissions) $10 per spectator (includes Museum admission) For more information on the entire three day event (July 11th-13th, 2003), please contact Charles or Nancy Gould @ (617) 965-4848 or e-mail chasgould@aol.com Website: www.bubbledrome.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Scooters</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216055445000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206934867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Auto Museum Micro Mini Car Day &amp; Picnic</name><id>7637513</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215882000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/7637513/</event_url></item>