<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Here's something&amp;nbsp;different: a FREE YOGURT SAMPLING courtesy of Activia by&amp;nbsp;Dannon!&amp;nbsp; Join SSDOMG Members and their Guests as we sample some Yogurt.&amp;nbsp; We have been given&amp;nbsp;12 (one dozen) 6 ounce samples each of Activia by Dannon Selects Greek&amp;nbsp;Yogurt and Activia by Dannon Selects French Yogurt with Fruit Bites.&amp;nbsp; There are only 24 samples and everyone will get one sample to enjoy.&amp;nbsp; In addition, they sent along nametags and would like us to take some pictures.&amp;nbsp; If you do not want to be in the pictures you do not have to be but it would be appreciated if you would since they are paid sponsors giving us free samples.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;For those who are unable to join us at this event, we do have 10 coupons that we will be giving out at our subsequent 2-3 events in September and into October.&amp;nbsp; In addition, if we have more than 1/2 dozen samples left another event will be scheduled within the next week or so.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We will spend about 45 minutes sampling and socializing.&amp;nbsp; We will take a couple of group&amp;nbsp;photos shortly after everyone arrives and gets their nametags and&amp;nbsp;samples and then again throughout the event. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Feel free to enjoy the Braintree Farmers Market and Earth Celebration Day before and/or after our event.&amp;nbsp; Please be advised that we will need to stay in our area for this 45-minute event as we do not want to interfere with or make any waves with&amp;nbsp;the Famers Market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Please check out our Sponsors and their offers on our Sponsorship Information page by clicking on the following link.&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Sponsorship_Info/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Sponsorship_Info/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;[b]Activia By Dannon Free Yogurt Sampling[/b]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Saturday, September 10th @ 10:30-11:15am&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Braintree Town Hall - Side Door&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;1 JFK Memorial Drive&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Phone #: None&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Website: None&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location:&lt;/em&gt; Side door of Town Hall under the overhang.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Costs&lt;/em&gt;: None!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fees&lt;/em&gt;: None!&amp;nbsp; You can become a 2011 Annual Member at today's event for $6.&amp;nbsp; Please bring exact change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: At least 6 Yes RSVP's by&amp;nbsp;Noon on Friday, September 9th.&amp;nbsp; Maximum of 20 attendees.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: One per member.&amp;nbsp; However, if we do get a Wait List we will kindly ask that we keep this to members only as we have a limit supply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Saturday, September 10th @ 9am&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/em&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&amp;nbsp; (Note: You don't actually need any money at all for this event.&amp;nbsp; You do need it, however, if you become an Annual Member and/or if you shop at the Farmers Market as most vendors do not accept credit cards.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Will be updated on Friday if it is questionable.&amp;nbsp; However,&amp;nbsp;the event&amp;nbsp;will go on, we just might have to move the location.&amp;nbsp; Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather").&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions to Braintree Town Hall @ 1 JFK Memorial Drive&lt;/em&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview&lt;/em&gt;: Located near South Braintree Square, directly across from the Thayer Public Library and next to Thayer Academy, Town Hall is a short walk from the Braintree T and a short drive from Route 3.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Routes 24/95/128/93:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Head towards Route 3 South/Braintree/Cape Cod.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route&lt;/em&gt; 3: Take Exit 17/Union Street/Braintree&amp;nbsp;(it will be your 2nd exit on Route 3 South), take the 1st right off the exit ramp (from Route 3&amp;nbsp;southbound/3rd right&amp;nbsp;from Route 3&amp;nbsp;northbound) keeping Motel 6 on your left.&amp;nbsp; Get in one of the middle lanes and go straight thru the 1st set of lights going under the overpass and keeping the T on your left.&amp;nbsp; Take a left at the light at the top of the hill and get in the right lane.&amp;nbsp; Take a right at the next light and an immediate left into the Town Hall parking lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the Braintree T on foot&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Exit the T heading towards Union Street and South Braintree Square.&amp;nbsp; Leave the front door, take a left and head towards the street (it's a one way so you may see a bus or taxi heading your way), then go down the steps and take a left heading under the underpass up the hill.&amp;nbsp; At the top of the hill at the light round the corner to your left heading towards The Fire Station.&amp;nbsp; At the next light if you walk diagonally across the street you will be at Town Hall.&amp;nbsp; Basically, cross the street in front of the fire station and then use the signal to cross Washington Street, or use the signal to cross Washington Street and then cross Central Street.&amp;nbsp; You will be at the Town Hall Mall once you have crossed the street(s).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Parking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;: You may park at Town Hall, Thayer Academy (opposite side of&amp;nbsp;Central Street), Thayer Public Library (across the street) or along Washington Street.&amp;nbsp; Please park in marked spaces only in parking lots, with care along the street, and do not block any driveways or streets.&amp;nbsp; (I think we're pretty good parkers but I'm just putting it out there.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note&lt;/em&gt;: As the library is open and there is an Event at the Farmers Market today parking may be tight.&amp;nbsp; Please allow a couple of extra minutes for parking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet by the memorial status near the flags on the Town Hall Mall across from the front door.  I will be the one with the Yogurt Samples, plastic spoons and napkins.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315836621000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315247179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Activia By Dannon Free Yogurt Sampling - 1st of 2!</name><id>32333232</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315665000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/32333232/</event_url></item>