<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1228 Riverdale St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.137860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On The Border Mexican Grill</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>669419</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.625950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Following last meeting's intriguing debates - we've selected Middlesex by Jeffrey Eugenides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A dazzling triumph from the best-selling author of The Virgin Suicides, Middlesex is the astonishing tale of a gene that passes down through three generations of a Greek-American family and flowers in the body of Calliope Stephanides. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a long one (544 pages) so plan ahead since it has been well received by readers and critics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2003, Jeffrey Eugenides received The Pulitzer Prize for his novel Middlesex (Picador, 2003). Middlesex, which was also a finalist for the National Book Critics Circle Award, the IMPAC Dublin Literary Award, France's Prix Medicis, has sold over 1 million copies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;As the Age of the Genome begins to dawn, we will, perhaps, expect our fictional protagonists to know as much about the chemical details of their ancestry as Victorian heroes knew about their estates. If so, Eugenides (The Virgin Suicides) is ahead of the game. His beautifully written novel begins: &amp;quot;Specialized readers may have come across me in Dr. Peter Luce's study, 'Gender Identity in 5-Alpha-Reductase Pseudohermaphrodites.' &amp;quot; The &amp;quot;me&amp;quot; of that sentence, &amp;quot;Cal&amp;quot; Stephanides, narrates his story of sexual shifts with exemplary tact, beginning with his immigrant grandparents, Desdemona and Lefty. On board the ship taking them from war-torn Turkey to America, they married-but they were brother and sister. Eugenides spends the book's first half recreating, with a fine-grained density, the Detroit of the 1920s and '30s where the immigrants settled: Ford car factories and the tiny, incipient sect of Black Muslims. Then comes Cal's story, which is necessarily interwoven with his parents' upward social trajectory. Milton, his father, takes an insurance windfall and parlays it into a fast-food hotdog empire. Meanwhile, Tessie, his wife, gives birth to a son and then a daughter-or at least, what seems to be a female baby. Genetics meets medical incompetence meets history, and Callie is left to think of her &amp;quot;crocus&amp;quot; as simply unusually long-until she reaches the age of 14. Eugenides, like Rick Moody, has an extraordinary sensitivity to the mores of our leafier suburbs, and Cal's gender confusion is blended with the story of her first love, Milton's growing political resentments and the general shedding of ethnic habits. Perhaps the most wonderful thing about this book is Eugenides's ability to feel his way into the girl, Callie, and the man, Cal. It's difficult to imagine any serious male writer of earlier eras so effortlessly transcending the stereotypes of gender. This is one determinedly literary novel that should also appeal to a large, general audience.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the book club meet-up when checking in</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205685479000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><why>This book will likely trigger some interesting conversations and debates.</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203470252000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Book Club Meet-up: Middlesex by Jeffrey Eugenides</name><id>7366425</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205274600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/7366425/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/d/global_719309.jpeg</photo_url></item>