<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>WHO:  
This is a combined gathering of MeetUp &amp; Single Event social networking groups, typically @ 12-36 of us party together each time (spontaneously, with or without RSVP's), sometimes many more!  NEW FRIENDS ARE ALWAYS WELCOME!

WHAT:
Please join us for a fun, BEAUTIFUL evening of "FREE Live Outdoor Music" (at what will most likely will be our FINAL outdoor concert of the season):  *Guitar Under the Stars* (Spanish, Latin, Jazz, and international guitar music) featuring (among others):
&gt;&gt;&gt; 4:00 PM  Randy Collins: High energy finger style acoustic guitar &lt;&lt;&lt;
&gt;&gt;&gt; 7:30 PM Daniel Salazar, Jr. and his ensemble with the Hartford Festival Orchestra. The internationally acclaimed guitarist and Guitar Under the Stars founder will perform popular Spanish classics and new, original works, accompanied by an ensemble of international musicians and the Hartford Festival Orchestra conducted by Brian Sparks.  
For full details: &lt;a href="http://www.ctguitar.org/events07-08/gus07.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ctguitar.org/events07-08/gus07.html&lt;/a&gt;

&gt;&gt;&gt; WHEN:  UPDATED TIME &lt;&lt;&lt;
THIS SATURDAY, 09/08.  This FREE concert runs from 3-10.  Feel free to come at any time, however, &gt;&gt;&gt; SOME OF WILL BE ARRIVING @ 3:30 &lt;&lt;&lt; to settle in for Randy Collins 4:00 performance while others will be coming @ 6:45 for Daniel Salazar, Jr.'s 7:30 performance.  Scheduled to end @ 10PM, but we'll party on outdoors in East Hartford (see below)!

WHERE:  
Check out: Mortensen Riverfront Plaza for directions &amp; parking info, or MapQuest Directions to:  Mortensen Riverfront Plaza - 300 Columbus Boulevard, Downtown Hartford, CT  06106

&gt;&gt;&gt; NEW PARKING LOCATION:  
Rather than pay to park in downtown Hartford, then drive to East Hartford for our outdoor "Fire-Pit under the stars" after-party... I recommend you CARPOOL (dropping off coolers, blankets, beach chairs, etc. near the base of the E.H. walkway steps) then simply PARK IN EAST HARTFORD (under Founders Bridge along East River Drive, OR at the intersection of East River Drive and Pitkin Street, OR in an after-hours office building parking lot) and take the short WALK OVER the "Founders Bridge Promenade". &lt;&lt;&lt;

&gt;&gt;&gt; NEW GATHERING LOCATION:
As our people will be arriving at various times, rather fight the crowds to get a good view of the performers, our group will settle BEHIND and BELOW the stage area, immediately by the railing along the Connecticut River!  We won't have a great view of the performers, but can easily hear them while having enough space to spread out for our growing group, have space to dance, and have relaxed conversations without interfering with the performers or audience.  Plus, we'll have easy access to the porta-potties, more privacy for discreet (they spot-check coolers for alcohol) beverages, and a great view of the river! &lt;&lt;&lt;
LOOK FOR: Al R's four orange traffic cones and/or my red reflectors on white sticks.  
&gt;&gt;&gt; IF YOU CAN NOT FIND US, twice hourly, at :00 and :30 (between 3:30-9:30 PM) one of our group members will hold up a homemade *S.E. / MeetUp* sign while standing at the top-most / center-most stairway for 5 minutes (only) to lead latecomers to the group.

&gt;&gt;&gt; FYI: Alcohol is NOT allowed to be brought in from the outside; however, beer and wine will be sold.  Food Vendors will be there, but you can bring in your own snacks / picnic dinner, if you'd like.  

&gt;&gt;&gt; Store EXTRA food and beverage, along with  beach chairs, blanket, etc. in your car for the post-party that ensues as we gather around a propane-fueled ceramic FIRE-PIT, continuing our own Under the Stars party in EAST HARTFORD, within walking distance or very short drive - possibly at the Band Shell.  (More reason to park on the E.H. side of the River!)  As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly! 

&gt;&gt;&gt; Please do NOT hit "reply" or call me as I've never parked there before and simply following recommendations, myself.  To cut down on email updates, check out who's coming, more details, &amp;/or to RSVP, please visit my free "FREE Live Outdoor Music" calendar posting (by 3PM the day of the event for any updated info):  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/6309683/" class="linkified"&gt;http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/6309683/&lt;/a&gt;

FYI: As the various summer concert series are winding down, please sign up for my FREE online calendar of fun (typically free or inexpensive) upcoming social networking events geared at singles in their 30's - 50's.  UPCOMING: Funny Bone comedy club, games nights, picnics, walks/hikes/camping, and various parties!  Visit: 
&lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/" class="linkified"&gt;http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/&lt;/a&gt; 

See you there!

- Rob

Rob Pudney 

***

Event Schedule:  {Rain Date: SUNDAY, 09/09}

3 PM  Judy Handler and Mark Levesque
&gt;&gt;&gt; 4 PM  Randy Collins: High energy finger style acoustic guitar &lt;&lt;&lt;
5 PM  Ron Affif Trio: Virtuoso jazz guitarist
6 PM  Viva Quetzal: Music of the Americas. Energetic, melodious rhythms.
&gt;&gt;&gt; 7:30 PM  Spanish guitar with Latin rhythms featuring Daniel Salazar and his Ensemble, with special guest Argentinian Tango master Tito Castro, accompanied by The Hartford Festival Orchestra</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189450986000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189104591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Guitar Under the Stars" Mortensen Riverfront Plaza 3:00-10:00</name><id>6309683</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189278000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6309683/</event_url></item>