<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Roger's Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.612628</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St Peter's Park</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>968113</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.660005</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The day is full of events one of the main one that we are going to see is the greasy pole event this event starts at 4:45, see more information below for the day's events and information on the Greasy Pole Event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;UPDATE: LET'S MEET AT THE FRIENDLY'S AT THE CIRCLE AND CAR POOL FROM THERE, OR IF YOU ARE IN THE AREA ALREADY CALL ME ON MY CELL @ 603-793-9191 AND WE CAN MEETUP FROM THERE!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:00 a.m. CELEBRATION OF MASS OF ST. PETER, at St. Peter's Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00 noon RELIGIOUS PROCESSION FOLLOWING THE CELEBRATION OF MASS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:00 p.m. BLESSING OF THE FLEET- at Stacy Boulevard –&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**3:00 pm Concert, United States Navy Band Northeast, St.Peter’s Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:45 p.m. SPORTS EVENTS - at Pavilion Beach - SEINE BOAT RACES and GREASY POLE CONTEST.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**6:00 PM CONCERT ST. ALFIO’S BAND,(1 HOUR) ST. PETER’S PARK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 p.m. CHILDREN'S PINATA CONTEST - at Pascucci Court&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**7:30-PM ------**AWARDS CEREMONY. for winners of Sporting Events&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Greasy Pole: is a most unique contest indeed. It takes place 200 feet off Pavilion Beach. A forty-five foot telephone pole is attached to a platform and extends out over the water. A red flag is nailed to a stick at the end of the pole which is then heavily greased. Then, one by one contestants take their turn trying to tear off the makeshift flag pole before slipping and and falling into the water. Some contestants sprint out like racehorses hoping momentum will carry them to the end of the pole. Others take a very slow approach, one step at a time, always trying to maintain their balance. It is not uncommon for these daring individuals to come away with scrapes, bruises or even broken ribs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come for all of the events or leave whenever you would like this event is open.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update a meeting place as we get closer to the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all so bring your children!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at the Friendly's at the circle!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246658414000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244292877000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St Peters Fiesta</name><id>10589687</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246201200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10589687/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/2/global_8992642.jpeg</photo_url></item>