<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 122</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.394558</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Ware River Watershed Trail</name><city>Rutland</city><id>4601322</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.051200</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sunday May 5, 2013 Paddle the Ware River in Barre, MA. Meet at the launch on Rt 122. There is nothing in the area for me to give you as a marker, the old road in the area is Old Coldbrook Road. The launch is where the Ware River goes under RT 122. You can see the launch to the north of the bridge. Plenty of parking and a port-a-pot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hoping the water is still high enough to get over the beaver dams. This is an easy paddle. some current but not much. Hopefully we will be able to paddle up to the Old Covered Bridge Rd. stop, have a snack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suggest you bring a change of clothes in a dry bag just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***PLEASE NOTE***&lt;/strong&gt; The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;: PFD (worn), whistle, headlamp/flashlight if near/after sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional/recommended&lt;/strong&gt;: pump/bailer, insect repellent, sunscreen, water, snack, change of clothes in drybag, hat with brim/visor and sunglasses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not use a paved boat ramp to load and unload your kayak, unless there is no other space available.  If you must use a ramp, do so quickly, and off to the side, to minimize the inconvenience to the people who have trailers and must use the ramp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that the time posted for the trip is the time we start paddling.  If you are not at the venue in time, we will leave.  If you arrive late, you will have to decide if you want to try and find us.  It is not fair to keep a large group of paddlers waiting for someone who may not even show up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan L</member_name><member_id>7773139</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367793230000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367609452000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ware River</name><id>117582182</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367762400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/117582182/</event_url></item>