<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mystic River Rd &amp; Fairfield St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.417501</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dugger Park</name><city>Medford</city><id>1253974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.140055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This particular session at Dugger is for rallying and practice to develop various tennis skills. The other session at Crosby at the same time is for those interested in playing matches.Please note the earlier (and final) start time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll see how the morning and afternoon meetups go on Saturday and we may do the same for Sundays as well, but for now we'll have two morning sessions. If there is a low sign-up, I will merge them into one Meetup at Crosby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These weekend Meetups are informal and unstructured - show up and play with whoever else shows up. Open to all levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will not be able to attend. Please let me know if you are willing to be the Event Host. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This session is for anyone just interested in rallying to develop their strokes. Although, there is no formal structure, I suggest having drills to develop control and consistency. This session can also be used as an opportunity to practice serving and returning serves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested drills:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mini-tennis:&lt;/strong&gt; Confine your hitting within the service boxes. Good as a warm-up and focusing on controlled strokes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Down the Line / Cross-court:&lt;/strong&gt; With four people at a court, begin with hitting down the line to person directly in front of you, then switch to hitting cross court. Then switch sides with your partner so that you hit cross court on your forehand and backhand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Variation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Add an element to this drill by attempting to continuously as long as possible. As soon as there is an error, both sides play out the remaining ball for points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volley / Overhand Practice:&lt;/strong&gt; Have one side at net hitting volleys, while the other side hits back from the baseline. Switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Practicing Serves:&lt;/strong&gt; This can also be done with four people on the court. One side of the court will practice serving while the other side will practice switching. Switch.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339343650000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Tennis Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tennis-240</urlname><id>432728</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Somerville Tennis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339040483000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday AM Tennis @ Dugger, Rally Practice</name><id>68117262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339331400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tennis-240/events/68117262/</event_url></item>