<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Cascade Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.281708</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sue Serpa's home</name><city>Worcester</city><id>3431492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.860573</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We're having another Truth Party! 10 Cascade Road Worcester, MA Celebrating the end of the Decade of Deceit and the beginning of the decade of Truth and Justice. Bring your favorite beverage and snacks to share. Come strategize, energize and PARTY! You deserve it after all you selfless efforts to bring 9-11 Truth to the voters. Follow your GPS or Mapquest directions EXCEPT at the end of the directions when you're on Mower St., PASS Cascade Rd and take the NEXT right onto Virginia Rd. (that end of Cascade Rd is impassible). From Virginia, take the next right onto Windemere St. My house is just beyond the next intersection on the right - white older colonial with black shutters. Park on Windemere St, or in my driveway (which is also on Windemere St.) I'll keep the light of Truth on for you! **********~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Susan Serpa 10 Cascade Road (corner of Windemere St. and Cascde Road - driveway and street parking on Windemere St) Worcester, MA 617-599-5195 neimpeach@gmail.com ____________________________________________________________________________ A message from 9-11cc MA: Thank You to EVERYONE who helped Senator Mike Gravel win the Massachusetts Attorney General's all-important certification for a Citizens' 9/11 Investigation Commission! A heartfelt congratulations to you on the MA Team and to Mike and his National Team. Due to the timing of the petition's release coinciding with several extremely urgent 9/11 projects on the 10th anniversary, such as drives for RememberBuilding7 and AE911Truth, our steady and impressive flow of donations out of the gate wasn't quite enough to get us on the ballot for next year. A Blessing in Disguise. We are keeping our powder dry for 2013, giving us plenty of leeway this time to get every detail right, plus having already scored our all-important legal precedent in 2011 and having learned BIG lessons by the whole whirlwind experience of having campaigned on short notice for a real, live 9/11 ballot initiative! Already we have found amazing and wonderfully generous new volunteers. Just think of how many more are out there, waiting for one of us to appear before them with our clip boards and our contagious optimism over the next 2 months. Even though we won't be on the 2012 ballot, the feedback we accumulate from everyday voters during the next two months (please share with us!) will be INVALUABLE for planning our pre-certified and pre-financed drive just 24 months from now! BUT here's the really great news...there's no pressure on you to actually get people to sign petitions! FAR more important now becomes simply giving out the official campaign DVD or flier or website URL, all with our contact info. These campaign info items, to be unveiled shortly, will be designed to tout our upcoming 2013 campaign and to collect new volunteers' emails as we go. The petition is really just a legal prop to get our foot in the door of the average voter. We've put a lot of work into our MA 9-11cc campaign, so let's get as much milage out of this golden opportunity as we possibly can. Let 2011 be remembered as the great warm-up year to a well-planned and financed 2013! Buckle up...we're just getting rolling... Rich&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317514498000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317260760000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open House Truth Thank you Party - Worcester Sat. Oct. 1st 7 PM</name><id>35406952</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317510000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/35406952/</event_url></item>