<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-903-7371</phone><name>Private Location #3</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1477076</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121896</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fun Little-Known Tricks To Have Compelling Conversations That Make You Unforgettable With Social Time To Practice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How To Endlessly Entrance Them With Captivating Conversation That Makes Almost Anyone Love Talking To You, Even If You Are Not A &amp;ldquo;Talker&amp;rdquo; Or Don&amp;rsquo;t Know What To Say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Brand New Exclusive Meetup Training On Conversation That Gets People Addicted To You And Social Time To Practice It With Other Members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you get ever have difficulty knowing exactly what to say to people?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have conversations that don&amp;rsquo;t lead to dates or new friends or people say that there was just no chemistry?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you ever &amp;ldquo;run out of things to say&amp;rdquo; or have your mind go blank in conversation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you ever just not know what to say when you&amp;rsquo;re talking to someone new and there is an awkward silence?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; If you answered yes to either of those questions, then you're going to love this month's workshop. You'll learn simple, proven conversation techniques that will compel most people to want to be around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you master this simple skill, you'll have the confidence to talk to anyone and have interesting conversations with people in any situation, and you will know what to say to get them talking.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Imagine being at a Meetup event, social event or party and effortlessly gliding around the room talking with anyone and everyone. You'll surprise yourself with how easy and effortless it is to strike up conversations with total strangers and get to know them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Once you have this skill, you'll be able to make friends and attract lovers anywhere you go, anytime you want.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; *************************************************  &lt;br /&gt; HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:  &lt;br /&gt; *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The secret I uncovered to being able to endlessly talk, even if you aren&amp;rsquo;t a &amp;ldquo;talker&amp;rdquo; or a &amp;ldquo;chatter box&amp;rdquo; or a person with lots of stories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;An usual way you can use feelings to create a powerful connection that will have them begging you to let them be around you all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The 4 key observations you need to make in your conversations that will captive your audience every time so they want to be around you and go on dates with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;A secret &amp;ldquo;nesting&amp;rdquo; technique I learned from a professional entertainer that will have people so captivated while listening to you that they will literally beg you to finish your conversation if you stop even for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;A simple way to have people think you are the most interesting person in the world even if you think your life is &amp;ldquo;dull and average.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;One secret conversational tactic I stumbled upon that instantly makes anyone want to tell you more about themselves so you barely have to do any work at all and they do all the talking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The one thing you must do in any conversation. (HINT: Miss this one element and all your conversations are doomed to fail)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;3 Topics you must avoid at all costs when telling a story or talking in any conversation or people will not want to be around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Much More..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt; HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt; *************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The meeting is limited to 20 people due to the size limitations of the classroom (we'll be moving around a lot). Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; #1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, March 6th available. The meeting runs from 3:30pm to 5:30pm and is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; #2 - If you have that evening free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now. Trust me, it's going to fill up fast. They always do.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; #3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for a professional training that includes these skill-building drills + personality feedback. Please remember to bring: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;$20 cash &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A pen &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;A great attitude &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I'm looking forward to seeing you there.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Eric &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems. My cell is: 617-903-7371.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door. The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Edgemont</member_name><member_id>12651136</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick Richards</member_name><member_id>12716842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299516101000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><why>How to Endlessly Entrance Them With Captivating Conversation That Makes Almost Anyone Love Talking To You, Even If You Are Not A “Talker” Or Don’t Know What To Say.</why><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298928807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Compelling Conversation Secrets That Make You Unforgettable</name><id>16740258</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299443400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/16740258/</event_url></item>