<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826942</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Metcalf Auditorium, RISD Chace Center</name><city>Providence</city><id>5404402</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408745</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Posted as an FYI for those that are interested!&lt;/p&gt;
Art RI Screening: Art Education Metcalf Auditorium, Chace Center 
&lt;p&gt;6:30 PM - 8:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art Rhode Island, a television series airing on RI PBS, features conversations about the arts in the state.  This episode on Art Education features Paul Sproll, RISD Professor in the Department of Teaching and Learning in Art and Design; Sarah Ganz Blythe, Director of Education at the RISD Museum, and Barbara Wong, Executive Director of City Arts in a conversation moderated by Martina Windels.  Following the screening, there will be a discussion with Joseph A. Chazan MD, executive producer of the series and long time supporter of the arts in the state, and Richard Goulis, the filmmaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.risdmuseum.org/events.aspx?id=2147522401"&gt;http://www.risdmuseum.org/events.aspx?id=2147522401&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that this is a Collective FYI, which is just that - For Your Information. I will probably be attending, but this is not a "hosted" event. If you are interested in attending, please RSVP so people know who to look for if they attend!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Posted as an FYI only, however, I'll be wearing a bright blue, gradated-dyed scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347557454000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346291916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI - Art RI Screening: Art Education</name><id>80014962</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347487200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/80014962/</event_url></item>