<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Old Church Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.557053</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First United Methodist Church</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1153543</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.647873</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,  at this past Monday's 12 Step Buddhist group meeting we discussed using other books than The 12 Step Buddhist by Darren Littlejohn and perhaps not just sticking with one book at a time.  Rather, we talked about having the chair of the meeting for each week select a book and a reading.  Some of the books we discussed include One Breath at a Time by Kevin Griffin, The Zen of Recovery by Mel Ash, 12 Steps on the Buddha's Path by Laura S and Burning Desire by Kevin Griffin.  I am sure there are other books and readings to be considered as well.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We'd also like to have a &amp;quot;business meeting&amp;quot;  following our regular group meeting on October 4.  We are particularly interested from feedback from those who have come to the group and found it did not meet your needs.  Please feel free to come to the Oct 4 meeting to provide your ideas and feedback or post comments that can be brought to that meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting is at the First United Methodist Church, 24 Old Church St., Middletown, Ct.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Thanks in advance for your thoughts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lori&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS - This is the first time I've ever posted on this type of website, so I hope I got it right.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lori</member_name><member_id>12999537</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286237511000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-469</urlname><id>836707</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>12 Step Buddhist &amp; Recovery Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285240136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>12 Step Buddhist Group meeting and business meeting</name><id>14868749</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286233200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-469/events/14868749/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/9/global_18176329.jpeg</photo_url></item>