<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Contribution</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Meet at Gas Station at the Concord Rotary Route 2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets get lost, or try to at least.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will stay off the beaten trail and may hit dead ends and cross our own path but see some nice little roads that we usually ride right past. First we will put about 30-40 miles behind us down Rt 2 to get away from familiar territory, then start carving up the countryside. Here the focus will be on finding those sweet little roads that we never knew existed, ones we want to visit again next year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be staring late so the world warms up a bit, riding for a couple of hours and then stopping for a bite someplace that none of us have never seen before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The high for Sunday Hopefully will be about 50 degrees at 1PM, but it's expected to be very sunny. All in all the ride will run till about 4 then we will make our way back to known areas and home to our warm homes - or some may choose to go for an evening shiver as the temps are expected to be in the 30's by sunset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fastest part will be in the beginning where we will go out on Rt 2, so anything 250cc's and up will work, no major highways on this ride and once we get off Rt 2, top speeds will be in the 40's at most.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come and get lost, if you know where you are.. you lose!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Concord Rotary Gas station on Rt 2</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Alden</member_name><member_id>5206555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227974508000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225237260000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lets get lost!</name><id>9050122</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226241900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/9050122/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/3/global_6082387.jpeg</photo_url></item>