<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Eastbound)</address_2><address_1>686 Worcester Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.297932</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-626-8989</phone><name>Whimsy arts and crafts studio</name><city>Framingham </city><id>766011</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.425194</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;Come learn more about our chapter, have some refreshments, and possibly even win some door prizes.   We'll have information about our playgroups, including a special Under One Club for moms of infants under one year old.   This is an &lt;i&gt;moms only&lt;/i&gt; evening event, but non-mobile infants are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each month we hold two meetings faciliated by either members or speakers on many topics including nutrition, safety, parenting issues, financial planning and career topics, and much more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also organize kids activities including our upcoming firehouse tour.  Every month we organize moms activities- which include scrapbooking nights,  monthly movie nights, dinners out, an upcoming introduction to poker night. And of course we celebrate with family parties including a Halloween costume party for the kids and a Winter carnival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We feature a number of sub-groups including a special needs group, a seasoned moms group, a book group, a and a cooking group.  We communicate every day through a VERY active local email list where we discuss everything from the best local pediatric dentist to answering questions on toilet training, sleep issues, looking for local preschool recommendations and hundreds of other topics.   We have members in Framingham and surrounding towns including, but not limited to Natick, Sudbury, Wayland, and Ashland.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the great door prizes at the Open House are Gift cards for: &lt;br /&gt;Panache, Plaster Fun Time, Whimsy, Butterfly Place, Pheasant Hill Landscaping, &lt;br /&gt;and Hokey Pokey Design&lt;br /&gt;A facial worth $90 and 20% coupons at Elizabeth Grady &lt;br /&gt;A basket of kids hair products and gift certificate from Snip-its&lt;br /&gt;A free photo session and 6 photo sheets at Portrait Simple worth $125&lt;br /&gt;Arbonne products&lt;br /&gt;Flip Video Camera&lt;br /&gt;I-pod Shuffle &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a door prize of a free one-year membership drawn from the names of those who officially join that evening! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn even more about the chapter, go to our local site at &lt;a href="http://www.mothersandmoreframingham.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.mothersandmoreframingham.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanya</member_name><member_id>7153030</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224764421000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221696792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open House</name><id>8779322</id><headcount>52</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224198000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/8779322/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/b/global_5549403.jpeg</photo_url></item>