<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be hiking up to Mt. Pierce on the Crawford Path which is the oldest continuously maintained hiking trail in the United States. It was constructed in 1819 by Able and Ethan Allen Crawford and was later converted into a bridle path to the ridge of the Presidentials. &lt;br /&gt;We will park at the parking lot for the AMC Highland Center. The trail has a cutoff that starts across the street from the Highland Center. In general, the trail is steady and moderate with no real steep sections. Snowshoes and some type of foot traction will be required.   We will cross several small streams along the way as we take the trail to the summit.&lt;br /&gt;The hike up to the summit is about 3.2 miles with a vertical gain of over 2100 feet. It will take between 2.5 and 3.0 hours to reach the summit. If we have a nice clear day, the summit of Washington and the rest of the Southern Presidentials will be visible from the bare rocky summit. We will return to the Highland Center via the same trail.&lt;br /&gt;For those of you getting into winter hiking and interested in doing a 4000 footer, this is a good hike.&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death, including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. You also agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has signed up for The New England Hiking and Adventurer's group is probably fully aware that there are risks involved with outdoor activities. Needless to say, we want everyone to have a safe and pleasant experience while participating in our events.&lt;br /&gt;You are responsible to read and agree to the risk and disclaimer along with the NEHAG Waiver of Liability.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a Black four door Echo with Maine Plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1237815740000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235399991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Pierce via the Crawford Path</name><id>9802713</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237642200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9802713/</event_url></item>