<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 1 South</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.547092</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-777-1266</phone><name>Calitri's Italian Restaurant</name><city>Danvers</city><id>1144479</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.884258</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ever want to go out for Authentic Italian instead of the American Italian you get from the local restaurants but you don't want to go into Boston to get it?  Are you Italian and won't order certain things on an &amp;quot;Italian&amp;quot; restaurant menu because it &amp;quot;just won't be like moms&amp;quot;? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well lets go out to Calitri's for an Authentic Italian meal.  This restaurant was highly recommended by a respected member of our group.  Here is alittle history on Calitri's:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;Where we come from, when you join a traditional Italian family for a meal, there are certain things you can expect... a warm welcome, lots of good food and a very enjoyable time. &lt;br /&gt;When our families came from Panni, Italy, in 1947, we brought that tradition with us, and our whole family works together to share it with you. &lt;br /&gt;The Calitri and Lapolla families opened Calitri's Restaurant in 1970, and over the years we've proudly served traditional Italian cuisine in the restaurant, fostered good times in the lounge and hosted celebrations in our function room. &lt;br /&gt;We make our own fresh pasta right here and we still use Papa Antonio's spaghetti and pizza sauce recipe.  We're always trying to improve, so please let us know if you have any suggestions. &lt;br /&gt;Welcome to the family&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets go out and try this out, we will try to get a reservation or a call ahead but given its Valentine's weekend we can't guarantee that we will get one.  &lt;b&gt;If you are the type of person that does not like to wait to be seated, this event may not be for you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a nice dinner at Calitri's, if time permits and there is interest we can then go to an area venue to do some dancing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the meetup table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266278967000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261352698000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Italian at Calitri's in Danvers</name><id>12122322</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266105600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12122322/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/1/global_12332417.jpeg</photo_url></item>