<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Jfk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.491.9851</phone><name>Redline</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692091</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a known fact among some of the Nerds that there is a popular, nerd-friendly, weekly trivia Meetup event in Harvard Square on Monday nights. But to call it to your attention more distinctly, Heather has permitted&amp;nbsp;us to cross-post it here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/e/2/5/event_22044101.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you attend other Nerd Fun events regularly, you'll probably see lots of familiar faces at Trivia. We've been regulars at Redline on Monday nights since the summer of 2009. While the size of our crowd varies from week to week, it's a rare week that one of our teams doesn't take one of the top two prizes. (And we've only earned the booby prize twice.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special Note:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This week's edition of Trivia is being cross-posted to both Social Fun and Nerd Fun for those Nerds who haven't found us at Redline yet, because it's our good friend, T.J. Maher's birthday;&amp;nbsp;he wants to celebrate with Trivia, and the more of his friends, the merrier!&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Please only RSVP to one of the two groups, so we can maintain an accurate head count for the reservation.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you've got a hankering to answer questions and psych yourself out about whether you actually know the right answer,&amp;nbsp;and especially&amp;nbsp;if you want to wish T.J. a Happy Birthday, come on down! &amp;nbsp;There's a&amp;nbsp;decent dinner menu and we have a blast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The fine print:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Trivia starts at 8:00pm and we will be making a reservation for 7:00pm for those who have signed up by 5pm. Show up earlier than 8pm to be guaranteed a seat with our group and a place on a team. We are usually seated at the tables along the wall opposite the bar - to the right past the hostess stand. &lt;strong&gt;We can have teams of up to 6 people.&lt;/strong&gt; Trivia ends around 10:00pm. Just ask for us, everyone at Redline knows who we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please RSVP if you think you will be coming - showing up unannounced makes it difficult for us to make a decent reservation with the restaurant. If you do not RSVP at all, we may have to turn you away from our group.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;We'll close RSVPs when the group feels unwieldy to us, so please change your RSVP if you know you can't make it. Showing up for dinner at 7pm allows the restaurant more time to feed us, so show up at 7pm for dinner,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;or as late as 7:45pm for just trivia, and tell us in your RSVP which you'll be.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Also, while I normally detest Meetup's dumb new "feature" of no Maybes,&amp;nbsp;in this case, please try to commit if you're coming, so we can plan TJ's celebration more effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;Finally, please bring cash with you to facilitate paying the group bill.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;(Making change is never a problem.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;FYI: Our standing rule is to multiply your tab by 1.25, and then round up (to cover tax and tip).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redline is located in Harvard Square on JFK Street underneath the Wagamama and Staples. Parking can be tricky in Harvard Square so come early to find a space or take the T (Harvard Square Station). Redline currently validates for free parking on weeknights in the Eliot St Garage, provided you purchase a meal there; the lot is directly above the restaurant, access on Eliot St.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're usually seated along the wall on the far side across from the bar, under the mirrors but ask any staff member and they'll point us out.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KateMcQ</member_name><member_id>6532193</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne Marie</member_name><member_id>6769686</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Will</member_name><member_id>7339843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300806850000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300204731000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and Trivia: It's T.J.'s birthday!</name><id>16929315</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300748400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/16929315/</event_url></item>