<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>365 Mather St</address_1><state>Co</state><zip>06514</zip><lat>41.357647</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>365 Mather St</name><city>Hamden</city><id>8715602</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The dog days of summer are slipping by so it's time for a summer potluck this sunday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who've been to these potlucks in the past you know the drill, super low maintenance is key so bring whatever you like, you can bring something you made, something you had leftover from last night or something you grabbed on the way over from the drive through...we wont judge. Just bring yourself, maybe a friend and something tasty to share. Both meat and vegetarian fair welcome. There will be some wine and beer on hand, please bring whatever else you may want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please try to rsvp so I have an idea of how many are coming. If you are a "maybe" or will be bringing any plus 1's please put so in the comments and try to update as sunday gets closer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;365 Mather street unit #19 (building #2). Complex name is Lake Whitney. When you pull in take your immediate 2nd left turn and building #2 is straight ahead with unit 19 on the ground floor. Park in any spot marked "V" in the front or back of the building (back of the building has a buzzer for entry, in the front just knock on the porch door).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring my phone number if you have any trouble. 203-499-7777&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;:)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>dave</member_name><member_id>12623808</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345601538000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344974357000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Afternoon POTLUCK</name><id>77737052</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345404600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/77737052/</event_url></item>