<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>NOTLOB CONCERTS is proud to present THE HANNEKE CASSEL BAND, featuring Avi Friedman (cello) and Christopher Lewis (guitar); Fionnuala O'Donovan opens, at the Clarendon Hill Presbyterian Church, 155 Powderhouse Blvd, Somerville, MA 02144 on Saturday, February 28 at 8:00 pm (doors 7:30).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“She is already a rising star in the Celtic skies…her musical ideas are savvy and sophisticated, but her throaty, gusting style is deeply banked in the Scottish and Cape Breton traditions.”                                                      &lt;br /&gt;- Boston Globe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“…elegant, graceful…Cassel’s tunes capture the mixture of sadness and hope found in much Scottish and Irish music and give it a fresh West coast spin.”&lt;br /&gt;            -  Dirty Linen Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“…the rhapsodic quality of Cassel’s ballads or slow airs evinces a soul’s fully expressed quest …Cassel’s rhythms are tenacious, and they weave through a set of reels with serpentine grace.”&lt;br /&gt;-Boston Herald&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested minimum donation is $15.00 at the door &amp;amp; $10 for seniors and students with ID.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information about the concert series can be found at the Notlob website:  &lt;a href="http://notlobmusic.googlepages.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://notlobmusic.go...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARTIST WEBSITES:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hannekecassel.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hannekecas...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ariandmiafriedman.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ariandmiaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In cooperation with Clarendon Hill Presbyterian Church’s “Peace, Justice and Mission Committee”, representatives from RESPOND will be in attendance to share information Patrons may also bring items from RESPOND’s wish list, or donate funds directly through RESPOND’s website - &lt;a href="http://www.respondinc.org/main.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.respondinc...&lt;/a&gt;  RESPOND’s mission is to help women and their children create options for a safer life, free from domestic violence, and to further the efforts of the larger community to end domestic violence. At this time we seek to fulfill our mission by providing shelter, support, advocacy and education.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask any of the volunteers</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238288126000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231971717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THE HANNEKE CASSEL BAND w/ Fionnuala O'Donovan</name><id>9524625</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235869200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/9524625/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/0/global_6936992.jpeg</photo_url></item>