<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Main Floor-North Entrance</address_2><address_1>404 Wyman Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02454</zip><lat>42.410244</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-781-895-1234 </phone><name>IBM Innovation Center</name><city>Waltham</city><id>893122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.256317</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This seminar is organized by our partner NECINA (&lt;a href="http://www.necina.net" target="_blank"&gt;New England Chinese Information &amp;amp; Networking Association&lt;/a&gt;)'s Semiconductor SIG.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Internet of things (IOT)", referring to internet network of everyday objects, is hot, especially in China. Internet unlocks the potential of billions of computers, and IOT will unlock the power hidden among trillions of objects. In 2010, the total IOT revenue in China is $30 Billion. It is expected to grow up to $100 Billion in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IOT is more than RFID, sensors and cloud computing. What would be the enabling technologies there? What opportunities can you grab? We are fortunate to have Sohail Khan, CEO of SiGe Semiconductor (RF silicon- germanium leader, M2M and smart energy RF front end provider and one of the fastest growing semiconductor companies based in North America), and Robert LeFort, CEO of Ember Corporation (Wireless mesh networking technology leader, Zigbee SOC provider, an initiator of Zigbee Standard) to talk about what is going on and what trend they see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please come to share your thoughts and spark new ideas in our discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registration&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Please register at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.acteva.com/booking.cfm?bevaid=216721" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.acteva.com/booking.cfm?bevaid=216721&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free for NECINA members and guests/studends, $15 for general public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Pizza will be provided&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 6:30 pm - 7:00 pm   Registration, Pizza and Networking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:00 pm - 7:30 pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;"RF Technology and Trend for Machine to Machine Applications",&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sohail Khan, CEO of SiGe Semiconductor&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:30 pm - 7:45 pm&amp;nbsp;Q&amp;amp;A for Sohail Khan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;7:45 pm - 8:15 pm "Enabling the IOT with ZigBee Wireless Mesh Networking", Robert Lefort, CEO of Ember Corporation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8:15 pm - 8:30 pm&amp;nbsp;Q&amp;amp;A for Robert Lefort&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8:30 pm - 9:00 pm Networking&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Contact: Yang Li (Please e-mail edwardliyang@yahoo.com or call 617-953-8654)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speakers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sohail Khan&lt;/strong&gt;, President and Chief Executive Officer, SiGe Semiconductor&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sohail has served as President, Chief Executive Officer and Director since 2007. Prior to joining SiGe, he served as an operating partner at Bessemer Venture Partners, a venture capital firm, from 2006 to 2007 where he assisted in the evaluation of new investment opportunities and provided support to portfolio companies. From 2001 to 2005, Sohail held various senior&amp;nbsp;management positions with Agere Systems, Inc. (acquired by LSI Logic Corporation), which was a publicly traded global leader in semiconductors and software solutions for storage, mobility, and networking markets, including executive vice president of infrastructure systems and executive vice president of strategy and development. He held senior management&amp;nbsp;positions at Lucent Technologies, Inc. from 1996 to 2001, AT&amp;amp;T Inc. from 1990 to 1996, NEC Electronics Corporation (now Renesas Electronics Corporation) from 1984 to 1989, and Intel from 1982 to 1984. Sohail serves on the board of directors of LightPath Technologies, Inc. and GainSpan Corporation. He holds a Master of Business Administration from the University of California at Berkeley and a Bachelor of Science in electrical engineering from the University of Engineering in Lahore, Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robert LeFort&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;Chief Executive Officer, Ember Corporation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert LeFort was appointed as CEO of Ember in April 2006. Most recently, he was the President of Infineon Technologies North America Corp. in June 2002, with responsibility for all headquarters business activity and key customers. Earlier, he was Vice President Infineon's Automotive &amp;amp; Industrial business, managing business development and relationships with companies using Infineon chips for dynamic vehicle management, engine control, automotive safety systems and related applications. Before joining Infineon in 2000, LeFort was Customer Manager at Delphi Corporation, a Tier One automotive electronics supplier, and held positions at Cherry Semiconductor (now part of ON Semiconductor), Unitrode Corporation and Analog&amp;nbsp;Devices. He holds an MBA from Boston University and a BSEE from the University of Massachusetts at Lowell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ning An</member_name><member_id>10728354</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299879648000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299718842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>[Partner]NECINA: Enabling Technologies and Opportunities for  Internet of Things</name><id>16865660</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299799800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/16865660/</event_url></item>