<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Some of us have employers that honor the President's Day holiday so yippy to them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to head out to Yale Forest in Ashford for a 5.6 mile thru hike.  This means we will have at least two cars to get from each end.  This is not a loop.  This is unchartered territory but sounds nice for this exploration hike.  The topo maps show no scarey ups and the promise of an overlook.  We will physically be south of Bigelow Hollow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is still winter so dress inlayers and make sure to wear boots.  Water is a must and snacks are encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at exit 67 on route 84 if you want to carpool at 9:30 a.m.  That exit has a Micky D's and Burger King for potty and snacks (yuk).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will then head north to exit 72.  At the end of the ramp take a right onto rt. 89.  Take your first left onto Hillside Rd.  Stay on Hillside to your second right onto Barlow Mill Rd.  The blue blaze Nipmuck should be a half mile down.  We should be at this spot for 10:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Ashford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=5+Barlow+Mill+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06278-0905" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That will be our end spot.  We are then shuttling down Barlow Rd, Right on Boston Hollow Rd, Left on Eastford Rd to the start. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a strong possibility we have to have a post hike conference at Willington Pizza afterwards to debrief all who attend.  It could get very intense and will require some kind of specialty pizza.  We will try to endure.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235227377000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234368248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nipmuck Trail, Yale Forest, Ashford, CT</name><id>9720597</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234794600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/9720597/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>