<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Suggested donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover Meetup fee</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Son, the future is in plastics...&lt;br /&gt;Well I've been thinking about plastic alot, more specifically the amount of petroleum based products in our lives.  Think about anything you have purchased lately, oil was involved at some stage of production.  Even my organic seeds from Johnny's arrived by truck.&lt;br /&gt;So this July we will be screening &amp;quot;Blue Vinyl&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;The story goes:&lt;br /&gt; Vinyl was my father?s answer to the rotten wood on our house. Everyone assured me that vinyl siding was safe, and would only let off toxic gas in the rare event of a house fire. But after my experience with cancer caused by DES [a synthetic estrogen and anti-miscarriage drug prescribed to my mother and millions of other women], I figured any material so loaded with synthetic chemicals had to pose some kind of risk. Later I asked my dad, &amp;quot;If you had known that over the course of its lifecycle, from the factory to the incinerator, vinyl produces a wide array of deadly pollutants that threaten our future with a global toxic crisis, would you still have put it on the house?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;I hope not, honey,&amp;quot; he said. &amp;quot;But they didn't write that on the box.&amp;quot; So, with a piece of vinyl siding firmly in hand (a remnant from my parent?s house) I took off ? on a journey to re-write the outside of the box.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Brooking</member_name><member_id>2040136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184540605000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Advocates for Oil Awareness</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-169</urlname><id>113465</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Oil Awareness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181347819000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Maine Oil Awareness July Meetup</name><id>5870548</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184367600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-169/events/5870548/</event_url></item>