<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>5322022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a non-traditional slideshow in the series. Rather than a trip report format this will be a discussion format with slides in support of speaking points and topics. The topic will be Military techniques of planning, leadership group dynamics and survival that can be applied to outdoor recreation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Military Forces routinely put themselves into harms way in order to conduct their mission sets. What we as recreational, outdoors people consider very bad weather, terrain or emergency situations are often just a “day at the office” for Military Forces. The tools, principals and techniques utilized by these men &amp;amp; women can be applied to our recreational safety and success. This talk will focus not on micro skill sets such as fire building and shelter construction but on macro skills such as trip planning, leadership and what to do when things go wrong in the outdoors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Our Speaker is a 14 year veteran of the US Military. He has multiple deployments to multiple continents. He is also an active outdoorsmen whom enjoys hiking, climbing, hunting and winter sports here in New England and around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Doors open @ 6:15 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Potluck @ 6:30 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Slideshow @ 7:15 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Join our email list and get all the latest updates and cancellation notices for all the shows: &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potluck Info:&lt;/strong&gt; Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome :) Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (with a stovetop, oven, microwave, sink &amp;amp; fridge). Please bring your own cooking pots if needed for stovetop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subway Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Take the MBTA to Park Street Station. Walk through the Boston Common uphill towards the State House on Beacon Street. To the left of the State House is Joy Street; follow Joy Street uphill to the AMC Auditorium Building (brownstone), #4 Joy Street on the left hand side. Map: &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; Nearby parking is available at the Boston Common Garage, located underneath the Boston Common. Access is off Charles Street, between the Public Garden and the Boston Common. More info about the Garage is here: &lt;a href="http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4471089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363462783000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351698066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Outdoor Leadership &amp; Planning for Recreational Hikers (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>89330172</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355355000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/89330172/</event_url></item>