<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Corner of Cross and Hanover Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.362556</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rose Kennedy Greenway Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>1616652</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055801</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Boston rally at 12 noon-Sunday, May 1, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Haymarket T Station-Rose Kennedy Greenway Park, in the corner of Cross and Hanover Street, Boston&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the rally we will join the East Boston march to the Chelsea May Day rally at 2pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We demand:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Stop attacks on workers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Stop the detention and deportation of migrant workers and their families!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Immediate permanent residency for all undocumented migrant workers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. No racist profiling Secure Communities programs!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Money for jobs and education, not for war and occupation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. Unity of all workers to defend our rights!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7. International unity for immigrant rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information: &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonmayday.org"&gt;www.bostonmayday.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by the Boston May Day Committee (Mass. Global Action, ANSWER Coalition,  Socialist Workers Party, Socialist Alternative, Socialist Party, July  26 Coalition, Tecschange, Latinos for Social Change). &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Endorsed by (list in progress): Boston School Bus Drivers' Union,  Boston United National Antiwar Committee, Centro de Trabajadores de  MassCOSH, Chelsea Uniting Against the War, Circulo Bolivariano MLK,  Dominican Development Center, Frente Uruguayo, Immigration Pastoral  Center, Industrial Workers of the World, International Action Center,  Mata Hari Eye of the Day, National Lawyers Guild - Mass. Chapter, NEFAC,  Network for Immigrant and African Americans in Solidarity, Proyecto  Hondureno, Resist the Raids, Sacco and Vanzetti Commemoration Society,  Stop the Wars Coalition, Student Labor Action Movement, Union of  Minority Neighborhoods, Women's Fightback Network, Workers International  League, Workers World Party.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304307206000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Come and show your support for workers' rights by participating in the Boston May Day rally!</why><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303362413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Day Rally</name><id>17382286</id><headcount>1000</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304265600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/17382286/</event_url></item>