<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>221 Daniel Webster Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.828773</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anheuser-Busch</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>7634462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.491196</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dogs of all shapes and sizes, their owners, and families are invited to join the Humane Society for Greater Nashua for their Annual Walktoberfest on Saturday, Oct. 1 from 9 a.m. to 4 p.m. on the grounds of the Anheuser-Busch Brewery. This fundraiser for the Humane Society for Greater Nashua is specially geared toward fun for your family and your pooch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walktoberfest features a morning dog walk, 40 pet-friendly vendors, an area just for kids with games, an obstacle course, face painting, and a photo booth with fun props, dog games with prizes for the winners, and an amazing raffle with more than 100 fabulous prizes. There will also police K-9 Unit demos, as well as two exciting performances by the New England Disc Dog Association and their high flying Frisbee dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The festivities start at 9 a.m. with vendors, entertainment, and registration for the morning dog walk, which starts at 10 a.m. People are encouraged to raise pledges for the walk to help support the shelter’s pets. Start your fundraising page or pledge sheet today by visiting www.hsfn.org. Admission is free to anyone who raises pledges and for those who do not, admission is $5 per person, while kids ages 11 and younger are free. Of course dogs are welcome all day but must be leashed, licensed and up-to-date with all vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Music will be provided throughout the day by DJ Bernie of Perfect Entertainment, and WZID’s Mike Morin will emcee the morning events. There will also be food all day provided by the Common Man and Chef on Wheels as well as a beer tent for those ages 21 and older.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walktoberfest is sponsored by Animal Medical Center of New England, Dell, Petsmart, The Telegraph and many other local businesses. For more information, visit www.hsfn.org or call 889-2275, ext. 27.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349554287000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348700445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua Humane Society Walktoberfest</name><id>84252632</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>25200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349528400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/84252632/</event_url></item>