<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Attention Boston Area Tea Party Patriots:&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a Strategy Meeting.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, November 8th, 3:30 – 5:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is critical that we strategize our group’s activities for the next twelve months.  November 2010 will be here before we know it and we need to be ready to show support for fiscally conservative candidates that advocate for small, limited government; candidates that will respect and defend our freedom and independence.  The time to act is now.  &lt;br /&gt;If you want to be part of the next American Revolution, join us.  We need the ideas and talent of proud, patriotic Americans who believe that the best is yet to come; people that believe we can turn around this leap to the Left that our government has taken and that it is up to the people to lead the charge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the Agenda &amp;#150; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#149; See and Comment on the Mission Statement&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#149; See and Comment on the Organizational structure&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#149; Take a Leading or Participatory role(s) that will make a true difference&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#149; Discuss, Participate and Take a Lead in Function areas, including Events, Recruitment and Communications&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#149; Assist with our Web site and networking/communications tools&lt;br /&gt; Discuss Critical Issues - Including Health Care, Cap and Trade, Immigration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are like so many of us, you are outraged by the actions of the current administration and are shocked by the consistent and methodical abrogation of our freedoms. Again, we cannot afford to waste another minute.  I know I a asking you to give up a Sunday afternoon but it is time to act.  Tea Party groups across Massachusetts are organizing and coordinating efforts.  Let’s get this done.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend.  I will send you a formal agenda and a worksheet to complete before the meeting.  If you have friends or family in the Greater Boston area that would be interested, please forward this to them.  If you are unable to attend but want to take a leadership role in the organization, please contact me. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you,&lt;br /&gt;Christen Varley  gopmom@gopmom.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.  We will have coffee, water &amp;amp; snacks.  Revolutionaries get hungry.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will post signs directing you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christen Varley</member_name><member_id>9247789</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257885589000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256941904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Tea Party Strategy Meeting</name><id>11752211</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257712200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/11752211/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/a/4/global_8615540.jpeg</photo_url></item>