<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/9/6/event_120468022.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Ok...I have been dying to see this ever since I heard that they were thinking of making it.   This will be awesome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Showtime is at 6.  I will be at the theater by 5 and we will head in for seats before 5:30.  Note with this movie they may make us line up before going to the movie.  Do not come late!!!!&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, I arrive at the theater an hour before the show to start gathering people, and we head in for seats about 30 minutes before the show, so we can sit together.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; This also allows us to take turns getting snacks, etc., before the previews start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;The fact that this movie already has tickets for sale should clue you in...this will sell out so do not wait!  I don't want to hear any complaints cause I warned you!  &lt;/span&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after and bring cash.$$$$&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; December 14, 2012 (&lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=40304" style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;/2D theaters and IMAX) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Warner Bros. Pictures &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Peter Jackson &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Fran Walsh, Philippa Boyens, Guillermo del Toro, Peter Jackson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Ian McKellen, Martin Freeman, Cate Blanchett, Orlando Bloom, Ian Holm, Christopher Lee, Hugo Weaving, Elijah Wood, Evangeline Lilly, Andy Serkis, Richard Armitage, John Bell, Jed Brophy, Adam Brown, John Callen, Luke Evans, Stephen Fry, Ryan Gage, Mark Hadlow, Peter Hambleton, Barry Humphries, Stephen Hunter, William Kircher, Sylvester McCoy, Bret McKenzie, Graham McTavish, Mike Mizrahi, James Nesbitt, Dean O'Gorman, Lee Pace, Mikael Persbrandt, Conan Stevens, Ken Stott, Jeffrey Thomas, Aidan Turner, Billy Connolly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Adventure, Fantasy &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thehobbit.com/" target="_blank"&gt;TheHobbit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey" follows title character Bilbo Baggins, who is swept into an epic quest to reclaim the lost Dwarf Kingdom of Erebor, which was long ago conquered by the dragon Smaug. Approached out of the blue by the wizard Gandalf the Grey, Bilbo finds himself joining a company of thirteen dwarves led by the legendary warrior Thorin Oakenshield. Their journey will take them into the Wild; through treacherous lands swarming with Goblins and Orcs, deadly Wargs and Giant Spiders, Shapeshifters and Sorcerers. Although their goal lies to the East and the wastelands of the Lonely Mountain, first they must escape the goblin tunnels, where Bilbo meets the creature that will change his life forever... Gollum. Here, alone with Gollum, on the shores of an underground lake, the unassuming Bilbo Baggins not only discovers depths of guile and courage that surprise even him, he also gains possession of Gollum's "precious" ring that holds unexpected and useful qualities... A simple, gold ring that is tied to the fate of all Middle-earth in ways Bilbo cannot begin to know.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355764135000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337362435000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey (6PM 3D Show)</name><id>65357732</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355608800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/65357732/</event_url></item>