<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Poole Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03452</zip><lat>42.845470</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Monadnock State Park</name><city>Jaffrey</city><id>5518752</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.088676</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I hate to miss autumn leaf-peeping.  If you have Columbus Day off, why not discover the colorful views from atop one of the world's most popular hiking destinations.  Also loved by Emerson and Thoreau, the 3,165ft. Mt. Monadnock is reportedly the second most hiked mountain in the world after Mt. Fuji in Japan. The word "monadnock" originally comes from the Abnacki Indian language meaning "mountain that stands alone."  Because Monadnock "stands alone", views from the treeless summit stretch far into the distance into surrounding states like Vermont and Massachusetts. Boston and the White Mountains are visible on a clear day. Mt. Monadnock forms one end of the roughly 50-mile Monadnock-Sunapee Greenway Trail. It is also the terminus of the 117-mile Monadnock-Metacomet Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is not a beginner's hike!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HIKE PLAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/MonadnockHikingTrailsMap_All_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click here for Mt Monadnock Hiking Trails map&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HIKE RATING:  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Terrain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (easy, average, &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;strenuous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, very strenuous); &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expected Pace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (slower, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;moderate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, fast, very fast); &lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall Difficulty&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: (introductory, easy, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;intermediate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, advanced, expert)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ascent (approx 2.5-3hr, approx. 3.5mi, elev gain=1700ft):&lt;/strong&gt; Beginning at the Park Headquarters area, we will start the ascent on White Dot Trail, passing White Cross Trail on the left to arrive at the Cascade Link.  Turning right onto Cascade, we will proceed just past Birchtoft (red blazed) to Red Spot Trail (also red blazed) to the left.  About half-way up the Red Spot, after the trail blazes disappear for a while, we will encounter a trail fork, to the left is the old Ski Path (leading to the White Dot), we will bear right onto the continuance of the Red Spot trail.  Eventually red spot blazes will appear on the rocks, confirming that we are in fact on the correct trail (trust me - wink).  When the Red Spot terminates into the Pumpelly Trail, we will bear left.  Soon after, only cairns will mark the path up the treeless rock to the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lunch:&lt;/strong&gt; We'll shelter out of the wind for about 15-20min to munch on whatever food we've remembered to pack.  Bring plenty of water (3-4L) and some foods containing protein and carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Descent (approx 1.5hr, 2.2mi, elev loss=1699ft):&lt;/strong&gt; We'll take the most direct way back to the Park Headquarters area, which is the White Cross to the White Dot.  These trails intersect in two places, so it will be a judgement call as to which elevation (2850 or 1700) we will cut over to the White Dot trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is plenty of &lt;strong&gt;general info about Mount Monadnock&lt;/strong&gt; wherever you look, see for example &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Monadnock"&gt;wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/explore/state-parks/monadnock-state-park.aspx"&gt;NHStateParks&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://monadnocktrails.com/"&gt;MonadnockTrails&lt;/a&gt;, etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRAIL MAP:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/MonadnockHikingTrailsMap_All_2010.pdf"&gt;Mt Monadnock Hiking Trails map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment:&lt;/strong&gt; Be prepared for changes of temperature and strong winds on the summit (you will be wet from perspiration so hypothermia is a concern). No cotton is acceptable for this hike and sturdy hiking boots required. Please dress in layers and have a wind jacket.  The wind at the summit is also very strong so the temperatures are much less at the summit, up to 15 degrees cooler than at the base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pets are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; in the park or on the mountain. Please note that this law includes all trails and areas on Mount Monadnock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Those who wish to go &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack - To carry clothing, trail food, water, and any extra items&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Multiple layers of non-cotton clothing (synthetic or wool)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* At least 3-4 quarts (3-4 liters) drinking water&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Hiking boots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Gloves or mittens advised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Glasses or goggles advised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Bug spray advised (to repel ticks, which are found in leaf litter even in winter; see &lt;a href="http://www.health.ny.gov/publications/2737/"&gt;this publication&lt;/a&gt; for discussion of tick and insect repellents)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Camera advised - to capture the stunning 360 degree views&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monadnock State Park may charge a &lt;strong&gt;$4/person entry fee&lt;/strong&gt; if the headquarters is staffed that day. I heard that the fee recently went up to $5/person, but this is unconfirmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking safety and equipment for high peaks: &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questions?&lt;/strong&gt; Call Kevin H at 860-373-0836&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://mapq.st/PIR4aJ"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here for MapQuest directions from Hartford&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>carpools are encouraged.  we will congregate in the Monadnock parking area, look for me holding a Hartford Area Hiking (TM) sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin H</member_name><member_id>10192861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349736725000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349546909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Columbus Day Hike up Mt. Monadnock in Jaffrey NH</name><id>85803062</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349704800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/85803062/</event_url></item>