<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Dorchester</address_2><address_1>934 Dorchester Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.318969</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 436 9747</phone><name>The Banshee Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>1011474</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056477</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Packers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been away for the last couple of weeks but good to hear the pack beat Minnesota, this week’s meet up is scheduled for 1pm on the 2nd floor of the Banshee. The Packers take on the Jets and we are expecting a good crowd, sorry to hear from Elizabeth that their was not a good crowd for the game on Sunday night, (it defiantly is not the case for the earlier Sunday games), I hope you can find the time to come back and check out the Jets game. On a side note we have booked the bus for the Green Bay v Pats game on December 19th, we have 40 names and the bus is full. The tail gate will begin at the Banshee from 1pm on that Sunday, once we arrive in Foxboro the tail gate party will be provided by Raddeberger, tickets for the day are $45.00 per person to be paid on or before the San Francisco game on December 5th, this will include bus (with bathroom), stadium parking, food and beer provided by Raddeberger (on bus and at stadium only). I just need some feed back from you, what time do you want to leave?, If we get to Foxboro for 4pm is this good with everyone ?, please let me know. I will start a list for a second bus if anyone else wants to join in. As usual all feed back welcome, have a great week and hope to see you on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray Butler,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;raybutler2000@earthlink.net&lt;br /&gt;6174369747 bar&lt;br /&gt;6178284350 mobile&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Packers Boston &amp; Ray Butler</member_name><member_id>9971064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288549768000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Greenbaypackersboston</urlname><id>1489502</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Green Bay Packers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288112413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Green Bay v Jets</name><id>15235037</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288544400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Greenbaypackersboston/events/15235037/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/4/0/global_9669904.jpeg</photo_url></item>