<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 wallace street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.304236</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-509-2907</phone><name>Peter house</name><city>rochester</city><id>900638</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.972141</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Trailblazers! Are you a paddler? Load up your canoe or kayak and join the &amp;quot;Spring on the Cocheco&amp;quot; river trip, Saturday, May 16 2009. The three-hour paddling expedition begins in Rochester site on Route 125, running down the Cocheco River and into the Isinglass river. I will have more details of trip latter on. After the trip there is a &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; lunch, where you can munch on as many hamburgers and hot dogs and drink as much as you like, yahoo! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been on this trip every year for the last eight years -- it's a lot of fun!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your own kayak or canoe, their is a good possibility that I might be able to get you a canoe or kayak for free, let me know if you need one and I'll see what I can do. If you know of someone going who has a canoe you can ride with them. There are other canoe and rental dealers in the area who rent them. If anyone know of any let me know and I'll post it on this site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year there were over a hundred and fifty paddlers who went. We had about 30 people come from our meetup group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This fun and informative workshop-on-the-water is sponsored by UNH Cooperative Extension in cooperation with N.H. Fish and Game, the Cocheco River Watershed Coalition and Waste Management of Rochester, New Hampshire. There is no charge for the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will have a shuttle bringing our kayaks and canoes back to the starting point for free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be providing more information about the trip as we get closer to the event. The rain date for this trip will be on May 23 (a week later). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants can bring their watercraft to the put-in site at 9:00 a.m. on Saturday, May 16th (the site will be marked with balloons). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I almost forgot to let everyone know to bring plenty of snacks for your leader! Also to bring a hat and sunglasses and maybe some suntan lotion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Periodic breaks will feature presentations on the subjects of &amp;quot;Fishing the Cocheco and Fish in the Cocheco&amp;quot; by Scott Decker of the N.H. Fish and Game Department; &amp;quot;Watching Birds and Other Wildlife on the Cocheco&amp;quot; by Darrel Covell of UNH Cooperative Extension; &amp;quot;Hunting as a Function of Wildlife Management&amp;quot; by Darrel Covell; and &amp;quot;Hunting on the Cocheco&amp;quot; by Alan Davis of Waste Management of Rochester. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, bags will be available for those who want to pick up trash in the Cocheco River that day. Waste Management will be at the Little Falls Bridge Road to take all of the trash bags to their dump site at the end of the tour. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;U.S. Coast Guard-approved life jackets must be worn on this trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me with the green kayak and a red "meetup" sign."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242652325000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238157716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring on the Cocheco River Trip-Canoeing/Kayaking/Free lunch.</name><id>10048386</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242478800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/10048386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/1/9/global_7853913.jpeg</photo_url></item>