<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For those of you not going to the play "Jesus Christ Superstar", and would rather play with fire ;) I'll know by 5pm if I can have a bonfire, as the town of Pelham, NH only issues permits after 5pm the night you want to have it. &lt;br /&gt;And even though I haven't washed my wood floors down good after this winter, please be cognizant of the shoes you wear (flat soles preferred) as those grooves do carry alot of dirt into my house, or bring slippers or a spare pair please. &lt;br /&gt;Also, bring a chair, and some good food to share, as the cubbard is bare...lol.&amp;nbsp; I'll be busy picking up food pantry bags in the morning and then dragging wood from the forest (if anyone wants to help) prior to 5pm, so no time to cook.&amp;nbsp; I'll provide soda, water, chips + dips,&amp;nbsp;and a sweet treat, possibly some kind of salad someone isn't bringing. BYOB and RED Wine is always&amp;nbsp;a favorite of mine, if you don't want to cook or bring anything to eat.&amp;nbsp; Please let me know in your reply what you are bringing, so others will know as well. &lt;br /&gt;I will email my address and phone number Saturday morning,&amp;nbsp;to those attending...please park on the same side of the street as my home.&amp;nbsp; You are welcome to call, or text preferred,&amp;nbsp;after 5pm, to see if the bonfire is on, or off.&amp;nbsp; If it's a nice night, I do have horseshoes (although after 7pm it's kind of dark out there)&amp;nbsp;and a grill, if you'd like to cook on it (I personally hate cooking on the grill, I just like to eat what others cook ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case of rain, I will cancell outside festivities, but maybe we can play cards or LCR, and I'll let those know who responded, so if you are a "maybe" put yes and update accordingly ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;suz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303088228000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>it's alot of fun, and Deb is a great little organizer and helps me keep my computer, and my parents computer, in good running order ;) a great big THANK YOU!</why><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302525121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Firebug Deb's birthday...bonfire anyone?</name><id>17260938</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302991200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/17260938/</event_url></item>