<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>October User Group:: Selecting A PHP Framework&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How many of us have searched Source Forge for a project that appears to fit our needs only to find there's no community or documentation behind it; or the code is really poorly written; or the project is about to fork...Sometimes selecting an open source project is like renting B-grade movies at the video store; it's not so much the cost that concerns you, but rather the time wasted if you select a dog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join BostonPHP in October when Seth Aaronson will moderate a panel discussion on how to select a robust PHP framework culminating in a &amp;quot;PHP framework bake-off&amp;quot;. BostonPHP members will showcase their respective frameworks:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Justin Hannus - founder of Opifex;&lt;br /&gt;    * Nate Abele - core developer of Cake, and&lt;br /&gt;    * Chuck Hagenbuch - founder of HORDE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each framework will develop a CRUD (create, read, update, delete) catalog application (e.g. products and categories) that we will each show multiple formats (xhtml + some xml, etc).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation will become the foundation of future bake-off/presentations (e.g. Zend, Drupal, Symfony) and the basis of an upcoming article in php|architect. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.BostonPHP.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.BostonPHP.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonPHP....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171779159000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1157672119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston PHP Meetup October Meetup:: Selecting A PHP Framework</name><id>5118227</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1160087400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/5118227/</event_url></item>