<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>401 Park Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.343790</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 424-6266</phone><name>Regal Fenway Stadium 13</name><city>Boston</city><id>669030</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;** FREE ADVANCED SCREENING &amp;amp; DIRECTOR Q&amp;amp;A - HONEYDRIPPER**&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MONDAY, JANUARY 14TH @ 7PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fenway Regal Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;** This special screening will include a reading of &amp;quot;Keeping Time&amp;quot; (the short story that inspired the film) by legendary independent film director, John Sayles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;** There will also be a brief question and answer session following the screening with the film's director, John Sayles and producer, Maggie Renzi following this special advanced screening.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring Danny Glover, Honeydripper has been nominated for two NAACP Image Awards including: Outstanding Independent or Foreign Film, and Outstanding Writing in a Motion Picture.  Film synopsis included below and more information available at &lt;a href="http://www.honeydripper-movie.com" target="_blank"&gt; HONEYDRIPPER&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie pass is located here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/225256/HONEY%20DRIPPER%20Fenway.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Synopsis :&lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Iconoclastic filmmaker John Sayles, in his 16th feature film, continues his extraordinary examination of the complexities and shifting identities of American sub-cultures.  With his usual understated intelligence, Sayles uses the rhythms of the citizens of Harmony, Alabama to immerse the audience into the world of the Jim Crow south.  It's a fable about the birth of rock n' roll-- a quintessentially American subject, but with a fidelity to time and temperament that is unusual in an American director.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's 1950 and it's a make or break weekend for Tyrone Purvis (Glover), the proprietor of the Honeydripper Lounge.  Deep in debt, Tyrone is deperate to bring back the crowds that used to come to his place.  He decides to lay off his long-time blues singer Bertha Mae, and announces that he's hired a famous guitar player, Guitar Sam, for a one night only gig in order to save the club.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Into town drifts Sonny Blake, a young man with nothing to his name but big dreams and the guitar case in his hand.  Rejected by Tyrone when he applies to play at the Honeydripper, he is intercepted by the corrupt local Sheriff, arrested for vagrancy and rented out as an unpaid cotton picker to the highest bidder.  But when Tyrone's ace-in-the-hole fails to materialize at the train station, is desperation leads him back to Sonny and the strange, wire-dangling object in his guitar case.  The Honeydripper lounge is all set to play its part in rock n' roll history.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Running Time:&lt;/b&gt;  123 mins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rated: &lt;/b&gt; PG-13 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directed/Written by:&lt;/b&gt;  John Sayles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cast:&lt;/b&gt;  Danny Glover, Lisa Gay Hamilton, Yaya DaCosta, Charles C. Dutton, Mary Steenburgen, Gay Hamilton, Stacy Keach, Sean Patrick, introducing Gary Clark Jr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opens:&lt;/b&gt; January 18th at Kendall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;[edit by JediFonger]PS there will be no discussion afterwards as it is a weeknight viewing. If you REALLY want to get in&amp;amp;get good seats, get there @6PM. Otherwise, you might not get int @all. That's how these things are usually, it's a huge crowd!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the writer/director's imdb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://imdb.com/name/nm0000626/"&gt;http://imdb.com/name/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh yeah BTW, here is the movie trailer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;object width=&amp;quot;425&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;355&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;embed src=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/v/r7j1M-Rf9-Y&amp;amp;rel=1&amp;quot;"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; type=&amp;quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;425&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;355&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/embed&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/object&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[end edit]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chelsea</member_name><member_id>3861711</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207482683000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Legendary independent film Director John Sayles will be reading "Keeping Time" (the short story that inspired the film) and will also be hosting a brief question and answer session along with the film's producer, Maggie Renzi following the screening.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200066660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>**FREE ADVANCED SCREENING &amp; DIRECTOR Q&amp;A - HONEYDRIPPER**</name><id>7089005</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200355200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7089005/</event_url></item>