<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Cutler Street #102</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02885</zip><lat>41.729534</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>East Bay Chamber of Commerce</name><city>Warren</city><id>7103432</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.278648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Understanding: Applying: Living... the Universal Law of Attraction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come play the game of Life by understanding the Universal Law of Attraction, which states that whatever we think about we bring about. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to embrace a new you, a year filled with unlimited possibilities?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you want to tap into the non-physical spiritual world to access a powerful Source that will help you co-create with the Divine…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we use the law of attraction to the fullest we become a Deliberate creator, we attract from an allowing perspective as opposed to forcing life to happen and living in a place that doesn’t feel good Life transformed into something we’ve dreamed of…relationships manifest, career opportunities manifest, money manifests, friendships manifests, trips manifest, our dreams and our passions manifest, life becomes magical!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connect with others, who are at various levels in Understanding and using the principles of  LOA...it doesn't matter where you are at...if you are being called to be here, you are being guided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We are a group of caring, kind, fun and brilliant individuals who know and live and practice this thought of Leading Edge Consciousness...sharing stories of manifestation and connecting from this unlimited place&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn't matter where you are on your journey, there's power in connecting with others who are also passionate about living life to the fullest!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can be, have or do anything that our heart desires...its a matter of thought...and awareness!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rapid Manifesting...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Vortex... and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The importance of gratitude will be discussed...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Some comments from the Meetup group:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ awesome ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; “ I was very impressed with all of them. A great group of very positive minded people ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; “ Only my first meeting, but if future meetings are like this one I'll attend as many as I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ Love it. Great group of people. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; “ Love it!!! A great way to wrap up a stressful week. Plan on returning. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; “ We're a very eclectic group and should get along very well with all those present contributing something for all the others to learn from. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; “ It was a last minute decision to go to this meetup, and I only knew about the subject matter from a quick read on Wikipedia. lol However, this was such a great group of people, eager to see others in the group do well and grow. I didn't feel like an outsider or unwelcome even a little. I still do not claim to really know anything at all about the Law of Attraction, but I got such a great feeling from this group of people and will be going back again! ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;What a client has said about Nicole’s LOA coaching:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicole's energy is amazing! Her insight and intuition is so accurate and she easily guides me back into feel-good mode when I get off track. By the time we end our coaching session, I am excited to take inspired action - getting me ever closer to my goals and dreams.     Thank you, Nicole!&lt;span&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;                                                                           &lt;/span&gt; Mair Hill, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nicole has participated and studied with a Law of Attraction coach.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; She's been leading law of attraction groups and clients from all over the globe! Currently she has over 400 people in her meetup groups and has helped many on their spiritual journey of understanding.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; She currently teaches many classes, is certified as an Angel Therapy Practitioner through Doreen Virtue, PhD, a Facilitator of the Point of Essence Process for Indigo's, Reiki Master and Crystal Therapist.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; For more info or to book a private consultation she can be reached through her website www.nicoleleblanc.me&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Next to Tom's Market on Child Street</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>8953582</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344449484000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Magnificent Manifestors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors</urlname><id>1552727</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>South Shore Law of Attraction  Manifestors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342313837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connect and Discuss Law of Attraction in Action</name><id>dcpsmcyqlbfb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344034800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors/events/73374782/</event_url></item>