<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet at the Mobile Station on Rt 138 at Exit 8 off of Rt. 495 in Raynham (taunton) at 8:00 am leaving at 8:30 am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2nd pick up at Burger King (Rt 140/Rt 122) in Grafton at 10:00am leave at 10:30am.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We usually wrap up the day around 3-4 pm to head home.  You are welcome to join any/all part of the ride.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For newer members, Gilda Musgrove was the assistant director of South Shore in 2001.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;While on an SSWOW ride to Mt. Graylock in 2001, a car driver, while reaching for a cell phone, crossed the double line and Gilda was killed upon impact.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Each year since, we have a ride to honor Gilda.  The ride goes past the accident site, where we have a memorial marker.  We do not stop, just a slow roll by to pay our respects.  We then turn around, stop for lunch up the street and then proceed onward to the cemetary where we meet up with Gilda's parents (Oscar and Hennie), her sister (Thalia) and brother-in-law (Brian).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This ride is a Celebration of who Gilda was in life and a rememberance of her spirit and ALL are welcome.  Her family is wonderfully spiritual and uplifiting. Those who have been on the ride often comment on how positive an experience it is.  Many never met Gilda but are glad they made the run and were able to meet her very loving and welcoming family. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Saturday morning,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace and Safety,&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie McKoy</member_name><member_id>8747514</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245067633000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bikers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>South-Shore-Women-on-Wheels</urlname><id>1366699</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>South Shore Women On Wheels®</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232915100000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gilda Musgrove Annual Memorial Ride</name><id>9598523</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244894400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Women-on-Wheels/events/9598523/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/b/global_7064827.jpeg</photo_url></item>