<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey all! We usually meet up on the 3rd Tuesday of the month, but lately we've been trying some new things to mix it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of us are planning to hang out at the Red Hat for food/drinks on Saturday, and we thought we'd make it a meetup. The upstairs section of the Red Hat is not usually very crowded on the weekends, so it's a great place for us to meet up and hang out. Come for dinner, drinks, or just the conversation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find us in the BACK section of the UPSTAIRS area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be there at 6:30, but come whenever you can -- I'm sure we'll be there for a few hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can make it! Feel free to bring friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;... The Boston Republican Meetup Group holds social events to give us MA Republicans/Conservatives/Libertarians/etc an opportunity to meet one another. The recent crowds have included a great mix of long-time members and first-time attendees, men and women of all ages!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First timers are always welcome! Feel free to walk right in and introduce yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Worried about how to find us? The place is not usually too crowded and we'll meet in the BACK section UPSTAIRS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most economical parking would be at meters, but there's also the Center Plaza Garage, the Government Center Garage, and the Boston Common Garage for 10-12 bucks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>UPSTAIRS in the back</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick</member_name><member_id>472135</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>4385831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329767613000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Republicans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>republican-94</urlname><id>131129</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Republican Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329269706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend Meetup at the Red Hat</name><id>52386802</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329607800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/republican-94/events/52386802/</event_url></item>