<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sorry for the last minute post, but I can never remember when the Coolidge runs these monthly German films.  It sounds like an interesting plot, so let's see it before Hollywood makes the second-rate remake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Gravity (Schwerkraft):&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the prestigious First Steps Award 2009 and the Max Ophüls Award 2010. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frederik Feinermann is an up-and-coming young bank employee who lives an ordinary life. When a client, whom Frederik has denied a loan due to the bank crisis, shoots himself in front of Frederik, he snaps. Together with ex-con Vince Holland he begins to live out a new, dark side of himself. He robs his rich bank customers' homes and gives the money to the needy. The initial rush of crossing social boundaries soon develops into an addiction to ever greater thrills. Gravity tells the story of a seemingly settled bank employee who breaks the shackles of his everyday life and becomes a wanderer between worlds. Dir. Maximilian Erlenwein, in German with English subtitles, 1h35m, 35mm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the theater exit holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289424387000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gravity (Schwerkraft)</name><id>15407552</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289750400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15407552/</event_url></item>