<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join our own Dave Homa (who has done pruning professionally) in learning how to &lt;b&gt;prune your apple trees while they are in their winter dormancy&lt;/b&gt; in order to improve their ongoing health and productivity.  Dave will be running this skillshare at Aaron Parker's house (aka The Bike Barn) in West Falmouth - about 25 min from downtown Portland. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will include discussion of techniques, common mistakes and suggested tools.  Handouts provided.  The session is expected to run about 3 to 3.5h and will be followed by the sharing of a potluck meal (please bring a dish to share). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rain/Snow Date is Jan 31, same time&lt;/b&gt;.  Space is limited.  If this fills up quickly and you still want to get in on this, please email the meetup organizer to start a list for running a possible repeat event! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)! Please consider bringing your digital camera and posting up a few photos after the event!  Potluck food safety ideas here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fycs.ifas.ufl.edu/news/2007/potluck.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://fycs.ifas.ufl....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress in layers for the weather.  We will have access to covered/heated spaces to warm up if needed.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please park on the side road just *before* the house rather than on Blackstrap Rd itself!  Thx.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263924665000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262716104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare:  Apple Tree Pruning</name><id>12229998</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263751200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/12229998/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/f/global_12513631.jpeg</photo_url></item>