<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>TUESDAY NIGHTS................ 6 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you come late, just paddle around the corner from the put-in, paddle out under the Seabrook Harbor bridge and you should be able to find us in the bowl or just around the corner.&lt;br /&gt;On Hampton Beach to the left or Seabrook Beach to the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free form skill session to practice in the ocean. Much of the session will likely focus on surfing skills, but it is not limited to that. The Seabrook Harbor &amp;quot;bowl&amp;quot; offers a very safe place to learn basic kayak surf technique and boat handling skills in the surf zone. The &amp;quot;bowl&amp;quot; is shallow water and self rescue is very easy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some weeks, the group may opt to head out of the harbor into the open ocean for surfing on Seabrook or Hampton Beach. We will also practice open water self and assisted rescues, towing and other basic kayak skills from time to time, depending on the desires of the group. Seabrook&lt;br /&gt;The Harbor is a safe place to work on skills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put-in is at Seabrook Harbor, Seabrook Beach, NH on the Seabrook side of the Hampton Bridge on Rte 1A in the large parking lot with a restroom, open from Memorial Day to Labor Day. The parking area is FREE parking with easy access to a sandy beach launch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See You There ........................... Bill Harter, Doug Mogill and Sal Puglisi&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Harter</member_name><member_id>7618241</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Mogill</member_name><member_id>7760142</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279723077000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278500828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seabrook Harbor + Ocean Skill + Surf Session</name><id>gnfwnynkbbc</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279663200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/14026365/</event_url></item>