<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4802 N Us Highway 301</address_1><state>Fl</state><zip>33610</zip><lat>27.993555</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>4802 N Us Highway 301</name><city>Tampa</city><id>7848962</id><country>us</country><lon>-82.364647</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;*Updated July 23rd* From &lt;a href="http://www.paulfestival.org/"&gt;http://www.paulfestival.org/&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul Festival... Music &amp;amp; Liberty From the organizers of R3VOLUTION March 2008. We proudly bring you "Paul Festival" The Largest Celebration of LIBERTY The World Has Ever Seen!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, in the spirit of that March in 2008,  several members of the original team of organizers have reunited with other proven grassroots activists in creating another hallmark "Paul Event" - an event which is sure to mark the beginning of a new era in the freedom movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the words of Dr. Paul:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...if you ever can bring about revolutionary changes, two things would be required:  young people would have to be involved and you would need music."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Dr. Paul's growing support among celebrities and musicians, it is our hope to accommodate that change through a momentous 3-day Festival which will include many of Dr. Paul's  celebrity-supporters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to have musical acts (of different genres), comedy, speakers, celebrity appearances with pictures and autographs, book signings, big screens showing Dr. Paul's famous speeches, vendors of all sorts, and really great food!  It will be all inclusive - family friendly during the day, and anything that is adult oriented will be held during the evening hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is our belief that this will be the biggest celebration of Liberty the world has ever seen - a tribute to Ron Paul and  the message of freedom.  Be a part of history!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in volunteering or being a part of this event, please feel free to contact us via this form: &lt;a href="http://www.paulfestival.org/contact-us/volunteers/volunteers/volunteers-2"&gt;Volunteers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.itickets.com/events/286777/Tampa_FL/Paul_Festival.html"&gt;Purchase tickets here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Festival Ticket Price Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Event Pass (3 days) - regular price $70.00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Single Day Ticket - regular price $35.00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***Combination Tent Camping/Paul Festival Ticket $175.00:*** &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Includes 1 Festival ticket and camping for up to 8 campers. &lt;br /&gt;

Purchase ONE Combo ticket and ask seven of your Paul Festival ticket-holding friends to join you - up to 8 per campsite!.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VIP Passes - $450.00 (limited availability)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FREE for credentialed Delegates to the RNC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early Bird Price (Before June 30th) - $199.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Before July 31st cut off - $450.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After Aug. 1st and at the door - $550.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;VIP Passes include:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paul Festival T-Shirt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VIP lines for food/drink&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VIP only lounge area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VIP first access to photos/signatures with bands and acts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free soda throughout event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special seating at select events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discount ticket qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ticket holders must provide valid proof of ID/ Badge at the gate, or they will have to pay the difference for the full AT-THE-DOOR price for admittance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Military, students, and first responders - show badge or ID at the door.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veterans - show proof of service (discharge papers along w/ photo ID, or past photo of self in uniform, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oathkeepers - show membership card and photo ID.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Peter Schiff:&lt;/strong&gt; CEO &amp;amp; Chief Global Strategist for &lt;a href="http://www.europac.net" target="_blank"&gt;Euro Pacific Capital&lt;/a&gt;, TV/Radio Personality, Author. We love &lt;a href="http://www.schiffradio.com" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Schiff&lt;/a&gt;, a true American hero. We make Schiff happen... 2016? &lt;a href="http://www.schiffradio.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.schiffradio.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Gov. Gary Johnson:&lt;/strong&gt; Former Governor of New Mexico, GOP Presidential Candidate 2012 and Libertarian Party Presidential Candidate 2012 &lt;a href="http://www.garyjohnson2012.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.garyjohnson2012.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lew Rockwell:&lt;/strong&gt; Best-selling author, former Chief of Staff to Congressman Ron Paul and founder of the well-known libertarian website &lt;a href="http://www.LewRockwell.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.lewrockwell.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Chuck Baldwin:&lt;/strong&gt; Former Constitutional Party Presidential candidate, pastor, author and radio show host&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.chuckbaldwinlive.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.chuckbaldwinlive.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Thomas Woods:&lt;/strong&gt; Historian, Economist, Political Analyst &lt;a href="http://www.tomwoods.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.tomwoods.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Michael Scheuer:&lt;/strong&gt; Former CIA intelligence Officer &lt;a href="http://non-intervention.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.non-intervention.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Gary Franchi:&lt;/strong&gt; One of the emcee's for Paul Festival, Franchi is the founder of "&lt;a href="http://www.rtr.org" target="_blank"&gt;Restore the Republic&lt;/a&gt;” &lt;a href="http://www.rtr.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.rtr.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walter Block&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Economist, author and Senior Faculty at the Ludwig von Mises Institute. Block has been a strong supporter of Ron Paul and libertarian ideals. &lt;a href="http://www.walterblock.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.walterblock.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Adrian Moore, Ph.D.:&lt;/strong&gt; Vice President of Policy at &lt;a href="http://reason.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Reason Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, a non-profit think tank advancing free minds and free markets. &lt;a href="http://reason.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.reason.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://theministeroftruth.blogspot.de" target="_blank"&gt;T.M.O.T.&lt;/a&gt; Derrick Grayson:&lt;/strong&gt; Minister with popular videos on YouTube focused on Ron Paul and the Liberty Movement &lt;a href="http://theministeroftruth.blogspot.de" target="_blank"&gt;www.theministeroftruth.blogspot.de&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Jerry Doyle &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Nationally syndicated talk radio host and well-known actor. Doyle publicly endorsed Ron Paul in his bid for the Presidency. &lt;a href="http://www.jerrydoyle.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.jerrydoyle.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Larry Pratt&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Executive Director of Gun Owners of America, which has been dubbed, "The only no-compromise gun lobby in Washington," by Ron Paul himself. &lt;a href="http://www.gunowners.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.gunowners.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stewart Rhodes:&lt;/strong&gt; Founder and President of Oath Keepers &lt;a href="http://oathkeepers.org/oath/bios" target="_blank"&gt;www.oathkeepers.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Gigi Bowman:&lt;/strong&gt; President and Founder of Liberty-Candidates.org &lt;a href="http://www.libertycandidates.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.libertycandidates.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Sheriff Richard Mack:&lt;/strong&gt; Former Arizona Sheriff and current Congressional candidate in Texas’ 21st district. &lt;a href="http://sheriffmack.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.sheriffmack.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Scott Horton:&lt;/strong&gt; Host of the Scott Horton Radio Show. &lt;a href="http://scotthortonshow.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.scotthortonshow.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;David J. Theroux:&lt;/strong&gt; Founder and President of The Independent Institute and Publisher of the quarterly journal, The Independent Review, all dedicated to boldly advance peaceful, prosperous and free societies. "&lt;em&gt;The top-notch Independent Institute stands steadfastly for liberty.&lt;/em&gt;"—Ron Paul 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Pop, Rock and Mixed Metal:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;The Red Jumpsuit Apparatus:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.redjumpsuit.com" target="_blank"&gt;Internationally acclaimed&lt;/a&gt; rock band based in Florida.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.redjumpsuit.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.redjumpsuit.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ron Keel:&lt;/strong&gt; Vocalist and guitarist for a number of bands from the 1980s to the modern day, including the glam metal band Keel. &lt;a href="http://ronkeel.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.ronkeel.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Jordan Page:&lt;/strong&gt; Musician who has appeared alongside Ron Paul. Page has been featured on numerous news and talk show programs such as Fox News Live and Freedom Watch. &lt;a href="http://www.jordanpagemusic.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.jordanpagemusic.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;REBEL Inc.:&lt;/strong&gt; An &lt;a href="http://rebelincmusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;intense rock band&lt;/a&gt; formed on the outskirts of Detroit, MI, now residing in Baltimore, MD.  &lt;a href="http://www.rebelincmusic.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.rebelincmusic.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Tatiana Moroz:&lt;/strong&gt; Musician whose recent LP was entitled, "&lt;a href="http://www.tatianamoroz.com" target="_blank"&gt;Love and Liberty.&lt;/a&gt;" Tatiana has performed at numerous events and rallies, including the recent Veterans March on Washington, DC. &lt;a href="http://www.tatianamoroz.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.tatianamoroz.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Deadbeatz Inc.:&lt;/strong&gt; Band whose &lt;a href="http://deadbeatzinc.bandcamp.com/" target="_blank"&gt;unique style&lt;/a&gt; blends  hip-hop, dance, reggae, funk and country.  &lt;a href="http://deadbeatzinc.bandcamp.com" target="_blank"&gt;deadbeatzinc.bandcamp.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Corrected Axiom:&lt;/strong&gt; or CO-AX. The idea being to correct what is perceived to be the truth and to act as the hip-hop/rock music representation of the liberty movement. &lt;a href="https://www.reverbnation.com/correctedaxiom" target="_blank"&gt;www.reverbnation.com/correctedaxiom&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Look What I Did:&lt;/strong&gt; A melodic mathcore band from Nashville, TN with over 11 full US tours over 11 years.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Prince Vega:&lt;/strong&gt; Hiphop/Rock musician and contributor for Infowars.com  &lt;a href="http://www.princevega.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.princevega.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Andi Hayes:&lt;/strong&gt; Rock singer known for garage and Gothic style music. &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/andihayes" target="_blank"&gt;www.myspace.com/andihayes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Circle II Circle:&lt;/strong&gt; CircleIICircle features the voice of Atlantic Records recording artists Savatage from 1992-2000, Zak Stevens. CIIC was formed in 2002 and has five world-wide releases to its credit over the last eight years &lt;a href="http://www.circle2circle.net" target="_blank"&gt;www.circle2circle.net&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Revolution:&lt;/strong&gt; An eclectic mix of nu-metal, hard rock, progressive, classical, and alternative influences, Revolution brings a fresh touch to the rock music scene. &lt;a href="http://www.revolutionofficial.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.revolutionofficial.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Vonabell:&lt;/strong&gt; She started singing as a child and has continued a dedicated path towards full time performing. Her experiences have included auditioning for major reality shows such as completing four rounds on American Idol two years in a row, making 3 qualifying rounds for the X factor. &lt;a href="http://vonabells.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.vonabells.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Heartless:&lt;/strong&gt; HEARTLESS performs Motown, Blues &amp;amp; Classic Rock from Janis Joplin to Kid Rock. Since 2002, HEARTLESS has been a favorite of audiences of all ages who know they can count on a memorable musical experience. &lt;a href="http://www.thebandheartless.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.thebandheartless.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Split Image:&lt;/strong&gt; This is definitely the band to see as 2012 brings new life to the band. Split Image has formally announced the return of vocalist Scott Yson and drummer extraordinaire Randy Van Patten back to the lineup for a new CD due by the end of the year from Retrospect Records. &lt;a href="http://www.splitimagerocks.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.splitimagerocks.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;LA Pussycat:&lt;/strong&gt; Fun, Glamrock, "sleeze" Band. &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/LA-PUSSYCAT/221493751224965" target="_blank"&gt;www.facebook.com/pages/LA-PUSSYCAT&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Tami Gosnell:&lt;/strong&gt; Musician/songwriter known for her audition on American Idol. &lt;a href="http://tamigosnell.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.tamigosnell.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Hawkboy:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/Tomahawkboy"&gt;www.facebook.com/Tomahawkboy&lt;/a&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345997516000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340374779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paul Festival 2012 Tampa, FL August 24-26th</name><id>70269232</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>187200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345809600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/70269232/</event_url></item>