<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>South End</address_2><address_1>541 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.344283</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-423-0069</phone><name>Beehive</name><city>Boston</city><id>709171</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071013</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From the Beehive's website: &lt;br /&gt;On Wednesday, May 26th, 2010, The Beehive presents &amp;quot;Belly Dancing at The Beehive,&amp;quot; featuring cuisine, libations and entertainment highlighting Middle Eastern culture. Join The Beehive for a celebration of Middle Eastern music and belly dancing featuring music by The Pharohs and nationally known belly dancer Phaedra Rose. &lt;br /&gt;The soul of the Middle East comes alive at 8:00PM with the sounds of The Pharohs, an international Armenian &amp;amp; Middle Eastern ensemble inspired by Middle Eastern, Arabic, Greek, Armenian and Israeli music. While The Pharohs perform watch a mesmerizing belly dance performance by the steamy, seductive and mystical belly dancer, Phaedra Rose. Come and enjoy the lovely melodies of the evening with Executive Chef Rebecca Newell's perfectly accompanied Middle Eastern fare with specials such as lamb filled Moroccan cigars, mezze platters and The Beehive's house cous cous. Enjoy some of The Beehive's summer cocktails such as their Pomegranate and Apricot Martinis ($11.50) or relax with an ice cold Harpoon beer from the event's sponsor.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the downstairs bar.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274920646000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274814978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buzz over to the Beehive May 26th at 7:30ish </name><id>13592451</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274916600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/13592451/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/8/global_10607608.jpeg</photo_url></item>