<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 New Park Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.747196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>8602366677</phone><name>Bowtie Cinema</name><city>Hartford</city><id>522813</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.713264</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yes, I know this group just saw Avatar but I was out of town so I'm hoping there may be a few people left who still haven't seen it and/or still want to.  For those who have already seen it, choose from one of the other movies playing at this theater and meet us afterward for dinner.  Not into a movie, just meet us for dinner.  For dinner/drinks we'll go to the Corner Pug, 1046 New Britain Avenue, West Hartford, CT 06110     TEL: 860-231-0241      &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.cornerpug.com/ordereze/Default.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cornerpug.com/ordereze/Default.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cornerpug....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Avatar: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;The movie is at 7pm so let's meet no later than 6:45.  As I'm sure you know, this is a very popular movie so you might want to consider getting your ticket in advance. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AVATAR takes us to a spectacular world beyond imagination, where a reluctant hero embarks on an epic adventure, ultimately fighting to save the alien world he has learned to call home. James Cameron, the Oscar-winning director of “Titanic,” first conceived the film 15 years ago, when the means to realize his vision did not exist yet. Now, after four years of production, AVATAR, a live action film with a new generation of special effects, delivers a fully immersive cinematic experience of a new kind, where the revolutionary technology invented to make the film disappears into the emotion of the characters and the sweep of the story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Sam Worthington, Zoe Saldana, Sigourney Weaver, Stephen Lang, Michelle Rodriguez, Giovanni Ribisi, Joel David Moore &lt;br /&gt;Director: James Cameron &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263793238000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263157115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Avatar in 3D - Movie and a Late Dinner/Drinks</name><id>12279273</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263599100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/12279273/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/9/3/global_12567987.jpeg</photo_url></item>