<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;(2010) Directed by Darren Aronofsky. Screenplay by Mark Heyman, Andr&amp;eacute;s Heinz and John McLaughlin. Choreography by Benjamin Millepied. Cast: Natalie Portman, Vincent Cassel, Mila Kunis, Barbara Hershey, Winona Ryder. Black Swan is the movie that has catapulted Darren Aronofsky to the ranks of top American filmmakers. While indie movie lovers championed Pi and Requiem for a Dream, and mainstream Hollywood cheered The Wrestler, Black Swan brings together Aronofsky&amp;rsquo;s intense originality with a new, dazzling virtuosity. Natalie Portman stars as a member of the corps at the New York City Ballet, whose dream of dancing the dual roles of Odette and Odile in Tchaikovsky&amp;rsquo;s Swan Lake turns to dangerous obsession. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m here to tell you that I found Black Swan&amp;rsquo;s tale of madness, music and sexual repression utterly overpowering from the first few frames of the film. One of the best films of the year&amp;rdquo; - Andrew O&amp;rsquo;Hehir, Salon.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300333659000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Several people said they hadn't seen it.  Cross posted on Hartford Area Movie Meetup.</why><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299100674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Black Swan</name><id>16771835</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300317300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/16771835/</event_url></item>