<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;--Edit: I've managed to borrow a few more chairs so the RSVP limit has been increased.  If you would like to come and we have reached the limit again, just give me a call that day.  I expect people to arrive and leave throughout the day --&gt;

Everyone cooks too much of something for Thanksgiving.  Well, now you can unload that unwelcome dish and play some games to boot.  Bring anything you don't want, or bring nothing at all (some body's got to eat it all).

Games will be provided but feel free to bring or favorites (or that one you never got to play).  We have all day so you can even bring those longer games.

I have comfortable table space for 12-16, but only comfortable chairs for about 10.  I should be able to scrounge up a few more, but feel free to call me about the chair status.


Directions:

Subway:  I live on the "B" line between the Chiswick Road Station and the Sutherland Street Station (3-5 min walk from either).  Easy 10-15 min walk from both the "E" Cleveland Circle Station and the "D" Reservoir Station.

Driving:  The closest parking is unfortunately resident only, but there is plenty only a 3-5 min walk away on Comm Ave.  For backup try Wallingford.  You can swing by my place to drop things off and pick me up to help you find a place if needed.  

Call me if you would like more specifics.


Ben 617-997-3545


P.S.  I have a gas stove/oven, a crockpot, a smallish microwave, and a fondue pot if you want to bring anything that needs heating up.  Just give me a call to make arrangements.</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Warmus</member_name><member_id>5401423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228351665000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224467098000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Leftover pot luck</name><id>8992912</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227891600000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/8992912/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>