<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Rogers Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03904</zip><lat>43.097225</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kittery Community Center - Star Theatre</name><city>Kittery </city><id>12465312</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.737495</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Turnip the Beet for Sustainability: Green Living Fair &amp;amp; Concert!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Saturday, May 4, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kittery Community Center - Star Theatre&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;120 Rogers Rd, Kittery , ME (map)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the eve of International Permaculture Day, bring your family and celebrate with globetrotting permaculture troubadour, Charlie Mgee, of Formidable Vegetable Soundsystem!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIME: doors open at 6pm for an Environmental Fair - local groups will table, give out info, and have some demonstrations - including live animals! Music starts at 7pm with local talent, Andrea Szirbik, then we'll move on to our main attraction, Charlie Mgee with his 12 songs of permaculture!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COST: $15 at the door OR $10 ahead of time from Amy or available mid-April at: &lt;a href="http://www.kitterycommunitycenter.org/star-theatre" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.kitterycommunitycenter.org/star-theatre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kids under 12 get in free (but do need a ticket)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This concert is a collaboration of the Greater Seacoast Permaculture Group &amp;amp; WSCA LP-FM Portsmouth Community Radio. It will kick-off WSCA's spring membership drive. In appreciation of our participation WSCA is going to donate $1 of every new membership that week to our permaculture group!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MORE ABOUT CHARLIE MGEE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Formidable Vegetable Soundsystem is an uplifting new experiment in ‘ecological edutainment’ that mashes together speakeasy electroswing-style wonk and live vocabulous ukulele quirk that aims to pound simple solutions of sustainability deep into your consciousness with a decent serving of Radish Beets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With music being one of the best tools for getting the word out there, globetrotting permaculture troubadour Charlie Mgee has dedicated the last couple of years to composing a repertoire of swingin’ tunes on a ukulele, addressing the 12 principles of permaculture in various musical styles ranging from ‘energy-descent electroswing’ and ‘climate-change reggae’ to ‘peak-oil polka.’ It all makes for an eccentrically entertaining, if not unforgettable, dance floor experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a world gone heckers, here’s one thing you can do for a better future: Lettuce turnip the beet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preview Charlie's music here: &lt;a href="http://formidablevegetable.bandcamp.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://formidablevegetable.bandcamp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Permaculture - a Rhymer's Manual uses the power of music, rhyme and humor to convey the permaculture principles in fresh ways to new audiences. Charlie Mgee is clearly a talented composer and performer, but his lyrics are also true to the complex systems thinking that is permaculture. Highly recommended as an educational resource useful in both introducing principles for the first time or consolidating understanding by permies from 8 to 80. To have the author of this framework of principles singing along rather than cringing at pop simplification is a rare achievement. Go Charlie!” -David Holmgren – Co-originator of the Permaculture concept&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "One of the most innovative and inspiring permaculture teaching tools I've ever encountered" - Earth Garden Magazine&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boiester</member_name><member_id>8570902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368585242000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365257873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turnip the Beet for Sustainability: Green Living Fair &amp; Concert!</name><id>112989072</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367704800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/112989072/</event_url></item>