<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>New Haven</address_2><address_1>50 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304424</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artspace</name><city>New Haven</city><id>176796</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.925110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'll show up at 6, though the activities go from 5pm to midnight. Grand opening reception for the 3 week City Wide Open Studios (www.cwos.org) Art Festival, with a block party and music in various venues (Cafe 9, etc), and LAMP (Light Artists Making Places), a set of indoor &amp;amp; outdoor multi-media displays incorporating light, projection, music, and dance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RAIN: It may rain. I'm still going.&amp;nbsp; Several events are indoors, and some forecasts say it will be clearing at night. Bring an umbrella though.&amp;nbsp; Or don't.&amp;nbsp; But I will be!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may link-up with another Meetup that is going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOST: Jason, cell # in RSVP. Texting is fine too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MORE DETAILS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Pick up maps for L.A.M.P. at Project Storefronts, 100 Crown St. LAMP includes over 30 artists in 10 sites in a two block radius each hosting a unique multi-media installation. Local galleries and merchants along the route and residents will also participate and show their support by shining a light and staying open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Local artists will use a range of devices from flashlights, viewfinders, slides, dead and vintage technologies to lasers, cutting edge light sources, and solar installations merged with dance, music and performance exploring light. There will be glowing tour guides and light spinning performers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Step Kids will be performing at Cafe 9 (cafenine.com) at 10pm delivering a Fusion of punk, jazz, West African traditional, 1960's folk, neo and classical soul, classic funk and 20th century classical. Live kaleidoscopic projections by NYC artist Jesse Mann consume the stage with light for a multi-sensory experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318634234000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318352514000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fri 10/14 - Free art reception, light show, block party, &amp; music</name><id>36981052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318629600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/36981052/</event_url></item>