<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Financial District Faneuil Hall area</address_2><address_1>160 Milk Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-451-9460</phone><name>Jose McIntyre's</name><city>Boston</city><id>326634</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052719</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is going to a vital game for the New England Patriots. Payton Manning and the Colts are one of only two undefeated teams left in the NFL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come watch this clash of the titans - two of the very best quarterbacks (Payton Manning and Tom Brady) and teams in the NFL (The Colts and The Patriots).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The game begins at 8:20PM but you'll need to get there earlier to help me with saving seats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Jose McIntyre's:&lt;br /&gt;Jose McIntyre's is located across from the Aquarium on Milk Street. This is Boston's only Mexican-Irish bar, specializing in 60oz Margaritas, which are perfect for sharing. Come on in the afternoon to watch the game, after work to unwind, or at night when Jose Mc's transforms into a lively and exciting dance/bar. This bar has a total of 5 rooms, 3.5 bars, 2 floors, 5 big screen TV's and a pool table. The newest room is the perfect place to relax after work with co-workers on big comfy couches and a smoothing atmosphere. The fare is a concoction of Mexican, Irish, Vegetarian, classic New England seafood and American favorites. Whoever you are, whatever you do, Jose's has something for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great sports bar!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258518478000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257214897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Big Game!! Sunday Night Football - Patriots vs. Peyton Manning and The Colts. </name><id>11777811</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258329600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11777811/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/1/global_11617761.jpeg</photo_url></item>