<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>380 Winter Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-7800</phone><name>Best Western</name><city>Waltham</city><id>746917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.258767</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.Bostonareia.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Craft, CPA will discuss the top 10 mistakes even your tax professional can make!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s your money!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So no one is going to watch it like you will!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don’t have to know every detail of how your accountant does your taxes but you know what they say: You don’t know what you don’t know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come and find out! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It may change your investing life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Craft will speak about the tax implications of real estate investing. He will cover topics such as:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to exclude the gain on a rental property &lt;br /&gt;How to know when you are keeping the property too long &lt;br /&gt;How to own real estate and maximize tax benefits; &lt;br /&gt;Tax advantages of seeking investor status in real estate transactions; &lt;br /&gt;Dealer status and how it is taxed differently; and, &lt;br /&gt;Using cost-segregation to lower your tax liability. &lt;br /&gt;Do you sell the building, or the entity that holds the building? Which is better for you? &lt;br /&gt;When to plan for higher capital gains tax rates &lt;br /&gt;Be careful how you limit risk – it can cost you &lt;br /&gt;How to treat your business like a business &lt;br /&gt;Tax ramifications of options – both buying and selling &lt;br /&gt;Can you take 100% depreciation on that office furniture – (hint: when you can write off the whole amount NOW) &lt;br /&gt;Land improvements and why they are not land, and not a building, and why you care &lt;br /&gt;And lots more!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe gives real-world information that you can use today, to keep more in your pocket. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Learn why it’s not what you make that matters, its what you keep that matters most.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Downstairs in the ballroom</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295624310000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>82</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294778265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LOTS OF TAX CHANGES IN 2011 - ARE YOU PREPARED?</name><id>16011613</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295562600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/16011613/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/f/global_16134911.jpeg</photo_url></item>