<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Minna-san,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's hot out, it's muggy, why stay in the city when you could go enjoy a wonderful day at the park?  Well, why don't you join us this upcoming Saturday for a barbecue, fishing, swimming, frisbee, or anything else you would like to do over at Cochituate State Park, just a bit west of Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Swimming&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring a bathing suit for swimming, and there are bathrooms at the park as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fishing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone is interested in fishing or learning how to fish, let me know.  I will also bring two extra fishing rods, and should have enough gear to keep you happy.  I don't have any live bait, so feel free to bring your own if you want.  Also, if you don't have a Massachusetts fishing license, you can purchase a 3-day license for $7.50 from this website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sport.state.ma.us/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sport.stat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Volunteering&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will need everyone to cooperate a bit in getting together food, drinks, and other lunch items.  Everyone should bring something to for themselves to eat and/or barbecue, but I also need some volunteers to bring the following items:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paper Plates: Rob S.&lt;br /&gt;Plastic Fork, Knives: maybe Rob S. (I'll see what I can find)&lt;br /&gt;Charcoal: Brian&lt;br /&gt;Spatula: Brian&lt;br /&gt;Napkins: maybe Rob S.&lt;br /&gt;Skewers: haikuguy&lt;br /&gt;Extra Spatula: Rob S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Extra Food (to share):&lt;br /&gt;Evan Owens - various munchies&lt;br /&gt;Jim Zhu - Chips&lt;br /&gt;Alisa - food (don't know what :P )&lt;br /&gt;Charlie - sausages&lt;br /&gt;Rob - (if I can get to the supermarket in time) hot dogs and hot dog buns&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Extra Drinks (to share):&lt;br /&gt;Jim Zhu - soft drinks&lt;br /&gt;Paul - beverages&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will keep updating this post as I receive volunteers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the park:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cochituate State Park is located in the greater Boston area in eastern Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;From East or West: Massachusetts Turnpike (Rte. I-90) to exit 13, Rte. 30 east. Park is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;From Mass Pike:&lt;/u&gt; Take the Mass Turnpike (Rt. I-90) to Exit 13 to Rt. 30 East. The park is ½ mile down on the on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;From Route 9:&lt;/u&gt; Follow Route 9 East or West to the Speen Street exit in Framingham. Go North on Speen Street. Follow Speen Street for 1 mile until you come to Route 30. Turn right onto Route 30. Park is 200 yards down on the right hand side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Available Transportation:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a car and are willing to transport people, please let me know by e-mail me through the meetup page or by posting to our message boards.  If you need a ride, also please let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian will bring a car and has room for 4 people.  I will find out where he plans to meet everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also take my car, and have room left for 1 person.  I live in N. Quincy off of the red line, and can either meet at my home, or over in front of MIT at Mass Ave. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fees&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It costs $5 to park at the Cochituate State Park, so if you are riding in someone's car, please bring a few dollars to help pay for parking and for gasoline.  There are also boats to rent at the park that cost about $15 per hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.  Everyone be extra nice to Brian for coming up with and organizing this event!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park/meet near the kayak rental and boat ramp - I will have my phone with me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217255694000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216487774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Barbecue, Fishing, Swimming, Sports, etc. @ Cochituate State Park!</name><id>8371033</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217082600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/8371033/</event_url></item>