<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 North St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.244400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tosca</name><city>Hingham</city><id>1087154</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.884600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Every year, restaurants in the Greater Boston area participate in the Super Hunger Brunch to benefit the Greater Boston Food Bank. This year, SSDOMG will be joining the diners at Tosca in Hingham - a restaurant that is consistently ranked in the top tier of South Shore dining establishments - as we participate in our first charitable event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Restaurants in the SHB each offer a brunch of their own devising at a fixed price. Brunch at Tosca for this event will be $35.00 and we expect the food to show the kind of creativity and quality that Tosca's offerings are known for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that since this is a charitable event, Angela has decided that our usual event fee of $2.00 will &lt;b&gt;NOT&lt;/b&gt; be charged. You will be able to pay for the brunch when you first come in, either in cash or with a major credit card.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special note on gratuities: The waitstaff are donating any gratuities they may receive to the SHB. Should you wish to leave a tip, it will be an extra donation to the SHB.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us as we sample the fare at one of the South Shore's top dining destinations and help a local cause at the same time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where and When:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tosca, 14 North St., Hingham, MA, 02043&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, January 27, 10:45 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price: $35.00, payable by cash or credit card when you come in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Handicap Accessible: Yes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Maximum of 16 diners.  Group Members Only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline: Monday, Jan 21 @ 7:00 PM.&lt;/b&gt; We are setting the RSVP deadline much earlier than usual because this is a charitable event and the number of people that the restaurant can accommodate is limited! Tosca needs an accurate and timely count for this event! If you need to change your RSVP after this date, please contact Mike or Angela directly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Route 3: From Route 3, take Exit 14 (Rockland, Nantasket) to Route 228 North&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 228 North to Route 3A North&lt;br /&gt;At the set of lights, go left, continuing on Route 3A&lt;br /&gt;Follow 3A for about a mile, until the rotary&lt;br /&gt;Take the second right out of the rotary&lt;br /&gt;Go left at the next set of lights (Stars is on the corner)&lt;br /&gt;TOSCA is on the left, STARS and CAFFE TOSCA are on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The names "Mike" and "South Shore Meetup Group" will be noted with our reservation.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202049112000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199426062000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Hunger Brunch!</name><id>7028244</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201448700000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7028244/</event_url></item>