<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Across from Copley Sq.</address_2><address_1>545 Boylston St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>627-638-9699</phone><name>Vlora</name><city>Boston</city><id>895794</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vlora is a wonderful space with a fantastic Mediterranean menu and an extensive wine list, right in the heart of the Back Bay.  Authentic Mediterranean fare finally has a  home in the Back Bay. Vlora is located in a trendy subterranean space on Boylston Street, right across the street from Copley Square (just below GNC). You can't beat the location! Because of it's lower level local it's a real hidden gem!!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we can get a large group to come, they'll work with us by proving us with hors d'oeuvres.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at the bar for wine tasting and/or white or red sangria and/or beer.  And... if you want, some tapas and/or dinner as we did at Stix. You'll really love Vlora! The staff is friendly and extremely accommodating. And the food Delish....!  I really like this place a lot. And it's family owned and run by a husband and wife and this is their only venue.  Their desire is to bring a real neighborhood place to Boylston and that means it's all about the food and the people. I also like that Cinque Terre Italy is featured on the wall there, a place I know well.  I'm telling you it's a good omen :) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Vlora Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;www.vloraboston.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;545 Boylston St (Right across the street from Copley Sq. (just below GNC)&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02116&lt;br /&gt;(617) 638-9699&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of Boston's Back Bay (Boylston Street and Clarendon Street), Vlora restaurant focuses on truly authentic Mediterranean cuisine that is characterized by an emphasis on flavors and taste and the use of the freshest ingredients. Owned and operated by husband and wife team Aldo Velaj and Cindy Tsai, the restaurant is named after Aldo's home town. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu stems largely from the Northern Mediterranean region of Southern Italy, Greece and Albania. The Restaurant's cozy subterranean location and trendy atmosphere mimic the lounges prevalent in NYC and Paris, Milan and Florance. Featuring an extensive yet reasonably priced wine and beer menu, the restaurant also offers food from 7am until 1 am seven days a week. GUYS... here's a late-night venue!!! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be there and Hope to see you at Vlora!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Need to RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237147304000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236296244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine Tasting/Happy Hour &amp; Tapas at Vlora </name><id>9891326</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236810600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9891326/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/9/e/global_7636510.jpeg</photo_url></item>