<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>690 Asylum Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.768452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Hartford Financial Services Group Plaza</name><city>Hartford</city><id>243433</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.685677</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>While it's not a hike in the forest, it is a 3-mile walk and for a good cause!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us to raise money to help Foodshare and local community kitchens and food pantries help end hunger in greater Hartford! The Walk Against Hunger begins and ends at The Hartford Insurance Group on Asylum Avenue in Hartford, where there is plenty of free parking. From The Hartford, walkers enjoy a three-mile loop through Hartford's historic west end, which returns the walkers right to the starting point. Walk registration begins and 1:00 and the walk will step off promptly at 2:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a fundraising walk, with a goal of raising $430,000! Last year, 3,000 walkers raised just over $400,000. Let's help them do even better this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit www.foodshare.org and click on the Walk Against Hunger logo to get all the details. You can join our team -- Gloria's Glorious Gang -- or if you are unable to walk, you can make a donation to support Gloria or another member of the team. If you are able to Walk, the web site will provide you with everything you need, including the ability to e-mail friends and family and ask for their support.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly will be our leader this day, as Gloria has to be at her son's confirmation.  This is the first Walk that Gloria has missed in 23 years!  But she will be walking in spirit and has already raised $500 toward her $600 goal.  Please plan to arrive at The Hartford between 1:00 and 1:30 and go to registration to get signed in.  Then head over to the team photo area and look for Kelly (Kevin will also be there, if you know him!) and a sign that says &amp;quot;Gloria's Glorious Gang.&amp;quot;  The group will have their photo taken at about 1:30 and then be ready for the opening ceremonies at 1:45 and to head off on the Walk at 2:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your support!  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178748199000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173574182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Foodshare's Walk Against Hunger</name><id>5557268</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178470800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5557268/</event_url></item>