<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We meet from 11:30 - 1:30 pm.  The first hour is a potluck lunch with a chance to get to know one another better.  The second hour is the presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$10 meetup fee.  RSVP with what you will bring to the potluck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group has found some &amp;quot;business development&amp;quot; presentations to be very enriching and helpful.  So, we are fortunate this month to have Robin Daiell with us to look at an important aspect of running a succesful mind-body practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tax Planning for Holistic Health Practice&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Robin Daiell, EA and QuickBooks ProAdvisor, caters to the bookkeeping and income tax preparation needs of the small business owner, with a focus on businesses in the health and alternative health industry.  Many of her  clients have their own small practices as psychologists, nurses, therapists, artists and photographers.  She sees clients in Massachusetts, NH and Vermont.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Robin’s first visit to the Meetup Group and her presentation will be geared to tax planning for an imaginary small business while leaving room to address questions afterwards.  Please note, however, that some specific problems may be too complex to be addressed in the forum of the meetup group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will welcome them at the door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Marks</member_name><member_id>5692888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292003350000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Alternative Health Practioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>alternative-703</urlname><id>1152400</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279895046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December  Meetup:  Tax Planning for Holistic Health Practice</name><id>14190259</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291998600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/alternative-703/events/14190259/</event_url></item>