<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>282 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.831347</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-521-7266</phone><name>Roger Williams National Memorial</name><city>Providence</city><id>1109857</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.410749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saturday, September 24 @ 12:00pm - 6:30pm Admission to this family event is FREE Rhode Islanders of all ages are invited to join in a lively celebration of our state's rich cultural heritage. The Roger Williams National Memorial (North Main St) will be filled with booths from countries such as Bolivia, Guatemala, India, Japan, Korea, Portugal, Haiti and others that will showcase their culture, music, and dance. This year the RIHPHC committ...ees have joined with the RI National Guard, The Peace Flag Project and RISCA (RI State Council on the Arts)to celebrate peace, diversity and the rich ethnic cultures in the state of Rhode Island. The booths will have cultural exhibits and display craft demonstrations from all over the world. The food court will have a mouth-watering array of traditional foods and drinks. The children&amp;#146;s area will have The Peace Flag Project, face painting, story telling, and arts and craft. The RING rock wall will be there for the adventurous at heart. There will be authentic re-enacting of the military branches from different eras. You can also watch The 2nd Annual Big Drum Powwow with Native American drumming, dancing and arts &amp;amp; crafts. A parade of international flags representing over 30 countries will start off the day. Dancers and musicians from various countries dressed in native and colorful costumes will perform Saturday afternoon. The RIARNG &amp;#147;Governors Own&amp;#148; 88th Army Band will be closing out this wonderful family friendly event. Afterwards you can then walk over and enjoy the WaterFire to close out the day. We are part of the Providence 375 Celebrations and RI Latino CommUNITY Celebration.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316884708000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316556503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RI Annual Heritage Day Festival &amp; RING Celebration of Diversity</name><id>34329332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316880000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/34329332/</event_url></item>