<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Near 10 Necco Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.349598</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fort Point Kayak Launch</name><city>Boston</city><id>7421132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050522</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will be putting in at the new Floating Dock Kayak Launch at Fort Point Channel in downtown Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We plan to Paddle to the Charles River, Pass through the locks, past the Museum Of Science and to the Cambridgeside Galleria. From there, We will paddle up the Charles River to the Esplanade and take a short break. We will leave the Esplanade, paddle back down the Charles, pass through the locks, and Paddle to the Charlestown Navy Yard to visit the USS Constitution. We will then paddle back to Fort Point Channel, stopping at The Barking Crab restaurant (located at the mouth of Fort Point Channel) on the way back to the put in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Distance Paddled Will Be Approximately 11 Miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Low Tide at the Charles River Entrance : 1:15 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High Tide at the Charles River Entrance : 7:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a Level Two paddle, restricted to Kayaks 14 feet or more in length, with Watertight Bulkheads. We will likely encounter Wind, Waves, Boat Traffic, Commercial Ships, and Tidal Currents. You will need to be competent in Self and Assisted Rescues, Paddling in Large Waves and Boat Wakes, Quickly Crossing Boat Channels, Paddling in Currents, and Launching and Landing on Docks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fortpointpier.com/info.php"&gt;Click Here For More Information About The Fort Point Kayak Launch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$$$ If you will be joining us at the Barking Crab, Bring some cash or plastic. $$$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.barkingcrab.com/menus/boston/"&gt;Click Here To See The Barking Crab's Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fort Point Channel&lt;/strong&gt; is a maritime channel separating South Boston from downtown Boston, Massachusetts, feeding into Boston Harbor. The south part of it has been gradually filled in for use by the South Bay rail yard and several highways (specifically the Central Artery and the Southeast Expressway). At its south end, the channel once widened into South Bay (Boston), from which the Roxbury Canal continued southwest where the Massachusetts Avenue Connector is now. The Boston Tea Party occurred at its northern end. The channel is surrounded by the Fort Point neighborhood, which is also named after the same colonial-era fort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The USS Constitution&lt;/strong&gt; is a wooden-hulled, three-masted heavy frigate of the United States Navy. Named by President George Washington after the Constitution of the United States of America, she is the world's oldest commissioned naval vessel afloat. Launched in 1797, Constitution was one of six original frigates authorized for construction by the Naval Act of 1794 and the third constructed. Joshua Humphreys designed the frigates to be the young Navy's capital ships, and so Constitution and her sisters were larger and more heavily armed and built than standard frigates of the period. Built in Boston, Massachusetts, at Edmund Hartt's shipyard, her first duties with the newly formed United States Navy were to provide protection for American merchant shipping during the Quasi-War with France and to defeat the Barbary pirates in the First Barbary War.The Constitution is most famous for her actions during the War of 1812 against Great Britain, when she captured numerous merchant ships and defeated five British warships: HMS Guerriere, Java, Pictou, Cyane and Levant. The battle with Guerriere earned her the nickname of "Old Ironsides" and public adoration that has repeatedly saved her from scrapping. She was retired from active service in 1881&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GPS Coordinates: N42° 20' 56.61'  X W71° 3' 3.68"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy a GPS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Or-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Take I-95 South&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) Exit 46 to US-1 South Towards Boston (There is a $3.00 Toll at the Tobin Bridge)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) Keep Left onto I-93 South / US-1 South&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4) Take Exit 20B-A to I-90 West / Mass Pike. Then take Exit 20A towards South Station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5) Turn Left on Summer Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6) Turn Right on Melcher Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7) Turn Right on Necco Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8) Enter the Large Parking Lot on the Right. The launch is at the back of the parking lot along the water. There is a $6.00 parking fee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?q=42.34913267841184,+-71.05092287063599&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=37.771008,-122.41175&amp;amp;sspn=0.043829,0.059137&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;Google Map Directions To The Fort Point Channel Kayak Launch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Launch is at the back of the parking lot along the water. Look for the Kayaks</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Eldredge</member_name><member_id>7765158</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Deasy</member_name><member_id>7817657</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug W</member_name><member_id>8995568</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343868833000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332189451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fort  Point Channel to the Esplanade and the USS Constitution</name><id>57006482</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343491200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/57006482/</event_url></item>