<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.25</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Organizer Michael Blair @ 9788081932&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;READ THE IMPORTANT NOTE IN THE CAMPING SECTION BELOW BEFORE YOU RSVP YES FOR ANY DAY OF THIS EVENT!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;3rd Annual Labor Day Weekend Peak-a-Palooza (September 1-5, 2011)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for something different and want a hiking and camping adventure outside of the White Mountains, then this is the trip for you. Each day we will make a short drive to our hikes from our centrally-located basecamp - the Devil's Tombstone Campground. I am listing it now so that you have ample time to plan and make the necessary arrangements. Don't wait, we had to turn people away last year because they waited until the last minute and the campground was full.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While only two of the peaks in the Catskills are above 4,000 feet (Slide @ 4,190 feet and Hunter @ 4,050 feet), there are 35 peaks that are above 3,500 feet. Yup, there is a list and there is a patch - if you are into that type of thing. Our goal over these five days is to climb as many as we can. I will update this listing with more details but here is the preliminary agenda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Hiking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;UPDATED ITINERARY 08/24&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Day #1 - Thursday 09/01&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;: No hiking today - people will be arriving and getting set-up at camp (or in their RV) so we will all hang by the fire and talk about our our upcoming&lt;/span&gt;peakbagging&amp;nbsp;adventures. &amp;nbsp;If we do want to do an easy sunset hike the&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;span&gt;firetower&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;on nearby&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;span&gt;Tremper&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;provides 360 degree views of the southern Catskills (~5.5 miles round trip with ~1,900 feet of elevation gain).
   &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Day #2 - Friday 09/02&lt;/span&gt;: This hike one-way hike will provide us with some on-trail and off-trail hiking as we climb to the summit of five of the Catskill 35 within the Big Indian Wilderness - Balsam (3,610'), Eagle (3,610'), Doubletop (3,870'),&amp;nbsp;Big Indian (3,710'), and Fir (3,630'). &amp;nbsp;The side-trips to Doubletop and Fir will involve some relatively easy off-trail travel. &amp;nbsp;
  &lt;strong&gt;We will hike about 12 miles and climb about 3,800 feet.&lt;/strong&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Devil's Path: According to the&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;AMC's&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Catskill Mountain Guide the name has a double meaning - "deriving its name not only for the devil that the Dutch settlers believed lived in the deep wild hallows and jagged cloves of the Catskills, but also for its demonic and unforgiving ascents, its rugged and punishing peaks, and particularly in the summer, its fiendish lack of water." While a traverse of the entire path can be done in one day we are going to spread it out over two days so we can branch off the main trail and climb some additional peaks along the way. 
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Saturday 09/03 Devil's Path - Part I: We'll drive to the eastern-most&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;trailhead&amp;nbsp;along Route 16 and head back toward our campsite. &amp;nbsp;Along the way we will climb over the summit of four of the Catskill 35 peaks - Indian Head (3,573'), Twin (3,650'),
    &lt;span&gt;Sugarloaf&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;(3,810'), and Plateau (3,850'). &amp;nbsp;We will then descend to our campsite - while&amp;nbsp;
    &lt;span&gt;some&amp;nbsp;people&amp;nbsp;go back to get the cars we left at the start the others can get the fire going and start cooking dinner. &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;strong&gt;This trip will involve STEEP sections - we will hike about 14 miles and climb about 4,500 feet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Sunday 09/04 Devil's Path - Part II: This time we will drive to the western-most trailhead on Route 6 and head back&amp;nbsp;toward&amp;nbsp;our campsite. &amp;nbsp;Along the way we will climb over three of the Catskill 35 peaks - West Kill (3,890'), Hunter SW Peak (3,750'), and Hunter (4,050'). &amp;nbsp;The side trip to Hunter will involve any easy off-trail trip while the trip to Hunter will net us one of the two 4,000 foot summits in the Catskills (Slide is the other). &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;We will then descend to our campsite - while&amp;nbsp;
    &lt;span&gt;some&amp;nbsp;people&amp;nbsp;go back to get the cars we left at the start the others can get the fire going and start cooking&amp;nbsp;dinner. &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;strong&gt;This trip will involve STEEP sections - we will hike about 13 miles and climb about 4,800 feet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Day #5 - Monday 09/05&lt;/span&gt;: We will get up early to bag a few more peaks in the morning before heading out to make the long drive home. &amp;nbsp;The plan will be to climb the three Catskill 35 peaks along the Blackhead Ridge - Blackhead (3,950'), Black Dome (3,990'), and Thomas Cole (3,950'). &amp;nbsp;We will leave a few cars at the end of this one-way hike and drive to the start at the end of Route 56. &amp;nbsp;
  &lt;strong&gt;We will hike about 8 miles and climb about 2,800 feet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Camping&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have already made reservations for two campsites at the Devil's Tombstone Campground ( 
&lt;a href="http://www.dec.ny.gov/outdoor/24462.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dec.ny.gov...&lt;/a&gt; ) located in Hunter, NY. We will arrive Thursday 09/01 and depart Monday 09/05. Each site can accommodate up to six people - and we learned last year that when they say six people, they mean it. Sorry, there are no dogs allowed at the campground. 
&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;NOTE: Each night there are 10 available spots &amp;amp;ndash; in order to reserve your space for a particular night you will need to RSVP for that day individually. The cost is $5.25 per person per night. You will need to pre-pay in order to register. If you don't want to pay online send me a note and I will send you my mailing address.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Devil's Tombstone is one of the oldest campgrounds in the Catskill Forest Preserve, offering mysteries of the Devil's Tombstone and a haven for primitive camping. The campground is an ideal base camp for serious hikers with trails leading to some of the highest peaks, such as Hunter with the highest historic fire tower in New York State, Indian Head and West Kill Range. The "Devil's Path" trails are accessible from the parking lot at the north end of the campground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Other Activities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't want to hike each day there are plenty of nearby activities - Hunter Mountain has a mountain-side zip line while the local villages provide restaurants, shops, antique shops, and a movie theater. Tubing, paintball, go-carts, miniature golf, and a number of golf courses and horseback riding facilities are located within easy driving distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318204278000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293944903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Labor Day Weekend Peak-a-Palooza (Day #1)</name><id>15881762</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314874800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15881762/</event_url></item>