<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>67 Johnson road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02825</zip><lat>41.752725</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Foster country club</name><city>Foster</city><id>1414618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.750627</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Peeptoad Presents: Gypsy Romantique’&lt;br /&gt;November 12, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;8:00 pm to 10:00 pm    /  $15.00 at the door or you can buy tickets online @ this web site. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  www.fosteringarts.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gypsy Romantique’, whose slogan is: a little Django, a little Tango, a little Swing, A LOT OF FUN!, is just all that. Whimsical and romantic with a lot of the humor infused in Dufresne’s lyrics, the band takes the audience on a magical tour through the jazz and swing era in a brightly wrapped package of new and original material.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Melding the gypsy inspired Paris hot club jazz of the 1930’s and American western swing of the same era.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The base trio consists of John Debossu on bass, Robert Davis , gypsy guitar, and Donna Dufresne, guitar/vocals. The quartet is made complete with the addition of accordion and/or jazz violin which polishes the ambiance of a French Café’ or perhaps a Mexican Cantina ala 1930-something.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;will ckeck if dinning is available at the country club and if dinner will be possible. &lt;br /&gt;this is a dinning, mostly light fare, sandwiches, burgers, ckeck the website fostercountryclub.com look at menu and we can decide to go early maybe 5:30 to have a bit to eat. If i dont get enough people interested in dinner prior to event we can just make the concert. Hope this is good never seen them but sounded interesting to me.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have meet sign and cell number available to all attending.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Claire</member_name><member_id>4222330</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289628937000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Exciting People Having Some Fun!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mingle-with-singles</urlname><id>1452082</id><group_lat>41.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Mingle with singles 45+ Socializing and dancing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288233126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Foster country club/ music/ concert/ ? dinner</name><id>15255060</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289606400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mingle-with-singles/events/15255060/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/0/global_10652416.jpeg</photo_url></item>