<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday at Patio along the Charles Hotel Harvard Square&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Harvard Square 6:45-9:45pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday July 17th. This time we are taking the party to the popular   expansive Patio of the Charles Hotel  located in Harvard Square.  The The Patio at the Charles Hotel (right next to Noir bar)  is one of the premier afterwork spots in the Boston/Cambridge area. If you enjoy making new contacts and friends, while enjoying some of the best cocktails on a warm summer day then this is the event for you!! Also if you are new member and have not been to an afterwork mixer, or have only been to a few events,  I highly encourage you to attend and meet many of our wonderful members. So what better way to come out this Thurs and have a few cocktails with the group as we gear up for another festive weekend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting details: The Charles Hotel  is located within  Harvard Square  at 1 Bennett St. Corner of Eliott and Bennett St.  The Patio area is located right in front of the hotel.  Less than a 5 minute walk from the red line.   I &lt;b&gt;HIGHLY&lt;/b&gt;  recommend going online (google) to get a better idea for directions. Also check out the venue website for  at &lt;a href="http://www.charleshotel.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.charleshot...&lt;/a&gt; This will give you a better overall sense of the venue and provide pinpoint directions from your destination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Outside we will meet at the  bar area . Like any event, when arriving please be sure to locate the organizer. Please do not hesitate to call or text me upon arrival if you are having trouble finding the group. My picture is on the site under the Assistant Organizer section so I should not be hard to find. This is the most packed and lively  afterwork scene in the Cambridge /Harvard Sq area  on Thurs nites so I highly &lt;b&gt;ENCOURAGE&lt;/b&gt; you to attend early as possible. My phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Harvard Sq&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event cost: Free.  (However please  feel free to grab a beverage for your hard working organizers) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note please see the message board regarding meetup/event etiquette**&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216508007000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216089114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Bash  Party on the Patio!!  Afterwork Mixer this Thursday!</name><id>8342644</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216334700000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8342644/</event_url></item>