<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Harvard Yard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374466</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Phillips Brooks House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1409076</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117557</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;James Croft will speak on "Building the Temple of the Future: Fulfilling the Promise of Humanism" this Sunday at Phillips Brooks House, in Harvard Yard. The talk will start around 12:30 pm. Before James begins, the GBH will provide a tasty brunch at 12 PM and there will be a Q and A after his remarks. James writes about his topic: "Humanists have high moral principles and lofty goals: a true Humanist vision would lead to nothing less than the transformation of the world. And yet, in the decades since Secular Humanism became a well-defined creed, we have not had the political and cultural impact we might wish for. If we are to build what Ingersoll called the Temple of the Future, we need to work harder, smarter, and with greater conviction than ever before. James Croft draws on history, culture, science and activist experience to show Humanists how they can come together, build community, and begin to fulfill the promise of their beliefs." James Croft is the Research and Education Fellow at the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard, and has been working on the Humanist Community Project since its inception, where he has been responsible for performing the research into community building, activism, and political persuasion which serve as its foundation. He is a Cambridge and Harvard Graduate, and is currently studying for his Doctorate in the philosophy of education at the Harvard Graduate School of Education - he is writing his thesis on the nature, value and development of intellectual autonomy, or "Free Thinking". He was raised on Shakespeare, Sagan and Star Trek, and is a proud, gay Humanist. With the lunch, lecture and Q &amp;amp; A, we'll still close before 3 PM (we are able to return to Phillips Brooks House in Harvard Yard without problems, but the PBH space is not available after 3 this day). Free parking is available in the Littauer Lot during this time (enter at the Dworkin Bldg. from Oxford St.) GBH's next meeting will be the third Sunday of February. DIRECTIONS TO PBH: &lt;a href="http://pbha.org/about/directions/" class="linkified"&gt;http://pbha.org/about/directions/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326809443000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326199805000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Boston Humanists: James Croft on "The Promise of Humanism"</name><id>47480792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326646800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/47480792/</event_url></item>