<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Off of Beacon Street - landmarks State House &amp; Fox TV</address_2><address_1>150 Bowdoin Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358318</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-227-7100</phone><name>21st Amendment</name><city>Boston</city><id>826137</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey All...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It seems that we have a large number... of members who love to travel. So Let's meet sometime/somewhere and discuss possible trip ideas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Further, we can also use this time to share with each other our own travel experiences and learn from one another as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can share with each other best deal finders/practices and best of websites for booking flights, hotels, and complete trip packages.  There is Always.... something to learn... deals to be made and places to go.... :) And, it has been my experience that many of the best places you'll ever find in this world, many of them are indeed off the beaten path. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've found it helpful to talk to other world travelers. I often learned from others when to go and when not to go to certain places around the globe. And, while I don't always listen to every word another says about a particular longitude and latitude because I still enjoy the adventure and making up my own mind about a place. With that said, though, I have gotten interesting and sometimes valuable tips on hidden gems that I might never have stumbled onto otherwise. In addition, I am constantly stumbling so I'm always discovering new and unexpected places to share with others. Especially in NYC. I must have walked about every inch of that city. I'm not kidding either :)    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way... has anyone heard about an airline from Ireland wanting to charge only $30 flights from Boston to Ireland? It's been a while since I've been over to Ireland. Also... been wanting to go to Africa, Scotland and Iceland. In the US... Alaska/Canada to see the Northern Lights. I also love to go to Nantucket, Seattle, San Fran, DC, London and Paris. And would like to get back to Russia, Germany and Italy at some point. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And needless to say... but I'll say it anyway, I love Manhattan, which I consider to be the best city in the world.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239549288000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235187014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Travel Enthusiasts let's talk - 21st Amendment</name><id>9787942</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239231600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9787942/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/7/global_7604215.jpeg</photo_url></item>