<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2> ( 1 block from Kenmore Square toward Brookline)</address_2><address_1>835 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215-3303</zip><lat>42.347176</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-262-2121</phone><name>RISQUE at An Tua Nua</name><city>Boston</city><id>231112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103035</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person for ALL DAY</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;BachataDVD.com Presents..... &lt;br /&gt;The Blazing Bachata Boot Camp Workshop International Tour &lt;br /&gt;Saturday Feb 14, 2009&lt;br /&gt;1-5pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;We JUST found out there will be some guest instructors from DC teaching a Bachata workshop this weekend!  I don't believe a Bachata bootcamp has been done before here, so don't miss out on this.  It should be LOTS of fun.  THEN join everyone after at the Knights of Columbus to get your Salsa, Merengue, and Bachata groove on for Edwin Pabon's Annual Valentine's Day Party! Evening Party Info: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=46520792780" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;BACHATA WORKSHOP INFO:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Workshops Location:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Tua Nua&lt;br /&gt;835 Beacon St&lt;br /&gt;( 1 block from Kenmore Square toward Brookline)&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02215-3303&lt;br /&gt;For Directions: 617 262-2121&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 per workshop &lt;br /&gt;All 4 Workshops for $50 &lt;br /&gt;Couple Valentine's Day Discount $85 for all 4 Workshops  MEET UP DISCOUNT&lt;br /&gt;Register online through meetup or call 703.599.3018 to get couples discount or pay by cash/check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register today! Don't miss this opportunity to learn from Lee &amp;quot;El Gringuito&amp;quot; &amp;amp; Nohelia right here in Boston!  Pay online through meetup today, or call today to take advantage of the special couple MEETUP discount. 703.599.3018&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Workshops!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lee &amp;amp; Nohelia have taught over 100,000 people in 47 States how to dance Bachata in The USA!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;You can't find a better class, from barely holding hands to drop-dead dirty moves to get your pulse pounding.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;-- Washington Post&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lee &amp;quot;El Gringuito&amp;quot; has taught more people to dance Bachata in the United States than anyone in the World! He has been seen on the final episodes of Americas Got Talent, Fox Television, Ambush Makeover, Telemundo and Univision. Get ready for amazing lessons that will take your Bachata to the next level! Together with his beautiful wife Nohelia they are traveling around the country in 2009. Workshop dates have been scheduled in Reno, San Francisco, Milwaukee, DC, Baltimore, Honolulu, Charlotte, and the UK. Their four hour workshop, Latin Dance Show, and DJ Experience will leave you wanting more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Workshop Description 4x 50 Minute Workshops&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bachata Foundation/Dominican Style Bachata -  1pm - 2pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to learn a great foundation of moves including Bachata motion, turns, half turns and Dominican motion. This class sets the foundation of the entire workshop. This workshop focuses on material taught on our Level I Bachata DVD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bachata Hot Combinations -  2pm - 3pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to learn amazing Signature Lee &amp;quot;El Gringuito&amp;quot; Bachata moves. This class will utilize many of the principles taught in Bachata Foundations. You will start to develop your Domincan Style Bachata step with moves like La Dominicana and then be ready for exciting combinations like Extreme Bachata. This workshop focuses on moves taught on our Level II Bachata DVD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bridging the Gap Between Bachata &amp;amp; Salsa- 3pm - 4pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this class you will learn how to take Salsa combinations and convert them into Bachata moves. Both dances share some basic musicalities. You will learn a number of Salsa combinations and then we will convert them into Hot Bachata Moves&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bachata Tricks and Dips  4pm - 5pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to Spice Up Your Bachata with amazing tricks and dips. This &amp;quot;LA Style Flair&amp;quot; can be added at key moments in songs to give that extra &amp;quot;punch.&amp;quot; You will learn Bachata Dip, Tango Lift and Dip and Hypnotic Bachata! We will also dicuss safety and common elements among moves. This workshop focuses on moves taught on our Level III Bahata DVD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Followed by:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enrollment Fee:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 per class per person - All four classes for $50.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COUPLES VALENTINE'S Day Special&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4 Classes $85 (two people)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Lee!  He will direct you to other meetup members!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237151140000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234509466000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bachata Workshops @ An Tua Nua in Boston! Valentine's Day Bachata &amp; SALSA!</name><id>9734535</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234634400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/9734535/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/b/global_7291819.jpeg</photo_url></item>