<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Cold Spring Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01007</zip><lat>42.242960</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Swift River</name><city>Belchertown</city><id>1253625</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.335400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;PLEASE NOTE the guest feature is turned off.  I did this due to limited parking. I have limited the group to 10 CARS. If you have a guests in the same car as you that is fine. If you have guest in their own car they need to RSVP on their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suitable to all levels. Please read the discussion on New to Kayaking if you are a new kayaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayak/Canoe Swift River in Belchertown, MA Saturday July 14, launch at 7:30 AM. This means we will be in our boats at 7:30 AM. Saturday's weather should be beautiful. Bring water and a snack/lunch. You MUST wear your PFD. This is an amazing river to paddle, slow water suitable for all skill levels and types of boats. The area is gorgeous, and for several miles of the river the water is crystal clear, you can see the beautiful formations on the bottom and lots of fish! Plenty of birds everywhere too! We'll be paddling upstream then back down to the launch area for a break. That will be about 1 1/2 hours. For anyone who wants to continue we'll then go downstream then back up to the launch, for about an additional 1 1/2 hours of paddling. Here is a link that shows a map to the boat access area - &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/d" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d&lt;/a&gt;... ------Directions------ If you are coming from the north, please use yahoo maps or mapquest with Cold Spring Road, Belchertown, MA as your destination, that should get you there. I also recommend looking at the map in the link above. The boat launch is on Cold Sping Road between East Street and River Road I go west out of Ware on Rt 9 and take a left on River Road or East Street. These roads go along the river down to the boat launch. They go off of RT 9 near the entrances for the Quabbin Dam From the Mass Pike – (These directions are from yahoo maps, but modified as their directions are misleading in a few places.) - Take Exit #8 (Palmer) - At the end of the offramp after the toll booth, turn left onto Thorndike St. - In 0.8 miles turn left onto High St. - High St. becomes Church St. - Church St. becomes Pleasant St. - Pleasant St. becomes Thorndike St. - At the end of Thorndike, bear right onto Rt. 181 North. - DO NOT Turn left onto Depot Road go straight onto Main St. which turns into S. Main St. then into Bondsville Rd. just keep the river to your left the whole way. At the T in the road take a left cross the bridge and turn left into the parking area. You’ll see a sign that says “Swift River Access” on the Left at the entrance to the parking area.  LOOK AT The MAP.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan L</member_name><member_id>7773139</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342479993000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342094867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Swift River in Belchertown, MA</name><id>73028402</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342265400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/73028402/</event_url></item>