<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Sustainable House&lt;/strong&gt; - “Clean and Profitable Living through technology that is Revitalizing the Real Estate Industry, Local Communities, and Government&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does the sustainable housing concept hold the potential to revitalizing the Real Estate Industry, Local Communities, and Government? Can entrepreneurs really build successful businesses, deliver genuine efficiencies, actualize cost savings attractive to anyone and solve one of the greatest contributors of carbon to the environment all at the same time? Great innovations often come where we don't believe change is possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freddie Mac’s 2012 housing assessment values the US housing stock at $16.4 Trillion. According to the Green Building Construction Report from McGraw Hill, 2012, green building accounts for more than one-third of all non-residential design and construction and will grow to more than one-half of all construction within the next five years. The US Green Building Council notes “Buildings contribute on average to about 45% of cities’ carbon emissions. The buildings sector is one of the least expensive, low hanging fruit of emissions mitigation opportunities.” The market is ripe for innovation and businesses that can deliver it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our next forum we will talk to industry leaders embracing these opportunistic challenges. We will hear from entrepreneurs that have real businesses capitalizing on the rapidly growing sustainable housing market through design, strategy, finance and technology. Whether you’re an entrepreneur working to commercialize ideas in sustainable housing or building a leading edge business, please join us as we explore how to make the dream reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panel:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/DHooghe.jpg" width="99" height="99" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Alexander D’Hooghe, Associate Professor in Architectural Urbanism at MIT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexander conducts a research group called ‘Platform for a Permanent Modernity’, and a design office called ‘Office for Permanent Modernity’, located in Boston and Brussels. He develops architectures of the territory: durable formal orders handling complexity within a simplified frame. The formalization of infrastructures is key. The group won several large-scale buildings and competitions overseas, currently in various stages of permitting; and published internationally, most recently with ‘the Liberal Monument’ (Princeton, Fall 2010),. D’Hooghe obtained his Ph.D. at the Berlage Institute in 2007 i.c.w. T.U.Delft, after achieving a Masters in Urban Design at the GSD in 2001. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/Slaughter.jpg" width="99" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;E. Sarah Slaughter, President and Executive Director, Built Environment Coalition&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sarah Slaughter is President and founder of the Built Environment Coalition. She was most recently the Associate Director for Buildings and Infrastructure in the MIT Energy Initiative, coordinating research across MIT focused on improving the built environment, and led the development of a program to improve the built environment and economic development across New England that involved over 120 companies, nonprofit organizations, and local and state government agencies. Before her work with MITEI, she was co-founder and head of the Sustainability Initiative in the MIT Sloan School of Management, focusing on strategies for sustainable organizations and communities. Previously, Dr. Slaughter was founder and CEO of MOCA Systems, Inc., a construction program management company based on the construction simulation software system from her MIT research. At MIT, she was a professor in the Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering, focusing on innovations for the built environment. Earlier, she was a professor of Civil and Environmental Engineering at Lehigh University and conducted research in the NSF Center for Advanced Technology for Large Structural Systems (ATLSS). Dr. Slaughter has published over 50 articles and books, and is a recognized expert in the field of sustainable facility assets, and in innovations in the built environment. She received her S.B., S.M., and PhD from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/Chipalkatti.jpg" width="90" height="136" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Dr. Makarand H. Chipalkatti, &lt;strong&gt;Sr. Dir. SSL &amp;amp; Emerging Market Initiatives, OSRAM SYLVANIA INC&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Makarand “Chips” Chipalkatti is Senior Director, Solid State Lighting and Emerging Market Initiatives for OSRAM SYLVANIA since March 2010 with special focus on SSL advocacy and standards for OSRAM in the NAFTA region. Chips began his professional career with GTE Laboratories and joined OSRAM SYLVANIA R&amp;amp;D in 1993. His work included research on advanced materials and organic light sources. In 2000, he started-up OSRAM’s LED lighting business in North America and led the business till 2005. Since then, Dr. Chips served as Head of Strategic Innovation Management for OSRAM SYLVANIA and continues to serve as a key member of OSRAM’s strategic innovation community. Chips’ role as a corporate entrepreneur has led to several new business and open innovation initiatives. Dr. Chips has played a pioneering role in the SSL industry and was a founder member and chairman of the Solid State Lighting Section of NEMA till 2006, and a founding member of NGLIA and ASSIST.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/merrick.jpg" width="90" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Micah Merrick, Associate, Saint-Gobain's External Venturing Team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saint-Gobain is the world's largest construction products company and Saint-Gobain's External Venturing team is responsible for facilitating commercial agreements between the 50+ business units of Saint-Gobain and companies developing new technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Micah has been a member of the External Venturing team for over a year, focusing on innovations in the Construction Products markets, with a particular focus on innovations in new insulating materials, composite building panels and cladding, and production process enhancements. Prior to working at Saint-Gobain, Micah worked as both an independent consultant to energy generation startups, including Joule Unlimited and Harvest Power, and business development for a wind energy startup in Philadelphia. Micah graduated with an MBA from the Wharton School in Philadelphia in 2009 has a BS in Economics from Penn State University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/malloy.jpg" width="90" height="90" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Ed Malloy, President &lt;br /&gt;

New England Renewable Energy Systems and Mercury Mechanical Services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company’s mission is to drive awareness and adoption of integrated renewable and non-renewable energy solutions into commercial and residential markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has served in senior and executive roles in engineering and business development for Fortune 500 companies providing integrated circuit (IC) design manufacturing and sales including LSI Corporation, NEC Electronics, and Cadence Design Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His experience provides seasoned and practical insight into value chain dependencies. His goal includes bridging gaps within commercial and residential heating and cooling market segments and encouraging cross-functional relationships to promote renewables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ed holds degrees in engineering (BSEE – Boston University), business administration (MBA – Boston College), and law (JD – Suffolk University).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/batshalom.jpg" width="100" height="144" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Barbra Batshalom, founder and President, Sustainable Performance Institute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barbra is a social entrepreneur and has provided the vision and strategic thinking to create organizations focused on market transformation towards sustainability. With a diverse background of fine arts, social psychology and more than 20 years in architecture and sustainability, Barbra brings a variety of skills to all of her work and a unique perspective engaging the human dynamics of decision-making and effective collaboration to technical work. She collaborates with cities, institutions and companies to transform their internal practices to improve performance, profitability and sustainability. Since founding The Green Roundtable in 1998, Barbra has pioneered many innovations from the first policy requiring green building from the private sector to supply chain innovations. Her NEXUS Green Building Resource Center franchise gives communities hubs for learning and interaction and her leadership to create accountability from design professionals lead to the creation of the Sustainable Performance Institute, whose industry Certification program is the only one in the nation to measure and validate the capability of design and construction companies to deliver consistent, high quality sustainability services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Dec2012Mtg/dings.jpg" width="100" height="151" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Ryan E. Dings | Blu Homes, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ryan E. Dings serves as Blu’s Vice President, Senior Counsel &amp;amp; Corporate Secretary, managing all legal and regulatory issues for the company. With a background in both law and design, Ryan initially joined Blu as its Director of Business Development and helped the company refine its business strategy for delivering inspiring green homes. Prior to joining Blu, Ryan practiced commercial real estate and construction law in Charlotte, North Carolina. Ryan focused his legal practice on working with developers, builders, and contractors involved in residential real estate development. &lt;br /&gt;

Ryan earned his Bachelor of Arts in Economics and American History from the University of North Carolina – Chapel Hill, his Juris Doctor from Wake Forest University School of Law and his Master in Design Studies (with a concentration in real estate) from the Harvard University Graduate School of Design. Ryan is licensed to practice law in the State of North Carolina and the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;

Ryan is an active member of the Urban Land Institute, U.S. Green Building Council, and Association of Corporate Counsel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfdec2012.eventbrite.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/7_contact.htm"&gt;Map and Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355884687000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348155500000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Sustainable House</name><id>83283092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355873400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/83283092/</event_url></item>