<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>414 Massasoit Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01601</zip><lat>42.233498</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-753-6087</phone><name>Broad Meadow Brook Conservation Ctr</name><city>Worcester</city><id>669443</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.763490</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Local bird enthusiast Alex Dunn will be leading a bird spotting, watching, and photographing adventure at Broad Meadow Brook Conservation Center and Wildlife Sanctuary on June 5th, from 10AM to 12 noon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Birdwatching is your lifetime ticket to the theater of nature.&amp;quot; Maybe you are frustrated because you can't identify all the birds at your feeder, in the woods, or along the roadside. We'll be using Alex's expertise to spot, and identify local birds. He'll be our &amp;quot;field guide&amp;quot; and teach us to identify characteristics (field marks) on birds that are most helpful to identification.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Broad Meadow Brook is a wonderful place to explore over 400 acres of woods, fields, streams, and marsh. Look for 78 different species of butterflies, prowl for owls, or learn to spot birds from our bird blind. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcoming you in the lobby of the new conservation center are interpretive exhibits including a large 3-D model of the entire sanctuary and a wall-to-ceiling map of the Blackstone River watershed. Nature-related gifts, children’s books, assorted field guides, and conservation advocacy and community resource information are available at the center, which also serves as a visitor site for the National Park Service’s Blackstone River Valley National Heritage Corridor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;414 Massasoit Road&lt;br /&gt;Worcester, MA 01604&lt;br /&gt;508-753-6087&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This sanctuary has the following universally accessible facilities: Nature Center, Restrooms, Troiano Brookside Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center/Trail Hours:&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center: Tuesday through Saturday, 9 a.m. to 4 p.m, Sunday, 12:30 p.m. to 4 p.m. Trails: Open every day, dawn to dusk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;Free for Mass Audubon members, Worcester residents, and Greater Worcester Land Trust members&lt;br /&gt;$4 for nonmember adults;&lt;br /&gt;$3 for nonmember children (2-12) and seniors &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I suggest you pack a snack, water and wear comfy hiking shoes! Please join us for a fun few hours of nature!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For Your Safety&lt;br /&gt;Do not feed any animals&lt;br /&gt;Stay on trails to avoid ticks and poison ivy&lt;br /&gt;Do not smoke anywhere on the sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;Do not pick or collect plants or crops without permission&lt;br /&gt;Avoid Conflicts with Wildlife&lt;br /&gt;Do not bring pets, leashed or unleashed, on to the site&lt;br /&gt;Picnic only in designated areas&lt;br /&gt;Do not bring motorized vehicles or bicycles onto the site&lt;br /&gt;Hunting, fishing, or trapping are not permitted&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the Mass. Turnpike (Rt I-90): Take exit 11 (Millbury) and go left onto Rt 122 north. Turn left onto Rt 20 west. Turn right at the traffic light onto Massasoit Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt I-290: Take exit 14 (Rt 122 south/Grafton Street). Bear right at the rotary and stay on Rt 122. At the intersection, bear right onto Massasoit Road. Follow Massasoit Road past a playground and park on the left. The sanctuary entrance is located five houses past the park on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the Nature Center's back porch area!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275950989000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273164037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Birds, Birds and more Birds! Walk, Learn, Spot, Photograph Birds!</name><id>13404538</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275746400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13404538/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/3/global_14867363.jpeg</photo_url></item>