<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Star Island</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03870</zip><lat>42.976505</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Star Island</name><city>Rye</city><id>6336762</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.612999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;NOTE: This meetup is&amp;nbsp;informational&amp;nbsp;for the NHSPA's Annual Star Island Workshop. If you're interested in signing up, please be sure to follow the instructions under "Registration" in the&amp;nbsp;information&amp;nbsp;below. Signing up on this meetup site will allow the usual notices and communications, but you will NOT be considered signed up until you&amp;nbsp;square&amp;nbsp;away with the NHSPA as provided below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This weeklong program is an opportunity to spend concentrated time working on photography. Instructor Peter E. Randall, who has been photographing on the Isles of Shoals since 1975, leads this digital workshop on historic Star Island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is an opportunity to improve your photographs, add to your portfolio, and work with other photographers in a supportive program. With digital photography we review work daily and see each other&amp;rsquo;s images using LCD projectors. Daily assignments and critiques will help participants sharpen their creative vision to make better photographs. Participants must have some experience with photography and be familiar with their digital cameras. We&amp;rsquo;ll make prints on the island and have a show at the end of the week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have them, bring a laptop, storage device, tripod, or other accessories that you normally use. The registration fee covers the cost of ink and paper for making prints. More detailed information will be sent to those who register. Limited to 15 participants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chair and registrar:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Peter E Randall, 377 Goodwin Road, Eliot, ME 03903. For more information, phone 603-502-6968 or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:petererandall@gmail.com"&gt;Email Peter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Registration:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A room and board deposit of $200/person and registration fee of $225 per person are due with registration. Please mail one check, payable to &amp;ldquo;Peter E Randall&amp;rdquo; and &lt;a href="http://starisland.org/PDF/2012RegistrationForm.pdf"&gt;a completed registration form&lt;/a&gt; to the above address. Registration begins March 10th. Room and board deposit and registration fee are refundable until May 27th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Room and board:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Triple $772, double $815, single $1040, motel double $913, motel single $1420. Motel units have two twin beds, sink, and toilet. Other rooms have shared bathrooms. Ferry fee is included in the room and board rate. Parking is an additional $10 per day, payable on Star.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Boat schedule: Please plan to arrive at the dock in Portsmouth between 11 am and 1 pm.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ferry departs Portsmouth Saturday July 28th at 2:25 p.m. Depart Star Saturday, August 4th at 8:20 a.m., arriving in Portsmouth at 9:45. Schedule is subject to change - please confirm with registrar before traveling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://starisland.org/conferences/info/"&gt;Important Star Island information&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boat schedule: Please plan to arrive at the dock in Portsmouth between 11 am and 1 pm. Ferry departs Portsmouth Saturday July 28th at 2:25 p.m.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343499073000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332526644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NHSPA Sixth Annual Star Island Digital Photo Workshop</name><id>57576542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343487600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/57576542/</event_url></item>