<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.407043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-1499</phone><name>Together in Motion</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.133880</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the regularly scheduled&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Wednesday Night MeetUp for the Martial Arts and Combatants Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Together In Motion has opened their gym for our group for Wednesday Nights typically to 10:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 to 8:00 is centered around those with limited background and the focus is on a basic physical Self Defense system incorporated with progressive boundary setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:00 on the pace picks up with a very open format gathering of Martial Artists of diverse backgrounds who work until everyone gives in to the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Donations are always welcome and go towards Not Me! a non profit organization dedicated to providing instruction, conditioning and training to at risk populations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit Not-Me.Org if you would like information on the group the donations benefit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This open mat time is open to all levels and backgrounds of martial arts, typically this is a self directed group which allows everyone to work on practice of their choosing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Past meetups have had flow drills, throwing practice, locking practice, punching mitt and kicking targets. This really is an open format which allows members to question what they have been taught, share with others and just practice with no pressure of joining a school or formal system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've been out of practice for years or months but want to start doing something again this is the place!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us with a friendly spirit, bring whatever equipment you have or just yourself, uniform or running shorts makes no difference to us. The Together in Motion facility has a large open area with raised spring hard wood floor with dense mats covering, so it is adaptable for just about any type of practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mat shoes or Socks are preferred on the practice surface&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Bob or Erik</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob</member_name><member_id>4202193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344391647000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Martial Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>martial-221</urlname><id>502152</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>The Arlington Martial Arts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343956492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Mat Time for Martial Arts</name><id>qfpxfcyqlblb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344380400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/martial-221/events/76114082/</event_url></item>