<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well, we celebrated the holidays in December with a giant wine tasting bash to ring out 2010 for auld lang syne. Now it would be good to greet baby New Year and ring in 2011 having a great time with friends over some interesting new wines at Ralph's house in Cheshire, CT.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine (no boxed wine or 1.75MLs please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food, hors d'oeuvres or desert. Please indicate what food item  &lt;br /&gt;you want to bring when you sign up. If you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is $15 or more ( 750 ml) with your dish. Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $30 or more depending on the quantity of people in the group, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste. Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste testing.  &lt;br /&gt;Reds - Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir.  &lt;br /&gt;Whites - sav blanc, chards, reisling, pinot grigio, etc  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a persons spot if you do not show up. If you must cancel, the earlier the better if there is a waiting list.  &lt;br /&gt;*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event if you don't have it already to all the &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVPs, due to this being a private residence. It should go without saying to Drink Responsibly. I will have water and coffee too.  &lt;br /&gt;This is for 3 meetup groups to keep the volume of people down from last time. Only sign up on one site if you belong to more than one for an accurate count.  &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the night in fun, style and class. * Private people parings MUST be taken off site!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**As always this is a multi group meetup and a BYOWG...bring your own wine glass!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event if from 6pm - 10pm. &lt;br /&gt;..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph</member_name><member_id>8774347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296863214000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294379117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Wine night of 2011!</name><id>15955214</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296342000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/15955214/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/a/global_20042698.jpeg</photo_url></item>