<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.205223</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pond Meadow Park</name><city>Braintree</city><id>669075</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join members and guests of the South Shore Hike, Bike &amp;amp; Social Club as we join members and guests of the South Shore Walkabouts in their new 4th Monday [Evening] Walk Series@ Pond Meadow Park (PMP)! This is one of our favorite walking locations and it's been several weeks since we have walked here as a group. We will be meeting and walking from the Braintree side of PMP.  One of the great things about walking here is there is some shade and a breeze. Let's meet and get to know each other while walking around the pond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pond Meadow Park consists of a paved loop as well as paved walkways to and from both sets of parking lots.  This path is hilly with some flat terrain.  If you choose to head out into the woods the trails are marked but not paved.  The loop is 1.6 miles, with the walk to and from the parking lot it is 1.9 miles. It takes about 35-40 minutes to walk the loop. If we walk the loop twice it's a total of 3.5 miles and takes between 1 hr and 1 hr and 15 minutes, depending on pace. If we walk to the street of the Weymouth entrance it adds .4 miles and takes about 5-10 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4th Monday Walk @ Pond Meadow Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monday, July 23rd @ 6:30pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pond Meadow Park&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;470 Liberty Street, Braintree&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-843-7663&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website:  &lt;a href="http://www.pondmeadowpark.org/"&gt;www.pondmeadowpark.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Flagpole in front of Ranger Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: At least 6 Yes RSVPs 48 hours in advance. Attendance is limited to 30 total people, 10 for this group and 20 for the walkabouts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Welcome!  1 Adult per Member Please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Late Arrivals&lt;/em&gt;: We will wait our traditional 5-10 minutes for late arrivals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Please finalize your RSVP by 3pm on Monday, July 23rd.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our No-Show policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Heavy rains will cancel. We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle. Please plan to bring a lightweight jacket with a hood just in case. (We will do my best to notify everyone if this event is cancelled by 4pm on the day of the walk.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain Date: None at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;: Best directions should be taken from mapquest.com or maps.google.com. Located on Liberty Street, 500 feet from the intersection of Liberty and Middle Street near the Route 3 overpass directly across from Zana Park Drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note there is a rotary now instead of a regular intersection just before PMP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 17/Union St., Braintree. Exit on the side of the (Sunoco) Gas Station and Police Station. Follow Union Street to the first set of lights. Take a Right at the lights onto Middle Street. Follow about 1 mile to a Rotary. Go 3/4 of the way around the Rotary and exit onto Liberty Street. (This used to be a regular intersection where you took a left.) PMP is 500 feet up on the Right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE NOTE: We recommend you park outside of the gate, as the gates are locked at approximately 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have now set the RSVP settings so no new Yes RSVPs will be allowed within 2 hours of the event.  Unfortunately it still allows people to change their RSVP from Yes to No.  If you decide to join us within 2 hours of an event please be sure to let me know the correct spelling of your name and your title (if you have one) upon arrival so I can add you to the Attended list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet by the flagpole in front of the Ranger Station.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343307322000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342386568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Walk @ Pond Meadow Park</name><id>73463352</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343082600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/73463352/</event_url></item>