<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Bloomfield Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06117</zip><lat>41.794683</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 768-4393</phone><name>Wilde Auditorium @ University of Hartford</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>826028</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.717615</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jeffrey A. Miron, senior lecturer and director of undergraduate studies in the department of economics at Harvard University, will be the featured speaker at this year’s Deeds Symposium on Thursday, Mar. 7, at 5:30 p.m. in Wilde Auditorium at the University of Hartford. &lt;strong&gt;The event is free and open to the public&lt;/strong&gt;. For tickets, call 860.768.4228 or 1.800.274.8587.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the perspective of his expertise in the economics of libertarianism, Miron discusses controversial issues ranging from abortion to the war on terror, with particular emphasis on the economics of illegal drugs&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; He was one of 166 economists to sign a letter to congressional leaders in opposition to the bailout plan put forth by the U.S. federal government in response to the global financial crisis in the fall of 2008. Miron advocated that companies that floundered during the crisis should go bankrupt instead of receiving government help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miron has appeared as a commentator on CNN and PBS, and has written for the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Forbes&lt;/em&gt; magazine. With a PhD in economics from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), Miron has chaired the economics department at Boston University and taught at the University of Michigan and MIT’s Sloan School of Management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miron is the author of &lt;em&gt;Libertarianism from A to Z&lt;/em&gt; and has published numerous articles in refereed journals as well as 30 opinion articles in the &lt;em&gt;Boston Globe&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Boston Herald&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Boston Business Journal&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hartford.edu/news/press-releases/2013/02/MironDeeds.aspx" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hartford.edu/news/press-releases/2013/02/MironDeeds.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park in Lot K - Visitor on the map. It's right next to #15, the Harry Jack Gray Center, where the Wilde Auditorium is located.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hartford.edu/visitingcampus/files/pdf/university-hartford-campus-map.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hartford.edu/visitingcampus/files/pdf/university-hartford-campus-map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is free and open to the public, but you must reserve tickets by calling the number above.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362706819000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362446036000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Economics of Libertarianism</name><id>107636812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362695400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/107636812/</event_url></item>