<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Winner of the 1999 Booker Prize&lt;em&gt;: Disgrace&lt;/em&gt;--set in post-apartheid Cape Town and on a remote farm in the Eastern Cape--is deft, lean, quiet, and brutal. A heartbreaking novel about a man and his daughter, Disgrace is a portrait of the new South Africa that is ultimately about grace and love. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

At fifty-two Professor David Lurie is divorced, filled with desire but lacking in passion. An affair with one of his students leaves him jobless and friendless. Except for his daughter, Lucy, who works her smallholding with her neighbor, Petrus, an African farmer now on the way to a modest prosperity. David's attempts to relate to Lucy, and to a society with new racial complexities, are disrupted by an afternoon of violence that changes him and his daughter in ways he could never have foreseen. In this wry, visceral, yet strangely tender novel, Coetzee once again tells "truths [that] cut to the bone." (&lt;em&gt;The New York Times Book Review&lt;/em&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

"The kind of territory J.M Coetzee has made his own. . .By this late point in the century, the journey to a heart of narrative darkness has become a safe literary destination . . . Disgrace goes beyond this to explore the furthest reaches of what it means to be human: it is at the frontier of world literature."--&lt;em&gt;Sunday Telegraph&lt;/em&gt; (UK)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs with a copy of the book visible on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>H H</member_name><member_id>6628358</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321751574000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1481208</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319645185000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Disgrace by J. M. Coetzee</name><id>38792692</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321399800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group/events/38792692/</event_url></item>