<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all. AMC/Boston Common is showing this as an IMAX feature, so it's downstairs. For crowd control they handle the line differently, so if you're running late you chance not sitting with the main group. Either way, we hang in the hallway afterwards for post-game chatter and bathroom breaks before heading to a bite afterwards. I will be at the theater by&lt;strong&gt; 6:10&lt;/strong&gt;, we will head in for seats around 6:40,  &lt;strong&gt;show time is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;7:10&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This looks like it might be a pretty cool movie.  Aliens....eye candy and cool abilities....what more is needed?   As usual, 7 PM is just an estimated time, I will update it when it gets closer to the event and actually movie times are released.    Be aware that I usually schedule meetups the first weekend that a movie opens, so it is a very good idea to buy a ticket in advance.    You can order on-line on Fandango only.  Other movie sites will not have tickets for this theater.       I will be wearing a meetup sign.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator, if it is showing downstairs, I will be by the ropes near the concession stand until they let us line up inside.   I will get to the theater and hour before showtime to start gathering people, the group will head in for seats 30 minutes before showtime.    If you miss the group before the movie, come find us after.  We gather outside the room where the movie was just shown to discuss the movie a bit, allow for restroom breaks and get a head count of those interested in going out for drinks, munchies and of course talk about movies at a nearby establishment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Director: D.J. Caruso   Stars: Alex Pettyfer, Timothy Olyphant, Dianna Agron (Full Cast)  Studio: Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures  See Trailer:   &lt;a href="http://www.findnumberfour.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.findnumberfour.com/&lt;/a&gt;   Synopsis: Three are dead. He is Number Four. D.J. Caruso ("Eagle Eye," "Disturbia") helms an action-packed thriller about an extraordinary young man, John Smith... Three are dead. He is Number Four. D.J. Caruso ("Eagle Eye," "Disturbia") helms an action-packed thriller about an extraordinary young man, John Smith (Alex Pettyfer), who is a fugitive on the run from ruthless enemies sent to destroy him. Changing his identity, moving from town to town with his guardian Henri (Timothy Olyphant), John is always the new kid with no ties to his past. In the small Ohio town he now calls home, John encounters unexpected, life-changing events-his first love (Dianna Agron), powerful new abilities and a connection to the others who share his incredible destiny. John (Alex Pettyfer) is an extraordinary young man, masking his true identity and passing as a typical student to elude a deadly enemy seeking to destroy him. Three like him have already been killed...he is Number Four. Based on the book by Pittacus Lore.-- (C)Dreamworks [Less&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the downstairs ropes around 6:10pm. I'll have a big Meetup sign stuck to my bag, and I look JUST like my profile pic. It's truly uncanny.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lou O</member_name><member_id>12201978</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298141016000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295639052000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>I Am Number Four</name><id>16135239</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298070000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/16135239/</event_url></item>