<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wow I cant believe the number of people that said NO..must be the largest number in 
Meetup.com History.
Or this is the worst event i could have ever chosen..yeh it must be this trip...

What do you think..40+ noes to only a measily 10 yesses..Cancel the trip ???

NO WAY..the only chickens on theis trip is in the meal....We are going to get wet for sure,
the water there is cooling and it should be EXCITING especially if you are up front.

Call Crabappel for a possible late cancellation, or trade your space to someone that wants to 
go real bad but waited to long to reserve, but call them.

XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX

Fridays weather report for sunday at shelbourne falls mass.:
Sunday: A slight chance of showers. Patchy fog before 9am. Otherwise, partly cloudy, with a high near 83. Northwest wind between 7 and 10 mph. Chance of precipitation is 20%.

This looks good enough for me..

Oh even though its warm the water isnt when its on you evaporating, or splashing for 
that long of a time..wear poly clothes..fast draining/wicking/that kind of stuff..
not cotton..or jeans.
the place has wet suits if you want them..i might wear my own own..i think they wash 
the rental ones..so you know what im thinking..

xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx

 you can ask for a reservation on their cancel list...

their number is 1 800 553 (raft) 7238
The Trip is reserved under the name AL -R
its 99 bucks for this day...a nice meal is included

The Monroe Bridge trip is full of big waves and fast action. The fun starts right after the dam with warm up rapids and then leads to a streach of more challenging class 3 drops such as DEVILS ODDS and LANDSLIDE. Along the way we take time to play and work the river in a SURFING HOLE or 2. Each rapid gets more exciting as the trip builds toward the last and most difficult rapids of the day, DRAGONS TOOTH and the TERMINATOR. These rapids require precise manuevering by the guide and strong paddleing by each rafter through these class 4 rapids climax an awesome day of white water action...

$99 prepaid for sunday

river trip includes safety instruction, guide, transportation to and from river and a great meal..

Crabapple Whitewater will handle the payment,
all i would do is have you reserve under AL R name for reservations..

See their website for more information

&lt;a href="http://www.crabappleinc.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.crabappleinc.com/&lt;/a&gt;

 START TIME&lt;(its 9:30) at crab appel
and takes about 1 to 1.5 hours to get there from Hartford..
better hit the road between 7:30 and 8
 WHERE TO MEET:  MEET IN THE LOT of crab appel
then LOBBY AT THE PLACE to do the final checkin.

9:30 at crabappel, 9:15, in the lot so you wont be left hi and dry and you can find us.
I will put the customary orange cones on the car somewhere.

E-Ticket
This E-Ticket is non-refundable and non-transferable. &lt;~~~
Now i see the non transferable thing..i dont know how they feel about this but call them..
they are the payment handlers and have the computer thing..i dont...
 Valid only
for dates(s) and river(s) indicated below, and must be presented
at check-in


E-Ticket# 36822




TRIP INFORMATION
Date         Trip Name                     
08/26/2007 DEERFIELD RIVER-MONROE BRIDGE
                                     1  ADULT      @    99.00    99.00
Meeting Time(s): 9:30


&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;
THE MEAL Includes a VAMPIRE STEAK, CHICKEN GIZZARDS, OR A FISH GUTS COOKOUT on 08/26
Bring your dentures..but most likely..after the trip..ya wont be able to eat for a week.its gut wrenching and make you scared.....
&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;



                                                  TRIP TOTAL     99.00

     Payment Information 
07/11/2007(P): $99.00 Sub Total                 99.00
                                        Payments Made             99.00
                                        
                              Cancellation Policy
If written cancellation is received by Crab Apple Whitewater Inc. 60 days
prior to the reservation date, a full refund less $10pp will be given.
Cancellations made within 60 days of the activity date are non-refundable.
Refunds will not be given for no shows.  We encourage you to find a
replacement.  Monies forfeited may not be applied to any balances that may
be due.  If Crab Apple Whitewater Inc. cancels an activity a full refund
or rain check will be given.


Connecticut 
FROM HARTFORD: 
Approximate Time 1 1/2 hours?Take I-91 north to Exit 26 in Greenfield, Ma. Go around 
the rotary and pick up Rte 2 WEST. Our base is about 11 miles west of Greenfield on the left 
side of Rte 2.

For Mapquest, GPS or others, use 2000 Mohawk Trail (sr 2) shelburne falls MA to get you close enough...</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188420405000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184170462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crab Appel White Water Rafting Trip...Last UPDATE</name><id>6007548</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188134100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6007548/</event_url></item>