<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364744</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-1580</phone><name>Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1019999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of the great crime novels of the 20th century, Patricia  Highsmith's &lt;em&gt;The Talented Mr. Ripley&lt;/em&gt; is a blend of the narrative  subtlety of Henry James and the  self-reflexive irony of Vladimir  Nabokov. Like the best modernist  fiction, &lt;em&gt;Ripley&lt;/em&gt; works on two  levels. First, it is the story of a  young man, Tom Ripley, whose  nihilistic tendencies lead him on a  deadly passage across Europe. On  another level, the novel is a  commentary on fictionmaking and  techniques of narrative persuasion.  Like Humbert Humbert, Tom Ripley  seduces readers into empathizing with  him even as his actions defy all  moral standards.
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike many modernist experiments, &lt;em&gt;The Talented Mr. Ripley&lt;/em&gt; is  eminently readable and is driven by a gripping chase narrative that   chronicles each of Tom's calculated maneuvers of  self-preservation.  Highsmith was in peak form with this novel, and her  ability to enter  the mind of a sociopath and view the world through  his disturbingly  amoral eyes is a model that has spawned such  latter-day serial killers  as Hannibal Lecter. &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;"[Highsmith] has created a world of her own--a world claustrophobic  and irrational which we enter each time with a sense of personal  danger." --Graham Greene &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;"Patricia Highsmith's novels are  peerlessly disturing . . . bad dreams that keep us thrashing for the  rest of the night, with the sense that an awful possibility has been  articulated only to be left unresolved." --&lt;em&gt;The New Yorker&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304965744000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303230238000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Highsmith: The Talented Mr. Ripley</name><id>17359929</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304892000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/17359929/</event_url></item>