<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>71 Union Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.329687</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-964-7100</phone><name>India Paradise</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>1186583</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192555</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>New restaurant -- this one in Newton - - India Paradise.  Yes, they have a buffet on weekends!&lt;br /&gt;Probable cost: $15 --  includes buffet, tax and tip, plus $1 to support the meetup.   (plus cost of any extras ordered from the menu)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month's book, Family Matters, from the author of A Fine Balance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DISCUSSION QUESTIONS ARE POSTED ON THE MESSAGE BOARD!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Review from Publishers Weekly:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Warm, humane, tender and bittersweet are not the words one would expect to describe a novel that portrays a society where the government is corrupt, the standard of living is barely above poverty level and religious, ethnic and class divisions poison the community. Yet Mistry's compassionate eye and his ability to focus on the small decencies that maintain civilization, preserve the family unit and even lead to happiness attest to his masterly skill as a writer who makes sense of the world by using laughter, as one of his characters observes. Bombay in the mid-1990s, a once-elegant city in the process of deterioration, is mirrored in the physical situation of elderly retired professor Nariman Vakeel, whose body is succumbing to the progressive debilitation of Parkinsons disease. Narimans apartment, which he shares with his two resentful, middle-aged stepchildren, is also in terrible disrepair. But when an accident forces him to recuperate in the tortuously crowded apartment that barely accommodates his daughter Roxana, her husband and two young boys, family tensions are exacerbated and the limits of responsibility and obligation are explored with a full measure of anguish. In the ensuing situation, everyones behavior deteriorates, and the affecting secret of Narimans thwarted lifetime love affair provides a haunting leitmotif. Light moments of domestic interaction, a series of ridiculous comic situations, ironic juxtapositions and tenderly observed human eccentricities provide humorous relief, as the author of A Fine Balance again explores the tightrope act that constitutes life on this planet. Mistry is not just a fiction writer; he's a philosopher who finds meaning-indeed, perhaps a divine plan in small human interactions. This beautifully paced, elegantly expressed novel is notable for the breadth of its vision as well as its immensely appealing characters and enticing plot.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Copyright 2002 Reed Business Information, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>book on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268672868000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265755196000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March 2010 - Family Matters by Rohinton Mistry</name><id>12564577</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268499600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/12564577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>