<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Imperial Pl</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.817040</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 751- 9164 </phone><name>CAV</name><city>Providence</city><id>391640</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.411674</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Meetup series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: CAV in the Jewelry District of Providence!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of my personal faves -complete with year-round twinkly white lights which are oh, so appropriate for this time of year! Has it really been over a year since we've been back........oh my!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAV is one of those places you need to know about. Located on the first floor of the old Imperial Knife building it has a funky-warehouse-arty feel enhanced by a decor of antiques, African and Asian art, tribal rugs and kilims that together creates a warm and inviting atmosphere. They have great food and an awesome brunch too. I'm confirming if we can get the back room, so there will be plenty of space! So let's check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check out the website for directions if you're not familiar with the Jewelry District. There is a free parking lot across the street from the courtyard entrance. The entrance to CAV is located inside the courtyard entrance. You won't see the courtyard entrance until you drive around to the back of the building (I hope I'm not confusing anyone).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.&lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291773600000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291343876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Happy Hour - CAV!</name><id>15627295</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291676400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/15627295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/4/global_7166916.jpeg</photo_url></item>