<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have volunteered to organize some early weekly hikes.   The Windsor Canal is an easy paved hike that offers views of the Connecticut River.  You may see different kinds of water animals in the canal, such as beavers, muskrats and fishers.  It is closed from Nov 14 through April for nesting eagles but right now some  are beginning to show up.  We will be starting our hike at the Windsor Locks entrance off of Rt. 140 on Canal Bank Rd.  We will walk for approximately 45 minutes then turn around and head back for a total of 1 1/2 hours.  This is a walk for health and fitness so the pace will be a bit faster than a stroll but still an easy pace.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To find the entrance, as you cross the bridge there is a large factory.  Right there is a driveway.  There are signs which say Windsor Canal, but you don't want to turn onto rt. 159.  Follow the driveway (it is very narrow and the canal will be on your left) and you will find a parking lot at the end of it.  That is where we will start the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow the link for a little more about this trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.traillink.com/ViewTrail.aspx?AcctID=6015440" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.traillink....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  &lt;br /&gt;To start at the Route 140 Mill Complex parking lot take exit 45 off of I-91 and go west on Route 140. Just after you cross over the Connecticut River there will be a Mill Complex on your right. Take the narrow road down along the canal to a parking lot.  The road is called Canal Bank Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For approximate map, follow the MapQuest link.  The trail is located on the side which says Springfield Terminal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Windsor+Locks&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;[1-2]+Canal+Bank+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06096&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.92855&amp;amp;longitude=-72.62675&amp;amp;geocode=BLOCK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>June M</member_name><member_id>9270463</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257364487000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256671740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Early Out Walk At Windsor Canal, Windsor Locks, CT.</name><id>11725449</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257191100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11725449/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/0/b/global_11248875.jpeg</photo_url></item>