<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1080 Chapel Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.308068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-432-2800</phone><name>Yale Center ForThe British Arts</name><city>New Haven</city><id>869091</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.930590</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets take advantage of the wonderful Arts &amp;amp; Ideas top knotch venues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rebuilding Culture In Iraq &amp;amp; Cambodia: From Crisis To Recovery&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GO ON LINE AND RESERVE A SEAT, THE SITE ONLY ALLOWS AN INDIVIDUAL RESERVATION, SEE BELOW SITE -&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Your reservation will allow you to gain access to priority seating on a first-come, first-served basis for Rebuilding Culture in Iraq &amp;amp; Cambodia: From Crisis to Recovery on Wednesday, June 16, 2010 at 5:30pm in the Yale Center for British Art, 1080 Chapel Street, New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.artidea.org/view_form.php?id=55" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.artidea.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Arts &amp;amp; Ideas Lecture&lt;br /&gt;FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helen Ibbitson Jessup&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Roach&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Bogdanos&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DURATION 90 minutes&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION Yale Center for British Art, 1080 Chapel Street&lt;br /&gt;The aftermath of war, civil strife and natural disaster often includes devastating cultural consequences. During the Khmer Rouge reign of terror, artistic and intellectual pursuits were systematically destroyed; at the beginning of the Iraq war, looting and mayhem resulted in the disappearance of countless treasured artifacts. U.S. Marine Colonel Matthew Bogdanos led an international investigation into the looting of the Iraq Museum. His investigation and subsequent recovery of thousands of priceless artifacts were the basis for his book, Thieves of Baghdad: One Marine’s Passion to Recover the World’s Greatest Stolen Treasures, and led to his being awarded the 2005 National Humanities Medal by former President George W. Bush.  Helen Ibbitson Jessup is a renowned scholar and curator who specializes in the art and architecture of Southeast Asia and Cambodia, and is founder of Friends of Khmer Culture.  Moderator Joseph Roach, Sterling Professor of Theater and English Director at Yale University, is the author of Cities of the Dead: Circum-Atlantic Performance, which looks at how strands of cultures from Mardi Gras Indians to Iroquois Indians in London  intertwine to recreate and restore history. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Metered street parking and public garages near the museum offer additional spots.There is also indoor paid parking at the Chapel-York Garage at 150 York Street. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet us in the lecture Hall, will try to get us all together if possible</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276798546000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270222834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rebuilding Culture In Iraq &amp; Cambodia: From Crisis To Recovery</name><id>13068265</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276722900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13068265/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/b/global_14079803.jpeg</photo_url></item>