<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1222 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.350238</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Scott</name><city>Allston</city><id>747168</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.130660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Monday, March 8 @ Great Scott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/viviangirlsnyc" target="_blank"&gt;Vivian Girls&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/malebonding" target="_blank"&gt;Male Bonding&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/youcanbeawesley" target="_blank"&gt;You Can Be A Wesley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;18+ 9pm, &lt;a href="http://www.ticketweb.com/t3/sale/SaleEventDetail?dispatch=loadSelectionData&amp;amp;eventId=1086125" target="_blank"&gt;tickets&lt;/a&gt; $10.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What a great line-up:  the awesome lo-fi all-female trio Vivian Girls; London-based lo-fi trio Male Bonding; and one of my favorite Boston bands You Can Be A Wesley.  I defy you to find a better way to spend $10 on a Monday night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vivian Girls (from allmusic):&lt;br /&gt;Deriving their name from the ill-fated characters featured in the work of writer/illustrator Henry Darger, the Vivian Girls (not to be confused with the &amp;quot;craft pop&amp;quot; duo of the same name) are a Brooklyn-based trio whose gritty lo-fi tunes nod to seminal indie pop acts like Black Tambourine, Talulah Gosh, and Tiger Trap. Comprised of Cassie Ramone, Kickball Katy, and Ali, the Vivian Girls sprang into the indie circuit in 2008 with a handful of 7&amp;quot; singles released on a passel of small labels, including &amp;quot;Wild Eyes&amp;quot; (Plays with Dolls Records), &amp;quot;Orphanage&amp;quot; (Woodsist Records), and &amp;quot;I Can't Stay&amp;quot; (In the Red Records). Their self-titled debut full-length was released on Mauled by Tigers Records and In the Red in September that same year. The record became something of a sensation and the trio spent the year touring and gaining fans the world over. Their quickly recorded follow-up album, Everything Goes Wrong, was released in late summer of 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Male Bonding (from allmusic):&lt;br /&gt;Male Bonding are a three-piece lo-fi indie rock band that formed in the London area of Dalston. Consisting of John Arthur Webb (guitar and vocals), Kevin Hendrick (bass and vocals), and Robin Silas Christian (drums), the band first appeared in the spring of 2008 performing live at a house party. The D.I.Y. nature of their debut gig summed up Male Bonding's approach to music, which first saw release through their own label, Paradise Vendors Inc., in the form of a split 7&amp;quot; with Pens. After appearing on a Flipper tribute 7&amp;quot; released through Domino Records, the group enjoyed touring the U.K. with New York all-female lo-fi outfit Vivian Girls and played shows with Lovvers, HEALTH, and Fucked Up, among others, before signing with Sub Pop in July 2009. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text/call me on 617-549-8453</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>8828135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269986871000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264258734000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vivian Girls / Male Bonding / You Can Be A Wesley @ Great Scott</name><id>12400127</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268100000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/12400127/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/f/global_12743951.jpeg</photo_url></item>