<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>rt 113</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03813</zip><lat>43.953327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Baldface Circle Trailhead</name><city>Center Conway</city><id>614763</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.987175</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Haven't done this one yet but I've heard the views form the Baldfaces are spectacular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance:&lt;/b&gt; 9.8 miles (minimum)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain:&lt;/b&gt; 3600 ft (minimum)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time:&lt;/b&gt; 6 hours and 40 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Baldface Circle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an extremely attractive trail, with about four miles of open or semi-open ledge walking between South Badlface and North Baldface. You will find less solitude here than on most of the other trails described here, but its remoteness keeps the crowds away. The section above South Baldface Shelter goes up steep open ledges that are dangerous when wet or icy, many will want to avoid them at all times. They can be bypassed using the Slippery Brook and Baldface Knob trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The shortest way is to do the entire loop on the Baldface Circle Trail, this loop is 9.8 miles with 3,600 feet of elevation gain, for a book time of 6:40.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailhead: NH Route 113 about 2.5 miles N of Maine state line at Route 113-B and about 1.8 miles S of Maine state line near Basin Pond, elevation about 510 feet&lt;br /&gt;44.238°N, 71.016°W (WGS84)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the south, follow Route 113 thirteen miles north from Fryeburg, ME. The Baldface trailhead is 0.2 miles north of the Cold River AMC Camp on the west side of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North/West, follow US Route 2 to Route 113 South 11 miles to the Baldface trailhead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 9.8 Miles&lt;br /&gt;Book Time: 6:40&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an advanced hike with steep sections.  Please be prepared to hike at book time or less.  Pace will be 1.5 - 2 MPH.  If you have any doubt please do not sign up.  If you are up to it, it will be a great hike with fantastic views.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cross posted with North East Adventures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death, including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. You also agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Edzo</member_name><member_id>7842164</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275142789000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275072056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Baldfaces - Evans Notch  Last Minute!</name><id>13625918</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275138000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13625918/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/e/global_15344382.jpeg</photo_url></item>