<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Avery Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.352853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Sports Club LA</name><city>Boston</city><id>951253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; Please Update your RSVPs and answer the Question about ticket purchase for this event. You must purchase a ticket from Boston Uncorked in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True Red Sox Natives love to be outside during the longest days of our so short Boston summer. This is one of the best parties and wine tastings of the year in Boston. I rarely miss it and it sells out every year. Five years ago it sold out in a few days! Purchase your $45.00 ticket now as you have been warned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is Summer Solstice: the date in late June marking the first official day of summer and the years longest day of sunlight. And then there is Summer Solstice: the much anticipated annual Boston Uncorked roof deck wine soiree. Each celebrates the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Boston Uncorked for a sun and fun filled evening of fine wine, food and music at the Summer Solstice 8th Annual Roof Deck Wine Tasting at The Sports Club LA Roof Deck on Wednesday, June 20 from 6:45-9:00 pm. Sample over 25 fine wines from producers all across the globe, paired with delectable bites atop one of the city's hottest roof deck venues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check In is 6:45pm. Event moves indoors if inclement weather. One must attend to experience it.  No check In after 7:45pm. For more information about the event and the wines go to [url=www.bostonuncorked.com][/url]. In order to attend you must purchase your tickets on line from Boston Uncorked.com in advance. Yes RSVPs who have not purchased tickets before the event will be changed to no. Arrive early. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MBTA - Green Line to Boylston  or Orange Line to China Town&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Car - Building's garage enter off Boylston /Essex St. between Tremont and Washington Streets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or The Boston Common Parking Garage&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also valet at 4 Avery Street at Ritz Carlton Hotel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVPs with Tickets will be E Mailed. Arrive early and meet in upstairs lobby of health club</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340326199000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337631693000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Uncorked Summer Solstice 8th Annual Roof Deck Wine Tasting Sports Club LA</name><id>65740812</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340232300000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/65740812/</event_url></item>