<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>567 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 491-5550</phone><name>Enormous Room</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>159152</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099998</lon></venue><fee><label>Suggested donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns over a couple of cocktails?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in?  Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unwind with us at the Enormous Room in Central Square!*&lt;br /&gt;[Located upstairs from Central Kitchen - look for the door with the red elephant on it.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program.  No speaker.  Just arrive and enjoy yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There isn't a DJ on Wednesdays so come prepared to just lounge and sample an array of excellent martinis and tapas.  Not into martinis? Red Stripe's always an option... or just come for the atmo and company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At SoJust you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that the people of Socializing for Justice share your vision of building a more just world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Sorry, this event is 21+ and the lounge is located upstairs (no elevator).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Socializing for Justice (SoJust) is for feminists, people working against racism, queer pioneers, genderbenders, environmental agitators, class activists, lefty artists and all people across Greater Boston working for justice in our neighborhoods, in our nation and beyond. But it's not work! Instead, we're building a strong cross-issue network through fun social events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Socializing for Justice Meetup Board and you'll be able to view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, print &amp;amp; on-line resources - and you'll be able to suggest or co-host future SoJust events like this one!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165014306000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163045415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cocktails for Justice</name><id>5254940</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1164841200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5254940/</event_url></item>