<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 N Main St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 454-6500</phone><name>RISD Museum of Art</name><city>Providence</city><id>777518</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408308</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, we branch out of live theatre to see other types of art in the area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This art exhibit at RISD is getting lots of buzz. It's a collection of British art donated by Providence native and major art collector, Richard Brown Baker. Some artists that are particularly interesting: &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banksy"&gt;Banksy&lt;/a&gt;, the notorious graffiti artist; and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anish_Kapoor"&gt;Anish Kapoor&lt;/a&gt;, who does some really cool things with space distortion. Plus a lot of other notable artists from the U.K.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/d/e/event_61557822.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Free admission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is normally $10 but is FREE the 3rd Thursday of the month from 5 to 9 pm (a.k.a. Gallery Night), so that's when we're going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 2 entrances to the museum. We'll meet in the lobby of the newest wing of the &lt;a href="http://www.risdmuseum.org/default.aspx"&gt;RISD museum&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;strong&gt;N. Main St. at 6:30 pm&lt;/strong&gt;. After the exhibit, we'll have dinner and stimulating conversation (well, that depends on you) at &lt;a href="http://www.harrysbarburger.com/index.php"&gt;Harry's Bar &amp;amp; Burger&lt;/a&gt;, just down the street. For non-meat eaters, there are a few vegetarian items on the menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No need to buy any tickets in advance (it's FREE), but &lt;strong&gt;please RSVP so I can try to make a reservation for dinner&lt;/strong&gt;. If you can't get to the museum right at 6:30, let me know, and you can catch up with us later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking - there are metered spaces, 2-hour spaces and paid lots along N. Main St. Bring quarters and an eagle eye for empty spaces!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary (from the &lt;a href="http://providence.thephoenix.com/arts/127775-britannia-rules-at-risds-%E2%80%9Cmade-in-the-uk%E2%80%9D/?page=1#TOPCONTENT"&gt;Providence Phoenix&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Made In the UK: Contemporary Art from the Richard Brown Baker Collection,"&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;a survey of&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;post-World War II British art, arrives as British artists are the top of the pops. When British figurative painter Lucian Freud died at age 88 in July, &lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; said he was "often considered the greatest living master of the human form." Team Britain also includes Banksy, regarded by many to be the greatest living street artist; Andy Goldsworthy, a preeminent land artist; and Damien Hirst, the sensational self-promoter best known for a 1991 artwork consisting of dead shark floating in a formaldehyde-filled tank that he poetically dubbed &lt;em&gt;The Physical Impossibility of Death In the Mind of Someone Living&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Everything here is from RISD's collection of British art (which the museum trumpets as "uniquely strong in the United States") thanks to Providence native Richard Brown Baker, a major New York art collector who died in 2002 and bequeathed some 170 British works and funding to the museum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet inside the entrance on North Main St.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319324413000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318001031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Made in the U.K. art exhibit - RISD</name><id>36524022</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319149800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/36524022/</event_url></item>