<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1360 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373419</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Au Bon Pain Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>703897</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119422</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Announcing a new social Meetup for Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group!&lt;b&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What:&lt;/b&gt; A Social Gathering!     &lt;br /&gt;Outdoors weather-permitting! (Au Bon Pain has indoor sitting if necessary).        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; Free! Just bring money if you would like to indulge in any of the many treats at Au Bon Pain (coffee, croissants, sandwiches, desserts, etc.)     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are adding a purely social venue to our more in-depth workshop style support group meetings. These are not intended on teaching anything, just have a fun social gathering where people can talk about what they like, share what worked in their healing, and figure out where they are still experiencing challenges.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some passages and ideas to get the conversation started and foster discussion: We will also end the gathering with a brief meditation/visualization.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   1) The following passage is taken from pg. 134 of Eckhart Tolle’s book A New Earth where he describes the symptoms the process of anxiety buildup :     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Although the body is very intelligent, it cannot tell the difference between an actual situation and a thought. It reacts to every thought as if it were a reality. It doesn’t know it is just a thought. To the body, a worrisome, fearful thought means ‘I am in danger’ and it responds accordingly, even though you may be lying in a warm and comfortable bed at night. The heart beats faster, muscles contract, breathing becomes rapid. There is a build-up of energy, but since the danger is only a mental fiction, the energy has no outlet. Part of it is fed back to the mind and generates even more anxious thought. The rest of the energy turns toxic and interferes with the harmonious functioning of the body.”     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Don Miguel Ruiz is the author of a book called The Four Agreements. According to Ruiz, a person can lead a happier life by following these four agreements:     &lt;br /&gt;1. Be impeccable with your word.  &lt;br /&gt;2  Don’t take things personally.  &lt;br /&gt;3. Don’t make assumptions. &lt;br /&gt;4. Always do your bests.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;What do you think of these agreements?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can bring our own ideas.  Use this a place to come and connect, and be welcomed especially if you are new or have not attended our events. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274444934000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273776870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Social Get-Together For The Healing Journeyers</name><id>13474979</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274392800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/13474979/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/b/global_15009403.jpeg</photo_url></item>