<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>With the help of the Boston Chihuahua organizer, Susan, DoggieDay is in search of Boston?s cutest Meet-up Pup!  To enter, please fill out an application at meet-up and submit it with your pup?s ?best? photo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each pup that wins cutest in their meet-up group will then move on to the ?DoggieDay Meet-up Pup? finals.  The pup to win the title of ?DoggieDay Meet-up Pup? will receive a complimentary birthday party for them and 9 of their closest puppy friends.  The birthday will be held during the week of their birthday on a date chosen by the dog?s guardian.  DoggieDay will send out the invites, track the RSVP?s, set your pup up on ?sPoochies Gift Registry, provide the puppy cake, goodie bags for the four-legged attendees, the decorations and all you have to do is show up for the soire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, all pups, who are finalists, may be approached to participate in various events we host throughout the year.  Events include fashion shows, calendars, TV appearances, commercials and documentaries.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below are the following meet-ups that you can register at.  Also, please RSVP for the meetups.  You must be a group member to join the contest.  To join the group, please go to www.meetup.com.  There is no fee to join meetup or the group.  We do rely on RSVP?s to reserve space for each group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Boston Terriers  Saturday, March 10, 2007 10am-12noon &lt;br /&gt;French Bulldogs  Saturday, March 10, 2007   1pm-3pm  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Chihuahua   Sunday, March 11, 2007  11am-1pm  &lt;br /&gt;Downtown Boston Maltese  Saturday, March 17, 2007 10am-12noon &lt;br /&gt;Boston Yorkshire Terriers  Saturday, March 17, 2007  1pm-3pm  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Little Yorkies   Sunday, March 18, 2007 1pm-3pm  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Italian Greyhounds  Sunday, March 25, 2007 10am-12noon  &lt;br /&gt;Jack Russell   Saturday, March 31, 2007 1pm-3pm  &lt;br /&gt;Boston mini-mutts   Sunday, April 1, 2007  10am-12noon  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Middi-mutts   Sunday, April 1, 2007  1pm-3pm  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Pug    Saturday, April 7, 2007 10am-12noon&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jen</member_name><member_id>2408295</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177336910000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Maltese Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-115</urlname><id>215542</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Downtown Boston Maltese Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174144223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Downtown Boston Maltese Meetup April Meetup</name><id>5578349</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177164000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-115/events/5578349/</event_url></item>