<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Lady Eve&lt;/b&gt; USA 1941 Starring Barbara Stanwyck, Henry Fonda   Directed by Preston Sturges &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know its a bit early for posting an event for 2010, but I couldn't resist. For those who have not seen this film before, its a real hoot- one of the best screwball comedies ever made.  &lt;br /&gt; Charles Pike (Henry Fonda) is a young, naive New Englander and heir of the Pike Ale Fortune- &amp;quot;The Ale That Won for Yale&amp;quot;. On a cruise ship he meets Jean (Barbara Stanwyck), the daughter of Colonel Handsome Harry Harrington, the  head honcho of a con-man and cardshark troupe. Jean invites Charles for a 'friendly' game of cards which is of course a ruse to win big-time bucks for her father and his cohorts. Sounds like a plan , but Charles falls for Jean and Jean for Charles. Let the real game begin....&lt;br /&gt;Barbara Stanwyk is nothing less than brillant  and William Demarest ( Uncle Charlie from My Three Sons) shines in a supporting role.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the original trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_b_DbppyLm8" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crackles with a level of wit and sexual innuendo that makes you wish they still made sex comedies for adults. Culturevulture.net  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Lady Eve&lt;/b&gt; is among the funniest films of the World War II era, and one of the few comedies whose humor has survived both cultural changes and shifting audience demographics. All Movie Guide (well some of it is outdated)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I were asked to name the single scene in all of romantic comedy that was sexiest and funniest at the same time, I would advise beginning at six seconds past the 20-minute mark in Preston Sturges' &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;The Lady Eve,&lt;/b&gt;'' and watching as Barbara Stanwyck toys with Henry Fonda's hair in an unbroken shot that lasts three minutes and 51 seconds.  Roger Ebert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;100% rating on Rotten Tomatoes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it and yes, we'll be going to a local eatery for our post-film discussion afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy New Year &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258601270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Lady Eve-Classic Comedy to Start the New Year</name><id>11909363</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262463300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11909363/</event_url></item>