<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;I just found out: Joan Anderson&amp;nbsp;needs to speak promptly at 6:30 pm and can only stay for an hour so please be prompt or come a little earlier if you can. Sorry for the late notice but I just found out myself!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Come join us for an incredible evening with&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;New York Times&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;best selling author&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Joan Anderson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;who will discuss her first book that was published &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;A Year by the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Sea&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Thoughts of an Unfinished Woman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Joan has been on Oprah twice! She has had several appearances on the Today Show, Good Morning America, ten book tours, and numerous articles headlining her as the &amp;ldquo;woman who got away,&amp;rdquo; the runaway wife,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the woman who took a sabbatical.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; My two sons were out of the nest, my husband was pursuing his dreams, and I needed to ask myself some hard questions without relying on the input of others. So I retreated to our Cape Cod cottage (off season) and gradually-- as I walked the beaches, ran into a fascinating mentor, and took a job in a fish market--came up with some unconventional answers for a new life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was when my best friends came to visit me and saw how different I was from the person that left them behind that they wanted me to tell them just what I had done to change. With their encouragement I began to retrace my steps and put my thoughts on paper. Several years later my first book, A Year by the Sea: Thoughts of an Unfinished Woman was published.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 36 rejects and 10 rewrites the book met with tremendous success. Women write to me from all over the world asking, &amp;ldquo;How did you know what was in my head?&amp;rdquo; The connection with these women has been more of a reward than I had ever imagined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Praise for A Year by the Sea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In this accessible memoir Anderson shares the joy and self-knowledge she found during her time spent in semi-isolation. Through vivid and meticulous observations about the natural world, Anderson makes clear her strong affinity for the ocean, with its changing tides, subtle colors, and burgeoning life." &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;mdash;Publishers Weekly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Curling up with this autobiography will refresh readers&amp;rsquo; souls and adjust their attitudes. During her year-long separation from family she was able to reestablish her connection to nature and discover new hope. She swam with seals, ran a mini-marathon, worked in a fish market, and earned extra income clamming&amp;mdash;activities that gave her the opportunity to shed her image as a family nurturer and allowed her to grow as an independent woman. Anderson&amp;rsquo;s story reminds readers not to overlook their personal needs. This is a good choice for discussion and a companion piece to Anne Lindberghs&amp;rsquo;s classic Gift from the Sea." &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;mdash;Library Journal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Please bring an appetizer or light bite to share, and BYOB!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Joan agreed to speak at our book club in exchange for each member purchasing a specialty inscribed Wine glass for $10.00 each, or a Coffee Mug for $7.00 each. (This is a mandatory purchase. I cannot cover someone that does not honor this agreement).&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You'll be greeted at the door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara </member_name><member_id>7313867</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharon</member_name><member_id>8235187</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nichole Graff</member_name><member_id>10861587</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319660586000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312294966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club with Author Joan Anderson</name><id>27948451</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316557800000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/27948451/</event_url></item>