<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Church St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373850</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-9007</phone><name>Fire and Ice - Cambridge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>867497</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120417</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;West Coast Swing is a flexible, slow swing dance that is danced to a wide variety of music: rhythm and blues, 60s, Latin, 70s funk, 80s pop, 90s boy bands, and hip hop. It is more sultry and sexier style of swing dancing than Lindy Hop (see below). West Coast Swing is the official state dance of California. It's has been gaining national attention recently, with West Coast Swing dancers appearing on a variety of TV shows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON &amp;amp; DANCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:00pm-9:00pm - West Coast Swing Lesson &lt;br /&gt;

 9:00pm - Midnight - Dance &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Fire+Ice Pricing: $10.00 Lesson &amp;amp; Dance &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;THE LESSON&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Lessons will be taught by different instructors each month, Rob, Joe, Neal and Guest instructors will share easy crafted moves that work on the social floor for West Coast Swing. These lessons are perfect for anyone who is new or a veteran to West Coast Swing. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;THE DEEJAY'S&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Boston has the best West Coast Swing Deejay's and they are fortunate to have Joe Mahoney as one of the top in the country. He is working on bringing great music and other Deejay's to the Wednesday Night Dance at Fire+Ice. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;THE VENUE&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is Boston's newest West Coast Swing hotspot! Make new friends and dance until Midnight in the club room at Fire+Ice in Harvard Square. The venue is complete with club lighting, high end speakers throughout the room and specially installed new wood floor just for dancers. Come to Fire+Ice every Wednesday for Boston's newest West Coast Swing Hotspot!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>James</member_name><member_id>9479702</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325124478000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Swing Dancers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>swingdancing-110</urlname><id>549506</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston-Area Swing/Blues Dance Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324498061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Every Wednesday Night - West Coast Swing</name><id>dvjbccypqblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325120400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/swingdancing-110/events/45157992/</event_url></item>