<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>The esplanade </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357726</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The foot bridge going over Storrow drive</name><city>Boston</city><id>1274741</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073362</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a free Festival at the Boston Memorial Hatch Shell! the festival is from 11:00 am until 5:00 p.m.!  I think this is a great opportunity for us to get out there and open some people's eyes! Via flyers posters or whatever we have, people need to know what's going on!!!&lt;br /&gt;-Dan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myradio929.com/EarthFest.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myradio929...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FULL LINEUP TO BE ANNOUNCED EARTH DAY - APRIL 22ND!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're thrilled to announce the 17th Annual Radio 92.9 EarthFest will be held on May 22nd, 2010 from Noon to 5:00 pm at the DCR's Hatch Memorial Shell in Boston. The free festival will feature performances from National and Local acts to be announced soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by Whole Foods Market and free to the public, Radio 92.9 EarthFest will once again be a celebration for the Earth showcasing environmentally friendly products, groups, and activities. Radio 92.9 EarthFest will also feature an all-star musical line-up, an interactive family area and more. Produced in conjunction with the Massachusetts Department of Conservation and Recreation, the event is expected to draw more than 125,000!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email the organizers personally that rsvp for the event or look for updates as the date approaches for meeting locations and times. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan</member_name><member_id>9020467</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274705750000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271129829000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5/22 Free Radio 92.9 EarthFest Concerts at the Hatch Shell </name><id>13166463</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274540400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/13166463/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/a/global_14349402.jpeg</photo_url></item>