<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.345455</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)450-7000 or (888)222-3711</phone><name>Mary Baker Eddy Library</name><city>Boston</city><id>932176</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086848</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>MEDICAL NEGLECT IS CHILD ABUSE! JOIN VICTIMS IN PROTEST!!!&lt;br /&gt;June 8 from 11:30-3:30pm &lt;br /&gt;200 Mass Ave., Boston, Mary Baker Eddy Library&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Seth Asser, a pediatrician who is dedicated to the cause of protecting children from medical neglect, CHILD, Inc, the RI skeptics Society and the RI Atheist Society would like to invite you to protest the practice of child abuse by medical neglect among religions like the Christian Science Church. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the 1970s more than 300 children have died and many more have become disabled because their parents have refused to provide medical care in favor of so-called religious or spiritual treatments. While most have been in obscure cults, many have been in the First Church of Christ, Scientist also known as Christian science. This church is especially notorious because they are very politically active and consistently lobby for special exemptions from child abuse laws for their members. Unfortunately, elected legislators have too often succumbed to that political pressure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the past five years, a group of protesters made up of CHILD members and supporters, have picketed in protest to these vile policies during the charges annual meeting in early June. The protest serves to create awareness and the surrounding community of the insidious philosophy that leads to these unnecessary childhood deaths and places the members of the church on notice that their brutal and archaic practices are not excused by the freedom of religion enjoyed in this country. The Supreme Court has stated that parents may be free to make martyrs of themselves but not of their children.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year we will have some special guests, actual victim/survivors of this church and they will make dramatic participants. We also plan to hold a mock funeral/memorial for members of the church from Massachusetts that have died in recent memory. I am hoping that these two enhancements will generate some media interest and coverage for this important issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark your calendars for Monday, June 8. Early June tends to have exceptionally nice weather in Boston and its a very pleasant way to spend an afternoon in the fresh air and amongst friends. The location is 200 Massachusetts Ave in Boston, a block east of the Boston Pops. We typically begin at around 11:30 a.m., march for a couple of hours until the formal festivities began inside at 1:30 p.m. We then take a lunch break and resume around 245 in time for the members to leave when the meeting is over at 3 p.m..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I believe if we begin to correspond with area groups and recruit volunteers we can have a great event. I hope you will help us plan and join us in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;(A message from Dr. Seth Asser and the RI Atheist Society)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan DaRocha</member_name><member_id>3370189</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245155066000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist</urlname><id>12929</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242571721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Protest of Christian Science</name><id>10430361</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244475000000</time><rsvp_limit>500</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist/events/10430361/</event_url></item>