<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>14 Mason Street</address_2><address_1>Radcliffe Institute</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375602</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Agassiz Theater</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1416452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122312</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Ten tickets are now being held for us at the door under the name Haimson. Cost is $14 cash. If possible, please have the exact amount with you so that we can expedite our purchase.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, November 12 at 7:30 (showtime 8:00) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; Agassiz Theater, Radcliffe Yard (for map: &lt;a href="http://map.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;http://map.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner before show&lt;/b&gt;:    &lt;br /&gt;           6:00 Food Court at the Harvard Square Garage, 36 JFK Street  &lt;br /&gt;           6:45 Hot chocolate/dessert at Burdick's, 52 Brattle Street &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gilbert and Sullivan--masters of &amp;quot;topsy-turvey&amp;quot;, the patter song, and general absurdly logical humor-- wrote 14 comic operas during their lifetime, including Pirates of Penzance and H.M.S. Pinafore. Each fall and spring, the Harvard Gilbert and Sullivan Players produce one of the operettas. This fall's production is Ruddigore, or 'The Witch's Curse'. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Harvard Box Office website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Baronets of Ruddigore are cursed. Anyone who succeeds to the title has to commit a heinous crime every day or perish in inconceivable agony. Robin Oakapple, a young farmer, loves Rose Maybud, but both are too shy to tell the other. Robin, however, is more than he seems.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is actually Sir Ruthven Murgatroyd, the rightful Baronet of Ruddigore, in disguise. Ruthven faked his own death to pass the accursed title to his younger brother Despard. Intrigue ensues when Robin's foster brother, Richard Dauntless, who is also besotted with Rose, informs Despard of Robin's deception. Robin is forced to accept his true position, losing Rose to his foster brother in the process. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now that he is the Baronet of Ruddigore, the ghosts of Robin's ancestors haunt him for failing to conscientiously commit his daily atrocity. Will Robin succumb to a life of villainy? Will he reclaim his true love? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find me at any one of these 3 locations (will have a Meetup sign with me): 1. At 6:00 for dinner at the Harvard Square Garage food court; 2, At 6:45 at Burdick's for hot chocolate, 3. In the lobby of the Agassiz at 7:30. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer </member_name><member_id>8178932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289695112000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288277075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gilbert &amp; Sullivan's Ruddigore at Harvard</name><id>15258572</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289608200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15258572/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>