<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;We have all the fascination of looking into another world and none of the annoyance of being told what to think about it.&amp;quot; -- Mary Frazier, London Times Literary Supplement&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Model is a 1980 documentary by Frederick Wiseman that gives the viewer a glimpse into the fashion industry and the lives of models (what they actually do during shoots for example). Supposedly, it allows viewers to see the actual world of fashion, instead of the usual Hollywood version shown in popular movies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It should be noted that this documentary has no talking heads and no narrator. Some reviewers have said the documentary is too long, so feel free to take a bathroom break at some point during the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This documentary was shown at various film festivals in Europe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because the film is over 20 years old and didn't get a mainstream release it is hard to find a lot of reviews. This NY Times overview gives a good idea of what is about: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/132021/Model/overview" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is being shown at the Boston Public Library, which means it's free. The Boston Public Library has a very good set up for viewing films. In addition, since the film gets out at 8:10, we can get coffee or tea and still get home at a reasonable hour.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a meetup sign at the end of the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221084546000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218714740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Model -- a Fashion Documentary at the BPL</name><id>8542583</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220911200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8542583/</event_url></item>