<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>[b]Update[/b]

I will be at the theater at 6:50. I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be waiting by the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where the tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand. We'll head into the theater 10 minutes before showtime, which would be 7:10.

The movie time is 7:20. I highly recommend buying tickets ahead of time at fandango.com. Be sure to buy tickets for the correct theater and date! AMC Loews Boston Common 19, the 7:20 showing of Burn After Reading on Saturday, Sep 13.

And my, we have a big group coming to this event! Woohoo! We had a lot of folks show up for Indiana Jones, and that went quite well, I thought. We all managed to sit together, taking up two rows of the theater! So please try to get to the theater early!
   

[b]Details[/b]

The latest from the Coen brothers, starring George Clooney, John Malkovich, and Brad Pitt. Can't miss this one! Even though sometimes I don't sleep that well after a Coen brothers movie.

For new folks, if you miss the gathering before the film, no worries, we regroup after the film just outside the room where the film shows. And then we go out to discuss the movie over munchies and a beer. Or two. 

[b]Synopsis[/b]

A dark spy-comedy from Academy Award winners Joel and Ethan Coen. An ousted CIA official's (Academy Award nominee John Malkovich) memoir accidentally falls into the hands of two unwise gym employees intent on exploiting their find.

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/1g_gxkpfoHU&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>45</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222684143000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218504458000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Burn after Reading</name><id>8525056</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221345900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8525056/</event_url></item>