<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 French Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01505</zip><lat>42.359173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 508-869-0314 </phone><name>Tower Hill Botanical Gardens</name><city>Boylston</city><id>718941</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.727748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Got this message today so we are moving the date of this click and shoot- please note the date and time change!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Donna,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I spoke with William from New England Photo Exbeditions meetup group would love to have the Worcester group join them on November 1 at 10am at THBG for the Sculpture exhibit. The weather forecast for this Saturday doesn't look promising.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Merline is leading this click and shoot at Tower Hill- if we get enough RSVPS we can get a group rate! So RSVP asap!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cosponsored by New England Garden Ornaments, Sudbury, MA&lt;br /&gt;and Shadows and Light, Conway, MA&lt;br /&gt;Produced by Nancy B. Grimes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.towerhillbg.org/th_sculptureshow09.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.towerhillb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The famed &amp;quot;Stone Show&amp;quot; formerly in Hardwick, Massachusetts, is expanding and moving to Tower Hill Botanic Garden to become “The Sculpture Show.&amp;quot; The show will be larger and more inclusive in every way, with contributions from more than a dozen skilled artists from throughout New England and New York. See stunning works in metal, wood, cast stone and carved stone, set amongst the incomparable beauty of Tower Hill's exquisite gardens and woodland trails—especially breathtaking during the fall foliage season. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participating Artists I Artists Bios&lt;br /&gt;Tim deChristopher I James DiSilvestro I Thomas Kellner&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Klemperer I Jill Nooney I Morris Norvin I Tom O' Connell&lt;br /&gt;Pat Plourde I Joseph Wheelwright I Carl White&lt;br /&gt;Gampo Wickenheiser I Jerry Williams I Jeane Wolfe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Garden Admission&lt;br /&gt;Regular Admission&lt;br /&gt;Adults, $10 . Seniors, $7&lt;br /&gt;Youth 6-18, $5&lt;br /&gt;Members and&lt;br /&gt;Children under six, Free&lt;br /&gt;Garden or Orangerie tour&lt;br /&gt;Every Sunday, 2pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reduced Admission Rates for&lt;br /&gt;Groups of 10+. Guided tours and&lt;br /&gt;Twigs Café boxed lunches are&lt;br /&gt;available. For details, please&lt;br /&gt;Call 508-869-6111 ext. 125 or&lt;br /&gt;grouptours@towerhillbg.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See the sculptures in the evening, lighted dramatically!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Michael at the Cafe!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257260779000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254062772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DATE CHANGE: Click and Shoot Tower Hill</name><id>11477619</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257087600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11477619/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/6/global_10920390.jpeg</photo_url></item>