<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.791451</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online Flex Meetup Group Connect Room</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1473709</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.661575</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Presentation Description: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Why unit test? What is a good unit test? Who are tests for? &lt;br /&gt;While we aren't going to get into the nuts and bolts of Flex Unit or ASUnit specifically, we WILL be talking about the aove questions that can be applied to Flex/AS3 projects or unit testing in any other language that you might mak use of. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Presenter Bio: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Joel Hooks is a Flash Platform developer with experience in Actionscript 3, Flex, and Python. Joel spent the first 13 years of his professional career as a 3d animator and graphic designer working on computer based training applications from that perspective. His interest in programming goes as far back as &amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo;TELL TURTLE&amp;rdquo;" and he has always been interested in the technological challenges related to developing software making work a little bit easier. With the introduction of Actionscript 3, Joel finally found a platform that allows him to architect useful tools while fully leveraging his experience as a visual artist. Joel is passionate about technology and enjoys exploring the landscape of frameworks, libraries, and tools that make his work constantly fun and challenging. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Joel currently resides in Fort Worth and works as a Flex consultant for Universal Mind providing clients with oodles of clean code and a focus on test driven development solutions. Joel can be found blogging on various Flex development topics at &lt;a href="http://joelhooks.com"&gt;http://joelhooks.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Outside of developing software tools Joel owns a photography studio &lt;a href="http://visualempathy.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://visualempathy.com&lt;/a&gt; with his wife who also collaborates on the raising and nurturing of his four children aged 12 to 2. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join At: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can join in at &lt;a href="http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/"&gt;http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Check what time this occurs in your time zone at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/fixedtime.html?hour=18&amp;amp;min=0&amp;amp;sec=0&amp;amp;p1=98%3Cbr%20/%3E%3Cbr%20/%3ELogging" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/fixedtime.html?hour=18&amp;amp;min=0&amp;amp;sec=0&amp;amp;p1=98 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Logging In: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you login to the Connect room (the link above) &lt;br /&gt;to view the meeting, PLEASE USE THE "LOGIN AS GUEST" option, and USE YOUR NAME, but do NOT &lt;br /&gt;attempt to use your meetup.com username/password or any Connect account. Just sign in as a guest. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;ADD THIS TO YOUR CALENDAR: &lt;br /&gt;Want to add this event to your own personal calendar? Click the link &lt;br /&gt;on the top of the event page, below the event title, saying, "Export to a calendar", which offers &lt;br /&gt;calendar downloads for Outlook, iCal, Google, and Yahoo calendars.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeffry Houser</member_name><member_id>2147426</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Wilker</member_name><member_id>2781881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299176937000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298506455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zen and the Art of Unit Testing w/ Joel Hooks</name><id>16680750</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299106800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/16680750/</event_url></item>