<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51, Room 315</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>836742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084771</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please RSVP! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (Parking behind the building, or one block West off Amherst Street)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trading Options for Income&lt;/strong&gt; by Dan Sheridan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that this talk is an intermediate options talk that assumes some knowledge of options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan Sheridan will show several options trades, and demonstrate how he is tweaking them in the current market environment.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;First he’ll show a credit spread, which involves buying one call or put and simultaneously selling another more expensive call or put at a different strike for a credit.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; Next, Dan will focus on butterfly trades and show 2 – 3 different ways of trading this versatile strategy in the current markets to bring in monthly income.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that this talk will be webcast, and we’ll be able to ask Dan questions.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; Following his presentation, some BIG members will discuss their experience trading these options strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan is a veteran options trader, who traded in the CBOE pit for 22 years.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; He worked for Mercury Trading, with Jon and Pete Najarian, making markets in options.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; Since 2004, Dan has run Sheridan Options Mentoring, which provides practical options education to retail traders.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; Dan hosts the popular show "Options Safari" on CBOE TV, which runs twice weekly. He is currently hosting a new CBOE seminar series titled: Be a Successful Retail Options Trader, which is 5 seminars, each focusing on a specific strategy and including some of the best retail practitioners of these strategies in the country. He also does monthly webinars for option brokers including Think or Swim, Options Monster, OptionsXpress, and Trade King.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;You can find parking behind the building, or one block West off Amherst Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;To join our online discussion go to &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/bostonibd"&gt;http://groups.google.com/bostonibd&lt;/a&gt; .  If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you! Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room. We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340201054000</updated><rating><average>2.25</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339597266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Speakers Meeting: Dan Sheridan on Trading Options for Income</name><id>68986512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340060400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/68986512/</event_url></item>