<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We invite you to join us for this spectacular community event as we kick off the holiday season with the Annual Lighting of the Nubble on Saturday, November 29th, 2008. Festivities get underway at 5:00 pm at Sohier Park with entertainment including the York High School Chamber Singers. The event includes traditional Christmas Melodies along with Kiddie Carols - something for the whole family. The United Divers of New Hampshire will once again, plan to raise the lighted tree from the ocean, we’ll have the ever popular visit from Santa who arrives by way of a York Beach Fire Dept. ladder truck and we’ll count down, together, the seconds before the Lighthouse is lit and adorned in it’s holiday lights. There’s plenty of hot chocolate and cookies for all, so we hope you’ll mark your calendar and plan to join us for this free community event. A COMPLIMENTARY SHUTTLE SERVICE IS AVAILABLE FOR YOUR CONVENIENCE. THE SHUTTLE WILL RUN FROM ELLIS PARK IN SHORT SANDS BEACH FROM 3:30 PM - 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone would like to arrive early for some ocean photography I will be arriving around 2:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great chance to practice some low-light and holiday light photography!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If people are looking to carpool please use the comment section to let us know.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be arriving early to get some setup shots - 2pm/ Will meet at park at 4</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228165946000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226326085000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Lighting of the Nubble Lighthouse </name><id>9131213</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227992400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/9131213/</event_url></item>