<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/c/a/event_79107082.jpeg" width="240" height="181" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of the workshop: $20 in advance&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; $25 on the day of the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As spring buds are blossoming so is our desire for more love, intimacy and passion in our life.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; But often wounds inflicted in past relationships get in a way.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Past hurts hold hostage parts of our ourselves and parts of our lost energy. &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We are also still burdened by dysfunctional energies we have brought out of a relationship.&lt;/span&gt; A form of shamanic retrieval, that is liberatingly precise, simple and concrete, because it is based on &lt;strong&gt;Quantum Universal principles of Effortless Healing&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;Energy Restructuring&lt;/strong&gt;, will bring you back into wholeness, no matter when and how the wounding took place.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To-day the power of the principles was affirmed when client, with whom I worked on a life long wound from a past relationship, gave me a heart warming testimonial.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; She said:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;ldquo;I know I have scraped the barrel of my trauma. Because when you resonate with trauma it is interesting, otherwise it is boring and tedious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how I know I&amp;rsquo;ve stopped resonating with it &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am bored with my trauma and its history&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sleep much better, which had not happened for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was so exhausted, and now I have a lot of energy, so much energy my brain is not prepared for it.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I do not know what to do with my time.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I may have actually energy to garden this spring!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In all of us there is a yearning for the wholeness and freedom and grace in healing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, join us for healing your past relationships in a way that does not require revisiting or re-experiencing one's trauma as we work at the deepest laws of the universal principles that allow the healing at the deepest level of being&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**********************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself a question:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you are now in a relationship that often brings up all sorts anxiety provoking related issues?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do you want to know how to remain energetically connected in a healthy way to your lover, your spou&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;e without being re-triggered by wounding form past relationships?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do you want to learn how to make every relationship beneficial?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you are, then come an join us&lt;/span&gt; to tend to the gardens of our souls as they bloom anew!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;You will also learn about energy cords which are conduits for an exchange of energies that either nourish us, or render us drained, assaulted and dis-empowered. The kind of energy flowing through the cords, and the way in which the energy is exchanged, determines whether relationships are beneficial or destructive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We yearn to be set free of those connections that do not serve us well, only to find ourselves, like puppets, manipulated by emotions that are beyond our control. Understanding the energetic aspect of our present and past relationships sheds light on how we can effectively break these patterns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ree yourself from destructive effects of bad relationships without painful cord cutting&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;General Attributes of Energy Cords that need healing &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Constant thoughts about a specific person,&amp;nbsp;place or idea.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A sense of loss of energy that accompanies those thoughts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Feeling drained after a conversation or a meeting with that person, visiting that&amp;nbsp;place or thinking about that idea.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;An inability to resolve the past related to that person, place or idea, and live in the present.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This evening workshop will inform, inspire and educate you, advancing you towards a mastery of energy intelligence that will keep you connected with the spiritual realm.&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;Energy intelligence is a skill that was, up to now, only available to a select group. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Now it can be accessible to all. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Please join us.&amp;nbsp; Invite your friends.&amp;nbsp; Fore more information on Energy Restructuring system please visit www.healingwithouteffort.com and check out interview and articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to sharing beautiful and healing time with you tomorrow&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blessings on your healing journey&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a yeallow road sign "Children" right next to the steps to the house.  The road is one way, and the house is on the left side of the street, if you are walking in the direction of the trafict.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333672814000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328210019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Universal Principles for Healing Wounding of Past Relationships</name><id>dvsnlcyqdbmb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333666800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/50757282/</event_url></item>