<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Yard</address_2><address_1>Harvard College</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374528</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John Harvard Statue</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>710042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117194</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Another poll read (sorry for the delay in posting...the schedule was beyond tardy this month): American Wife by Curtis Sittenfeld.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied (in bits) from: &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://curtissittenfeld.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://curtissittenfe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On what might become one of the most significant days in her husband’s presidency, Alice Blackwell considers the strange and unlikely path that has led her to the White House–and the repercussions of a life lived, as she puts it, “almost in opposition to itself.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Alice Blackwell, New York Times bestselling author Curtis Sittenfeld has created her most dynamic and complex heroine yet. American Wife is a gorgeously written novel that weaves class, wealth, race, and the exigencies of fate into a brilliant tapestry–a novel in which the unexpected becomes inevitable, and the pleasures and pain of intimacy and love are laid bare.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to try and make the summer last beyond labor day by heading again to Harvard Yard.  I'll have my blue beach blanket.  Bring something to sit on and munch on if desired.  I'll probably have leftovers from something :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it rains, we're braving the fans at Au Bon Pain in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya then!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252624334000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250976840000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: American Wife by Curtis Sittenfeld</name><id>11174419</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252450800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/11174419/</event_url></item>