<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/c/d/e/event_53556062.jpeg" width="190" height="289" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Take a step back in time at the Renaissance Faire... &lt;br /&gt;

Enjoy some shows or shop for unique gifts. Feast and be merry. Cheer on your favorite knight in the joust. &lt;a href="http://www.ctfaire.com/index.php"&gt;http://www.ctfaire.com/index.php&lt;/a&gt; Check out the site for more details but as a renfaire goer, I assure you, they are fun especially if you dress up in the garb :)&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The CT faire runs for the next few weekends from 11am-6pm and Fall seems to be filling up fast for us all, so I am listing the themed weekends coming up so we can take a vote on which date we should go. I know we want to have many options for meetups, but we can't always pull off being in 2 places at once (well, I know I haven't mastered that skill yet!) If you choose a date I can't make, I just ask for a volunteer to host. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday October 1: Vow renewal day (Romance anyone?) &lt;br /&gt;

Sunday October 2: Babes in Bodices Contest (for the guys) &amp;amp; Highland games (so muscular men in kilts for the ladies) &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday October 8: Halloween Knights with costume contests, scary ghouls and zombies and um... barbarian invasion too. &lt;br /&gt;

Sunday October 9: Pirate invasion &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday October 15: Children's Fantacy/Masquerade/Pet weekend with Halloween Knights &lt;br /&gt;

Sunday October 16: Pet weekend (Really - you can bring your pet) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Admission is $16.00 which you can buy online (for a small fee) or at the gate (no credit cards at the gate) I would suggest bringing cash for food - some vendors accept credit cards. Parking is $3 so we should plan carpool meetup locations as well. The shows and entertainment are free but there may be additional activities available for an extra cost. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

They have sample itineraries on the website or we can just wing it (haha - get it? really , it's my last one)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Outside Front Gates - Text/Call Andi 203-805-8279</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andi</member_name><member_id>14218596</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318421174000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316645605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecticut Renaissance Faire</name><id>34483502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318172400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/34483502/</event_url></item>