<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;No rest for the weary - we've finished our NH 48 (Kate, Kelby and Loki!) and are now on to hiking the NE 100 Highest points. &amp;nbsp;Vose Spur is a bushwhack on the NE 100 list. &amp;nbsp;Bob &amp;amp; Geri have graciously offered their bushwhacking experience to help us bag this peak!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This climb is estimated to take 7 hours. &amp;nbsp;For a description of Bob and Geri's 2009 ascent click here: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://rbhayes.net/latest/VoseSpur-June-09/index.htm"&gt;http://rbhayes.net/latest/VoseSpur-June-09/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cool and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This is a BUSHWHACK, so please dress appropriately. &amp;nbsp;If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. &amp;nbsp;Come prepared to stay dry!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This IS NOT a traverse and we will NOT need to carpool to another location.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will meet at the intersection of Sawyer River Road and Route 302. &amp;nbsp;The road will be closed, so we will have to walk 2 miles in along Sawyer River Road to the Signal Ridge Trail head where we will start.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunset will be at &amp;nbsp;about 4:42 pm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike will NOT be very exposed, but there is a somewhat exposed rock scramble (Talus field) along the way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will NOT pass a hut on this climb.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water sources appear to be *very* limited on this trail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headlamps are required. &amp;nbsp;Always be prepared to come out in the dark if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you. &amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Since this is a bushwhack, it is important that the group stay together.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I (Kate K) am NOT a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace. &amp;nbsp;I'm doing about book time these days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day. &amp;nbsp;I would like you to be around for another day too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My hikes are always dog friendly, but please know the limits, abilities and behavior of your dog(s) &amp;amp; bring plenty of water. &amp;nbsp;I will probably have at least one of my dogs on this hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. I (Kate) rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I (Kate) will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors. &amp;nbsp;If the weather looks like it will be miserable, including rain, we will reschedule. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;RSVP Questions are NOT optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Totals&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 --------&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;7 hours round trip&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THIS PEAK BEFORE AND I HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kate K:  Green honda civic with Namaste sticker on the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321194804000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310390159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NE100:  VOSE SPUR (Bushwhack)</name><id>25308821</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321106400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/25308821/</event_url></item>