<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well, it was like this, pard...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angela and Mike were talkin' the other day and Angela suggested that it might be time for another ice cream social...but Mike said that anything ending in &amp;quot;social&amp;quot; just sounded too highfalutin', and besides, he had a hankerin' for some good old-fashioned barbeque!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He may have thrown a &amp;quot;yee-hah&amp;quot; in there, somewhere, but don't expect him to admit to it...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyways, since Mike was runnin' the event, he got to pick! Barbeque it is!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barbeque restaurants are still pretty uncommon on the South Shore, and &lt;a href="http://www.truebluebbq.com/" target="_blank"&gt;True Blue BBQ &lt;/a&gt; is unusual even among the few that we do have here. How so? For one thing, it's run out of a &lt;a href="http://www.truebluebbq.com/TRUEBL~2/About_Us/IMAG010A.JPG" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt; and only open Friday, Saturday and Sunday from 11:00 AM - 8:00 PM. For another, it sits on the grounds of another business: &lt;a href="http://www.truebluebbq.com/TRUEBL~2/About_Us/IMAG011A.JPG" target="_blank"&gt;Kingston Nursery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Something that isn't unusual about True Blue? The food. &lt;b&gt;That&lt;/b&gt; is just plain good!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Out plan for this event is too take advantage of everything that the site has to offer. First and foremost, that means the chance to eat barbeque outdoors (there's seating for 11 people, with room for more to stand, if it came to that). After we've eaten, those who are interested are welcome to walk the nursery with Mike and watch him play horticulturist. If nothing else, this will give you a better idea of why he doesn't get invited to too many parties...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;True Blue BBQ (at Kingston Nursery)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;191 Summer Street, Kingston&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 19 @ 11:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; None for this (probably) small and (definitely) informal event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, July 18 @ 9:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of you said in the Poll that Saturdays are good for you to Meetup with us this Summer so come on out to join us for this event-fee-free bbq social!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; From Rt 3, take Exit 10 and head towards Route 3A South and Route 53 North; that is,  take a left off the ramp from Rt 3 North (coming from the Cape) or a right off the ramp from Rt 3 South (coming from Braintree). Note that if you find yourself heading North on Route 3A you need to turn around! Coming down off the ramp, you should find yourself at a traffic light looking directly across Route 3A at a mall containing an Ocean State Job Lot and a Hannaford Supermarket. Turn &lt;b&gt;right&lt;/b&gt; (this is the beginning of Route 53) and start looking for Kingston Nursery on your right as it comes up within half a mile. True Blue BBQ is located on the left side of Kingston Nursery's yard.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the trailer on the left side of the yard at Kingston Nursery.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217128745000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215832881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Impromptu Barbeque!</name><id>8324829</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216481400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8324829/</event_url></item>