<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Every time I walk by this place the aroma is so so intense.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not just for brunch but for for lunch and dinner also.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since we have not done a early dinner Meet-up and I have ask Tonya in regards to dinner ,she said yes,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well here it is....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner at Alfresco...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the mature crowd with a unique palate..  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our reservation will be at 6 :30 pm. If you arrive late, ask for Jo-Ann Reservation at the door.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry about the two times I had on the description and place.&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for understanding see everyone there.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This restaurant is located  in Davis Square Somerville.  Parking is free on Sunday.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do not Park in the Rite Aid Parking Lot you will be towed even on Sunday (Be Advise). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their menu consist of Fresh Antipasto , Vegetarian Plates such as Ravioli Pomodoro, Porcini Ravioli and Gnocchii to name a few.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrees consist of Shrimp Risotto, Grilled Salmon, Shrimp or Scallops Linguine, Pan Seared Chicken, Chicken Carciofi wow can I say more...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meat - Tortellini with Prosciutto, Veal Parmesan, Veal Alfresco, Veal Marcela, oh my..  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Desert - New York Style Cheesecake, Carrot Cake to name a few.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This restaurant is quaint and relaxing day or night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prices range from $8.95 to $15.95.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry at this time they do not have a website.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need more information on their menu let me know will send it to you.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would love to get  together before the New Year, let's enjoy, talk, mingle whatever... &lt;br /&gt;2008 is around  the bend... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's enjoy each others company, conversation....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location is accessible by the MBTA Red Line to Davis Square T Stop.    &lt;br /&gt;For more information go to MBTA.org  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By car go to Mapquest.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash only to pay for menu and 20 % tip plus tax on all meals.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is a waiting list let me know that you are interested and I will see what I can do  - thanks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEMBER GUIDELINES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on a friendly and respectful gathering while sharing a fantastic meal with one another.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow dining companions time by arriving on time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, and tip including tax.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES Only if your are certain you will be attending.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you  have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-Show.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO in less than 24 Hours of the event you are counted as a NO-Show.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you have RSVPd for NO-Show it will count as if you have NO-Showed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you NO-Show fir three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198930746000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195965149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Time Dinner In Davis  Square</name><id>6798098</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197243000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6798098/</event_url></item>