<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>38R Merrimac Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.812216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newburyport Chamber of Commerce</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>862498</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.872032</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Mass Audubon is having an Eagle Festival celebrating the return of the Bald Eagle that includes tours by bus to Eagle hot spots.  Advanced reservations are required.  I have reserved eighteen spots for the 10:30am tour.  They leave every half hour and it's an hour and a half trip.  All events for the Eagle Festival are free.  There are many more events going on all day.  You can find it on the web for the Massachusetts Audubon Society.    After the tour we can meet for lunch.  When I know how many are attending I will try to reserve a moderately priced restaurant.  Suggestions are welcome in your reply, right now I am thinking of the Park Lunch or The Grog.  The Audubon suggested Michael's Harborside because they help sponsor the event.  After that we can cover the other events at Joppa Flats Education Center, Parker River Wildlife Refuge and Newburyport's City Hall or you can go on your own.  Be at the meeting place by 10:00am so we can group together and be on time for the 10:30am tour.  This is an event that is open to the public and you can reserve your own time but I thought it would be fun to do it as a group.  There will be two Meetup groups going on the same tour.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the west end of the board walk with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234830717000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233000890000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Merrimack River Eagle Festival</name><id>9605676</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234623600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/9605676/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/d/global_6592605.jpeg</photo_url></item>