<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The presentation will be a case study on the upcoming completely redesigned website for the Alumnae Association of Mount Holyoke College. We'll attempt to review the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Motivation behind the redesign &lt;br /&gt;

 * The RFP process &lt;br /&gt;

 * Design Process &lt;br /&gt;

 * Hosting &lt;br /&gt;

 * Themes and plugins used &lt;br /&gt;

 * Development workflow &lt;br /&gt;

 * Content migration &lt;br /&gt;

 * Mistakes made and lessons learned&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a little something here for everyone whether you are a designer, developer, blogger, consultant, or customer. It can be interesting to hear the back story of a web site and hear the answers to the how, why, who, and what questions. Hopefully, others will be willing share case studies of sites that they have worked on. It can be educational and apply to a broad audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the holidays, we'll take the month of December off and resume in January. In the meantime, explore the new website at &lt;a href="http://valleywp.org"&gt;valleywp.org&lt;/a&gt;, sign up, and participate. There are groups and forums. It is a place to &lt;span&gt;continue the conversations or start new ones, to ask questions or provide answers and share your experiences. It only made sense that a WordPress group have it's own website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The original winning domain name in a  recent straw poll was "valleywordpress.org," but WordPress frowns on using their name in the domain. The initials "wp" are fine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ed Gray</member_name><member_id>8270759</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354204552000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352864934000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2012 November WordPress Meetup: A Website Case Study</name><id>91315362</id><headcount>12</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354147200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/91315362/</event_url></item>