<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sharing October's Free Class at Wayland Wellness with you:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Meditation Can Be Easy!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Evening, October 23rd, 7:15 –8:30pm, Wayland Wellness, 15 East Plain St., Wayland, MA 01778&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you aware of the benefits of meditating, but can’t get yourself to do it or you think it’s too difficult?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meditation can be one of the easiest and most effective means to living with greater harmony, happiness and well-being.  &lt;i&gt;It’s an opportunity to peacefully transform your problems, your fears, and any pain and stress in your life into something more positive.&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;b&gt;And, it's a great way to set or shift into the perfect mood for your day, feeling perfectly aligned with all that you desire.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• You don’t have to sit in silence for long periods of time to gain the multitude of emotional and physical benefits!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come to this Free Introduction to Meditation Class and experience how simple and delightful it can be.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ll learn:&lt;br /&gt;• Some simple techniques you can do for yourself for any length of time that is comfortable for you.&lt;br /&gt;• How to easily get into a meditative state and create pleasurable feelings.&lt;br /&gt;• The difference between active and passive meditation.&lt;br /&gt;• What you can use meditation for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;We will not be doing traditional silent meditations.  The class will consist of 2-3 guided meditations.  All you have to do is let go and listen to Ann’s voice as she leads you through the process, like listening to a good story.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;The meditations will leave you totally relaxed with magnificent feelings of peace, love, happiness and hope - essentially feeling really, really good!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;All are welcome.  Please share this with your e-mail lists and groups, your friends, and your family!  It's a wonderful evening - like going on a mini retreat!  All you need to do is rsvp with your guests on this meetup site, or have them e-mail me their name, e-mail and phone # to AnnIde@NewPossibilitiesCoaching.com. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** If you prefer to meditate lying down, please bring whatever you might need to be comfortable: mat, pillow, blanket, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This class is co-sponsored by Wayland Wellness and New Possibilities Coaching as a free service to their clients and the surrounding communities.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256512954000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254435993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meditation Can Be Easy!</name><id>11523274</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256339700000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/11523274/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>