<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well of the few people that voted on the poll, the majority wanted a potluck, so a potluck it is. Now that's real democracy in action! So start thinking of what vegan delight you'd like to share with the group. Please let me know what you are bringing so we can make sure that everyone doesn't make the same thing. As always, please contact me if you have any questions or suggestions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location is listed finally!! Regarding parking: Parking is ok on all side streets, but is NOT ok on Avalon Place (gravel road). It's a private road and all spaces are assigned. Christina's doorbell is on the left side next to her name. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There also is the possibility of a demo/protest either before or afterwards...so stay tuned for that info as well. Yes I know it's Super Bowl Sunday...but there is no Super Bowl without the Pats!!! Just in..possible AR movie viewing too! Man do we know how to pack it all in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is ok on all side streets, but is NOT ok on Avalon Place (gravel road). It's a private road and all spaces are assigned. My doorbell is on the left side next to my name. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170785220000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168196652000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp February Meetup</name><id>5373431</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170612000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/5373431/</event_url></item>