<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>How to find the organizer(s)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This is a private event, with advance registration and payment to the workshop instructor required, so it will be easy to find me! Limited reservations available.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;--M (Nor'easter Gal) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration limited to 8 people: call workshop instructor at 603-319-1786 &lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Alissa Cohen Living on Live Food&amp;quot; Level I Chef Certification Class registration is $125 (non-refundable) and includes: &lt;br /&gt;~ A delicious 7 course Living Foods meal &lt;br /&gt;~ Recipes &lt;br /&gt;~ Instruction &lt;br /&gt;~ Living on Live Food Chef Certificate sent to you from Alissa Cohen &lt;br /&gt;The Level I Chef Certification Class is a 4 hour LIVING FOODS WORKSHOP. This course gives you the basics of the raw food diet through the Living on Live Food plan. All the food we make and eat is included in the registration fee. All of the recipes are included in the handouts. The food is organic, as much as is available at the time of the class. &lt;br /&gt;This is the Living Food menu we will prepare and enjoy together: &lt;br /&gt;~ Mock salmon pate, a yummy sweet red bell pepper and walnut pate &lt;br /&gt;~ Collard green roll-ups with guacamole, marinated mushrooms, onion rings &lt;br /&gt;~ Angle hair vegetable pasta with outrageously delicious marinara sauce &lt;br /&gt;~ Vegetable Fettuccini with a cashew, macadamia, pine nut Alfredo sauce &lt;br /&gt;~ Warm broccoli soup made in the Vita-Mix blender &lt;br /&gt;~ Stuffed marinated mushroom w/sprouts, onion, avocado, tomato &amp;amp; olives &lt;br /&gt;~ Delicious date nut torte for dessert &lt;br /&gt;You will leave the Level I class knowing: &lt;br /&gt;~ What an Enzyme-Live/Living Foods diet is &lt;br /&gt;~ How to make delicious Enzyme-Live/Living Foods meals &lt;br /&gt;~ How to prepare gourmet raw food meals, simply and easily &lt;br /&gt;~ How to shop for raw foods &lt;br /&gt;~ How to get others excited about Living Foods! &lt;br /&gt;With a Level I Chef Certification you can receive discounts for Alissa Cohen's products which can be ordered online or over the phone, and you have the option of purchasing your own Living on Live Food web site through AlissaCohen.com &lt;br /&gt;Having the Level I Chef Certification makes you eligible for the 2-day Level II Living on Live Food Instructor Certification. &lt;br /&gt;To register for the Level I class on Sunday, June 8, 2008 from 1pm-5pm at SoBo Book &amp;amp; Bean, 241 Main Street, South Berwick, Maine 03908, please call Magnolia at telephone 603-319-1786 or fax 207-438-0756 with the $125 registration fee. Credit cards accepted by fax or phone. &lt;br /&gt;Magnolia Thomas is a Certified &amp;quot;Living on Live Food&amp;quot; Level III Teacher/Trainer/Chef living in Kittery, Maine. www.rawfoodteacher.com/magnolia AskMagnolia@aol.com &lt;br /&gt;Sign up today for Level I and be on your way with a Living on Live Food lifestyle! We will prepare and enjoy a delicious gourmet, Enzyme-Live Food meal, so plan on arriving with a good appetite! &lt;br /&gt;Magnolia Thomas, Certified Living on Live Food Teacher Kittery, Maine &lt;br /&gt;email: askmagnolia@aol.com phone:603-319-1786 fax:207438-0756&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a cozy place, I'll be easy to find and so will you! Private workshop, requires pre-registration and pre-payment, so the venue will be open only to registrants that day as a private event.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213293424000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Hands on, all ingredients and tools provided, walk away with handouts of recipes and methods, and eat your successes AND your mistakes! :-)</why><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211485935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hands-On Raw Foods Chef Workshop</name><id>7993177</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212944400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/7993177/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/e/global_1941310.jpeg</photo_url></item>