<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Littleton Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.596606</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 256-0001</phone><name>The Java Room</name><city>Chemsford</city><id>751175</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354094</lon></venue><fee><label>Voluntary Donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This meeting will be in a coffee shop where folks grab a coffee, soda, dessert, or a glass of wine and enjoy conversation with other folks interested in Linux.  People in this group have a wide range of experience with Linux, and often there are small demos running on laptops.  The Java Room offers free WiFi access to its customers, and we make good use of that resource.  There are a good number of folks in attendance who mix their Linux interest into other interests such as  ham radio, MythTV, homebrew firewalls, virtual machines, disc jockies, junk box electronic projects, and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is a &amp;quot;birds of a feather&amp;quot; setting, we don't have one person giving a presentation to the entire group.  This is much more interactive, where people move from one small group to another, checking out different projects, demos, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people stay for the entire 2 hours, but if you need to leave beforehand, we'll be glad that you came to visit, even if for only a short time..  :-)  Many people often continue the meeting in the parking lot, especially when the weather is good.  11:00 PM comes up fast, especially when you're having fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy Stewart</member_name><member_id>3117855</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200096233000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Linux Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>linux-393</urlname><id>304994</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>The Chelmsford Linux Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196305989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Linux @ The Java Room</name><id>6822306</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199923200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/linux-393/events/6822306/</event_url></item>