<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Time TBD &lt;br /&gt;2008 NCAA Tournament - First Round &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, March 23 - 7:00 p.m. - ESPN2 &lt;br /&gt;vs. No. 16 Cornell (20-8) &lt;br /&gt;The Huskies will play their opening round game vs. Ivy League champion and No. 16 seed Cornell (20-8) at the Arena at Harbor Yard (9,000) in Bridgeport, Conn., on Sunday, March 23 at 7:00 pm in an ESPN 2 telecast. No. 8 seed Texas (21-12) will battle No. 9 seed Minnesota (20-11) on Sunday, March 23, approximately 30 minutes following the UConn-Cornell match-up. &lt;br /&gt;Sunday's first round winners will advance to the second round games on Tuesday, March 25, also at the Arena at Harbor yard in Bridgeport. The winners of Sunday's first round sessions will play at a time to be announced. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Huskies, who have claimed three of the last six NCAA titles (a total of five in the program?s history), their last coming in 2004, will be making their 20th consecutive NCAA Tournament appearance and boast a 61-14 (.813) mark all-time in NCAA play. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UConn earned an automatic bid to the 2008 NCAA Tournament following its BIG EAST Tournament and Regular Season Titles. The Huskies captured the tournament title with wins over DePaul, Pittsburgh and Louisville following a 15-1 BIG EAST mark during the regular season. Connecticut currently stands at 32-1 overall and is ranked No. 1 nationally in both the Associated Press and ESPN Coaches polls. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The automatic berth marks the Huskies? first since 2006 and the 14th in the program?s history. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut has advanced to the Final Four eight times in the program's history, including five of the last eight seasons overall. The Huskies have advanced to the regional round of the NCAA Tournament in each of the past 14 seasons (1994-present). The Huskies are 33-4 all-time in NCAA Tournament games played in the state of Connecticut, including a 3-1 mark in NCAA games at the Arena at Harbor Yard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This season marks the 11th time UConn has entered the NCAA Tournament as a No. 1 seed. The Huskies boast an overall mark of 43-6 in NCAA Tournament games when playing as a No. 1 seed and have captured four National Championships in those seasons. The Huskies were also a No. 1 seed last season when they advanced to the Fresno Regional Final before falling to LSU 73-50. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During nine of the last 14 NCAA Tournaments (since 1994), the Huskies have either won the national championship or have lost to the eventual national champion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2008 NCAA Women?s Basketball Championship First and Second Rounds &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at the Arena at Harbor Yard (Bridgeport, Conn.) &lt;br /&gt;First Round Games - Sunday, March 23 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greensboro Regional &lt;br /&gt;No. 1 seed Connecticut (32-1) vs. No. 16 seed Cornell (20-8), 7:00 p.m. (ESPN2) &lt;br /&gt;No. 8 seed Texas (21-12) vs. No. 9 seed Minnesota (20-11), 30 minutes later (ESPN2) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Head Coach Geno Auriemma | Ketia Swanier | Tina Charles |Charde Houston| Renee Montgomery | Maya Moore &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What were your reactions after hearing Rutgers being called? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?I think probably everybody was surprised, with so many teams to choose from it was kind of ironic. I guess Rutgers is the number eight seed in the country and I find that hard to believe but I guess they are. If I was them I would be questioning what is going on. Like I said before if it was a real tournament it would be one versus eight, two versus seven, three versus six but not that it is going to play out that way. There is no guarantee that one plays two at the end but if you project that far, you hope that is the case. I don't know what Rugters? RPI was at the end of the season but I have to believe that it was better than eight.? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it was one versus two and they put Tennessee on the other side of the bracket, what is your reaction to this possible match up? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?As I said there are no guarantees for anything so it doesn't matter where they put anybody. When you are a number one, you are a number one. It doesn't really matter what number you are, it is more what your bracket looks like. In the NCAA Tournament you like to play teams that you have not seen before. Certainly like the people said on the telecast, having to play a team that you have played, like the top two teams in the league have to play again then I guess Rutgers was penalized for getting knocked out early in the BIG EAST Tournament. I really was not paying attention to any other brackets, I really didn't look at them well enough.? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is your initial reaction of looking at your bracket? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think you are always looking for possible mismatches that don't make too much sense. In generally speaking, when you look at a bracket you like to see a lot of teams that you don't know much about and they don't know you. So I was kind of disappointed about how I feel out but it does not change how I feel about what we are going to try to do. I think it is pretty neat for this group of players and what they have gone through.? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.uconnhuski.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.uconnhuski...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206664624000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Because we are great Uconn fans</why><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205812940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NCAA CHAMPIONSHIP FIRST ROUND   Game starts at 9:20</name><id>7554293</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206491400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/7554293/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/4/global_3286548.jpeg</photo_url></item>