<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Turn brown paper lunch bags into a colorful, cute journal in this quick and easy workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIME:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; 1 pm to 4 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Scissors, glue stick, a wide (1-1 1/2 inch) paintbrush.&amp;nbsp; Materials for 1 book will be provided, but you may bring extra bags and any paints or other embellishments you wish to use.&amp;nbsp; You may also want to bring a drink or small snack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$12 per person. We can accept cash or checks made to "ArtStudio 360." &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;This fee helps keep ArtStudio 360 open, so we can't accept IOUs or partial payments&lt;/span&gt;; please plan to pay when you arrive. We're happy to direct you to a nearby ATM if you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.) and some supplies including acrylic paints, collage materials, embellishments, paper and more.&amp;nbsp;Access to a microwave, toaster oven, refrigerator, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Anyone! (18+ only, please.&amp;nbsp; A version of this workshop for kids is forthcoming.) Just sign up through the NE ATC+ Meetup Group. Membership in the Meetup group is free; joining simply allows you to reserve a space in events at ArtStudio 360.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;These smaller sessions&amp;nbsp;often fill&amp;nbsp;quickly.&amp;nbsp;Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly so that your space becomes available to someone else. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;In the unlikely event that we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Applegail</member_name><member_id>26569312</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329848773000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325454617000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paper Bag Books: The Workshop</name><id>46180302</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329674400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/46180302/</event_url></item>