<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Photo Plus</address_2><address_1>655 West 34th Street</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10001</zip><lat>40.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>774-239-0214</phone><name>Jacob K. Javits Convention Center</name><city>New York</city><id>199356</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.989998</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello All!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott and I are considering going to this trade show in NYC. It's the biggest Photographic Trade show in the US. I've gone every year for the last 5 years and always find it fun and exciting. It is NYC! ... and the show lasts from Oct 18-Oct 20. I think we will be going down on the last Day. The 20th. Maybe we can car pool if folks are interested in going? I think 10.00 each should cover tolls and gas and parking if we get 4 folks to split it...Let me know your thoughts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you sign up on thier web site before 9/26 you can get into the expo for free. After that it is 40.00. So even if your not sure about going you should sign up now and be free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is some info and a link to the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.photoplusexpo.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.photopluse...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most comprehensive event in the photography &amp;amp; imaging industries. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be there as the ever-changing world of photography &amp;amp; imaging comes into focus at PDN PhotoPlus International Conference + Expo 2007 - the premier event for innovative imaging solutions, photographic education and unparalleled networking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PDN PhotoPlus International Conference + Expo 2007 is your chance to:&lt;br /&gt;Discover new imaging solutions: Preview the hottest products and technologies on the market from over 300 of the industrys leading manufacturers and suppliers.&lt;br /&gt;Awaken your creativity: Learn the newest techniques and rules from the world?s greatest photographers and imaging experts at the PhotoPlus Conference.&lt;br /&gt;Find visual inspiration: Get up-close and hands-on with the latest advances in digital, film and output; and rediscover your passions in the extraordinary photo galleries on the Expo floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connect with creative minds: PDN PhotoPlus International brings the leaders, innovators and rising stars in our industry together at the hottest networking events.&lt;br /&gt;Simply stated: PDN PhotoPlus International Conference + Expo has the products and education you need to be a leader in the photography and imaging industries?today and in the future. Whether you?re a professional or advanced amateur, you will discover a marketplace of solutions that is unrivaled worldwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pricing&lt;br /&gt;Expo Only&lt;br /&gt;On or before September 26 - $10&lt;br /&gt;Register online and expo only registration is FREE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After September 26 - $40 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gold Expo Pass&lt;br /&gt;On or before September 26 - $59&lt;br /&gt;After September 26 - $79&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two Hour Seminars On or Before September 26 After September 26&lt;br /&gt;1-2 Seminars $80 each $95 each&lt;br /&gt;3-4 Seminars $70 each $85 each&lt;br /&gt;5-7 Seminars $65 each $80 each&lt;br /&gt;Full Seminar Package (8-9 Seminars) * $495 $495&lt;br /&gt;*Does not include Hands-On or Three Hour Seminars&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Three Hour Seminars On or Before September 26 After September 26&lt;br /&gt;  $105 each $120 each&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hands-On Labs On or Before September 26 After September 26&lt;br /&gt;  $150 each $170 each&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193065893000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187019565000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photo Plus NYC</name><id>6172526</id><headcount>472</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192892400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6172526/</event_url></item>