<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Not hiking related really but a volunteer opportunity for our members. This is an opportunity to help out with remodeling, construction, &amp;amp; in some cases landscaping projects for elderly &amp;amp; disabled people in our communities. Each HomeFront Day is carried out by thousands of volunteers who represent corporations, businesses, faith-based organizations &amp;amp; civic groups coming together as a community to assist neighbors in need. I've volunteered the past three years for this annual event &amp;amp; this year's AmeriCares HomeFront project will be on Saturday May 7th, from 7:30 AM until 5:00 PM. &lt;strong&gt;I will post the location of the event &amp;amp; info about the project &amp;amp; the needs that we want to fill as we get closer to the date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be renovating &lt;span&gt;(#TBA)&lt;/span&gt; Enfield homes this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee and donuts are provided in the morning. Lunch is also provided &amp;amp; snacks &amp;amp; cold drinks are available all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;House Co-Captains (in charge of work and site):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phil Shea&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be working in Thompsonville, CT on an old Presbitarian church which has been bought by a soup kitchen (I think it is Enfield Loaves and Fishes). We will be installing new windows and doors as well as some painting in a dining area downstairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate Location (somewhare around the house number, the captain was unable to give exact street number but it is a church so can't miss it!):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(old Presbitarian Church) &lt;br /&gt;28 Prospect St. &lt;br /&gt;Thompsonville, CT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Enfield&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=28+Prospect+St&amp;amp;zipcode=06082-3443&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.99713&amp;amp;longitude=-72.601166&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS"&gt;http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Enfield&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=28+Prospect+St&amp;amp;zipcode=06082-3443&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.99713&amp;amp;longitude=-72.601166&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you will be working at my location or another location (update your RSVP with that information).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team we will be joining is the one I've worked with the past few years (address is only team host's address/phone, &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not work location&lt;/span&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St. Patrick's HomeFront Team&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;64 Pearl St.  &lt;br /&gt;Enfield, CT 06082  &lt;br /&gt;(860) 745-2411&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne Marie Gallagher  &lt;br /&gt;Volunteer Coordinator  &lt;br /&gt;(860) 745-9556&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are starting work at 7:30 AM. When you arrive, please sign-in, sign the liability waiver, &amp;amp; grab your tee shirt. Every member working must be wearing an AmeriCares HomeFront tee shirt throughout the day.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be aware that you will need to wear sturdy shoes, and clothing you don't mind getting dirty in. Bring work gloves, hand-tools, ladders, and rakes, shovels, etc, if you have them. Please make sure to put your name on your tools so you get them back at the end of the day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please know that if you cannot contribute the full day to this proejct, it is quite ok to come for part of the day&lt;/strong&gt;... That is perfectly ok and understandable... So... if you can only participate for a portion of the day, please indicate in your RSVP when you can get there, ie. full day, morning only, afternoon only, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more about Americares Homefront at:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americareshomefront.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americares" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americares" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americares" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americares.org&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;General individual volunteer information is at (&lt;strong&gt;you don't need to do any of the forms, just show up at the event and you can sign in there and start helping out!&lt;/strong&gt;):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americareshomefront.org/volunteer/individuals.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americares" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americares" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americares" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americares&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1988, AmeriCares HomeFront is a community based volunteer home repair program that helps homeowners who are physically or financially unable to maintain their properties. AmeriCares HomeFront Day takes place during the first weekend of May, when teams of "hands-on" volunteers representing businesses, civic groups and faith-based organizations complete necessary repairs at no cost to homeowners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions for the actual address will be e-mailed to Yes/Maybe RSVP's Saturday, 4/30/11</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307307477000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298945877000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Americares HomeFront Day - Enfield, CT  Area</name><id>16744737</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304767800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/16744737/</event_url></item>