<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 South Main Street</address_1><state>SC</state><zip>29601</zip><lat>34.846958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online ONLY | LibertyPAC.com | RonPaul2012.com</name><city>Greenville</city><id>1610731</id><country>us</country><lon>-82.400696</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=144335795652038" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; THIS EVENT IS SPECIFICALLY TARGETED AT FOLKS WHO HAVE REACHED THEIR FEC CONTRIBUTION LIMIT WITH THE OFFICIAL CAMPAIGN. THERE ARE NO LIMITS ON DONATIONS TO THIS PAC BUT IT IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH THE OFFICIAL CAMPAIGN! &lt;a href="http://www.RevolutionPAC.com/superbomb" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Revolution...&lt;/a&gt; Revolution PAC, the Super PAC formed in July to support the presidential ambitions of Congressman Ron Paul, has announced a money bomb fundraiser &amp;#150; a &amp;#147;Super PAC Superbomb&amp;#148; &amp;#150; for September 19. &amp;#147;September 19 marked the first of the battles of Saratoga, which taken together amounted to a significant turning point in the War for Independence,&amp;#148; said Revolution PAC President Gary Franchi. &amp;#147;We hope ...this Superbomb, and the resources it brings in, will propel us toward a victory no less dramatic for Ron Paul.&amp;#148; In advance of the Superbomb, the Super PAC is emphasizing its grassroots nature, its low overhead, and its effective use of funds. &amp;#147;We are regular Americans, each of whom has a track record of support for Dr. Paul and what he stands for,&amp;#148; said Thomas Woods, Revolution PAC Advisory Board Chairman. &amp;#147;We aren&amp;#146;t paying the six-figure salaries and five- and six-figure expense reimbursements we often encounter in the political world. We are simply dedicated to the cause, and we have employed every penny donated to us wisely and conscientiously.&amp;#148; The Super PAC form of organization, made possible by two court rulings in 2010, has gathered steam quickly during this election cycle. Unlike a presidential campaign, it can accept unlimited donations from individuals, businesses, and other groups. During an event outside the Chicago Federal Reserve over the weekend Franchi remarked: &amp;#147;We&amp;#146;re changing the game. Anybody can donate to us, but in particular those who have reached the $2500 legal limit in donations to a presidential campaign can now continue to help Ron Paul by supporting the Revolution Super PAC. &amp;#147;We will devote whatever we raise to carrying out the most efficient and effective political marketing campaign Americans will see this cycle. Ron Paul and his message will be everywhere. The Ron Paul grassroots will have been underestimated for the last time.&amp;#148; The Revolution PAC is asking foreign supporters of Ron Paul to patronize US businesses who support the Super PAC. Ron Paul supporters are being asked to pledge to contribute to the September 19th Superbomb at &lt;a href="http://RevolutionPAC.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://RevolutionPAC....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316452882000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314648479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revolution PAC Super Money Bomb</name><id>31424792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316448000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/31424792/</event_url></item>