<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Worcester Photo Center Members and Guests-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Holidays to one and all! It's that time of year again for us to start planning the Holiday party. Yes it is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what shall we do this year? Our Print Swap of course! What's a print swap- well, I'll tell you! You pick out one of your very own photographs, have it printed, matted, and signed- by you- then you wrap it up in a fun and festive way- bows are optional of course- and you bring it along the night of the party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you arrive in your festive and cheery mood- you write your name on a slip of paper provided, place it in the santa hat and leave your wrapped print on the table for all to wonder about. Then after eating, drinking, and being merry- we pull names from the hat one by one and folks can come up and pick a wrapped print from the pile. You open it and share it with the group! Your photo collection grows and you share a little piece of your talent with the rest of us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And since it is a party... we also ask that you bring one food item to share! Last year we had a wonderful array of foods! Chix Wings, Chips and dip, Cookies, Flan, Chinese Food, sweet treats and mini apps abound. So bring a little something to share. We'll take care of the plates, napkins, silverware and cups. And the soda, juices, cider, and hot coco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Finally- please feel free to bring a friend, a significant other, or a husband or wife. It's a party after all and we'd love to meet the important folks in your life. Why not give them a sneak peek in to where you go once a month to chat about photography. So hire that Baby Sitter now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to seeing you all there- seeing your prints - and of course meeting your "others"! In the mean time Happy Holidays to each and everyone of you from Donna and Scott.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS: Special note on the print swap- we get asked these questions each year so i thought I'd head them off ahead of time- but if you have a question- feel free to email me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Size of the print- is completely up to you! Small or large doesn't matter. Simply do what you think works best. I got a beautiful 4x4 inch print one year and a large 16x20 another year. I love them both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Why matted? We would like for you to mat the print so that folks can have you sign the mat. Part of building a nice photo collection is the lovely personalized signature from the artist. If you mat the print you can sign the lower right corner and the person will know who it was from. You can get a mat at the local walmart/target or from a framers. I know the Christmas Tree Shops also has them. Try not to spend to much as that is not the point. Which brings me to...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Framing- again- it's completely up to you if you want to frame the piece- it is not "required!" So do not feel like you have too. But here is the thing- if you'd like to- go ahead. Again - your choice!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. This is a no pressure completely fun and stress free thing- so just enjoy it! Go with the flow! And it's a fun way to start your photo collection...I know I love the images I have gotten over the years.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Scott and I are always to try to greet everyone who comes to the meetups.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Walker</member_name><member_id>2654920</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alan J. Kidawski</member_name><member_id>5162177</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Iadarola</member_name><member_id>5198329</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Lane</member_name><member_id>5229126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325732836000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852146000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Holiday Party and Print Swap</name><id>pglbzypqbmc</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325205000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/16002753/</event_url></item>