<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gap Mountain Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03465</zip><lat>42.814663</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gap Mt. Trailhead </name><city>Troy  </city><id>793884</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.156063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.beqbooks.com/gap/gapsilo.jpg" width="300" height="113" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #4477cc ; font-size : large"&gt;Gap Mountain Reservation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in southern Troy NH, Gap Mountain offers a spectacular view of Mt. Monadnock and the surrounding countryside for the price of a climb of less than an hour through lovely stands of pine and hardwood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Gap Mountain Reservation is owned by the Society for the Protection of New Hampshire Forests and administered by the State of New Hampshire Department of Parks and Recreation. The SPNHF maintains two parking areas that provide off road parking to the South and the North of the Mountain. Come visit one of the outstanding natural preserves in southwestern New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click below for more information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.beqbooks.com/gap/gap.htm"&gt;http://www.beqbooks.com/gap/gap.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to Get Here&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the North and West:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Keene NH, take Route 12 south through the town of Troy. About 2 miles south of Troy, turn left on Gap Mountain Rd. Follow this road for 8 tenths of a mile, bearing right at the first fork. At &lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;8 miles, take a sharp left (a sign points to Gap Mt). The parking area is about two tenths of a mile on the left. This lot is know as the South Parking Lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the South and West:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Route 2 in Massachusetts, take Route 140 north to Route 12 just south of Winchendon MA. Follow Route 12 thorough Winchendon and across the state line into New Hampshire. 10 miles north of Winchendon, you will come to an intersection with NH Route 119. From this intersection, continue north on Route 12 for 2.4 miles to Gap Mountain Rd. on your right. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;NOTE: Do not take the Gap Mountain Rd. that is a half mile north of the intersection with Route 119.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn right on Gap Mt. Road. Follow this road for 8 tenths of a mile, bearing right at the first fork. At .8 miles, take a sharp left (a sign points to Gap Mt). The parking area is about two tenths of a mile on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the East:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the Eastern part of New Hampshire, take route 101 or 202 to Peterborough. Then take Route 202 south to Jaffery. Take Route 124 west from Jaffery through Jaffery Center. One Route 124 you will pass a parking lot for access to Mt. Mondnock on your right. 8 tenths of a mile beyond this parking area, look for Bullard Rd. on the left. Turn left onto Bullard Rd. and follow it for half a mile. (This is a narrow road, so drive cautiously.) Just before the road bends sharply to the right, you will see the road to the trailhead parking lot on your left. This lot is known as the North Parking Lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a 1.3 mile hike to  Middle Summit. Weather is looking good....let's check it out!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309291452000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305486545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GAP MOUNTAIN - 1,862'</name><id>18460291</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309095000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/18460291/</event_url></item>