<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join my husband and me as we roll our way around Ashland Reservoir in our Greenland kayaks.  If you've ever wondered what those people with the skinny sticks (Greenland paddles) are doing in those strange kayaks, now is your chance to find out.  Greenland-style kayaking is becoming more popular in the US with more and more people building replica skin-on-frame kayaks.  These low volume kayaks are lots of fun and a great way to learn skills beyond staying upright in your kayak.  We enjoy being upside down as much as right side up!  We'll paddle over to the beach and demonstrate some of the basic Greenland skills (side scull for support, balance brace) and more difficult Greenland rolls and answer any questions you may have about Greenland kayaking.  Feel free to join us in whatever kayak you are currently paddling (or walk in from the main entrance if you do not want to bring your kayak).  Warning: lots of dogs on beach!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are still not quite sure what Greenland paddling is all about, visit:  &lt;a href="http://waldenqajaqsociety.org" target="_blank"&gt;Walden Qajaq Society&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ashland State Park's Main entrance is closed for the season, but people do park in a lot and by the side of the road leading to the locked gate at the main entrance and walk in to the beach.  The boat launch, however,  is at the opposite end of the reservoir on Spring Street in Ashland.  To get to the launch, take Route 135, just past Weston Nurseries (heading east) and turn right on Clinton, left on Olive and right on Spring St.  Shortly past a gravel operation you will come to a dirt parking lot on your left where the launch is located.  Parking gets creative, but there is usually enough room.  The entrance to the beach is on State Park Road in Ashland, 1.3 miles past Clinton Street (still heading east on 135).  You'll have to walk in about 1/2 mile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No need to RSVP unless you are bringing a kayak.   It will take about about 20 minutes to get down to the beach, where we will spend at least an hour before a leisurely paddle back to the launch.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253458199000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252538998000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ashland Reservoir with a Greenland Theme</name><id>11332600</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252850400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/11332600/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/global_2046284.jpeg</photo_url></item>