<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Union Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.379608</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 623 9211</phone><name>Precinct Bar</name><city>Somerville</city><id>743340</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095481</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Atlas Soul, a 3 times Independent Music Awards winners/finalist is playing Precinct a small and intimate venue in Union Square Somerville. Friday June 18 @ 10PM&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to help promote the show (and get a free CD) please contact Jacques Pardo. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Effortless cross-cultural blend with enticing results!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The hallmark of the North African musical tradition is openness to others. Musicians from this culture effortlessly blend centuries-old rhythms, instruments and melodic concepts with modern ideas and innovations from the world over, creating a constantly changing panorama of styles. Atlas Soul’s musicians exemplify this spirit. In their recordings and their live performance the group serves up a tantalizing stew of musical styles. The delighted listener hears the influences of jazz, Latin, flamenco, French hip-hop and the traditional North African music, all blended with the deft and sure hand of a master chef. Great vocals top off the warm and savory instrumental mix.&lt;br /&gt;Mike Crager&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Atlas Soul's blend of jazz, funk and Middle-Eastern/Arabic grooves is a fascinating sonic stew that will catch any listener's ear. This is their second appearance on our CD's compilation. We like'em, and you will too&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt; Global Rhythm Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“What hits hardest about Atlas Soul’s sound is the natural funk of North African music and also powerful vocals, which span fluid, passionate Gnawa melodies and husky Raï hooks. There is great wisdom in a world-music outfit that embraces divergent genres  (but not so many that the sound loses its identity)&amp;quot; writes world music journalist Banning Eyre. The Phoenix&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An evening of World Music, Funk, Jazz, Fun and Dancing!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3 awesome bands:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:00 PM Persian Blue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.persianbluemusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.persianblu...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;10:00 PM Atlas Soul&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlas-soul.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlas-soul...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;11:30 PM The Diversions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kelsmusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kelsmusic....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Precinct is this real nice, friendly and intimate little club in the heart of Union Square in Somerville. Make sure you say that you are coming for Atlas Soul (so we get credited for it)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheila </member_name><member_id>6189105</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277031495000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275835957000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atlas Soul  bring North African Funk to Somerville</name><id>13713800</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276909200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/13713800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/b/e/global_15531518.jpeg</photo_url></item>