<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>152 Commonwealth Ave Unit M-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.458334</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(877) 578-4777</phone><name>Lens Pro To Go</name><city>Concord</city><id>1066094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.396617</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>For those of you who haven't attended these events before, you're been missing out. We organize a huge gathering of working professionals in the fields of photography, modeling, wardrobe, hair and makeup. This is a huge networking and portfolio building event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We rent out a huge photography studio in Concord for the day and we setup lots of backdrops and lighting setups for everyone to use. We also have hair and makeup people in the back room to help with some touch ups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The general idea is share share share. Bring your equipment, props and unique skills to the table. Share your pictures with the models, make-up artists and other collaborators. For the professional models out there you get lots of different photographers shooting you the entire day for the low price of $20. The photographers get to expand their portfolio ten-fold for only $40. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're still working out the details of this shoot. The last model shoot GMS4 we had snakes, spiders. We had a live band and over twenty pizzas with over 12 shooting areas to choose from. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're a photographer please feel free to bring some lighting equipment and any backdrop stands you may have. The more equipment the better. This event also heralds education and skill knowledge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Models, show up with any basic touch ups such as foundation and blemishes covered and the make up artists will be able to work wonders and add a little extra something to your look. &lt;br /&gt;Bring a small suitcase of outfits that fit a Summer day theme like sun dresses, swim suits or anything that doesn't make you realize its -10 outside&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make-up artists (MUA's) &lt;br /&gt;We always get so many inquiries about our shoots and many promise to come. We always fall short on this. So i'll give it to you straight, we usually have around 30-40 models and your only duties are to be creative and have fun with whatever you want to do with the models. You are not required to do touch ups if you don't want to and you can do as little or as much as you want. You can get digital copies from any of our photographers. You get to attend for free, and you get to build your portfolio and maybe your client roster. Please contact us if you are interested in participating. &lt;br /&gt;patrick@pcsphotography.net or 508-353-9900&lt;br /&gt;mikey@unitymike.com or 508-471-0069 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is on Winthrop Street which is directly behind LensProToGo Studios.&lt;br /&gt;Please also note that Models start to get there at 9am as it takes awhile for them to get ready and photographers dont need to be there until 10 but feel free to come early to help out if you want.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301260579000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295798888000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Great Model Shoot v5 "everything summer" </name><id>16152684</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299420000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/16152684/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/6/global_20990502.jpeg</photo_url></item>