<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;directions to Mount Roberts Location: Northeast of Lake Winnipesaukee East of the town of Center Harbor, NH. Driving (one way from Nashua, NH): Distance: 85 miles Time: 1 hour 50 minutes Parking: at road-end parking lot by the gate house for Castle in the Clouds If you use a car GPS, here are the road-end parking lot coordinates (in degrees and minutes): N 43 43.896 W 71 19.514 Roads: - Everett Turnpike north - Route 93 north to Exit 23 - Route 104 east - Route 3 north - Route 25 northeast through Moultonborough - Route 109 southeast (for 2.2 miles) - Route 171 southeast (for 0.5 miles) - Ossipee Park Road (for about 1.2 miles)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;Hiking (LOOP): Distance: 7.5 miles Time: 5.5 hours Trail: Mt. Roberts Trail&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail Guide: AMC Southern NH Trailguide Trail Map: Hiking Trails of the Castle in the Clouds Conservation Area published by Lakes Region Conservation Trust GPS Track: Mount Roberts GPS Track Hiking (one way, up to the summit): Distance: 2.5 miles Vertical: 1300 feet Time: 1 hour 50 minutes Summit: Wooded summit with directional view, plus ledge views along the trail Height: 2582 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winter Accessibility: Available year round&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324820171000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324303677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT ROBERTS AND FARAWAY MTN IN THE OSIPEE RANGE</name><id>44895812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324737000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/44895812/</event_url></item>