<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kancamagus Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>44.008961</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>CHAMPNEY FALLS TRAIL</name><city>ALBANY</city><id>4218502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.269997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;#65279;All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;starting at Champney Falls Trailhead Back to here hike 0.07 mi/2 min/+9 ft on the Champney Falls Trail Leaving the parking area, the trail soon crosses Twin Brook on rocks (the footbridge here was severely damaged by a flood in March 2011 and is unsafe to use), turns right, passes the junction, where the Bolles Trail diverges right, and proceeds south with easy grades, mostly on an old logging road, to Champney Brook. to the junction of Bolles Trail hike 1.33 mi/55 min/+477 ft on the Champney Falls Trail There it swings right to avoid an abandoned section of trail along the brook, then descends left and returns to the old road along the brook. A loop path diverges left to Pitcher Falls and Champney Falls, climbing steeply near the falls. Caution: Many of the ledges in the area around the falls are very slippery; there have been many serious accidents in this vicinity. The main trail passes a restricted outlook to the north, and the loop path rejoins. to the junction of Champney Falls loop hike 1.60 mi/1 hr 26 min/+1268 ft on the Champney Falls Trail The steady ascent continues. The trail passes a good outlook to the north and reaches the first of several switchbacks, and the Champney Falls Cutoff (also known as Middle Sister Cutoff) diverges left toward Middle Sister. to the junction of Middle Sister Cutoff hike 0.30 mi/16 min/+220 ft on the Middle Sister Cutoff Leaving the Champney Falls Trail, it follows an old road past an outlook ledge, then swings to the right onto open ledges and soon reaches the Middle Sister Trail. to the junction of Middle Sister Trail Totals Distance 3.30 mi Time 2 hr 39 min Elev Gain +2012 ft Elev Loss -38 ft Elev Change +1974 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.36 mi/14 min/-57 ft on the Middle Sister Trail The trail descends across ledges marked by paint, passes the Champney Falls Cutoff (right), and climbs over the open ledges of First Sister to its terminus on the Champney Falls Trail. to the junction of Champney Falls Trail Totals Distance 3.66 mi Time 2 hr 53 min Elev Gain +2110 ft Elev Loss -193 ft Elev Change +1917 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.15 mi/9 min/-163 ft on the Champney Falls Trail It passes the junction on the right with the Middle Sister Trail in the ledgy saddle, and soon passes a side path to an outlook on the left. to the junction of Middle Sister Cutoff hike 1.60 mi/1 hr 26 min/-1268 ft on the Champney Falls Trail The Champney Falls Cutoff (also known as Middle Sister Cutoff) diverges right toward Middle Sister, then the Champney Falls Trail descends by switchbacks and passes a good outlook to the north, and the steady descent continues. to the junction of Champney Falls loop hike 1.33 mi/55 min/-477 ft on the Champney Falls Trail The trail passes a restricted outlook to the north, and a loop path exits right to Pitcher Falls and Champney Falls, descending steeply near the falls. Caution: Many of the ledges in the area around the falls are very slippery; there have been many serious accidents in this vicinity. The loop path reenters the trail and farther down, the main path swings left off the old road to avoid an abandoned section of trail along the brook. The trail returns to the old road and continues its descent. to the junction of Bolles Trail hike 0.07 mi/2 min/-9 ft on the Champney Falls Trail Keeping mostly to the old logging road, the trail follows Champney Brook at easy grades. The Bolles Trail diverges left, and soon the trail crosses Twin Brook on rocks (the footbridge here was severely damaged by a flood in March 2011 and is unsafe to use) and arrives at the parking area. to Champney Falls Trailhead Totals Distance 6.81 mi Time 5 hr 25 min Elev Gain +2142 ft Elev Loss -2142 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326678129000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326113164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MIDDLE SISTER</name><id>47312022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326551400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/47312022/</event_url></item>