<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>New Haven</address_2><address_1>2 Lighthouse Point Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06512</zip><lat>41.252910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lighthouse Point Park</name><city>East Haven</city><id>157379</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.892105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Y-ME is a national organization that provides programs and services to breast cancer patients, survivors and their loved ones. This year, two of its founders will be joining the Mother's Day walk right here in swingin' New Haven. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone interested in joining us for a fun 3 mile walk through Lighthouse Park on Mother's Day morning has been promised a pretty cool time! There'll be lots of corporate sponsors giving free hand-outs, food, music, and other fun stuff. Also, my company is putting a team together, with friends and family welcome. Our captain, Eileen, has made up T-shirts for all of you who come join us (for any Pinky and the Brain fans out there, we promise not to lure you to Chia-Earth). Also, if we have 25 people, there will be a nice table and stuff for us. Eileen said that with friends and relatives we have almost 20 already. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Y-ME is asking every participant to try and raise $100. Check-in starts at 7:30, the walk begins at 9am, and should be done by ten, leaving much of the day free. But if you're out of town that day or just can't make it, you can just give me money. Granted, you can always hand me money, but for once I won't blow it on comic books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To register, go to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://newhavenwalk.y-me.org/site/PageServer?pagename=MDE_NHCT_homepage" target="_blank"&gt;http://newhavenwalk.y...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click on &amp;quot;register online&amp;quot;. Then &amp;quot;Join an existing team&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;search for a team&amp;quot;. Put just &amp;quot;454&amp;quot; in the company box, hit search. You should get &amp;quot;Team 454&amp;quot;, with Eileen Shields as the captain. Click on join the team.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see a lot of you there!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210680447000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208043815000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mother's Day 3mi walk for breast cancer = free T-shirts! Walkers/donors welcome</name><id>7728192</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210507200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7728192/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>