<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Spring is just around the corner and I plan on being at the Track again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out this beginners Running Plan From &lt;a href="http://www.coolrunning.com/"&gt;www.coolrunning.com&lt;/a&gt;....    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This beginner's running schedule has helped thousands or Walkers/Runners get off the couch and onto the Roads. Walking and running 3 miles in just two months. Nine weeks! To learn how to safely Walk, Jog or Run Three (3) Miles or 30 minutes. (April 2- June 4) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too many people have been turned off of Running simply by trying to start off too fast. Their bodies rebel, and they wind up miserable, wondering why anyone would possibly want to do this to themselves. That Said, I would like People interested in Walking as Well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Me on Tuesdays to start off and another Day may be added as well. Each session should take about 20/30 minutes, and should be done three times a week. May start walking the first week!. Last year as the season progressed I added in a workout on the benches and found enjoyment in a lite am rain in the hot summer months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The Boston Shape Diva Dash is Saturday September 7th 2013. It can be hard getting motivated, so I welcome  support and accountability from others. I can’t always make it to other posted evenings to run so I thought I would open up a meet up when I go to the track please Join Me... On This Running/walking Plan. This will repeat into the Summer and  may need to adjust based on&lt;/span&gt; school programs. &lt;strong&gt;LOOK for other events coming up AS  Many of our Organizers posts running events, Biking and triathlons.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Track</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Evans</member_name><member_id>12731994</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366121067000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362337740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Couch 2 5K Walkers/Runners Plan</name><id>qtztmfyrgbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366110000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/113628582/</event_url></item>