<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 North Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03303</zip><lat>43.287703</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Hampshire State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>1406437</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.604050</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Although this is a non-partisan group, many of our members may find this of interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A committee hearing will be held on a bill to push back on Obamacare. Please come and speak to your representatives at the hearing, if you can make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the bill's sponsor, Bill O'Brien:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The current batch of NH legislative proponents of Obamacare have scheduled a legislative committee hearing for Tuesday, February 5 at 10:00 am in Representative Hall in the State House on House Bill 271, one of the few bills this session th&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;at will push back on Obamacare.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 HB 271 is a bill I sponsored that would prohibit the state from expanding Medicaid under Obamacare. NH’s option to reject Medicaid expansion was one of the few choices that the U.S. Supreme Court left to the states last June when it upheld Obamacare. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Clearly, by scheduling the hearing in Representatives Hall, the NH proponents of Obamacare plan to turn out a large crowd to “demonstrate” the popularity of that federal takeover of health care in NH. We need to match their numbers and show that NH understands that Obamacare not only exceeds the limits of permissible federal intrusion on both individual liberty and state sovereignty, but also that it will be a financial disaster for NH. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Obamacare seeks to provide government-paid health care coverage for millions of people who earn up to 133 percent of the federal poverty level, which is $14,856 for a single person this year. So far, nine states, all with Republican governors have announced they won’t offer these expanded welfare benefits. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Part of the objection is to providing free health care to able-bodied adults. As Governor Duagaard of South Dakota recently said, in words that apply to New Hampshire, “They're not disabled; we already cover the disabled. They're not children; we already cover children. These are adults -- all of them."  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The most substantial reason to oppose this expansion however is that it is unaffordable. Based on the present population of NH, adopting enhanced Medicaid under Obamacare here would expand free health care welfare roles in New Hampshire in the years 2014 to 2022 from 138,000 individuals now to 180,000 recipients, an additional 42,000 adults, according to a November 2012 study issued by the Urban Institute and the Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation. (See &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kff.org%2Fmedicaid%2Fupload%2F8384.pdf&amp;amp;h=YAQFhR8rn&amp;amp;s=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kff.org/medicaid/upload/8384.pdf&lt;/a&gt;).  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Now, the federal government is claiming it will pay 90% of the cost of this new group, at least for a while. Even with that promise, the expansion will cost NH taxpayers tens of millions of dollars a year. Moreover, that 90% funding promise is likely to go the way of the 40% federal funding promise for special education, which now is about 17% and going down. The federal government itself is running out of money and borrowing capacity, so that day likely will come sooner rather than later. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 In addition to this first group of new Medicaid recipients, due to other features of Obamacare, tens of thousands NH residents who already qualify but aren't enrolled in Medicaid likely will sign up for Medicaid benefits over the next few years starting with the nationwide rollout of Obamacare that begins next. The exact number of this group is unknown as it is unclear how many employers will end health care plans in the face of federal mandates, thereby dumping new recipients on to Medicaid. What is known is that even with 138,000 individuals receiving Medicaid today, there is almost equal number who are income eligible, but don’t receive Medicaid. Ninety percent of those individual chose to stay off Medicaid because they now have private insurance. But much of that private insurance for lower income workers will go away with Obamacare’s expensive mandates of what have to be in qualified, employer-financed plans. In other words, employers will chose to pay the fines or will bring the full-time employee numbers below 50 to avoid the mandates or fines. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The potential financial impact of this second group should be particularly frightening to NH taxpayers, because most of them, being presently eligible, will come on Medicaid with only the traditional federal 50% contribution.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The average Medicaid recipient costs NH taxpayers approximately $7500 annually, so you can see how quickly this additional effect of Obamacare potentially doubling Medicaid rolls will result in hundreds of millions of dollars in new Medicaid obligations that have to be funded by the state budget. It will make the $900 million Democrat budget deficit that we had to close in the budget we enacted in 2011 look like child’s play. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Republican governors such as Daugaard, Rick Perry of Texas, Bobby Jindal of Louisiana and Mary Fallin of Oklahoma have cited the cost of the Medicaid expansion as a primary reason to opt out. New Hampshire should too. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 HB 271 is fairly short, so I have posted it below: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Be it Enacted by the Senate and House of Representatives in General Court convened: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 1 New Paragraph; Commissioner’s Duties; Prohibition on Expanded Medicaid. Amend RSA 126- A:5 by inserting after paragraph XXI the following new paragraph: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 XXII. The commissioner shall not accept any federal moneys or in any way expand Medicaid pursuant to the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act of 2009, Public Law 111-148, as amended by the Health Care and Education Reconciliation Act of 2010, Public Law 111-152. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 2 Effective Date. This act shall take effect 60 days after its passage. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please come to the hearing next Tuesday (February 5) at 10:00 am in the State House. Help us out. Let’s make sure they don’t steamroll NH into this financial disaster without at least a protest from fiscally responsible conservatives. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 -Bill&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Facebook the event is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/408431109245339/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/408431109245339/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Room TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd Puterbaugh</member_name><member_id>4083337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360088123000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359863121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH House Committee Hearing on Obamacare Expanding Medicaid Coverage</name><id>102744262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360076400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/102744262/</event_url></item>