<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 William Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.399132</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Unity Somerville</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1497020</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>AOIFE CLANCY Aoife Clancy brings a refreshing new voice to folk music, one that ranges from traditional Irish songs to ballads and contemporary folk. Aoife comes from the small town of Carrick-on-Suir, in Co Tipperary, Ireland, where her musical career began at an early age. Her father Bobby Clancy of the legendary Clancy Brothers, placed a guitar in her hands at age ten, and by age fourteen was playing with her father in nearby pubs. She later moved to Dublin, where she studied drama at the Gaiety School of Acting. After a season at the Gaiety, Aoife was invited to do a tour of Australia. There she performed at festivals and concerts sharing the stage with some of Ireland&amp;#146;s greatest performers, including Christy Moore and the Furey Brothers. Her performances also include a Caribbean cruises with the Clancy Brothers, the Milwaukee Irish Festival and a seven week tour of the United States with the renowned Paddy Noonan Show. In 1995 Aoife was asked to join the acclaimed group &amp;#147;Cherish the Ladies&amp;#148;, which is one of the most sought-after Irish American groups in history. For the past four years Aoife has toured extensively doing no less than two hundred dates a year throughout the United States and Europe. She has been a featured soloist with orchestras such as the Boston Pops and Cincinnati Pops and, while performing with Cherish the Ladies, collaborated with the Boston Pops on their Grammy nominated Celtic album. Now with seven recordings under her belt in the last decade, Aoife has clearly established herself as one of the Divas of Irish and contemporary Folk Music. She has recorded two solo projects &amp;#147;Its about Time&amp;#148; and &amp;#147;Soldiers and Dreams&amp;#148; on Rego Records. On her debut CD &amp;#147;It&amp;#146;s About Time,&amp;#148; Aoife presents some traditional favorites, such as &amp;#147;Factory Girl&amp;#148; and &amp;#147;Mrs. McGrath,&amp;#148; but she also presents a sassy rendition of Leon Russelson&amp;#146;s &amp;#147;Don&amp;#146;t Get Married Girls.&amp;#148; As one reviewer remarked, &amp;#147;she has a breadth of styles that make her concerts fascinating. Her singing would melt packed ice with it&amp;#146;s warmth and richness&amp;#148;&amp;#151;Mike Jackson, Canberra Times. On Aoife&amp;#146;s second Rego solo album, &amp;#147;Soldiers and Dreams,&amp;#148; Al Riess, from Dirty Linen magazine, wrote: &amp;#147;Soldiers and Dreams has a contemporary-meets-traditional-music feel and Clancy&amp;#146;s smooth, expressive singing works both ways&amp;#151;ensuring a successful merger of the two approaches and an enjoyable listening pleasure&amp;#148;. Currently, Aoife is touring with her own band in support of her two Rego solo releases and her latest Appleseed release &amp;#147;Silvery Moon&amp;#148;. When she comes to a town near you, be sure not to miss this totally enchanting performer. More information: &lt;a href="http://www.aoifeclancy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aoifeclanc...&lt;/a&gt; KYLE CAREY Kyle's songs take us from the hills of Appalachia, to the shores of Cape Breton, to the Highlands of Scotland. Her musical journey began while working as a waitress at Caffe Lena, America's most prestigious folk venue, where she was able to listen, every weekend to the best in folk, and culminated this past year in western Ireland, where she recorded her debut album. Kyle's earliest musical memories come from the Alaskan Bush, where she was immersed in the Yupik language and its songs. By college, she had already began molding her songwriting and performing skills, traveling afterwards to Cape Breton on a Fulbright Fellowship to study traditional Gaelic and Cape Breton fiddle styles. She struck up a friendship with fiddler Jerry Holland, and wrote songs such as The Star Above Rankin&amp;#146;s Point, based on a short story by Cape Breton author Alistair MacLeod. The language and culture fostered by the music of both Cape Breton and the Appalachians led Kyle to the Isle of Skye in Scotland, where she deepened her study of Gaelic song and achieved fluency in the language. Under the tutelage of songstress Christine Primrose - a native of the Isle of Lewis, and one of Scotland&amp;#146;s respected traditional singers - she learned the secrets of pronunciation, tone, and delivery displayed in the traditional Scottish waulking song, Gaol ise Gaol I. Skillfully produced by the legendary Irish guitarist Donogh Hennessy (L&amp;amp;ugrave;nasa) in his West Kerry studio, Kyle&amp;#146;s debut album Monongah features Athelone-based guitarist Neil Fitzgibbon, Pauline Scanlon (Lumiere) and Aoife Clancy (Cherish the Ladies) on harmony vocals, Cape Breton fiddler Rosie MacKenzie (The Cottars), Brendan O' Sullivan (Gr&amp;amp;agrave;da), old-time fiddler Cleek Schrey, Appalachian expert John Kirk (Quickstep) on mandolin and banjo, and Trevor Hutchinson (The Waterboys) on double bass. Kyle's website: &lt;a href="http://www.kyleannecarey.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kyleanneca...&lt;/a&gt; Accompanying Aoife and Kyle will be Rosie MacKenzie (fiddle) - At age 20, Rosie MacKenzie is already a veteran performer and recording artist, recognized as one of the finest young Cape Breton fiddlers on the traditional music scene. She exploded onto that scene as the youngest member of The Cottars in 2001, and has been winning over audiences with her electrifying musicianship, engaging stage presence, and stepdance prowess ever since. Rosie is the latest in a proud lineage of Cape Breton fiddlers including greats such as Buddy MacMaster, Jerry Holland, Natalie MacMaster, and Ashley MacIsaac. When Rosie carries that proud musical legacy onto the stage, she does so with an unmistakable flare and passion, which immediately draws the audience in, and captivates them throughout her performance. And Rosie is downright kinetic when she takes the stage &amp;#65533; she is in constant motion from start to finish, standing, sitting, stomping her feet, interacting with fellow musicians and the audience, even stepdancing while she plays. More information about the series and dinner discount at nearby restaurants: &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sites.google....&lt;/a&gt; To reserve: notlobreservations at gmail dot com Suggested donation $20, $15 adv., $5 student rush&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316826879000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314087961000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Aoife Clancy, Kyle Carey and friends</name><id>30541331</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316822400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/30541331/</event_url></item>