<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>249 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga In The Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>941611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121885</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sat, Nov 14, 1-5pm, $45/person prepaid by Thurs, Nov 12, $55 thereafter  (Special price!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you crave more erotic fire and deep intimacy in your relationships? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Are you curios about integrating spirituality and sexuality? &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you feel like more is possible, but aren’t sure how to get there? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this introductory tantric workshop, you will learn the fundamentals of: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Creating Sacred Space &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Cultivating the Presence, Key Attitude and Intention for an Ecstatic Energy Exchange&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Principles of Sacred Sensual Touch&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; The Art of Surrender/'Presencing yourself to Pleasure'&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Chakra Breathing to Ignite and Circulate Sexual Energy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a clothes-on, non-explicit class in which we will create a safe space to learn tantric principles and practices incorporating caring, non-sexual touch. You will learn to deepen your experience of pleasure, whether giving or receiving touch. You can then take your new-found skills home to skyrocket your lovemaking to unimaginable heights of ecstasy! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is open to people of all genders, sexual orientation and relationship styles, whether single or partnered. You may attend alone or with a partner or a friend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please wear loose, comfortable clothing. We will be sitting on the floor. Bring a backjack or pillow if you like. Blankets and mats are provided. Bring a water bottle and snack, as there will not be time to go out for food on our break. Stock up on quarters! Metered parking on street and a few small lots. We will refill meters on our break. Plan extra time to find parking (up to half hr)!*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Bodyworker, Tantric Educator and Intimacy Coach with over twenty years experience in the fields of Somatics, Spirituality and Consciousness Relating. Brynn assists women and men in increasing their capacity for Intimacy and Pleasure, and in accessing their full Aliveness and Passion! Her training in Taoist and Hindu Tantric Practices, Body-Oriented Psychotherapy, Authentic Movement and Expressive Arts Therapy provides a uniquely integrative approach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info, contact Brynn Bishop at core.empowerment@gmail.com or 415-244-1652.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Private Coaching also available. Free initial consultation!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Through the door to the  left of the Burren Pub, Upstairs at the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258566150000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255291591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantric Secrets of Sensual Touch and Emotional Intimacy</name><id>11602518</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258221600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/11602518/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/a/0/global_9965280.jpeg</photo_url></item>