<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt; WEDNESDAY UPDATE: Yes, it's raining -- but the venue is open and the workshop is on. PLEASE CALL ME IF YOU CAN'T MAKE IT (cell phone sent in previous messages). See you tonight!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BY POPULAR DEMAND...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the first ATC 101 workshop for those who are newcomers to ATCs and to our group. This is an experiment, so we'll see how it works. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unlike our Meetups, which are generally free-form get-togethers, this will be a short intensive instruction session. The locations under consideration are all small classrooms, so each session will be limited to a handful of participants. (But don't worry; as long as there's interest, I'll keep scheduling occasional sessions like this one.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm still working out the exact venue, but it will be in Wellesley. Cost is to be determined, but should be  $15-$20 per person, which will cover any space-rental charges, shared supplies and a take-home starter kit of blank cards, envelopes, collage sheets, embellishments, a resource list, a storage box and possibly some additional supplies (I'm looking into a bulk purchase of high-quality glue sticks and craft scissors). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details, including the ultimate location, will be sent to those who RSVP &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot; Oh, and wherever we end up, it will have free parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interested? RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; (you can always change it later).  Questions? Let me know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anne&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send location details to those who RSVP. It's right in Wellesley Center, easy to find with ample parking.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202511897000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>This crash course will give you everything you need to get started with ATCs. You'll learn about basic ATC guidelines, tools, techniques and resources, and you'll take home an ATC starter kit to jump-start your own creative efforts.</why><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201795489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ATC 101 Workshop for Newbies </name><id>7233996</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202338800000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/7233996/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/f/d/global_2986349.jpeg</photo_url></item>