<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A shortish hike with a BBQ at the end! We will hike around the trails in Northwest Park in Windsor for about 2 to 2.5 hrs. and then have a fundraising steak BBQ at the Warming Shed to enjoy with the Hartford Heights Tall Club. The fundraiser is for the Hartford Heights Tall Club Scholarship Fund and will assist in funding a competitive annual scholarship for a tall senior graduating and going to college from an area CT high school. The donation/fee of $25 covers the cost of your steak with the rest going to the scholarship fund. There will be some outdoor games set up and friends to make! Bring more friends and family to support a worthy cause!!       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The $25 donation/fee must be paid by May 25th to get in on this hike and BBQ. No hikers allowed on this hike without participating in the special BBQ and making the donation. No refunds as the steaks will be bought so please remember to join us. :-) For the event, you don't have to hike and can just join in on the games and BBQ at Noon if you like but please mention that option in your RSVP.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Warming Shed at the park to start the hike. BBQ starts at Noon, Grills fired up at 2 PM. Bring your own drink (no alcohol). Basic water and maybe lemonade will be available. Bring a food to share if you like but this is not required. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BBQ runs rain or shine. Hike will likely run too rain or shine but hiking portion may be canceled if heavy rain or thunderstorms threaten.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payments are online via Amazon Payments. If you can't pay via online, talk to me and maybe we can arrange an alternative but the May 25th deadline is firm for payments in full. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A link to the location of the park will be posted (by 5/20/10) in case you have trouble locating the park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you for your support!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275172050000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274227007000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and fundraiser BBQ at Northwest Park in Windsor CT</name><id>13525356</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275138000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13525356/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>