<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>148 Grove Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.277518</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508.753.9543</phone><name>Ralph's Rock Diner</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1021842</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802646</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;THE CHICKEN SLACKS ARE BACK IN CENTRAL MASS!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's roll out the new year with an early Mardi Gras night and the Chicken Slacks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, it's time for everyone to discover the &lt;b&gt;Beyond&lt;/b&gt; part of the Beantown and Beyond group!  Hey if this Boston centric band sees fit to head out to Worcester, then maybe you should head out too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is a cross-group meetup&lt;/b&gt; and sure to be another great night.  If you didn't make it before, you'll definitely want to mark your calendar and check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lets loosen things up&lt;/b&gt; and head out to &lt;a href="http://ralphsrockdiner.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ralph's&lt;/a&gt; in Worcester to listen and dance to the music of the Chicken Slacks, a great soul, funk, and R&amp;amp;B band.   Dubbed “Boston’s hardest-working funk and soul band,”  they typically play in Cambridge/Somerville area but now they are in Worcester!  One thing's for sure, wherever they play, it's &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; a great show!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't seen them before, you should know that the Chicken Slacks will get you moving, not only with their rousing covers of songs we all know, but also with great songs you never knew as well as their own original material.  Soul, funk and R&amp;amp;B not your thing?  I used to think so... now they are one of my favorite local bands!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Band, The Music&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more on the band, check out the &lt;a href="http://www.chickenslacks.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Chicken Slacks web site&lt;/a&gt; and read the &lt;a href="http://www.weeklydig.com/%5Bcatpath%5D/200906/funky-stuff" target="_blank"&gt;Weekly Dig's take&lt;/a&gt; on the band.  Also check out &lt;a href="http://www.thenoise-boston.com/content/view/217/17/" target="_blank"&gt;this review of their latest cd&lt;/a&gt;.  If that doesn't do it for you then check out their &lt;a href="http://chickenslacks.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; and you'll feel the energy.  Seriously, these links don't do them justice.  They have a great stage presence, heavy on the dance tunes, light on the mellow stuff and really get things going!  So come check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meetup Details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Yes RSVP's will get my cell number the night before and again by 5 pm the day of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will keep an eye out for people but please look for me.  My picture is accurate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There WILL be a cover charge of $10. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Details may change as the date gets closer so keep an eye on this page!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Yes RSVP's will get my cell number the night before.  I will keep and eye out but look for me too!  See my photo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>3305855</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265757732000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263400517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Funky Friday With The Chicken Slacks</name><id>12308584</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265421600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/12308584/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/1/global_8137809.jpeg</photo_url></item>