<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Salisbury Beach </address_2><address_1>4 Ocean Front North </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.843468</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 462 5888</phone><name>Tupelo Music hall </name><city>Salisbury </city><id>1046594</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.816143</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Lets go check out 3 great comedian's right on Salisbury Beach, we did this a few months ago and it was a great night let’s go and check out 3 different comedians this time!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;UPDATE 1/1/10: We have checked the Tupelo website and the comedy show is still scheduled.  We suggest checking the Tupelo site to see “weather” it is.  See below for the ticket information from their website:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What if I cannot attend a show that I have purchased tickets for?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We fully recognize that sometimes life throws us a curveball and are aware of the fact that it stinks to buy tickets that you find yourself stuck with. Having said that, all sales are final. There are no refunds or exchanges for purchased tickets unless the show has been rescheduled or cancelled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you cannot attend a show but would like someone else to use your tickets, they will need your physical tickets to do so. Picking up tickets at the box office requires the photo ID and credit card of the purchaser&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do you cancel shows due to inclement weather?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Our inclement weather policy is simple. If the traveling artist can get to Tupelo Music Hall Salisbury for the show, we hearty New Englanders can too. In these cases, the show will go on. Only if an artist cannot get to the venue will we ever cancel a show. We do not issue refunds for those who choose to stay home when the weather isn’t so good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JOE WONG:&lt;/b&gt; As an “all American immigrant,” Joe Wong came a long way from a rosy-eyed new immigrant to a blossoming comedian. His jokes range from ethnic, personal, political, observational to bizarre. It’s not always easy to categorize his humor, but it is always inspired. JoeWongComedy.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;STEVE MACONE:&lt;/b&gt; Steve Macone is like a cross between the life of the party and the most nervous person in the room. He has entertained audiences across the US, Canada, Ireland and England with his brand of observational humor and absurdist one-liners, a high-energy style that blends extreme confidence with a social awkwardness that sometimes makes the inside of your chest hurt. SteveMacone.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PAUL D'ANGELO:&lt;/b&gt; Who is the comedian/writer/actor that the Los Angeles Times calls “… quite likely the funniest entertainer you’ve never heard of… yet”? Comedian Paul D’Angelo has been headlining A-List comedy clubs around the country for 20 years, entertaining hundreds of prominent corporate clients, and opening for over 50 international stars such as Aretha Franklin, Ray Charles, The Beach Boys, Tony Bennett, George Carlin, Joan Rivers and Dennis Miller. PDangelo.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;TICKET INFORMATION:&lt;/span&gt; When you buy your ticket and update this site please put what table you are sitting at so if some one else gets a ticket at your same table then you will see a familiar face at that table, or bring a friend w/you so you already know someone at the table. Or if you don’t want to sit at a table with out members from the group, please change you’re RSVP here on the site, so then someone else can take the opportunity to go to this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;SEATING:&lt;/span&gt; Here’s the information to buy your ticket/reserve your seat for this event, we will be posting this on 3 meetup sites so there may be room for all of us at the tables  I have picked tables 59 &amp;amp; 60 for us to sit at, I originally had 3 different tables here, but as I check back I see that they are already booked up so I have picked different tables, (when you buy your ticket if these 2 tables are full then pick another table that is around us) all the tables fit 6 people, these tables are NOT reserved for Meetup until we have ordered/filled the tables, anyone (outside of the group) can make reservations at any of these tables. If you wait to long to order your ticket these table(s) may be filled, and you may not be sitting w/the rest of us from the meetup group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ordering is easy and only takes a few minutes, so order your seat soon so we are sure to sit together!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note to order your ticket on the site there is a $3.00 Service fee (for each ticket purchased) and a print and a mailing ticket cost to use this service. For The Will Call Tickets choice - The box-office will generally be open 2 hours before every performance. For Will Call tickets, you will need to pick up your physical tickets before the show. “Will Call” is a term that means you will pick-up your tickets at the box office the night of the show. “Will Call” does not mean that they will call you. Will Call tickets will not be sent to you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticketing fee: &lt;br /&gt;Every ticket sold has a fee associated with it. The fee is over-and-above the posted ticket price. All fees are clearly outlined in our ticketing system. Fees are charged for each ticket, regardless of how the ticket was purchased.&lt;br /&gt;To reserve your seat go to &lt;a href="http://www.tupelohallsalisbury.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tupelohall...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Click on schedule, &lt;br /&gt;Scroll down to Tupelo Night of Comedy, &lt;br /&gt;Click Buy Now, &lt;br /&gt;Click on either one of those tables and you will see a grid of 6 yellow framed empty squares (as seats are being reserved at that table you will see that the squares get highlighted &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;red&lt;/span&gt; which means that seat is sold). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To reserve your seat click on one of those squares that is not highlighted red. &lt;br /&gt;Then all you have to do is put in your credit card billing information and you are all set.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to change your RSVP on the site to “reserved seat” so we know to look for you on the night of the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are only: $15.00 all seats (please note you are responsible for ordering and getting your own ticket).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup location: At the above tables,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Time: 7:30, show starts at 8:00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To Purchase tickets: 978-462-5888 or check out their website &lt;a href="http://www.tupelohall.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tupelohall...&lt;/a&gt;. to see the other options for getting your tickets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Tupelo Music Hall Salisbury is literally on the beach in Salisbury, MA &lt;br /&gt;From 95 or 495, take the Salisbury exit, route 110. Follow 110 East through town. You will come to a set of lights near Simmies garage, take a left. At the second set of lights, take a right onto Beach Rd. Follow Beach Rd until you reach the beach center. At that stop sign, take a left onto North End Blvd and then a right onto Driftway. We are in “The Pavilion” building that is on the beach. &lt;b&gt;Parking is free.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note bad weather may cancel this event and as always please check back for updates!&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to see you there!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the table(s)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262651626000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261104451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go back to Tupelo!!!</name><id>12107690</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262478600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12107690/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/3/global_12287859.jpeg</photo_url></item>