<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On a clear day, the bare rocky summit of Mt. Firescrew, and Mt. Cardigan afford panoramic views stretching from rural New Hampshire in the foreground to the summits of the White Mountains in the distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the AMC Cardigan Lodge for the latest trail information before heading out on trails Manning, Mowglis, Clark, Holt-Clark Cutoff, and Holt in a loop back to the Cardigan Lodge. The round trip distance is about 5.5 miles and can be completed in less than 5 hours. We can talk about extending our hike another couple hours (round trip 2.4 miles from the lodge) to visit the beautiful Welton Falls once we are back at the lodge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Winter hiking is more strenuous in general. Please be prepared for full winter conditions along the entire route and then on the exposed summit. There will be snow, ice, cold temperatures, and whipping winds. This is not a beginner's hike! &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a list of minimum clothing and equipment required to participate in this event. You will not be allowed to participate if you show up without them:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt; &lt;u&gt;Footwear:&lt;/u&gt; Waterproof/insulated winter hiking boots. Snow shoes and Traction (full crampons on preferred but MICROspikes are acceptable). Waterproof gaiters.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt; &lt;u&gt;Clothing:&lt;/u&gt; Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON. Bring extra clothes to keep you warm during breaks and lunch.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;li&gt; &lt;u&gt;Outerwear:&lt;/u&gt; Waterproof/windproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants made of either coated nylon or breathable fabric (e.g. Gore-Tex or similar). Fleece hat, fleece balaclava or face shield, waterproof gloves, and waterproof over-mittens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*** Foul weather and unsafe travel conditions cancel this hike. Mountains are not going anywhere! ***&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Babul</member_name><member_id>8035781</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265722733000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265246544000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Firescrew, Mt. Cardigan, and (may be) Welton Falls... (2nd try)</name><id>12513044</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265549400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12513044/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/6/global_12936534.jpeg</photo_url></item>