<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Swazey Parkway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.985245</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Swazey Park</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1304482</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.951249</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Unlike the rest of the country, Exeter celebrates our nation's independence on the third Saturday of July. The reason is simply &lt;span&gt;that it&lt;/span&gt; took a couple weeks for word of independence to reach us here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the night of July 4, 1776, Philadelphia printer John Dunlap slaved over his printing press, turning Thomas Jefferson’s handwritten pages into 200 posters that were then sent off to the King of England and the colonies via horseback and coach. New Hampshire’s copy arrived in Exeter, the Revolutionary-era capitol, on July 16, 1776. Twenty-two year old John Taylor Gilman put his life on the line as he read the Declaration of Independence to the townspeople of Exeter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/e/f/event_16537359.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The revolutionary war festival is not to be missed. For one week prior to festival night, people come from all over the world and dress and live as we did two centuries ago - everything made by hand and without modern conveniences such as electricity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[u][b]Schedule[/b][/u] The festival runs 10AM-5PM. Live music starts at 6:45 at the Swazey Parkway Bandstand, and the fireworks begin at 8:45PM. Some items you may want to photograph: The cannon on Swazey Parkway is fired every hour on the hour between 11AM and 4PM except at 2PM. Bring ear protection - it's beyond loud, but if you can time the photograph so you see the blast from the cannon, you'll have a print you'll cherish for many years. From 1-2P watch practice military maneuvers and practice musket firing on Swazey Parkway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/8/event_16504920.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;At 2PM you'll enjoy the Battle Portrayal, where Redcoats and Minutemen will re-enact the battle with smokey muskets. You'll need to stay behind the barricades on the opposite side of the street (across from the river). Keep as far right in the crowd as you can, so as to keep modern buildings out of your field of view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've ever wanted to shoot bands, then head to the river bandstand at 6:45PM and practice shooting Amorphous as they play for the crowds. Bands here are usually happy to accommodate with a smile as you shoot away, and you'll have the river as a backdrop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/4/7/event_16504935.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Finally, shoot the fireworks starting at around 8:45PM. Come a bit early to set up on the lawn, and be sure to bring a tripod, a small flashlight, and bug spray.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[b][u]The Plan[/u][/b] You're on your own for most of the day, so come and go as you please, but you'll see a lot of fellow photographers at the battle re-enactment at 2PM (and you should, too). The re-enactment occurs on the same side as the canon, but we photographers will be restricted to across the road. It's a good idea to get there early, at least 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/4/4/event_16504932.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In between the canon and battle, roam around the tents to try to get shots of the 18th century re-enactors, visit the Independence Museum (there's a cost, but it's worth it) to see how work was done back in the day, and (for extra credit) get a shot of a redcoat sipping a latte.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone interested in shooting the band will have plenty of time. They're a captive subject and the setting is good, so think about shooting the band from 7-8PM. It's also a good time to claim a spot on the lawn for the fireworks. Many people will come early, so bring a blanket and chairs, a cooler with something to drink or snack on, and - very important - bug spray so your evening isn't completely ruined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/2/1/event_16510017.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Anyone interested in a fireworks photography tutorial (it will be quick and easy, I promise) should show up on the lawn across from the bandstand during this time. To shoot the fireworks, you'll want to bring: [list] [*]SLR Camera (duh) [*]Fresh batteries and backups [*]Sturdy tripod [*]A flashlight (so you can see to change your settings) [*]A remote trigger release (if you have one, not a big deal if you don't) [/list]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

As for lenses, it will depend on whether you want to shoot just fireworks, or include the background as well. For including the background (river, trees, etc.) you will want to shoot with a short lens, around 20mm or less (30mm in full-frame equivalent). For closeups, you'll want 30-60mm (or a 45-90mm full-frame equivalent). We'll cover aperture and shutter speed on the lawn while the band plays, and while it's still somewhat light out. Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the concrete outcropping just north of the band pavilion on Swazey Parkway by 8:45.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343042941000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342727942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revolutionary War Festival with "Bombs Bursting in Air" (Fireworks)</name><id>74063792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342917000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/74063792/</event_url></item>