<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>HEY GANG! PLEASE SPREAD THE WORD ABOUT THIS TO ALL YOUR DOG LOVING PALS!  IF YOU BELONG TO OTHER MEET UPS- AND COULD LET THEM KNOW WE STAND A BETTER CHANCE OF A BIG TURNOUT. THANKS A BUNCH!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;The economy has gone to the dogs and animals are suffering too. With the economic downturn, there are many more animals surrendered to rescue groups by owners who can’t afford to care for them any longer. At the same time, the shelters are receiving far less in donations, making for a critical situation. So what’s a dog lover to do?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Boston Dog Photography has the answer with the “Pimp My Pug” photo shoot, with proceeds benefiting Pug Rescue of New England and Lowell Humane Society.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When: Sunday November 7th&lt;br /&gt;Time: 11:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where: Boston University's Center for Digital Imaging Arts&lt;br /&gt;274 Moody St., Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $25 per session (for up to 2 dogs) AND a bag of dog or cat food&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER HERE AND BUY YOUR TICKET: &lt;a href="http://pimpmypug.eventsbot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://pimpmypug.eventsbot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://pimpmypug.even...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;questions: info@bostondogphotography.com&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The professional photographers of Boston Dog Photography are volunteering their time to photograph your dogs and donate the sitting fees to the Pug Rescue. The bag of dog (or cat) food you bring will be donated to Lowell Humane Society where they are currently caring for 150 animals.  Don't have a pug? No problem!  Any dog is welcomed!&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring accessories for Fido or Fluffy to wear (full costumes are not recommended but you can be creative with boas, hats, bandanas, collars etc.).&lt;br /&gt;Participants sign a photo release allowing the photographers to use the images for their portfolios, web sites or advertising.&lt;br /&gt;The photos will be posted to an online gallery for easy viewing/purchase within 4 days of the event.&lt;br /&gt;A separate online photo gallery will be set up so folks can vote for their favorite dog. Votes for “Top Dog” will cost $1 each and the funds will be donated to the Pug Rescue. The 12 dogs with the most votes will be featured in a 2011 calendar.&lt;br /&gt;So put on the dog and come on out for a fun time and photos—all for a great cause!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be photographing the doggies!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cheryl Colombo</member_name><member_id>756456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289845764000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Chelmsford-Lowell-Pug-small-dog-meet-up</urlname><id>1553224</id><group_lat>42.6300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3300018311</group_lon><name>Chelmsford/Lowell Pug &amp; Small Dog Meet-Up</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286216560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pimp My Pug  Photo Shoot for Pug Rescue of New England and Lowell Humane Society</name><id>14996925</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289147400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Chelmsford-Lowell-Pug-small-dog-meet-up/events/14996925/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/7/d/global_11802893.jpeg</photo_url></item>