<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Just north of Dunkin Donuts on same side (south of ski area) Rt 138/ Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02021</zip><lat>42.141953</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rt 138 Park and Ride (3173 Washington St, Canton MA)</name><city>Canton</city><id>7535312</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.149345</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can’t get to the Whites this weekend? Join us for a moderately fast-paced 5 mile training hike in the Great Blue Hills in Canton, MA. Want a better workout? Bring a pack filled with whatever weight source and amount you prefer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We are doing a loop of the Skyline Trail in the Great Blue Hills Reservation from 138 Park and Ride to the Police Barracks and back. Despite this being in the Blue Hills this is hike has a lot of steep but short ups and downs and we will not stop for more than a few minutes. You will need to be in decent physical shape in order to keep up with us. We will be hiking about 5 miles and climb about 1,500 feet - this is the equivalent of a short hike in the White Mountains. It should take us about 2.5 hrs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Great Blue Hill is the highest point in the 7,000 acre Blue Hills Reservation and the highest coastal elevation along the Atlantic seaboard south of Maine. This large dome of granite measures 635 feet at the summit. Hikers will be rewarded with a spectacular view of the surrounding countryside. To the east, you see the Harbor Islands dotting the coastline. To the north, skyscrapers tower among the Boston skyline. To the west, Mount Wachusett can be seen 44 miles away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We will leave from the Park and Ride as it steeply ascends the Great Blue Hill following the Skyline Trail as it passes over numerous hills on the way to the Police Barracks and then return following the South Skyline back up Great Blue then down to the parking lot. Click here for a link to a map of the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are out of shape and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Organizer: Pam Wilmot (six one seven) nine six two 0034 (cell)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate but stiff pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; round trip we will hike about &lt;strong&gt;5 miles and climb about 1,500 feet&lt;/strong&gt; it should take us about 2.5 hrs. These are estimates since no matter where you look you get different information. &lt;br /&gt;

 I did my research using a trail map and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 • &lt;strong&gt;Click &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue%20hills%20brochure.pdf"&gt;here for a link to a map of the area&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;Click &lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=42.1584324&amp;amp;lon=-71.14477320000003&amp;amp;site=all&amp;amp;smap=1&amp;amp;searchresult=Canton%2C%20MA%2C%20USA"&gt;here for the current weather forecast (noaa.gov)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 • &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click for a list of items needed for a day hike (Appalachian Mountain Club)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone! &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be meeting in the park and ride lot on Rt 138 (3173 Washington St, Canton MA) just north of Dunkin Donuts on the same side of the street as DDs and just South of the Ski area and Trailside Museum (on the opposite side).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;q=3173+Washington+Street,+Canton,+MA&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=0x89e37e1f760042fb:0x987829cf21040514,3173+Washington+St,+Canton,+MA+02021&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;ei=jSd3UIHNI-Lr0gGJ74GgDQ&amp;amp;ved=0CCEQ8gEwAA"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click here for approximate location in Google Maps (its actually a little south of the marker):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>(This is the opposite side from the Ski area) Should be obvious.  I'll be driving a silver Nissan Quest minivan</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam</member_name><member_id>6419698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350141449000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349984944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Blue Hill Skyline Loop</name><id>86571802</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350129600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/86571802/</event_url></item>