<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

April 16, 2012. 5:45 pm to 9:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Crowne Plaza Hotel &lt;br /&gt;

100 Berlin Road. Cromwell, CT &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=431"&gt;Click Here to Learn More and Register&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This month's meeting is all about getting the deal and structuring the deal. Your profit is made when you buy. Once you find and control the deal, the money you can make with that deal is astronomical. This meeting gives you all of the tools you need to find the deal, analyze the deal, create your offer, and exit or hold and fund the deal for massive profits. Sue and her business partners own over 1500 commercial units. She is now one of the worlds' leading experts on Commercial Real Estate. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Will Learn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* How to make massive profits step by step buying REO's and Notes Directly from Banks. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* How to take advantage of the banking crisis, regardless of where you're located and from the comfort of your home and Regardless of your experience! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* Why NOW is the time to buy from the most motivated seller in the market, BANKS! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* How you can do this business with NO Experience whatsoever. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* Why bank owned notes and properties are so plentiful and marked down at such a HUGE discount. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* How to get past the gate keepers and have them open their inventory up to YOU. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* Powerful software that will structure and analyze any deal a bank or seller may have for maximum profits i.e. Apartments, Retail, Office Space, Self Storage, etc... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* How to fund your project whether you're purchasing a note or hard asset. We even share with you our hedge fund to fund your deals! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* How to maximize your profits from the strategy of your choice; Wholesaling, Flipping, Joint Ventures, Buy and Hold, etc... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

* Sue's powerful strategy that covers apartment investing as well as other commercial deals, and how you too can take advantage of the banking crisis, and buy commercial and residential property at bottom basement prices in your back yard or emerging market. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

5:45 - New Members Workshop - Discover how CTREIA benefits you! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

6:00 - Early Bird Workshop - Deal or No Deal. Have your property deal analyzed by CT REIA experts. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

6:30 - Speed Networking &amp;amp; Member Deals - organized so that you get to meet the people you need to meet! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

7:15 - Sue Nelson - Learn how to get and structure real estate deals in Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334617282000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333459433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA April Monthly Meeting: Getting And Structuring Real Estate Deals In CT</name><id>59049012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334612700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/59049012/</event_url></item>