<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This Is the COOKIE  Packaging Day!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is Infromation about the EVENT!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a special project for the bakers and wanna be bakers of The Hartford Cooking and Recipes Meet Up. We are forming a 'Cookies Committee' to provide the 'desert' table at a special non profit event: The People's Music Network, Winter Gathering 2011 to be hosted in Hartford on Friday, January 28th. In brief, for reasons to many to list, there will be limited food served at the concert, where 800 people are expected to attend. There will be a desert table, or as we have come to call it, a Cookie Counter. The plan is to organize, bake up a storm of treats and present and sell the treats at the concert. The Cookie Committee had its first team meeting on December 27 at 6:30 pm at the house of David Kaplan, a non baker with great aspirations. If you have interest in any part of this project: planning, organizing, shopping, baking, serving the goodies, please put your comments in  when you sign up  Hey, we may only need the one meeting unless it is so much fun that we do two. Note that the concert is sponsored by the non profit PMN. The show has listed 8 acts performing with the headliner being Pete Seeger. All donations made at our Cookie Counter, after expenses, will go to PMN as a donation. Those lucky enough to be working the Cookie Counter are of course right there for the concert. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be more meetings before this Event. !!!!!So stay tuned!!!!!!  We need at least 600 packages of cookies.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What Kinds  of cookies and who will make them and a wish list&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joyce           Chocolate Jumbles&lt;br /&gt;Caryl            Apple Coffee drops&lt;br /&gt;Susanne       My Mind Escapes me&lt;br /&gt;Margo Lynn  Gluten free Gingersnaps&lt;br /&gt;Sandy           oatmeal raisin&lt;br /&gt;Gayle            Peanut butter Chocolate chips&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer &lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;Nancy&lt;br /&gt;Cookies we would Like&lt;br /&gt;Snickerdoodles&lt;br /&gt;Rice Crispy treats&lt;br /&gt;Chocolate Chip&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Becky Brown. suggested can also host a cookie bake at my house with 6 or 7 other bakers - we could get many dozens done all at once. Let me know if this works for anyone.&amp;quot; Sandy  also have access to a  huge double oven at my church were we will be gathering to bring the cookies and Bag them &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need people to bring a couple bags of Apples so we can sell those to the healthy people. As You sign up Please Post what you will bring and How you can help so we can keep it organized.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Happy Baking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be the one that looks like me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296651118000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293643197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pete Seeger PMN Cookie Counter Packaging</name><id>15849368</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296171000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/15849368/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/3/global_20359475.jpeg</photo_url></item>