<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Folks My name is Anthony Pasquale from The Ideal Business Center. We hold informative seminars to help the community through these trying times! I hope you can join us in this cause. If you know someone who needs this help, please let them know, they can get help!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Homeowner Alert!!!!&lt;br /&gt;Free Seminar&lt;br /&gt;March 30th, 750pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The federal Government has called on lenders, services and banks to assist homeowners. With the bailout the government has afforded these lending institutions you no longer need to be late or in foreclosure to lower your payments and interest rates. Right Now is the best time to take advantage of this federal stimulus package. The following topics will be covered by Real Estate experts and an attorney. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Refinance or Loan Modification.&lt;br /&gt;How to stop foreclosure.&lt;br /&gt;Should I deal directly with my leader&lt;br /&gt;Predatory Lending&lt;br /&gt;Forensic Audits&lt;br /&gt;Short Sale&lt;br /&gt;Deed in lieu of foreclosure&lt;br /&gt;House is underwater &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss this vital information. Have all your questions answered by a real estate attorney.&lt;br /&gt;Know your rights! Seating will be limited. First come, First serve basis.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Ideal Business Center&lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street&lt;br /&gt;Danvers Mass 01923&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;One qualified homeowner will receive a complimentary Loan Modification service. Random drawing. some restrictions apply. Value &amp;quot;Your Home&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Pasquale &lt;br /&gt;AJP Enterprise Group&lt;br /&gt;United Martial Arts Center&lt;br /&gt;Osanna Seminars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Live with purpose and passion everyday&amp;quot; !&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;www.usamodifiedloans.com &lt;br /&gt;www.umachealth.com &lt;br /&gt;www.danversmartialarts.com&lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street, Suite 100 &lt;br /&gt;Danvers MA 01923 &lt;br /&gt;(978) 836-6501 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain &amp;quot;average&amp;quot;. These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will greet you at the door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240061626000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237503199000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Homeowners that need community Help!! Homeowners Alert! Free Seminar</name><id>9991680</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238456700000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/9991680/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/e/1/global_7343345.jpeg</photo_url></item>