<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Deja vu.... Next stop on our ethnic dining tour is El Sarape! Lets have dinner and a margarita or sangria to toast the approach of Fall.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in Weymouth Landing, the bustling business district at the Weymouth-Braintree line on Route 53, El Sarape has been serving food widely acclaimed as some of the best Mexican around since 1988. Posters online seem pretty uniform in their advice: Skip the stereotypical Tex-Mex fare like tacos and enchiladas and go for something more authentic, like Mole poblano or one of the dishes incorporating cilantro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is sponsored in part by Body Transformation by KJ.&amp;nbsp; We will be sharing and enjoying 2 free appetizers courtesy of our sponsor at this evening's event.&amp;nbsp; It will be a great way to sample some items on the menu.&amp;nbsp; Please check out our Sponsors and their offers on our Sponsorship Information page by clicking on the following link.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Sponsorship_Info/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Sponsorship_Info/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to the chance to share with our members a venue and a cuisine that are definitely out of the ordinary for SSDOMG's region. Please join us at this small but significant piece of the South Shore dining mosaic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;El Sarape - Take 2 (Dos)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, September 21st @ 6:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;El Sarape Restaurant
 &lt;br /&gt;5 Commercial Street
 &lt;br /&gt;Weymouth Landing
 &lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184
 &lt;br /&gt;(781) 843-8005&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.elsarape.com"&gt;www.elsarape.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Organizer:&lt;/strong&gt; Alison&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; [Current] Annual Members&amp;nbsp;FREE, Members - $2 each, Guests - $2 each; $6 to become a 2011 Annual Member&amp;nbsp;for the remainder of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/strong&gt; Minimum of 4 and&amp;nbsp;no max at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 8pm on Tuesday,&amp;nbsp;September 20th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Please bring cash.&lt;/strong&gt; You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;FROM ROUTE 3 NORTH (COMING FROM CAPE COD):&lt;/strong&gt;El Sarape is located on Commercial St. in Weymouth Landing. This section of Commercial St. is part of Route 53.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Exit 16 onto Rt 18 North. Go straight through the first light (Dairy Queen is on your right).
 &lt;br /&gt;Next light is the end of Rt 18. You will be facing one of the large chain drugstores: turn left onto Rt 53.
 &lt;br /&gt;Follow Rt 53 straight through one light (Broad St.), then straight through the next light (Sacred Heart Church on the near right corner, note do not turn right even though the sign says Commercial St).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;El Sarape is on your right in the row of buildings between this light and the next. Parking is mostly on either side of the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;FROM ROUTE 3 SOUTH (COMING FROM BOSTON):&lt;/strong&gt;El Sarape is located on Commercial St. in Weymouth Landing. This section of Commercial St. is part of Route 53.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Exit 17 (Union St.), which lets off onto a rotary. Get off the rotary onto Union St.(third exit you'll come to), passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.
 &lt;br /&gt;Go straight through two traffic lights. The third traffic light is at Weymouth Landing (7-Eleven convenience store on left), don't go straight through the light but bear right onto the intersecting road (Rt 53).
 &lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the light that comes up immediately - El Sarape is in the row of buildings on your left between this light and the next one (intersection of Front and Commercial St., Sacred Heart Church on far left corner). Parking is mostly on either side of the street.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a small place but I will be carrying the Pinata!!  Just joking! Meet us inside the entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316727587000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315112411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>El Sarape / Take 2</name><id>32186572</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316644200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/32186572/</event_url></item>