<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Vision Boards/ Vision Books &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The beginning of the year is a great time to refocus your energy and bring more clarity to your life! &lt;br /&gt;

Which things did you decide to work on for your New Year's resolutions? How are things going so far? &lt;br /&gt;

Are there things that you would like to ATTRACT into your life, but you are not sure how to? Do you want to find INSPIRATION for clarifying your goals and dreams??? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

...Come join us for another Vision Board/ Vision Book gathering! Vision Boards and Books take your desires and put them into a visual format. When you can LOOK at the things you desire, it is easier to feel their impact and imagine your life WITH your desires. This tool is also great as an "easy and accessible" reminder of your desires in between the fast-paced momentum of daily life; something that can take you out of "the daily-grind" and instantly put you in a better feeling place. :) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We will provide some supplies for this meetup, but you are encouraged to bring anything that you feel will be helpful to the group. ...You never know WHO might need the word or picture that YOU have in your magazines or newspapers ;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Bring what ever you would like to, but here is a list of things that may be beneficial for the sharing of abundance and empowerment between us: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Typical scrapbooking, collaging supplies; glue sticks/ adhesives, good scissors, stickers, markers &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Magazines and newspapers; think "Money" "Relationships" "Traveling" and all of the other keywords people want in their dream life. Bring whatever you want to recycle! You never know what someone is looking for! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Blank poster board or memory-books/ scrapbooks (For yourself OR if you would like to donate for others to use) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Anything else related....? Bring it if you would like, and we will see if someone can use it :) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you have started a vision board or book already, and you would like to keep working on it, please bring it with you! Start fresh or pick up where you left off... whatever you feel like you need to do. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This is usually a very laid back and supportive event! If you feel like you need some encouragement and vibration enhancement, come get recharged and work on your goals with like-minded people :) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The cost is usually $10.&amp;nbsp;On that night if you want to bring a food or beverage of equal value to share the fee will be waived. This is a great way to add a little more fun. The space is available until 9:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cohosted by Barb and Kerri.,&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.thehsccenter.com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330352072000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329181413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VISION BOARDS Welcome to everyone who is ready to create!</name><id>52245912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329953400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/52245912/</event_url></item>