<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi, Jazz musicians and fans, your founder, Ed (me), is playing in a friend's senior recital at Berklee, if you'd like to check it out. It will be an organ trio (drums, B3, and guitar) set of about 5 tunes, followed by a guitar/vocals and drums rock duet, by the drummer's duo band (which doesn't include me).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concert is at the Lawrence and Alma Berk Recital Hall at 1140 Boylston St. room 1A. It is free and open to the public, and I would love to have you guys come. I have heard the drummer's rock duo, by the way, and they are great, so you may want to stay and see that too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chances are, there will be other recitals going on around the same time close by, perhaps right after or before ours, so you may be interested in checking them out. There are flyers saying what's going on in the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you all seem interested in this type of thing, I have a couple more recitals coming up in early May, which I can let you know about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, if anyone is interested in hosting and organizing jams, please let me know and I can make you and event organizer! With better weather on the horizon, let's try to have some jams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ed&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ed</member_name><member_id>7538494</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269886564000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans/Musicians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>jazz-190</urlname><id>1202977</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge/Somerville/Boston Jazz Meetup/Jam</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268631971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Senior Recital at Berklee - Organ Trio</name><id>12879097</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269712800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/jazz-190/events/12879097/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/5/global_13350981.jpeg</photo_url></item>