<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Slab Bridge Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02702</zip><lat>41.779331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-644-5522</phone><name>Freetown State Forest</name><city>Freetown</city><id>713635</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.041939</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We recently saw the following hike listed in Backpacker Magazine as the spookiest place to hike and thought that it would be an interesting and easy post holiday hike.  According to the article dayhikers have spotted UFOs and ghosts.  (Backpacker Magazine, November 2008).  Sounds interesting and should be fun.  We always try to do any hike that we can that is listed in Backpacker Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is the Massachusetts's Freedom-Fall State Forest.  We will meet at the pavillion 12 miles north of New Bedford on located off of Payne Road (which is off of Slab Bridge Road referenced in the address block.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is a 10 mile out and back, starting at the pavillion.  We will head south on Bent Rim Trail for one mile and turn left onto Makepeace Road, which snakes around the Hochomock (named by the Native Americans and means &amp;quot;place where the spirits dwell&amp;quot;.  We will then take Grinnell Path to Whitetail Loop and The Ledge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional information can be found at &amp;quot;mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/free.htm&amp;quot;.  Please note: I don't know if a fee must be paid there or not.  I'm also not sure how long it will take us to hike it.  I'm estimating 4 to 5 hours.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A BLACK FOUR DOOR TOYOTA ECHO WITH MAINE LICENSE PLATES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230593060000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228146878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MASSACHUSETTS'S FREETOWN-FALL RIVER STATE FOREST</name><id>9256965</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230386400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9256965/</event_url></item>