<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Bedford Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.989769</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-622-7531</phone><name>Millyard Museum</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1036347</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467545</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our reading for August &amp;amp; September:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Dancing With Life - Buddhist Insights for Finding Meaning and Joy in the Face of Suffering" by Phillip Moffitt, with a preface by Venerable Ajahn Sumedho, c. 2008, paperback edition published by Rodale 2012 with a new chapter: &lt;em&gt;The Suffering of Ambivalence and Ambiguity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please read up to Chapter 13.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This book focuses on the Buddha's teachings on the Four Noble Truths and on mindfulness practice. Author Phillip Moffitt writes about the twelve insights contained within the Four Noble Truths. Moffitt was inspired by the teachings of the Venerable Ajahn Sumedho, the founding Abbot of Amarvati Buddhist Monastery in Hertfordshire, England. Venerable Sumedho had been a student of Ajahn Cha, the great Thai Buddhist teacher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"The Four Noble Truths are at the heart of every Buddhist tradition. Phillip Moffitt's wonderful book, 'Dancing with Life,' plumbs their timeless wisdom with a refreshing depth of insight,"&lt;/em&gt; Joseph Goldstein, author of "A Heart Full of Peace"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At age 40 American Phillip Moffitt was editor, chief executive and co-owner of Esquire magazine. He gave it all up and devoted himself to the study and practice of Buddhism. He has come to a personal and intellectual understanding of the role suffering plays in our lives, and how we can fee ourselves from it. As he states &lt;em&gt;"I do not write as a Buddhist scholar, nor am I claiming to be enlightened; I am simply giving witness to what I've seen really make a difference in people's lives."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter by Commercial Street side of building - first door on left</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345074020000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340938900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion of "Dancing With Life" by Phillip Moffitt</name><id>71230482</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344898800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/71230482/</event_url></item>