<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On July 18th 2009 the Worcester Photography Center members will be walking downtown Worcester taking hundreds of photos together for a fun filled day of exploring! Please join us on the Scott Kelpby World Wide Photo Walk....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Web site for more details is:&lt;a href="http://worldwidephotowalk.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://worldwidephoto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, what exactly is a photo walk?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You take yourself and a camera to a designated meeting place to meet up with other photographers, then venture out into an area and snap away! Walk around taking pictures for a couple of hours, then gather at a restaurant, bar, or other eatery/drinkery, and compare, share, discuss, and have a good time. Then, if you want, submit your favorite photos from the day to the leader of your photo walk to be put in the running for the GRAND PRIZE! What’s the grand prize? Watch the video in the home page of the site to find out &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the benefits of going on a photo walk? If it’s an area that you’re already familiar with, being there with a group of creative people can help you see things in ways you hadn’t noticed before. Or if it’s an area you’re unfamiliar with, you can get to know the area with other people who may have lived there all their lives! But the best part (I think) is that you get to meet fellow photographers, make new friends, and have fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What do you need to bring? Yourself and a camera. Doesn’t matter what kind. If you want to come with a cell phone, go for it. If you want to show up with a top-of-the-line camera and an assortment of lenses and accessories, great. Just remember that it is a photo walk, so what you bring with you, you’ll be carrying the entire time. Personally, I would recommend bringing fairly minimal gear that’s versatile so you don’t have to change lenses every five minutes. As David duChemin says, “Gear is good. Vision is better.” Oh, and money for food and/or drink at the end of the photo walk. Wouldn’t want you to starve &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’re looking forward to a great day of fun, photography, and forming new friendships across the world. As of this posting we have over 340 locations with leaders (a number of which are already full), and over 2,600 participants signed up since the Photo Walk was announced on Monday! I’ll be blogging here each day as we add new locations and update this website with more information, so check back often to keep up with the latest. You can also subscribe for updates to this blog by clicking here.PLEASE get your friends to join us for the day!!! Up to 50 people can join in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is some info: &lt;br /&gt;The best photo from the day (as chosen by your local walk leader) will win a copy of Scott's &amp;quot;Lightroom 2 Book for Digital Photographers&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. What is a Photo Walk? &lt;br /&gt;A. It's a social photography event where photographers get together, usually in a downtown area or trendy section of town, to walk around, shoot photos, and generally have fun with other photographers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. What day is this special Worldwide Photo Walk? &lt;br /&gt;A. July 18th, 2009- 8:30AM-11:30AM Aprox. Three hours, from start to finish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Is the number of people in each city limited? &lt;br /&gt;A. Yup. It's limited to just 50 people per city (If groups get much bigger, it gets really hard to manage; hard to find a restaurant to hold more people, it creates crowd control problems, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Do I have to sign up in advance? &lt;br /&gt;A. Yeah, you have to let us know you're going to a part of a particular city's event by using the registration form (found right here). Don't forget to choose your city from the pop-up menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Do we have to stick together as one big group? &lt;br /&gt;A. Nope. Once the walk starts, you kind of move at your own pace, and we try to make the routes short enough so you have plenty of time for shooting and exploring along the way, and still get to the ending point on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Are there any prizes involved? &lt;br /&gt;A. You betcha! Since this Worldwide Photo Walk is to celebrate the release of the update of the world's bestselling Lightroom book (Scott Kelby's &amp;quot;Lightroom Book for Digital Photographers&amp;quot;), the best photo from the day (as chosen by your local walk leader) will win a copy of Scott's new book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Where will these photos be posted for judging? &lt;br /&gt;A. We've asked approved leaders to set up their own flickr group, a link will be posted on each individual photo walk page to this group (by the leaders, when they set it up), so you can see the best shots from the other photo walkers in your area (and around the world).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Is there a Grand Prize? &lt;br /&gt;A. Oh man is there a grand prize!!!! Check out this mega prize package (awarded by Scott to the single best overall photo taken that day, from all the Photo Walk locations around the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. How should I dress? &lt;br /&gt;A. Casual, and wear comfortable shoes because you'll be walking (Hey, it's a photo &amp;quot;walk,&amp;quot; right?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q. Anything else? &lt;br /&gt;A. Nope, just go and spend a great day, with some great people, who love making images just like you do. :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the one organizing the motley crew...wink wink</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1248524385000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243892231000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Scott Kelby World Wide PhotoWalk-Limited to 50 People!</name><id>10548029</id><headcount>47</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247920200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10548029/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/5/global_8932645.jpeg</photo_url></item>