<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>574 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01826</zip><lat>42.685254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-452-8800</phone><name>American Legion</name><city>Dracut</city><id>1200222</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.277431</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As most of you know my daughter Lauren passed away on Friday night, after her 3.5 week fight to survive. The docs and nurses at Mass General were/are wonderful and caring people, and did everything they could.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I didn't know how else to #1 express my gratitude and love, for all of you who have helped me through this past month, while Lauren was critical, in the hospital, and #2 to invite you to celebrate, with me, her short life, accomplishments and meet the rest of her/my family who love her so dearly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not your conventional &amp;quot;wake&amp;quot;, although we will have a blessing of her ashes (which are in a beautiful Dolphin Urn, that her honey Matt C. picked out for her). &lt;br /&gt;Lauren loves tulips, the colors yellow and blue and her love for animals (esp. Dolphins) was only surpassed by the love she has for her family and friends. &lt;br /&gt;thank you to my friends and family for making this night possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 5-9 you are welcome to join me for this Celebration, at the American Legion, 574 Broadway Rd, Dracut, MA 01826, in the upstairs hall. There is a cash bar and with a donation from some very dear Realtor friends...there will also be food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you cannot make it and would like to make a contribution, checks may be sent to the  &amp;quot;Lauren Tisbert Memorial Fund&amp;quot; at TDBank, 155 North Broadway, Salem, NH 03079.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thank you all again for your support, love, gifts, food, rides, meals, etc. etc. etc. the list is too long to mention. you have touched my heart and made me realize how very special you all are, and how very loved Lauren, myself and family feel right now.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285370440000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285031472000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Celebration of my daughter Lauren's life ;)</name><id>14839733</id><headcount>300</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285275600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/14839733/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/c/global_18129084.jpeg</photo_url></item>