<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From a single, abbreviated life grew a seemingly immortal line of cells  that made some of the most crucial innovations in modern science  possible. And from that same life, and those cells, Rebecca Skloot has  fashioned in &lt;em&gt;The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks&lt;/em&gt; a fascinating  and moving story of medicine and family, of how life is sustained in  laboratories and in memory. Henrietta Lacks was a mother of five in  Baltimore, a poor African American migrant from the tobacco farms of  Virginia, who died from a cruelly aggressive cancer at the age of 30 in  1951. A sample of her cancerous tissue, taken without her knowledge or  consent, as was the custom then, turned out to provide one of the holy  grails of mid-century biology: human cells that could survive--even  thrive--in the lab. Known as HeLa cells, their stunning potency gave  scientists a building block for countless breakthroughs, beginning with  the cure for polio. Meanwhile, Henrietta's family continued to live in  poverty and frequently poor health, and their discovery decades later of  her unknowing contribution--and her cells' strange survival--left them  full of pride, anger, and suspicion.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaimee</member_name><member_id>8486641</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303344747000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>For April, we'll be reading "The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks" by Rebecca Skloot</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club</urlname><id>1332912</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>The Southern NH Books and Brew Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301355849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Want to be immortal without becoming a vampire?</name><id>17093440</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303340400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club/events/17093440/</event_url></item>