<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP and &lt;i&gt;only sign up for one or two mini-meetups a month&lt;/i&gt;.  See this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt; for more details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;Texas Hold'em.  'Nuff said. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come with $1 or $2 and see if you got the skills like those people on tv.  We will play an official tournament in the beginning and then move on to whatever as the night goes on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, feel free to private message me. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Food theme:&lt;br /&gt;The theme for this event will be &amp;quot;beer &amp;amp; pretzels&amp;quot;.  You don't have to interpret that as bringing beer and pretzels exactly. It just means casual junk food that you probably shouldn't be eating. :-)  We will also have generic drinks and snacks on hand for people with special diets.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;About the location:&lt;br /&gt;Pickman Street is located between the Commons and the water. Parking on Pickman can be tight, but there should be ample parking along either Pleasant Street (by the Commons) or Collins Street (by the water) &lt;br /&gt;It will take place on the third floor unit. &lt;br /&gt;Note: there will be two cats present that will be very very sad if they have to get locked up. They are very polite however. If anyone would like to attend but has allegeries please send me a private message.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297029376000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291579285000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Poker Tournament</name><id>15649174</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296948600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15649174/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_11205793.jpeg</photo_url></item>