<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Mt Garfield is our choice for this Sunday. ice trails MICROSPIKES ARE REQUIRED, Dress in layers, it will be sunny, but don't know how windy yet. Most of the trail is protected, but the summit is open and a favorite of many.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We will meet together and&amp;nbsp;identify&amp;nbsp;the pace groups so everyone hikes at a comfortable pace. &amp;nbsp;The summit is an option. All hikers are welcome to hike. Your group can enjoy a great hike with a shorter turn around option.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;A minimum of 4 hikers will be desired in each group if more than one. While we will hike at a comfortable pace, no one should hike alone. &amp;nbsp;Proper "Hikesafe" clothing and gear required. Know your equipment and how to pack your gear, review the weather conditions before you arrive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;In addition to the standard lists, remember to pack "gatorade" drinks or gels to replace your electrolytes. This is advised for any high endurance exercise that lasts for over one hour.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1"&gt;http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Hike&amp;nbsp;Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty/hike rating:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; moderate (easy paced but have mountain trail experience 1 mph pace if elevation&amp;nbsp;is steep)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Time:&lt;/strong&gt; My rough guess would be around 8 hours. With a 9:00 am start time, this would have us back at the cars at 5:00pm so try not to be late };-) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mileage:&lt;/strong&gt; about 12.4 miles including the extra road walk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elevation gain:&lt;/strong&gt; about 3000'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; The parking at the western side of the Gale River loop road is visible from rt3 but only holds a max of 8 cars.&amp;nbsp; There is more parking across the street from the eastern entrance of the Gale River loop road which is .3 miles farther east called 5-corners.&amp;nbsp; If need be, we could shuttle people from that parking area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?msid=208920697845127440222.0004b9a25cebd4c604c93&amp;amp;msa=0"&gt;link to the parking areas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bathrooms:&lt;/strong&gt; Closest one I know of is at the Beaver brook recreational parking area about 1.5 miles farther east on rt3.&amp;nbsp; I've never used this restroom so I don't know if it's maintained in the winter.&amp;nbsp; I will usually stop at the Basin parking lot or the old bridle path/falling waters trail head parking area(across from the Lafayette campground) both areas are accessed heading northbound on 93 in the Franconia notch. &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We start our hike at the western entrance to the Gale River loop Road.&amp;nbsp; It is a 1.2 mile road walk on the Gale River loop road to get to to the Garfield Trail trail head. &amp;nbsp; We will take the Garfield trail until it intersects with the Garfield ridge trail (4.8 miles).&amp;nbsp; We will then take a right onto the Garfield ridge trail to the peak of Garfield (.2 miles).&amp;nbsp; We will then retrace out route back to the cars.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather and trail conditions:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; www.noaa.gov is predicting breezy weather at the top of Garfield with a temperature of around 10.&amp;nbsp; Fortunately, most of this hike is protected with the exception of the very top.&amp;nbsp; They are also predicting 4-6 inches of new snow between Friday and Saturday so snowshoes might not be a bad option.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; (I always bring mine)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; if people feel energetic and inquisitive, we could take a .7 mile side trip to visit the Garfield ridge campsite.&amp;nbsp; This is completely optional which can be discussed once we are at the summit &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Our goal is to start together as a group, hike together and finish together as a group. A winter group can be as small as 4 people, but no one should hike alone. Adhere to the Hike-Safe guidelines. Anyone could need help and stuff does happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/7/event_10322999.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet 7:30 at the I93 exit 23 carpool or 9am  west entrance of the gated gale river loop road   phone/text so we have real plans to meet you for the meetup, and no question of if your in the right location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330520020000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326924822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT GARFIELD!  9am west entrance of the gale river loop road</name><id>dgmrlcyqdbjc</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330264800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/48669952/</event_url></item>