<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.406082</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781) 648-4340</phone><name>Capitol Theater</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Due to the popularity of the movie, i will highly recommend that tickets are bought early at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bombaycinema.com/beta/index1.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bombaycinema.com/beta/index1.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bombaycine...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bw2OnEIoLH0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed:  Rakeysh Omprakash Mehra&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast:  Abhishek Bachchan, Sonam Kapoor, Waheeda Rehman, Om Puri, Amitabh Bachchan, Om Puri, Atul Kulkarni, Divya Dutta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Producer: Ronnie Screwala&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music: A. R. Rahman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distributors: UTV Motion Pictures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Releasing Date: February 20th 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About The Movie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the major hit RDB, Rakeysh Om Prakash is back with yet another flick Delhi 6 which emphasises on his own story during his childhood in Chandni Chowk area in Old Delhi. The movie has Abhishek Bachan to play the lead role named Roshan. The movie also has Sonam Kapoor, daughter of Anil Kapoor, whose debut film was Saawariya. Amitabh Bachan is also offered a special guest role as the grandfather of Roshan, along with Waheeda Rehman as his grandma. The much talented Gulshan Grover plays the role of Abhi’s dad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailer&lt;br /&gt;You need to a flashplayer enabled browser to view this YouTube video&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the name of the movie implies, the whole of the movie is a self-portrait of old-Delhi and the name is given so because the pin code of old-Delhi  is 110006.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like his earlier movies Rakeysh Om Prakash is trying to send a message through the movie that each and every man has their own weaknesses, and that no one is perfect. So you have no right to judje others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Roshan is an Indian-American citizen who is compelled to come to India along with his grandmother, as her days were getting over and that she was stubborn enough to die in her own country.  After reaching Delhi 6, Roshan is forced to stay there for a while and so he finds new friends in his neighbourhood, who had a completely different lifestyle from his.  It is only after becoming a part of the community that he comes to know that the people around him were trying to take advantage of his sleek nature. The story further shows how he tries to overcome these difficulties.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ram's cell is 9173629790. We can meet in the lobby of the cinema at 1:30</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ram</member_name><member_id>7601407</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246755653000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231899580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bollywood Movie - Delhi-6 </name><id>9518453</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235242800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/9518453/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/9/global_4274761.jpeg</photo_url></item>