<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At all of our recent meetings in Cambridge, a common feeling mentioned has been that of 
&lt;strong&gt;Overwhelm&lt;/strong&gt;: about life being so full ... too full, it sometimes seems! Come learn how to cope with the suffocating or drowning feelings associated with overwhelm- to take control of life once more and head confidently in the direction that we ourselves choose, freed of as much unnecessary baggage as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Martin (me) will join us again to share insights gleaned from neurolinguistic programming (NLP)- which I have been finding so beneficial, along with many others in our Meetups this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin (again, me) will also we sharing a new, fantastic strategy called 
&lt;strong&gt;S.O.R.T&lt;/strong&gt; which can be used to help 
&lt;strong&gt;clean up mental mlutter&lt;/strong&gt; which can be the source of 
&lt;strong&gt;Overwhelm&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free also to come share your SUCCESSES in Tackling Overwhelm - as well as to raise any other particular clutter-related challenges for which you seek solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-And perhaps come away with a Decluttering Buddy to help you steer into September with a cleared-out living space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;(If you plan to eat, please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to order; otherwise, by 7 pm will be fine. While no purchase minimum for refreshments is specified, participants are encouraged to order something substantive to support the business in appreciation of Management's permission to meet in their space. PLEASE ALSO BE ADVISED: Commercial eating establishments generally do not permit on-site consumption of refreshments brought from elsewhere, due to liability concerns.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314662898000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313529069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dealing with Overwhelm- FAST!!</name><id>29743641</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314658800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/29743641/</event_url></item>