<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>115 Empire St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-861-9190</phone><name>AS220 </name><city>Providence</city><id>483693</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This month, &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #605e6c ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Urban Greens&lt;/a&gt; is hosting PGD from 5-8pm at &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #605e6c ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;AS220&lt;/a&gt;, located at 115 Empire Street. Urban Greens will provide apps and AS220 has a great little bar. Urban Greens is also greening the event by contributing to &lt;a href="http://www.ripower.org/renewable-energy?utm_source=PGD+April+2012&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ug+pgd&amp;amp;utm_medium=email"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #605e6c ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;People's Power and Light&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who haven't heard about Urban Greens, they are working to open a&amp;nbsp;full-scale consumer-owned cooperative grocery store&amp;nbsp;in Providence, to provide direct access to affordable, local, and natural products. They will provide an alternative to corporate chain grocery stores; help support local farms and producers; and provide access to affordable healthy food in west and south Providence.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-ops benefit both the individual member-owners and the broader community:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Member-owners benefit because they have a&amp;nbsp;direct say&amp;nbsp;in the food they're eating and the store they shop at, and because the store is&amp;nbsp;invested in its member-owners! They also receive&amp;nbsp;financial benefits&amp;nbsp;in the form of member sales, bulk ordering, and patronage dividends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Community benefits because more&amp;nbsp;dollars are kept in the community&amp;nbsp;as opposed to going to the central offices of a chain store, and the coop will be&amp;nbsp;buying directly from local farmers,&amp;nbsp;building&amp;nbsp;local infrastructure&amp;nbsp;and creating&amp;nbsp;year-round access&amp;nbsp;to healthier, tastier and more affordable food.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #605e6c ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;join Urban Greens now&lt;/a&gt;, you can help them reach their goal for founding members and open the cooperatively owned community store!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Providence Green Drinks monthly gatherings (always held on "Thirsty Third Thursday") provide a great opportunity to meet with people in the area who are personally and/or professionally interested and involved in a variety of environmental, conservation, and sustainability issues. It's an informal and fun time and usually draws an eclectic group of several dozen people over the course of the evening.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Posted as an FYI - please RSVP if you're going so others can see who you are and look for you! If you'd like to host, please say so in your RSVP!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335061663000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333507555000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI  - Providence Green Drinks by Urban Greens at AS220!</name><id>59170052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334869200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/59170052/</event_url></item>