<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Wood Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.218399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-848-2300</phone><name>F1 Boston </name><city>Braintree</city><id>669076</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.039398</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://f1boston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://f1boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tracks are described as &amp;quot;European-style&amp;quot; and that's good enough for me.  We could race then have dinner at the Ascari Cafe after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that these are not kiddy go-karts, but proper racing karts.  They use a Continuously Variable Transmission, so no shifting is required.  We will be provided with helmets, neck braces and racing suits.  These things corner like they are on rails, so you will experience significant G-forces and should not participate if you have health concerns.  You must be 18+ and have a valid Drivers License.  They have a strict no alcohol or drugs policy, so save the fun for after the race.  I have raced real cars and I can assure you that these karts are fun and challenging and a great way to learn some basic performance driving techniques.  Plus you don't have to spend days of preparation, you just show up and race.  I recommend that you visit their website and review their policies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost for public &amp;quot;Arrive &amp;amp; Drive&amp;quot; racing is $10 for a day license plus $28 per race.  Each race lasts approximately 15 minutes.  Dinner would be off the menu which can be found at the F1 Boston website.  Please indicate how many races you would be interested in participating in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need a minimum of 8 people plus a deposit if we want a private event.  If we get 8+ RSVPs, I'll provide more details.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lets meet in the lobby near the license application station.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maia</member_name><member_id>3083598</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297091505000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294024086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kart Racing at F1 Boston</name><id>15892040</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296943200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/15892040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/2/global_13743234.jpeg</photo_url></item>