<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Balcom St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02825</zip><lat>41.811977</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Corner of Balcom and Route 6</name><city>Foster</city><id>8799882</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.748840</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Domenic and myself are coming up with some very pretty and nice roads to ride which would be a good ride for the fast and the slower. No major hills.   Follow route 6 past the red light at rt 94, part way up on up the hill is balcom road.  turn in and drive up the hill to where it flattens and shaded by trees.  and park along side...(my error previously, further on 6 is boswell road, but balcom is before the top of the hill, and goes up a hill then flattens out)  we will go from there down to north rd, follow that to end, meeting foster center rd heading right, this takes us to foster center and howard hill rd is straight across the intersection, on the side of the red library, which was one room schoolhouse once, past a big white house which is the current police dept, and so on...  follow it to end, about 3 miles, becomes briggs rd, then is howard hill again til it becomes rt 14/102 the first "busy" road for 1/4 mile or less, and then a right onto moosup vly rd for a short ride to johnson road on the right, which leads to the foster country club.  nice country road to ride on.  middle of golf course, harrington rd takes off on left, and meets up with cucumber hill road.  it is as busier a road as we shall meet... occassional cars.   take right on it to meet south killingly rd 2 miles or so up on the right.  follow it back to boswell road to north road, down a hill, and part way down the biggest hill, on the left is where we turn in on balcom, where we ride to the beginning and our cars.   a nice "easy" ride, beautiful area, and quiet roads usually.  We added miles, but took away major hills(Foster is full of hills)**Follow the path on the map, it is quite easy to see.  one big ellongated square &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting to starting point: to Foster, from East, take route 6 (highway)from Providence to Johnson exit onto route 6 follow thru Scituate out to Foster.  you can drive old rt 6 thru no scituate on original 6, or take bypass which breaks from 101, and meets up with 6 again in foster.   GPS or mapquest makes it easier than it sounds. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;from south, take 295 to Johnston and see above, or take rt 102 which exits from 95N, and follow 102 to where it intersects 6 and take a left there...in foster, follow 6 to balcom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From north, take either 395S in CT, exit on 6East and come to Foster... take 146s to 295S and exit in Johnston, and move along rt 6 to Foster &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Easy as kittens, and a marvelous ride!!!  We can go to Lucky's Tavern and Pizza on Route 6  just a top of hill on Rt 6 from Balcom Rd.,  easy to see on left side... further on rt. 6 is wendys place, other food and beer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AVOID VASA CLUB, WHICH IS ON BOSWELL, NOT BALCOM.  BALCOM IS EASIER TO FIND, THE FIRST ROAD TO APPEAR ON ROUTE 6 AFTER THE ONLY RED LIGHT IN FOSTER.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Turn in on Balcom off 6, Look for VASA park/club</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick Clark</member_name><member_id>17851281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348182444000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345431048000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ride through the Countrysides of Foster</name><id>dxglkdyqmbvb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347804000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/78482712/</event_url></item>