<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Ballfield Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.422870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-439-2572</phone><name>Lincoln Public Schools Campus</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>229094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.313896</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This walk will be through some fields and forest in Lincoln. We will walk around Flints Pond and through the De Cordova scuplture park. Boots are recommended as it may be muddy in parts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:30 in the school campus parking lot. Ballfield Rd is off of Lincoln Rd between Tower Rd and Pierce Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will have lunch at &lt;br /&gt;Bison County&lt;br /&gt;275 Moody Street Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;(781) 642-9720&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flint's (or Sandy) Pond (Lincoln, Mass.)&lt;br /&gt;Flint's Pond is a mile east of Walden Pond, hidden behind Pine Hill. Thoreau's roommate at Harvard College had a boyhood cabin on Flint's Pond, on a knoll at the top of the photo below. Thoreau is said to have spent a summer vacation there. He later sought permission from Farmer Flint to build his own cabin on Flint's Pond but was rebuffed. So Thoreau built at Walden Pond instead. But for the turn-down, could Walden have been named Flint's, do you suppose?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Now, recreation use of the pond and shore is banned to protect drinking water. But in 1646, diverse Indian sachems had declared to the English their interest in establishing a village in the chestnut grove on the east shore, so they could coexist as Christians with the English in Concord. It never happened. In the 1800s, as many as ten couples would enjoy gala events on the pond in a calico-curtained boat. Above the pond (at left) is the Decordova Museum and its outdoor sculpture garden, probably on &amp;quot;Three Friends' Hill,&amp;quot; named at the time for Emerson, Channing, and Thoreau. ]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265124874000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264624385000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flint Pond walk</name><id>12441592</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264951800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/12441592/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/a/global_3504746.jpeg</photo_url></item>