<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bear Mountain State Park</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10911</zip><lat>41.310000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>845-786-2701</phone><name>Bear Mountain Inn</name><city>Bear Mountain</city><id>1363141</id><country>us</country><lon>-74.000000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a full day trip to hike 6 miles on Bear Mountain in Bear Mountain State Park in southern New York along the Hudson River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pack a hearty trail lunch and a quart of water for this trip. Hiking boots are recommended as well as warm layered clothing so layers can be removed as you warm up on the hike. A pack is advised to store your lunch and layers removed. Your hands need to be free for the hike. Carpool (limited capacity) from Hartford area leaves 7 AM, group for hike meets at park at 9:30 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The view is dramatic starting with the Hudson River valley as we approach the park. The valley is a fjord at this point, deepened by glaciers long ago. The mountains on either side of the river are over 1,000 feet in altitude and they rise about that much above the river. We cross Bear Mountain Bridge over the Hudson with our vehicles and the view is wonderful up and down the valley from such a high path. We'll park at the Bear Mountain Inn (closed for renovation though) and wait for the gathering of hike participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll hike a small portion of the Appalachian Trail from the Inn up to the peak of Bear Mtn. The gain in altitude is roughly a respectable 1,100 feet in 1.75 miles of hiking. Generous time has been allotted for the ascent (up to 2 hours) and it is not recommended for those with heart or breathing issues. At the peak we'll temporarily pass the Perkins Memorial Tower to reach the true peak of the mountain a little further on. We then backtrack to eat our packed in lunch at a picnic area. After lunch we backtrack a little more to the tower to check it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We then start out decent, still on the Appalachian Trail until we intersect with a Red blazed trail in a small valley and start heading southeast. We'll intersect a Yellow blazed trail and take that around a swampy area and up a couple hundred feet on a shoulder of Bear Mountain as we make our way northeast. Once over the shoulder we descend and intersect a portion of the Appalachian Trail we used for the ascent and return to the Inn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many interesting amenities and views in the area of the Inn we'll have about an hour of free time to check out (see below). We plan on going to the &amp;quot;New City Diner&amp;quot; to have dinner together (please bring enough cash to facilitate paying the check) before we all head home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you carpool, please chip in a fair share for the ride. Parking fee is $6/car. Bridge toll to leave the park (to east) is $1/car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTES:&lt;br /&gt;+ 1,100 ft total gain in altitude to peek (160 ft at start - 1,284 feet at peak).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ Rate hike to be moderate difficulty overall, for those without heart or breathing issues, not for absolute beginners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ Must pack for the hike a good trail lunch and 1 qt. water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Travel/Meet-up--&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 AM Leave with carpool from CT, Harford area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 9:30 AM Arrive and park at the Bear Mtn. Inn parking lot. Wait for members to collect and check out the old Inn (closed).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 10:00 AM Be assembled for hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Ascent--&lt;br /&gt;* 10:00 AM Start hike up Bear Mtn. via AT trail (alt. 160 ft., SLOW 70 min./mi. pace).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 12:00 PM Reach Perkins Tower (at 1.75 mi., alt. 1,280 ft.), continue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 12:10 PM Reach actual peak (at 1.95 mi., alt 1,284 ft.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 12:15 PM Back to Picnic Area (at 2.05 mi., alt. 1,280 ft.) &amp;amp; have packed lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 1:00 PM Continue hike to Perkins Tower (at 2.15 mi., alt. 1,280 ft.) &amp;amp; check it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Descent--&lt;br /&gt;* 1:30 PM Continue hike on AT down Mtn. (at 2.15 mi., alt. 1,280 ft., 30 min./mi. pace).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 2:15 PM Reach intersection with Red trail and take it to SE (at 3.65 mi., alt. 600 ft., 30 min./mi. pace).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 2:35 PM Reach intersection of Red and Yellow trails take to NE, down/up hill (at 4.25 mi., alt. 500 ft., 45 min./mi. pace).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 3:10 PM Continue on Yellow Trail downhill (at 4.95 mi., alt 620 ft., 30 min./mi. pace).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 3:40 PM Back to start by Inn (6 mi., alt 160 ft.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 4:00 PM Free time! (approximate SUNSET time!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Free Time--&lt;br /&gt;* 4:00 PM Suggestions: Outdoor Skating Rink (open 4 - 5:30 PM; $4, +$4 rental); Marry-Go-round ($1 ride); check out the Inn, lake, buildings; and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 5:00 PM Be assembled for dinner trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dinner--&lt;br /&gt;* 5:00 PM Travel to dinner location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 5:30 PM Start dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 PM Dinner done.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Return Travel--&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 PM Start travel back to CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 9:30 PM Arrive back at carpool start in CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION (can get directions here):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=bear+mountain+inn&amp;amp;address=&amp;amp;city=&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;zipcode=" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MORE INFORMATION:&lt;br /&gt;Bear Mountain State Park:&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://www.hudsonriver.com/bearmtn.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hudsonrive...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://www.friendsofpalisades.org/content.php?mode=parks&amp;amp;object_id=5" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.friendsofp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://3dparks.wr.usgs.gov/nyc/parks/loc9.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://3dparks.wr.usg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165234161000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1164216779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Bear Mountain State Park, NY</name><id>5285257</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165060800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5285257/</event_url></item>