<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a reposting of this hike.&lt;br /&gt;I am planning another section of the Appalachian Trial for a day hike.  I know this falls early on Father's Day but I am hoping others, like myself, do not have plans that day.  You could definitely make dinner with Dad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will cover a very steep section where we will climb Mt. Everett to see amazing views and finish at the base of a section called Jug End.  The distance on this is 5.5 miles but the elevation gain could be about 1500' to the top of Mt. Everett (elev 2,062').  This will be a challenging experience for all involved but will be very rewarding.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin on Route 41, Undermountain Road near Sheffield MA.  We will take the Race Brook Falls Falls Trail to intersect with the AT.  From there we are heading north on the white blazed AT up Mt. Everett.  The views promise to be spectacular.  We continue along the ridge over Mt. Bushnell and then over and down Jug End.  The finish spot is on Jug End Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need two cars to shuttle folks.  I will certainly coordinate carpooling from the Hartford area.  If you are meeting there, please meet at the ending site on Jug End Road at 9:00 a.m.  We will shuttle to the beginning from there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please wear study hiking boots and bring water (at least one liter).  We will eat on the trail for lunch so pack food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a challenging hike with a great deal on climbing.  I expect a hike time of four hours.  Please do not plan on bringing dogs to this hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the spot for where the hike starts.  Across from Salisbury Road on Route 41 is a parking area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Sheffield&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=%5B1542-1599%5D+Salisbury+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=01257&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.08865&amp;amp;longitude=-73.41015&amp;amp;geocode=STREET" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THIS&lt;br /&gt;This the end spot for the hike.  The AT breaks on Jug End Road.  The mapquest directions take you to Guilder Hollow Road.  Go down this road as it turns into Jug End Rd.  The parking area is before the turn for Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Sheffield&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=1+Guilder+Hollow+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=01257-9644&amp;amp;country=US" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273544590000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243709763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt. Everett to Jug End, South Egermont MA</name><id>10531073</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245589200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10531073/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/e/global_2859934.jpeg</photo_url></item>