<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We did this walk back in March, but its better in the summer because, if we want, we can go swimming when we get to Walden Pond. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 10:30 am in the parking lot in front of Donelan's supermarket and the part of Lincoln commuter rail station adjacent to Donelans (the commuter rail station is on both sides of Lincoln Road).  Donelans is located at 145 Lincoln Rd Lincoln, MA and is part of a gray, modern looking &amp;quot;strip mall.&amp;quot; There is a large parking lot with plenty of spaces-I suggest parking in the back of the lot where the supermarket is.  It is actually conceivable to take the T there (commuter rail-North Station to Fitchburg line - Lincoln  stop) - see www.mbta.com for details - but I recommend getting a ride if you don't have a car (I can drive up to three people from Alewife).   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk goes from Donelans/Lincoln Station to Walden Pond, and then back.  It takes a tad over two hours.  The walk goes through forests and fields, some up and down portions, a couple quiet streets to cross, and ends up at Walden Pond.   We will take a break at Walden Pond at one of the &amp;quot;beaches&amp;quot; and I am going to at least take a dip in the pond (and linger in there if everyone else is up for a swim) because it may be hot out.  So bring your bathing suit if you want (sorry Greg,no skinny dipping...) - and no drowning allowed-I'm not a lifeguard! Then we walk back.  Sneakers are fine, bring boots if it rains.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll then have lunch at a restaurant in Waltham center at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Margarita's Mexican Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;Address:   211 Moody St, Waltham, MA 02453  &lt;br /&gt;Phone: (781) 893-9990 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187707440000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181960174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lincoln Station - Walden Pond Walk</name><id>5896904</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187533800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5896904/</event_url></item>