<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>6 Hours Of Golf Lessons</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Learn to play Golf + Improve Your Skills -Discount Group Golf Lessons in Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf is a challenging and rewarding sport that is very important in the business world. Many business deals and business relationships are made on the Golf Course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because Golf Lessons can be expensive costing $50 to $75 per hour, www.CTGolfTips.com has organized a series of discount golf lessons that include 6 hours of quality hands –on Golf Instruction by a certified Golf Teaching Professional for $100 – which is $17 per hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our golf lesson students include Men, Women, Couples, Family, Teens, Children from, CT – Connecticut, MA – Massachusetts, RI – Rhode Island and NY – New York. The golfer takes a 2 hour lesson on 3 days of their choice for a total of 6 hours.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf 101 is designed for the new or beginning Golfer who wants to learn golf, teaching proper Golf technique including Driving, Putting, Chipping, Golfing rules, Video Swing Analysis, and playing out on the Golf Course. This course is ideal for all ages, new Golfers or anyone breaking in new equipment or needs to improve their skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Golf 102 consists of Playing Lessons on a 9-hole Golf course while the Certified Golf Instructor helps you improve your Golfing skills. Golf 102 playing lessons are a great course for the more experienced golfer, and for Golf 101 graduates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf Lessons are held at Miner Hill Golf Course in Middletown, CT - 10 minutes from Hartford or New Haven ,  and close to Meriden and Wallingford Connecticut -Exit 20 Country Club Road off I-91 North or South. Our flexible schedule allows you to pick the dates and times that you want to take lessons. Our Golf Teacher will contact you to schedule your Golf Lessons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf 101 and Golf 102 class sizes are kept small (9 students) to ensure personal attention, and is only $100 for 6 hours of instruction. All equipment including golf balls, golf clubs and fees are included, or students can bring their own clubs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf 101 and Golf 101 lessons are held at Minor Hills Golf Club in Middletown, CT (Exit 20 off I-91) Students select their dates and times of lessons. After the student signs up Golf 101 or Golf 102, they will be email their payment receipt, a welcome email with lesson information. Next, the student s contacted by the Golf Instructor to schedule their lessons. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Lessons are held at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miner Hills Golf Course and Driving Range&lt;br /&gt;85 Miner Hills Drive&lt;br /&gt;Middletown, CT 06457&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PURCHASE YOUR SPOT ONLINE AND SAVE 33%!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6 hours of Lessons -$100 Online ($17 per hour) Pay with Credit Card using the Buy Now/Pay Pal button&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or $150 at the course ($25 per hour CASH ONLY) if any space is available. &lt;br /&gt;Please call (860) 436-9449 for available space before the lesson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LESSON DATES: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturdays 4-6 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sundays 4-6 pm  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday 6-8 pm  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday 6-8 pm &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsinCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See You On The Course!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT OUR STUDENTS ARE SAYING:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ Golf 101 was a fun and inexpensive way to learn Golf from the beginning. Having never golfed before, I was nervous, but our Instructor George did a great job teaching our group, and I am having a great time in Golf 102!”   &lt;br /&gt;Rodney P, New Haven CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ Inexpensive, high quality Lessons in a small group, I made new golfing buddies and am enjoying the game of golf” &lt;br /&gt;June B, Bloomfield CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ I have taken lessons from golf pros before, but Golf 102 Playing Lessons were more effective and less expensive than any other lessons.”&lt;br /&gt;Jim S, Newington CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ I was not sure if I would enjoy Golfing so I tried Golf 101 and I love it! The Instructor was very patient and answered all my questions, and made the lessons fun!”&lt;br /&gt;Gloria W, Milford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look For Us In The White www.CTGolfTips.com Hats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>CTGolfTips.com</member_name><member_id>7047572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245458346000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244568670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Learn to play Golf and Improve Your Skills -Discount Group Golf Lessons in CT</name><id>10613220</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244923200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/10613220/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/4/global_9067652.jpeg</photo_url></item>