<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Moving from Resisting to Allowing by Resolving Conflicting Beliefs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want more money, but you don't really believe it's possible for you, that belief is going to have a significant impact on your likelihood of success. If you have a physical problem, and you have a belief (perhaps subconscious) that “this is going to take a long time to recover from”, what effect do you think that might have? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;It’s becoming more and more recognized that to be effective and succeed in anything, you need “to believe”.  Part of the “formula” for deliberately practicing the law of attraction is to believe in what you are asking for.  But what if you don’t?  Sometimes “faking it” will work, but sometimes it just isn’t enough.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;In this month's meeting you'll have the opportunity to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Discover any possible conflicting beliefs you might have regarding something you want, and &lt;br /&gt;• Do a process for changing that belief to a more &amp;quot;allowing&amp;quot; one  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This level of personal evolution is extremely important to living the life you desire.  Hope you'll join us for this evening of opening up new possibilities!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to come early to hang out, eat, and have extra time together! We'll have dessert-type snacks; but you can bring your dinner, if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here for you,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;Note: Please RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;br /&gt;Since we usually provide refreshments, handouts and set up chairs,  please only RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; if you know you can attend, and are planning on it.  If your plans change, please be considerate and notify us by e-mailing me.  Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be upstairs.  Go to back of front lobby for stairway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240351815000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234919365000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metro West Law of Attraction/"Good Vibrations" March Meetup</name><id>9764002</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237330800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/9764002/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/c/global_7047340.jpeg</photo_url></item>