<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This hike is sponsored by our group and is a 3.0 mile looping hike of low to moderate effort on mostly forested land. There is a gradual upward trend for the first half of the hike on the South Boundary Loop and that is where some effort will be expended. A few stream crossings over small rough bridges of half logs and peaceful atmosphere prevail on this conservation land hike. Snow, rain, or shine the hike will go on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the lot at 2:30 PM and start the hike shortly thereafter. We should be done by about 4 PM. Optionally, we can go to one of the local eating establishments for an early dinner after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: The McCann Family Farm is a hilly 84 acres of farmland and mixed forest. Located on it are two brooks and two vernal pools. It includes extensive hiking trails and the Whit Davis Bird Sanctuary, and is the location of several wildflower and bird watching hikes each year as put on by the NCLT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/Directions:  The McCann Family Farm is Route 190 east of the village of Somers. Parking lot is on the south side of 190, about 0.7 miles east of Route 83. THe entrance is a short dirt road with a very dark wooden sign marking the entrance. Parking is in a dirt lot. Approximate location of the McCann Family Farm given by the URL (and turn-by-turn directions can be found there):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.yahoo.com/maps_result?addr=650%20Main%20Street&amp;amp;csz=Somers%2C+CT&amp;amp;country=us&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;qty=&amp;amp;cat=fin&amp;amp;trf=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.yahoo.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this hike is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;) so please direct questions on the hike to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the property, see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/Lists/Properties/DispForm.aspx?ID=2"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northern Connecticut Land Trust (NCLT)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1168975810000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1167768540000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at the NCLT's McCann Family Farm Nature Preserve in Somers CT</name><id>5359311</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168803000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5359311/</event_url></item>