<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;About the Boston Vegetarian Food Festival&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;This event is not to be missed. It is great every year!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Boston Vegetarian Food Festival&lt;/b&gt; is a full day of fun, good food, and learning! It brings together exhibitors of vegetarian natural foods from across the country and locally, offering free food sampling and &amp;quot;show special&amp;quot; discounts. It provides a welcoming environment in which to explore a wide variety of delicious, healthy, and readily available vegetarian foods. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Festival offers the opportunity to talk to food producers, see and taste the latest vegetarian products being introduced to the marketplace, and shop at discounted prices. Attendees can learn from speakers who are top national experts on health and nutrition, and presenters who inspire compassion for animals and respect for the environment. Award winning chefs and cookbook authors teach their recipes and offer free samples of the dishes they demonstrate. Educational exhibits on animals and the environment, and a children's activity center round out the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The longest running event of its kind in the country, the Festival is a resource for vegetarians and vegans, and for anyone wanting to include a greater variety of healthy and delicious plant-based foods in their diets. It also interests those wanting to live in greater harmony with animals and the environment.  Our past Festivals have each attracted thousands of attendees who come from all over the Northeast and beyond. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Boston Vegetarian Food Festival is FREE to the public and features:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;100 exciting exhibitors &lt;br /&gt;free food sampling! &lt;br /&gt;grocery and natural foods store exhibits &lt;br /&gt;food producers and new products &lt;br /&gt;cooking demonstrations by noted chefs &lt;br /&gt;book and cookbook publishers and authors &lt;br /&gt;top national speakers &lt;br /&gt;educational exhibits on protecting animals and the environment &lt;br /&gt;Festival discounted shopping &lt;br /&gt;registered dietitian consultants &lt;br /&gt;children's activities &lt;br /&gt;restaurants &lt;br /&gt;exhibitors of products and services which support a vegetarian way of life &lt;br /&gt;free parking and a subway stop across the street &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonveg.org/foodfest/" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonveg.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reviews&lt;/b&gt; of past Veg Food Festivals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonveg.org/foodfest/reviews.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonveg.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You can join the Boston Vegetarian Society here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonveg.org/membership" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonveg.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evelyn Kimber, long time veg activist, does a fantastic job with BVS. We highly recommend that you join and support BVS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BVS Calendar of Events&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonveg.org/calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonveg.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Boston Raw Food Group posted files,&lt;/b&gt; please check the files section&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawfood.meetup.com/343/files/"&gt;http://rawfood.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To promote the BRFG,&lt;/b&gt; please print out and post our tear-strip flyer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/733136/BostonRawFoodMeetupTear-stripFlyer.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For upcoming events,&lt;/b&gt; please check the calendar&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rawfood.meetup.com/343/calendar/"&gt;http://rawfood.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For other raw events&lt;/b&gt; around New England, please visit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.NewEnglandRawCommunity.com"&gt;http://www.NewEngland...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may make an optional small contribution to our Meetup group via PayPal to elliott7 [@] comcast.net . Please email after a donation so we may send a thank you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227153043000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207939120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Vegetarian Food Festival!</name><id>7721200</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225544400000</time><rsvp_limit>200</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/7721200/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/5/global_6046245.jpeg</photo_url></item>