<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>984 Lowell St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01741</zip><lat>42.554144</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-658-5374</phone><name>Great Brook Farm State Park</name><city>Carlisle</city><id>712406</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353268</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I've been told that The Boston Mycological Club generally schedules their first &amp;quot;walk&amp;quot; in mid-May for morels. So lets plan on kicking off 2010 by meeting at Great Brook Farm State Park. Lets meet at 10 am in the parking lot nearest the Park Headquarters - 984 Lowell Street, Carlisle, MA. We'll pick a trail or two and go from there. After our hunt we can go for bite to eat and discuss our hike, etc. Please email me if you are coming. If it's a rainy day we'll do it on Sunday the 16th, same time and place. Bring a bag or basket, knife, drinks and pack a lunch. Dress accordingly, hiking boots, hat. Please check out morels in the web so you know what you're looking for and what the poisonous false morel looks like. Every year I read about someone dying from eating poisonous shrooms. Please note that I am note responsible for what you pick and decide to eat. I recommend buying the Audubon Society's book on North American Mushrooms. I've found it very informative with photos, descriptions, etc. See you soon. Rick&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Mushroom Lovers USA sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Richard P.</member_name><member_id>9495023</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276396034000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fungi's &amp; gils</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mushroom-Lovers-USA</urlname><id>1497456</id><group_lat>42.4700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>Mushroom Lovers USA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269143100000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Brook Farm Shroom Hunt</name><id>12944541</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273932000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mushroom-Lovers-USA/events/12944541/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/1/global_13896161.jpeg</photo_url></item>