<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>60.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a workshop designed to introduce the photographer to some basic portrait studio techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 4 hour (1:00 pm to 5:00 pm) workshop will be a combination of classroom instruction and hands on studio shooting. We will be demonstrating how to use and control a single light for making portraits. Using a single light allows us to describe/demonstrate lighting techniques that can be applied to more complex, multi light sourced studio work. We will also be discussing general studio equipment and techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concepts covered also can be applied to very basic lighting equipment so that the average photographer who is interested in studio portrait making can get into it with a modest investment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;We will be working with a few live models&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to provide a more realistic studio experience.  Bring your cameras with charged batteries and plenty of memory cards and come ready to do some shooting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;u&gt;THIS CLASS IS LIMITED IN SIZE&lt;/u&gt; and requires payment to confirm your attendance.  Payment via PAYPAL does not require that you have a PAYPAL account of your own&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For directions go to my website -- http://www.testoftimephoto.com/DIRECTIONS.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278856735000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276269453000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to studio photography - ONE LIGHT PORTRAITS</name><id>13770651</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278781200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/13770651/</event_url></item>