<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Northeastern Blvd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.732246</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>321-4818</phone><name>Holiday Inn Nashua</name><city>Nashua</city><id>747227</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.475945</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am a meet up organizer from Hudson, NH.  I am writing to you &lt;br /&gt;to ask if you would mind sharing the information regarding an &lt;br /&gt;upcoming fund raiser for the NH Food Bank.  It is a wonderful &lt;br /&gt;Sound Healing Concert called Holiday Vibrations.  We are trying &lt;br /&gt;to get as many people as possible to be aware of this event.  &lt;br /&gt;The Advance Ticket Sales are only $14.00 if reserved prior to &lt;br /&gt;Dec 1st.  I thank you for taking the time to share this &lt;br /&gt;information with your group and others that you may know who &lt;br /&gt;may be interested in this performance. &lt;br /&gt;Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;Blessings,&lt;br /&gt;Angie D'Anjou&lt;br /&gt;603 912-5633&lt;br /&gt;A Benefit for the NH Food Bank... &amp;quot;Holiday Vibrations&amp;quot; Sound &lt;br /&gt;Healing Benefit Concert &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Dec 5, 2010  choose from 12:00pm performance or 4:00pm &lt;br /&gt;performance&lt;br /&gt;Location: Holiday Inn, 9 Northeastern Blvd., Nashua, NH &lt;br /&gt;Visit www.crystaljadeshop for more details.&lt;br /&gt;The performance last year was absolutely astounding! The four &lt;br /&gt;major performers including Joseph Carringer,Didgeridoo &lt;br /&gt;International Sound Healer Richard Gandiva Lorcan, &lt;br /&gt;International Gong Master Healer, Bindy Johnson, international &lt;br /&gt;Crystal Bowl Sound Healer, and Michael Longrider, Traditional &lt;br /&gt;Flute player have created through their musical and spiritual &lt;br /&gt;attitudes a remakable atmosphere that was enjoyed by all who &lt;br /&gt;attended. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to allow yourself to experience this Holiday &lt;br /&gt;Extravaganza! You will not be sorry! Feel the true peace of the &lt;br /&gt;season! Absorb the Healing Energy and Re-Energize your mind, &lt;br /&gt;body, &amp;amp; spirit! &lt;br /&gt;A great way to help raise money for our local NH Food Bank! &lt;br /&gt;We thank you for attending and donating to a great cause! &lt;br /&gt;Blessings, &lt;br /&gt;Angie D'Anjou, Event Coordinator&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two performance times to choose from scheduled at 12:00pm or 4:&lt;br /&gt;00pm. Tickets are only $14.00 per person if purchased in &lt;br /&gt;advance prior to Nov. 29, 2010. Tickets purchased after Nov &lt;br /&gt;29th will be sold at the original price of $30.00 per person. &lt;br /&gt;This is a benefit concert for the NH Food Bank. Call Angie at &lt;br /&gt;603 912-5633 to order your advance discounted tickets today or &lt;br /&gt;visit www.crystaljademetaphysical.com for further information &lt;br /&gt;and order forms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year's performance will also include a special Opening &lt;br /&gt;Performance by American-Israeli folksinger, RAHEL who will &lt;br /&gt;share her unique Hebrew Chants in &amp;quot;free-verse&amp;quot; style award-&lt;br /&gt;winning songs. The Main Concert performers include: Joseph &lt;br /&gt;Carringer, Gandiva Lorcan, Bindy Johnson, and Michael Longrider &lt;br /&gt;Joining together to bring all a delightfully relaxing and &lt;br /&gt;inspiring healing concert. &lt;br /&gt;In addition there will be a variety of unique gift items &lt;br /&gt;available for purchase including CD's, Crystals, Hand Carved &lt;br /&gt;Wooden Art &amp;amp; Flutes, Soy Candles, and a variety of other &lt;br /&gt;merchandise. &lt;br /&gt;All performers will be available before, between and after each &lt;br /&gt;performance to meet with those who wish to learn more about &lt;br /&gt;sound healing therapies, receive autographs, or purchase CD's. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angie D'Anjou</member_name><member_id>7038429</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291573716000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gifted</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Friends-in-Spirit</urlname><id>1373252</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Friends in Spirit</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290899638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Benefit for the NH Food Bank... "Holiday Vibrations" </name><id>15569708</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291568400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Friends-in-Spirit/events/15569708/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/4/global_7183796.jpeg</photo_url></item>