<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>One of my Favorite Painters in Worcester is having an open studio - and I just had to tell you all about it. Check out his work and see if you'd like to go down and meet him- see his work- maybe buy a piece for your home or office. Scott and I will be there after 5 to see the new work ourselves. If your free come on down!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note from Brian -- &lt;br /&gt;The open house is coming up.. just nine days out, I figured I'd put out a notice so people can plan ahead.  Hoping the Friday date works out for people to drop in after work, or before they head out for the evening, have a bite and a glass. Should be about thirty pieces ranging about the studio and spilling into the hall.  Six new. Feel free to forward this to anyone you might think interested, and thanks.  Hope to see you there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the link for how to get up into the building. &lt;br /&gt;                      www.burrisworks.com/unrepentant_studio_open_house_info.html&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address for the building is 75 Webster St, but my studio actually fronts 6 Jacques St (not Jacques Ave: that'll take you somewhere you don't want to be).  Mapquest the intersection and you can't go wrong, and there's parking across the street from Jacques St as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Normally it would drive me nuts to have to change the date.  However, this opportunity is too good to pass up.  I just found out that two other artists in my building--Jonathan Lucas and Rose Russell--are having open studios April 17th.  The chance to add to that synergy and open up all our studios and works to new audiences tipped the scales  and overcame my reluctance to subject everyone to the possible confusion.  So please note the change:  Open Studio, April 17th, 4 to 8pm.  The new show card is below and here's the link again for how to get to my studio within the building:&lt;br /&gt;                             &lt;a href="http://www.burrisworks.com/unrepentant_studio_open_house_info.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.burriswork...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Small place- I'll find you...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240172396000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237923264000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Its' not Photography but it's still AWESOME!</name><id>10026000</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239998400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10026000/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/global_7854145.jpeg</photo_url></item>