<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Back Bay</address_2><address_1>907 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348457</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 236-1767</phone><name>The Pour House</name><city>Boston</city><id>820623</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084312</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a good time to benefit a fantastic charity! We will munch on free appetizers and play some team trivia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We will meet on Sunday, June 24th from 5:00 to 8:00 at the Pour House (907 Boylston St in Boston; see &lt;a href="http://www.pourhouseboston.com/menu.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.pourhouseboston.com/menu.htm&lt;/a&gt;). We have a separate room for the event, so you can ask for us or just find us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* This is a team trivia event (4 to 6 players per team), so bring 3-5 friends to join in the fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* The Pour House is providing free appetizers for our group! Drinks and other food will be available for purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Proceeds will benefit efforts to improve oral health in Zambia. 100% of donations will support a trip by students and faculty from the Tufts University School of Dental Medicine to provide care in Zambia, where oral disease is a major problem. The suggested donation is $20 per player, but giving is completely optional. Any donation, big or small, will be gratefully accepted and appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* All players must be at least 21 years of age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members of other volunteer and social groups are also attending this event, and the Pour House has limited space, so please RSVP to secure your spot. Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340583987000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338658808000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivia night at the Pour House:  benefits a great cause</name><id>67432132</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340571600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/67432132/</event_url></item>