<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Do you like the water? Do you like to play in the water? Well we will be playing and having fun with Trailblazers first &amp;quot;Water Day&amp;quot; come enjoy yourself at &amp;quot;Merrymeeting Lake, (the second cleanest lake in NH). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you enjoy sailing, well I will take people in my &amp;quot;16 foot Hobie Cat&amp;quot; sailboat or my &amp;quot;Force 5&amp;quot; racing sailboat, then again if it's not windy enough you could always try my &amp;quot;hydroplane&amp;quot; boat or drive a jetski. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have a potluck lunch in the middle of the lake! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you scuba dive, well we will have a couple of air tanks available for anyone brave enough to try scuba diving or if you have your own gear we could dive for sunken treasure! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will take a cruise around the lake in a pontoon party boat! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So bring your jetski's, sailboat, kayak's or whatever you have and come to &amp;quot;Water Day&amp;quot; we will be watersking and windsurfing! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We could boat over to the famous &amp;quot;rope swing&amp;quot; and splash into the water! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will let people try &amp;quot;sculling&amp;quot; (rowing a scull boat) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a tour of the biggest fish hatchery in New England right next to where we will be meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So bring your bathing suits, mask and snorkel, kayaks, jetski's, sailboat's or whatever type of boat that you would like to share with others! And don't forget your potluck lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If people want to share the cost of gas that would be great; please ask for contributions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have an extra life jacket bring it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your water guns, water balloons, or any other water fighting blaster for a water gun fight!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please no alcohol or glass bottles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come one, come all for a fun filled day of water fun! Please let me know if you are bringing a boat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it's raining I will notify everyone by email that we will be rescheduling this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions I can be reached by phone at 603-509-0907. Note: I do not have reception at the lake or up in that area on my cell phone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be leaving McDonald's restaurant at 12 pm or you could meet us at the Dam at the entrance of Merrymeeting lake, near the fish hatchery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me there or look for a "Meetup" sign.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219075772000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216807492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Water Day</name><id>8394877</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218902400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/8394877/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/8/7/global_4894999.jpeg</photo_url></item>