<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1398 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.424763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 643-9090</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668948</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.186264</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>6:00 - 6:30 pm -- Socialize&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 - 8:30 pm -- Plan 2008 Meetups: topics, schedule, activities, speakers, events, resources, venues ... with discussion of how this group can most help YOU. I'll bring a digital camera if you may want to post your photo on our Members list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 - 9:00 pm -- High-fives or hugs for MOTIVATION!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the most special people in my life happen to be &amp;quot;Messies&amp;quot; -- blessing so many with their riches of caring and spirit while suffering silently under burdens of stuff. I don't know if any may join us at meetings, but I hope so.  I'd love for you to get to know them too. I'd love to find ways to declutter that work for us all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For inspiration:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Chocolate calcium &amp;quot;chews&amp;quot; vs. chalky tablets ... which do you suppose get ingested more?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Lessons from a Goose: www.problogger.net/archives/2005/05/19/blogging-in-formation-lessons-from-a-goose&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Seabiscuit documentary (PBS) about the beloved &amp;quot;little brown racehorse&amp;quot; who became proxy for this nation during the Great Depression ... anatomically comical in respects, with an abysmal track record as a colt, Seabiscuit appeared best suited for hauling ice carts. But a wise horse trainer caught an indomitable glint in his eye and took him on, pampering him ... and inspiring generations ever after through his discovery. Tears come to my eyes each time I watch Seabiscuit's spirit open up and focus, head to head against the beautiful, magnificent, seemingly invincible War Admiral -- to &amp;quot;race to parts unknown!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Batteries ... plain commodities on store shelves vital for many important functions: light, music, fun, work (even TASERS!). Each of us is like one: sometimes only one is needed to do a job; usually morec an create synergy. Clutter MAY be a clue that more &amp;quot;batteries&amp;quot; are needed to complete a connection for the matter and energy stuck around us to flow again -- helping us do what we most WANT to do. How to better share the wealth of what we've collected, perhaps attract more batteries to &amp;quot;rock our world&amp;quot;? Consider how you might want to do so. What may be special about your stuff ... what wisdom is in it for you to be keeping around? Might sharing about it help release it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Saving Private Ryan - opening scene ... U.S. military risks their lives for our freedom to create value. (Also: clutter can't fight back!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't attend this Organizational meeting, you CAN let me know your preferences for the group, such as best days of month and times of day for you ... also ideas to help make decluttering more FUN, increasing our chances for success, such as (friendly) competitions for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- most $ earned by eBaying/selling stuff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- most creative way to reward oneself&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- the inspiration/strategy/technique/resource/organization/person most helpful for clearing clutter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- most progress made decluttering quarterly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- greatest value added to a space cleared of clutter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- best use/home found for stuff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- idea to make decluttering the MOST FUN for the most members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- idea that helps the most people who canNOT attend our Meetups to declutter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...or dream up ways to best motivate YOU, even if you may not be representative of our group, &amp;amp; come share them: you may find kindred spirits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who have requested suggestions to get started before our first Meetup, how about first analyzing what has been accumulating: does it seem most related to security (finances, job-related), sentiment (mementos), projects (reminders of to-do's), or what?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Often much of a problem can be found to be attributable to just a few causes ... e.g., 20% of the organizations  sending us junk mail may be responsible for 80% of our clutter! If we determine which are the Worst Offenders, we can tell them to remove us from their mailing lists, to help TURN OFF THE SPIGOT of junk into our lives. Bring a sample mailer from your Worst Offender to the upcoming Meetup for an opportunity to fill out a request to have your name removed from their mailing list. Then you or I will mail it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Resources I've found to be particularly helpful include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Stephanie Winston's and Julie Morgenstern's books on getting better organized&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* David Allen's book, Getting Things Done&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Disaster Masters' resources at www.disposophobia.com ... in particular, their online e-book, &amp;quot;101 Strategies to Master the Clutter,&amp;quot; helped me to progress in recent months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helpful resources (e.g., web sites, books, local services) are on our Message Board for those who may not be able to come to Meetups.  Thank you (especially to Pamela, our Assistant Organizer, who set up our Board)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IDEAS WELCOMED! You can also find me at FUPC Sunday a.m.'s to do brainstorming:  www.cambridgepres.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                  The portal of our sorrow can become our Gateway to Joy.  -- Elisabeth Elliot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                         &amp;quot;I set myself on fire, they come to watch me burn.&amp;quot; -- John Wesley&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                     Philippians 4:6-9 - Thanks in All&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please look for our Meetup signs. Bill at Panera Bread has us on their calendar now, expecting up to 25; he just asks that participants plan to spend $3-6+ each on refreshments in order to use the restaurant so long...believe me: this is a bargain!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204591847000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Look at your space/yard/vehicle: too much stuff? Or have folks commented on how much is accumulating around you? Want to change? If so -- welcome to our Meetup! Come to meet other like-minded individuals and discuss how this Meetup can most help YOU.</why><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200806521000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston-and-Beyond Decluttering Organizational Meetup</name><id>7155211</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204066800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/7155211/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/8/global_3017160.jpeg</photo_url></item>