<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Dilla Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.159979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Milford Upper Charles Trail</name><city>Milford</city><id>570593</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.516873</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our FANTASTIC, popular and very dedicated walking group is moving to Saturdays for the month of November. It has been suggested, requested and seconded to try it on this more popular weekend day! Who's ready to brave the chill? I can get the motivation if you can! The way this walking group works is: we meet at the parking lot of the Milford Bike Path (Rail Trail), say our hellos, do our group photo and head out in either direction - whatever the flavor of the week is. We stop every so often, train a new behavior, or practice a new one, walk a little more, train a little, walk a little, and you never know what we might come up with! It could be loose-leash walking, two by two, "reverse" command, or even "sit pretty!" And we ALWAYS use what is at our disposal to glean better behavior from our dogs. Bikes coming? Baby stroller? Other dogs? Time to get your dog's attention! I will personally attest to the fact that my own dog's behavior is SOOOOOOOOOOO improved since doing this walk 'n train every week. You'll be able to say the same :) It's practically a free training class PLUS a little exercise and socialization for you AND your pooch! All breeds and ages welcome. NO flexi/extendable leashes. Fear not if your dog has some issues to work through; safety first, but remember, this is what we are here for and as long as YOU are ready to work, we're happy to have you :) Hope to see you there! Bundle up; and don't forget treats!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322748951000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319765977000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Battle the Milford Rail Trail 'n Train (moved to Saturdays!)</name><id>qmfxfcyppbjc</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322328600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/39009272/</event_url></item>