<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because of a scheduling error, we are allowing interested people the opportunity to pay at the door, but seating is *VERY* limited so please arrive early!&amp;nbsp; This is a fantastic opportunity to see Joseph work at a fraction of his normal fee.&amp;nbsp; Don't miss out!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

Thursday, June 30 &amp;nbsp;7:00 pm
&lt;p&gt;The ancient Aboriginal Australian didgeridoo is capable of producing sound waves in the inaudible 0-20 Hz (Hertz) range (the same frequency range as human brain waves) with several harmonics approaching 1,000 Hz. These waves are claimed to affect the "whole" body, including your "Ethereal being," and they may relax and bring your body and mind to a state of deep self-healing and personal awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harmonic therapy has been used to aid in meditation and relaxation, and are said to act as a "tuning fork for your body's natural resonant vibration on a cellular level," according to Carringer. Reported effects from treatments range from relief of muscle pain and stress to a greater sense of clarity and heightened energy flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;Didgeridoo Journey Circle&lt;/strong&gt; offers an introduction to the therapeutic principles of the didgeridoo, and overview of shamanic journeying / meditation, how to set intention, and a discussion of healthy meditation practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presented by Joseph Carringer: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Joseph Carringer is a professional didgeridoo musician and sound therapist. In his sound therapy practice he uses only concert class didgeridoos, combining Traditional Chinese Medicine meridian and organ theory with Ayurvedic Chakra philosophies, creating a unique and powerful therapeutic sound healing experience. Joseph has been playing an Australian Aboriginal didgeridoo for over a decade, using it as a deep meditative tool in his personal shamanic journey as well as a therapeutic instrument for his clients. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please visit &lt;a href="http://www.didgetherapy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.DidgeTherapy.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a &lt;strong&gt;limited seating event&lt;/strong&gt; - Pre-Registration is required &lt;br /&gt;

Please contact Valerie Roy at &lt;a href="mailto:vroy@kripara.com"&gt;vroy@kripara.com&lt;/a&gt;, or call (603) 319-8153 to arrange. &lt;br /&gt;

Special one-time cost - &lt;strong&gt;$30&lt;/strong&gt; per person (&lt;em&gt;normally $45!) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From the I-95, take exit 3 (95 northbound) or exit 3B (southbound) to Route 33 W. The Center will be 2.6 miles on the right, at the corner of 33 and Bayside, in the Gowen's Corner Plaza. The entrance is just to the left of Bayside Custon Frame</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309540957000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309360342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Didgeridoo Journey Circle</name><id>23961841</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309474800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/23961841/</event_url></item>