<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be our very first meeting!  I'm looking forward to meeting everyone!!!  I've chosen Danehy Park in Cambridge because there's a decent amount of parking and the dogs can be off leash in a somewhat secluded area.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are directions:  &lt;br /&gt;From Boston, take Storrow Drive/Soldiers Field Road or Memorial Drive (both can be accessed from the Cambridge exit 18 off the Mass Pike) to Fresh Pond Parkway (Rtes. 2, 3 &amp;amp; 16) towards Arlington. Follow through light at intersection of Huron Avenue and past Porter Chevrolet on right to rotary with Sozio Electronics store, through rotary and immediate right onto New Street (that´s the name of the street, not the state of it´s construction) just after Sozio, Danehy Park is ahead on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From outside city, take Rte. 2 East from Rte. 95 (Rte. 128) to the Alewife T Station (can also take Rte. 16 from Arlington/Medford area), go past the train station and over the bridge towards Fresh Pond on Alewife Brook Parkway, go all the way around the rotary at the ground round to reverse direction, then turn right into the parking lot at the Fresh Pond Mall, go around to the left and past the cinema to New Street and Danehy Park behind the mall, the entrance will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to see everyone!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273539971000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1131144203000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Bulldog November Meetup</name><id>4794701</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1132423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/4794701/</event_url></item>