<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Market St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.077868</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-430-9122 </phone><name>Portsmouth Gaslight</name><city>Portsmouth </city><id>750121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757330</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Learn about ghost hunting, meet the psychic medium and review evidence at the Portsmouth Gas Light!  There will be a cash bar and you must be 21 years or older to drink.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is a Ghost? Is it somehow different from a Spirit? And can either manifest itself onto our earthly plane of existence? Join A. J. Kitt, founder of the Seacoast Paranormal Research Group and founder and lead investigator of Kitt Research Initiative, and Isabeau Esby, internationally known Psychic Medium, as they discuss the realities of hauntings and what possibilities may lurk in any home, business, or graveyard!  Paranormal evidence, both audio and visual will be presented during the lecture from a variety of ghost investigations performed in the New England area.  Are you ready to see a ghost?  Hear the dead?  If you are, join us for this informative, humorous and sometimes eerie event. &lt;br /&gt;AJ Kitt, professional artist, Mensan, and founder of the Seacoast Paranormal Research Group, has a University of New Hampshire Bachelors degree in Journalism. Together, Isabeau and Andy lecture on Spiritualism and Paranormal activity, and with a team of investigators they test the validity of claims of paranormal activity across New England.  &lt;br /&gt;*The event will take place on the third floor*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;$10.00 per person in advance, $15.00 at the door visit &lt;a href="http://www.isabeauesby.com/Isabeau_Esby/Events.html" target="_blank"&gt;www.IsabeauEsby.com&lt;/a&gt; to purchase tickets&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the third floor!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257030495000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255202464000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ghosts and Spirits at the Gaslight bar!</name><id>11596637</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256857200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/11596637/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/1/global_2599441.jpeg</photo_url></item>