<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I saw Part 2 of this masterpiece and was moved and intrigued. The movie speaks to us about war and humanity in a way that is relevant today, while illuminating the world-wide struggles from the past.  I'd love to share Part 3 with the movie group.  Here's what Wikipedia has to say about it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Human Condition is a Japanese epic film trilogy made between 1959 and 1961.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was directed by Masaki Kobayashi and stars Tatsuya Nakadai. The trilogy follows the life of Kaji, a Japanese pacifist and socialist, as he tries to survive in the fascist and oppressive world of WWII-era Japan. The character development of Kaji through the three films is considered by many to be inspirational.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first film, No Greater Love (1959) opens with Kaji marrying his sweetheart Michiko despite his misgivings about the future. The couple then move to a large mining operation in Japanese-colonized Manchuria where Kaji is a labor supervisor assigned to a workforce of Chinese prisoners. He tries and ultimately fails to reconcile his humanistic theories with the brutal reality of forced labor in an imperial system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the second film, Road to Eternity (1959), Kaji, having lost his exemption from military service by protecting Chinese prisoners from unjust punishment, has now been conscripted into the Japanese Kwantung Army. Despite his anti-militarism, Kaji excels in his training and tries to implement his ideals in his dealings with other soldiers in the face of the prevailing brutality. The film ends with the Soviet army's victorious onslaught.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The final film in the trilogy is A Soldier's Prayer (1961). The Japanese forces having been shattered, Kaji and some comrades embark on an epic journey on foot southward to where Kaji hopes to rejoin Michiko. After surviving many perils he is captured by the Red Army and subjected to treatment that echoes that meted out to the Chinese in the first film. Eventually, disappointed that Communism, which he had hoped would be a force for human liberation, seemed little better than the oppressive systems he had been struggling against all along, and still dreaming of finding his wife, Kaji escapes and faces his ultimate trial in the vast winter wasteland.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each film is divided into two parts. Altogether, the trilogy is nine hours and forty-seven minutes long, not including intermissions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The British film critic David Shipman described the trilogy in his 1983 book, The Story of Cinema, as &amp;quot;unquestionably the greatest film ever made.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm not sure if there will be time and energy to catch a bite after, but if there is, I will be happy to lead the meal and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the front of the theater on the right after the movie</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230570995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Part 3 of the Human Condition at the MFA</name><id>9402005</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231027200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9402005/</event_url></item>