<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Salisbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.273173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 799-4406 </phone><name>Worcester Art Museum</name><city>Worcester</city><id>719621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802015</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come see the magnificant floral interpretaiton of the artwork from The Worcester Art Museum's collection. It's a feast for the eyes and in the middle of winter! Presented in partnership with Tower Hill Botanical Gardens.                            &lt;br /&gt;The Museum comes alive for our 6th Annual Flora in Winter celebration. Worcester Art Museum and Tower Hill Botanic Garden collaborate to host Flora in Winter, the premier floral design event of the year. Skilled artisans from across New England create clever, provocative interpretations at both venues. It is a succulent feast for the eyes and spirit in the middle of winter! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instrumental Music&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, January 27, 12-2PM&lt;br /&gt;Selected Public Spaces&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the musical ambiance as you stroll through the Museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Museum Café Hours&lt;br /&gt;Thursday - Sunday 11AM?3PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;            &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Worcester Flora in Winter Hours at the Worcester Art Museum&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, 11AM-5PM. Museum reopens from 6-8:30PM for Flora Euphoria.&lt;br /&gt;Friday, 11AM-5PM, Saturday, 10AM-5PM*, Sunday, 11AM-5PM&lt;br /&gt;General admission: $10.00 per adult&lt;br /&gt;*There will be no free admission at the Worcester Art Museum Saturday morning, January 25, except for Museum Members. Free Saturday mornings from 10AM?noon will resume following Flora in Winter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Art Museum?s presentation of Flora in Winter is generously sponsored by Unum and Flagship Bank and Trust. Additional generous support provided by the Worcester Telegram &amp;amp; Gazette and WICN Public Radio 90.5 FM, New England?s Jazz and Folk Station.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meetup inside the Lancaster St. entrance. I will be there at 11:15 or a few minutes after. 
For those who may not know me please look for the Meetup Logo sign.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201624654000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>This is a once a year event.</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199638340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FLORA IN WINTER '08 @ The WAM</name><id>7044814</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201451400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7044814/</event_url></item>