<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Porter Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.389165</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Red Line T Station</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>683976</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Car pooling: Meet at Porter Sq. T stop 9 AM. We will be at Rumney at roughly 11:30 AM.  Look for us in the big parking lot.  Google Rumney for directions to the climbing spot.  I'll give better directions in the next couple of days.  When you RSVP, please tell us whether you can offer people rides.  If you can offer rides, please also mention (a) how many rides you can offer, and (b) where people would need to meet you to get a ride.  Also please mention whether you have a rope and/or a rack of quickdraws that you can bring.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rumney is pretty much all lead climbing.  Most routes can be top-roped after someone else has led it, but few of the cliff tops can be accessed by trail.   At Rumney smaller groups of climbers can often get in much more climbing than larger groups.  Ideally, we will organize things so people (a) know and trust each other, (b) collectively have the gear and skills they need to climb, and (c) can climb together all day long (so no one accidentally gets left behind!).  If you are brand-new to the meetup, please contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You will need to bring:&lt;/b&gt; your personal climbing gear (harness, belay device, shoes, helmet if you have one), a rope and rack, if you have them, food and water for the day, $$$ for your share of gas, and possibly for dinner afterwards.  It may be a bit chilly still when we first get there.  Be prepared for that, and dress in layers.  The approach trails are short, but often steep and dirty, so wear hiking boots if you think you'll need them.  I'll be wearing my trail runners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special note:  If you want to just hang out and get sun or swim in the small river below you are more than welcome.  People can make this into a party if they like. But I will not try to find you if you get lost on a trail. All of this is at your own risk.  Bad weather &lt;b&gt;will not&lt;/b&gt; cancel unless it is raining buckets.Have fun.&lt;br /&gt;Geoff&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Cell phone 617 501-6217.  You can also text me - might work better in NH.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Geoff</member_name><member_id>3444525</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214244954000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Rumney is hands-down the best sport climbing area anywhere near Boston, and arguably the best east of the Mississippi.  Wow, you should totally show up!</why><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213617014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rumney! </name><id>8151329</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214053200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/8151329/</event_url></item>