<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8th Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.374149</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pier 6</name><city>Charlestown </city><id>1615109</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052010</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us as we sail around beautiful Boston harbor for two hours (4-6pm) with Captain Don aboard the private charter sailboat, Tupelo Honey. The boat can have a max of 12 people and must have a min. of 10 guests to run. Guests can bring food and beverages (including alcohol)- so feel free to bring drinks and snacks. This is going to be a wonderful time, so be sure to join us! What a wonderful way to spend part of your Memorial Day weekend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come Sail Away Now is giving our group a special discounted rate of $41 for the 2 hour harbor cruise. They are holding spots for us until May 7- if 12 people from our Meet Up group haven't purchased their tickets by May 7,  they will open it up to the general public. Lets make this a private cruise just for our group, so get your tickets early! &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You MUST get your tickets in advance at:  &lt;a href="http://www.comesailawaynow.com/Purchase_Boston_Harbor_Tour.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.comesailawaynow.com/Purchase_Boston_Harbor_Tour.html&lt;/a&gt;  Click on the drop-down button on the "purchase harbor tour" link (located above the Add to Cart button) and select the Meet Up special ticket price. &lt;/strong&gt; If you can not attend, tickets can be transferred to someone else. In case of inclement weather, the tour will be rescheduled. Please be sure to bring layers of clothing in case it gets chilly on the water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Captain Don is a US Coast Guard Licensed Master. He is certified to captain a motor, towing, or sailing vessel of up to 50 tons in near coastal waters. Check out their website for more info: &lt;a href="http://comesailawaynow.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://comesailawaynow.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tupelo Honey is located at Pier 6 Charlestown, Massachusetts, near Tavern on the Water. It is easily accessible and very easy to drive, walk or take a ferry.  There are T-Boats run by the MBTA and for only $1.70, you can use this ferry to take a ride from Central/Long Wharf to Pier 3. From there it is only a 5 minute walk to Pier 6.  Visit the MBTA's website for more information on prices and schedules on the T-Boats&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine near the sailboat. If you have trouble finding us, please call 774 232 0000.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306806094000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Enjoy Saturday afternoon cruising Boston harbor on a private charter sailboat. Bring your own food and beverages and relax!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303267708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Memorial Day Weekend, Harbor Cruise on Private Charter Sailboat, Discounted Tix</name><id>17368217</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306611900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/17368217/</event_url></item>