<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Members-Free, Non-members</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The NEREIA Welcomes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DON DEROSA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Subject To” – Owner Financing that’s Safe, Quick and Easy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don DeRosa’s presentation on buying ‘Subject To’ covers the major steps any real estate investor needs to follow in order to buy houses quickly and easily, especially in this market. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don will discuss how you can buy an unlimited number of houses if you learn some crucial, yet simple techniques that made him successful.  Don has found that the key to making a fortune in real estate, having bought over 200 houses in the last few years, is to avoid using his own money or credit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By utilizing the existing financing, or what’s commonly called “Subject To,” investors can act quickly and don’t have to go to the bank to buy the property.  And you get the benefits of ownership– including cash flow, appreciation, tax benefits and profits from the sale – because you own the property.  You’re in control. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the end of Don’s presentation, you’ll know&lt;br /&gt;• how any person can set themselves up for success by following a systematized approach.   &lt;br /&gt;• how to find motivated sellers and have them call you!&lt;br /&gt;• how to prescreen sellers so you don’t waste your time or end up a motivated seller yourself&lt;br /&gt;• how to make offers with complete confidence – knowing how much you can offer and how much you’ll make&lt;br /&gt;• how to find all the private money you need to buy all the houses you want, and&lt;br /&gt;• how to sell quickly to reap the profits and stuff cash in your pockets each month&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By learning the key techniques Don will share, investors have unlimited potential for building wealth with real estate to attain financial freedom.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie Trajlinek</member_name><member_id>4673573</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244059667000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nereia</urlname><id>593272</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238630710000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association May Meetup</name><id>10092839</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241650800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nereia/events/10092839/</event_url></item>