<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be discussing current events at the local and national levels, election results and what happens next in terms of our future party activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would also like to ask all of you, even if you can't make it to the meeting, to let me know WHY..  We have been meeting for quite a long time now, and I have seen very few of you at the meeting.  While it makes for a nice evening out, two or three people in attendance doesn't really make for a very fun or interesting meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can I do to try and make it possible for more of you to attend?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is it the time? - Would you prefer earlier or later?  (Note that one frequent attendee is from Worcester, and would have trouble making it very much earlier)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is it the place?  - I am open to alternative locations, although the Outback has been very good to us.  One of the reasons that I like the Outback is that it is very easily accessible from both Rt 3 and 495 - since we have an attendee from Worcester, I'd like to keep it easy for him to find, and minimize the amount of time he has to spend off the highway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is it the day of the week? - Weekends are often a problem for me, and as a Town Meeting member in Billerica, I chose the fourth Tuesday date in order to minimize the impact of the various meetings I attend in that role.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is it something else? - Feedback as to what everybody needs and wants would really help me out...  Currently I'm planning to keep this meeting as scheduled, but I'm open to trying something else in August.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ART&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the Hostess for the "Lowell Area Liberty Association"  Important note - please RSVP so that I can tell the restaraunt how many to expect, and get an appropriate size table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>7353328</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251245396000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-413</urlname><id>1175394</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2900009155</group_lon><name>The Route 495 Area Libertarian Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245805448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Route 495 Area Libertarian July Meetup</name><id>10721069</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248825600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-413/events/10721069/</event_url></item>