<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>252 Buckland St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.804916</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Buckland Hills Mall Commuter Parking Lot</name><city>Manchester</city><id>6099582</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.554451</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join the CT Liberty Revolution as we sign wave for the only presidential candidate who will Restore America Now at the classic "Buckland Hills Mall" location. This was our go-to spot for Ron Paul waves in '07/'08 and offers plenty of corners and traffic. The sign wave begins at noon and will last until around 4 or until the last sign waver decides they're done. You can park in the nearby commuter lot and easily walk to the intersection. Specifically, we are waving at the intersection that leads to Lowe's and Home Depot, the one across from the Olive Garden. We've got until April 24th to let as many people know about the best candidate for president as possible, we aren't even close to done here in CT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit: The map previously incorrectly listed the address for the commuter lot as further up the mall than it is. The sign wave itself will be at the intersection of Buckland Street and Buckland Hills Drive. The meeting place is in the commuter lot that's behind the old John Harvard's restaurant (now the Tullycross Tavern) and the Mobil station (with the Dunkin' Donuts in it). As always please give 860-730-3RON a call if you're having trouble finding us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We cannot allow the controlled media to stop our momentum, there are still over 30 states that have not yet held their state nominating primary. Feeling dejected and hopeless is PRECISELY what the establishment is hoping we'll do. I plan to show them that we are in this for the long haul and that right will eventually trump wrong if we keep fighting for the ideals that this country was founded on and never give up.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331487212000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331242323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buckland Hills Mall Sunday Sign Wave</name><id>55558122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331481600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/55558122/</event_url></item>