<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Long Pond Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.133976</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-312-6735</phone><name>Peters Foam Home</name><city>Durham</city><id>1250419</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.926445</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us for an outdoor barbecue. There will be a gas grill and a campfire available as well as a couple of burners and an oven inside. Bring hamburgers, hotdogs, or whatever you'd like to cook. We will be playing board games inside, so bring your games. Come see my new home that I built with my own 2 hands. I will be explaining the fundamentals of this super energy efficient house. The first floor is complete and I am now living in my own homebuilt home. I will be having some classes here this summer on how to build a solar hot water heater for under a hundred dollars. As well as classes on building a bio-gas power plant, a hydroelectric generator, and home built wind generator.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come out and party with the us and meet new people and have fun!.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Long Pond Road/Drive is not yet in GPS the house and road is so new that people don't know where I am yet, so use 12 Hampshire Avenue which is next to Long Pond. Look for the tiki torches and Meetup sign. It's a long driveway and the house is at the end--Park along the drive near the house. Bring chairs if you have them. Bring wood if you have any! &lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Will be joined by other meetup groups! &lt;br /&gt;Peter &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272926406000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271763072000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adventures in Outdoor Cooking Night / Game Night! </name><id>13234749</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272753000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/13234749/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/6/global_14521030.jpeg</photo_url></item>