<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This hike is one of the best in the White Mountains and one of our favorites.  It is a great hike for intermediates and advanced hikers alike.  It offers great views and is truly a wonderful hike.  This hike is meant to be enjoyable for everyone and we will be taking at least two breaks above treeline so that people can eat, take pictures and just generally enjoy the fantastic views.  Please note that there are some steep spots on both the ascend and descent trails.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total mileage and estimated times are 8.8 miles and 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route Summary   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a loop hike starting and ending at the Lafayette Place parking area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Start out on Falling Waters Trail (which for the first 0.2 mile is also the same trail as the Old Bridle Path). &lt;br /&gt;• After 0.2 mile, turn right to stay on Falling Waters Trail and follow that until its on Little Haystack Mountain, 3.2 miles from the parking area. &lt;br /&gt;• From the end of Falling Waters Trail, turn left onto Franconia Ridge Trail. &lt;br /&gt;• Follow Franconia Ridge Trail 0.7 mile up to the summit of Mt. Lincoln. &lt;br /&gt;• Continue on Franconia Ridge Trail, down the other side of Mt. Lincoln, for 0.9 which will put you on Mt. Lincoln's summit. &lt;br /&gt;• From Mt. Lincoln, turn left to descend on Greenleaf Trail. &lt;br /&gt;• Follow Greenleaf Trail for 1.1 miles until reaching Greenleaf Hut and Eagle Lakes. &lt;br /&gt;• Turn left to get on Old Bridle Path. &lt;br /&gt;• Follow Old Bridle Path for 2.9 miles all the way back to the parking lot (upon reaching the junction with Falling Waters Trail, turn right). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, since weather conditions can change rapidly above treeline, please bring a wool hat, mittens/gloves and multiple layers of clothing to wear.  At this time of year it can be rather warm or cool, so please be prepared.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, or I can provide any additional information, please let me know.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>DIANNE AND I WILL BE IN A BLACK FOUR DOOR ECHO WITH MAINE LICENSE PLATES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222776675000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220894844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Lafayette, Mt. Lincoln, Little Haystack Mtn.</name><id>8714633</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222603200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8714633/</event_url></item>