<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1/4 mile from Mt Cranmore</address_2><address_1>Kearsarge Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.063870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ski Wheelers Ski Club</name><city>North Conway</city><id>597153</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/3/3/event_4153107.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canoe / Kayak Party weekend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, July,22, 23,24,th,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcoming Party 6 pm. to 11pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ski Wheelers&amp;rsquo; Ski Lodge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;N. Conway NH. ADULTS ONLY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry, but the RSVP deadline is July 9th..&amp;nbsp; Total inclusive price $133.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make your check to Wayne P.. Not to the Ski Wheelers! Host:Wayne .603-421-0822 wc.potter@comcast.net Send check &amp;amp; form to:3 Angus Ave Londonderry,NH 03053&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-Host: Steve Obermiller ob@tds.net 603-491-1962&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-Host: Steve O. wrote: Last year Wayne Potter from Ski Wheelers Lodge invited me up for this fantastic weekend. So, I ask him if I could bring some friends? So, we had 37 from Meetup join us. Out of the 85 who went down river with us. So please join me and my friends for a weekend you will not forget. This is a fun filled weekend of meeting new people, and discovering new ways to enjoy the great outdoors on the cheep. Total Cost is $133. and that includes meals, and your canoe or kayak rental. Take $25 off, if you bring your own boat? The weekend is $85.+Lodging $48 for Friday &amp;amp; Saturday nights. If you would like to stay with us? Total again price $133. The lodge is clean, up to six people in one room and a lot like camping indoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will boat down the Soco Riveron Saturday morning. The skill level required for this river, is that your beer and wine should be cooled the night before. Also, you will need a good gun. They have river pirates on this river. Some of those pirates are almost six years old. So, a good water gun is really needed to keep from being hosed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOST: Wayne P. wrote: Join us Friday night for our happy hour and meet and greet. Saturday 9 am. a day of floating down the river. 7 am. 2 breakfasts / picnic lunch on the river.&amp;nbsp; lobster, steak,or chicken dinner. Friday, 7:30-11pm Check in, get settled, and join us for a welcoming get together. Friday, We will have snacks, beer or wine for all. Saturday 7:00 am Meet in the dining room for a make-your-own breakfast (breakfast foods provided). Pack your coolers&amp;mdash;lunch foods and drinks will be provided to make a picnic lunch. 8:40 am Leave lodge for Northern Extremes (formerly Saco Canoe), Rte 16, Conway. 9:00 am Must be at Northern Extremes for 9:00 am shuttle. LIMITED space on shuttle. Those with their own canoe/kayak should car pool to put-in and arrange for a ride back to take-out. Lunch on the river, sun, laughs, water battles, swimming!!! 3-6 pm.. Volleyball, pool,darts, socializing, or relaxing after a hard day on the river. 7:00 pm Feast of lobster, steak, and BBQ chicken at the Ski Wheelers lodge. 9:00-1am Informal party at the Ski Wheelers! Music, dance, pool, (BYOB). Sunday Wake up to fresh coffee and have breakfast at your leisure. Enjoy the day&amp;mdash;hike, bike, shop, take a river swim, or hang out and get to know your new friends! What to bring: &amp;bull; A small cooler &amp;bull; A sweatshirt or fleece. It can get cool and windy on the river. Allow for the possibility of rain and bring foul weather gear (we go even if it rains!) &amp;bull; A dry bag or a large zip-lock bag to keep things dry (such as your camera) &amp;bull; An arsenal of water-ejecting weaponry (please NO water balloons) &amp;bull; Insect repellent and SUNSCREEN &amp;bull; Beach towel, bathing suit, watershoes/sandals or old sneakers &amp;bull; A sleeping bag or linens and blankets, pillow, and bath towel (members remind your guests) &amp;bull; Your sense of adventure, a willingness to help out, and your sense of humor!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve O. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311376930000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308249454000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canoe/Kayak Party Weekend</name><id>22452051</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311372000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/22452051/</event_url></item>