<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 York St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.309032</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>GPSCY</name><city>New Haven</city><id>448087</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.931210</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>So maybe it's because of its fragrant aroma.  Maybe it's because of the gorgeous color.  Or maybe it's just because like my love of needlepoint and bingo, I share many common interests with old women.  Regardless of the explanation though.... I adore scotch.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In my free time, I work at GPSCY (Graduate &amp;amp; Professional Student Center at Yale) (www.gpscy.net) which is this neat Yale graduate-student run bar.  The average clientele is 23-35 (emphasis in the middle) but people 21+ are welcome (ID is a must).  They generally like it if you are part of the Yale community or with someone from Yale, but that's not necessarily a requirement if you seem respectable enough. (You can say you're with me - unless you're creepy.  Or an angry drunk. Then leave me out if it.) : P &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This seems like a fun class.  They'll be tasting several scotches with an emphasis on single malts.  Off the top of my head, I believe they said Macallen 18 (that's the reason I'm coming!), Balvennie (I don't remember the year, probably 12), Johnnie Walker Green (This is a blended whiskey, but it's blended from single-malt vats - it's pretty good) and I believe at least 3 others.  The fee is $25 cash (though there is an atm on premises). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I may not be there at the dot of 7pm, but I will be there shortly there after.  RSVP so I can look out for you.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPSCY is literally located in the middle of a block - the block surrounded by Chapel, Park, and York.  It's really close! I'll be happy to provide more explicit directions later if there is interest. Feel free to call my cell: 203-314-4329.  It's like a minute walk from the Yale Rep so I could always lead you from there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More detailed info ? coming from Park, go past 217 Park street, Yale Cabaret, (slightly set back from the street on a paved pathway, past the Afro Culture building.  Keep walking, and right after you go through an archway, there is a gothic looking wooden door directly to your right.  You?ve arrived! The official address is 204 York St.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from York, walk up from Chapel. Turn onto the first driveway on your left that is not blocked by construction.  Follow the building that is now on your left (it will feel as if you?re slightly back-tracking) until you are facing 204 York St.  (The above mentioned archway will be diagonally to your right.  The door directly before the archway is where you want to go) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It sounds more complicated than it is, trust me.  If you have trouble just call me or flag down a Yalie and ask where GPSCY (pronounced Gypsy) and/or Gryphon?s Pub is.  Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact is Devorah 203-314-4329&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197331436000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196963662000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scotch Tasting</name><id>6867826</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197158400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6867826/</event_url></item>