<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><fee><label>Donation at the door</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for non-members only</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us at our May meeting where we will be joined once again by actor Richard Clark who will be performing &lt;span&gt;his one-man show &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clarence Darrow&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Attorney Clarence Darrow defended the Tennessee high school teacher John Scopes in the 1925 "Scopes Monkey Trial." Scopes was charged with violating a state law that barred public schools from teaching the theory of evolution.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Clark developed Clarence Darrow from his own research, and incorporated books and letters about the trial and the work of other playwrights. The Clark version depicts an intense courtroom drama with some comic elements. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;"This play features intense court room drama and comic relief as it highlights the life and times of ClarenceDarrow, attorney extraordinaire and defender of the downtrodden and the damned. From his youthfulinnocence in small town Ohio to the embattled national stage of the “Scopes Monkey Trial” and Leopoldand Loeb court rooms, it is a roller coaster ride into the heart and mind of a complex American Hero."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Richard Clark is an actor with over thirty years of experience in New England regional theater, New York Theater and television. He is a graduate of Clark University and studied at the American Academy of Dramatic Art, The Actor’s Connection, and the Actor’s Loft in New York City. His Keeping History Alive series brings historical figures such as Mark Twain, Andrew Carnegie, Clarence Darrow, John Barrymore, Ernest Hemingway and William Shakespeare back to life. His shows are based on biographies, autobiographies personal letters, books and the works of various playwrights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program is scheduled to start at 7 at the UU Church of Worcester, with doors opening at 6:30 for socializing and conversation. We are asking nonmembers for a donation of $5 to help cover costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please watch this page for updates and changes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368731748000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362252645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Meeting: Richard Clark performs his one man act "Clarence Darrow"</name><id>107253882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368572400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/107253882/</event_url></item>