<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Barber Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.298023</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>+15088536015</phone><name>Higgins Amory Museum</name><city>Worcester</city><id>603221</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.798630</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come join your fellow Humanists on a trip to visit the Higgins Armory! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Higgins Armory Museum is a nonprofit educational institution that presents the history of arms and armor in a broad cultural context. The Museum achieves its mission by preserving, researching, exhibiting, and interpreting its collections for the benefit of the general public and specialized audiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission, tour, and live show is only $7 per person! Plus we get a 45 minute guided tour, so be sure to come along &amp;amp; bring some friends!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the &lt;a href="http://www.higgins.org/home.php" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;A visit to the Higgins Armory Museum will spark the imagination of visitors of all ages with arms and armor ranging from ancient Greek Corinthian helmets to ornate suits of armor crafted at the height of the Renaissance. Informative and entertaining demonstrations and programs bring to life arms and armor from around the world and across centuries!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Constructed in 1930 by John Woodman Higgins to house his elaborate and eclectic collection of arms and armor, The Higgins Armory Museum opened to the public in 1931 in a sleek state-of-the-art glass and steel building. Today, artifacts are arranged gallantly in a spectacular two-story Medieval Great Hall arranged with more than 35 suits of armor and a stunning array of arms amidst tapestries, stained glass, and soaring ceilings.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Lackey</member_name><member_id>7618967</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285459135000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280089687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Humanist Excursion - Higgins Armory Museum Trip/Tour</name><id>14209005</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284912000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/14209005/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/2/global_7423922.jpeg</photo_url></item>