<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Summer is almost here, with thoughts of barbecue and burning things, so . . . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Sam Raimi (Spider-Man trilogy, Evil Dead series) returns to the horror genre with 'Drag Me To Hell,' an original tale of a young woman's desperate quest to break an evil curse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine Brown (Alison Lohman) is an ambitious L.A. loan officer with a charming boyfriend, professor Clay Dalton (Justin Long). Life is good until the mysterious Mrs. Ganush (Lorna Raver) arrives at the bank to beg for an extension on her home loan. Should Christine follow her instincts and give the old woman a break? Or should she deny the extension to impress her boss, Mr. Jacks (David Paymer), and get a leg-up on a promotion? Christine fatefully chooses the latter, shaming Mrs. Ganush and dispossessing her of her home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In retaliation, the old woman places the powerful curse of the Lamia on Christine, transforming her life into a living hell. Haunted by an evil spirit and misunderstood by a skeptical boyfriend, she seeks the aid of seer Rham Jas (Dileep Rao) to save her soul from eternal damnation. To help the shattered Christine return her life to normal, the psychic sets her on a frantic course to reverse the spell. As evil forces close in, Christine must face the unthinkable: how far will she go to break free of the curse?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Alison Lohman, Justin Long, Lorna Raver, David Paymer, Dileep Rao, and Jessica Lucas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:25, so let's plan on meeting around 7 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need directions - I will email my cell to all yes and maybe RSVPs mid-day the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, if there is interest, we'll head to Friday's or John Harvard's for food, drinks and conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244936997000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244140359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drag Me To Hell</name><id>10576664</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244674800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10576664/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/4/global_8974100.jpeg</photo_url></item>