<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 New Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.387730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 9219922</phone><name>Basha Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>904055</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.140850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We continue our conversa e musica meetups on October 20, with Brazilian music and conversation in as much Portuguese as we can! Basha Cafe is an ideal place for a meetup. It's a lovely restaurant with Middle Eastern food--beautiful decor, good food, and the tables are even already set up perfectly for a meetup! There's also space for dancing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've scheduled some of the best players and singers of Brazilian music in Boston for Tuesdays in October, to make the nights a feast for the ears, as well as the appetite! The bands play all different kinds of music with Brazilian roots, so you can expand your knowledge of the music of Brazil at the same time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the deal: we meet at 7:00 for eats/drinks and conversa; music starts around 8. There's NO COVER; you just need to buy something to eat or drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On October 20 we have a special Brazilian double-bill! Starting at 8:00, I'll be singing Brazilian bossa novas, sambas, and MPB (musica popular brasileira), featuring the music of great composers like Jobim, Chico Buarque, Djavan, Rosa Passos, and João Donato, accompanied by the excellent guitarist Steve Kirby (you can check out the music at www.myspace.com/evelynrosenthal). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then at 9:30 we turn over the stage to the wonderful Brazilian singer/composer/guitarist Fernando Holz. Fernando will present his own exciting versions of bossa nova and other Brazilian favorites, as well as some of his beautiful originals (you can hear a few on his MySpace page: www.myspace.com/fernandoholz). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots of free parking around the restaurant; 10-15 minute walk from Alewife T. New Street is behind the Fresh Pond shopping Center, off Concord Ave. Also bus no. 74 from Harvard Square (Bennett Alley stop--near Charles Hotel).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Espero que todos venham!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will put a "Portuguese Meetup" sign on the table, so look for it!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evelyn</member_name><member_id>4577146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256338468000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255807627000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conversa e Musica at Basha Cafe</name><id>11649318</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256079600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/11649318/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/c/global_1153820.jpeg</photo_url></item>