<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Those of you who have been involved in a healing circle before know how extremely powerful they can be when attended with purity of intention. If you have not participated previously in a healing circle, you will discover how Sacred Medicine and group support can work on very deep levels, inviting connection, renewal, healing and and transformation beyond our wildest dreams. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will call on the medicine of the Sacred Directions, Heaven and Earth energy, and Source, along with the power within ourselves, to invoke healing and renewal for this New Year filled with promise. With the support of the group, we will exhale our negative patterns and emotions from the past year into a stick and throw it into the Sacred Fire, releasing and cleansing our energy bodies of these scars.  We will individually receive healing from the group, helping us to manifest our intentions for positive transformation , moving forward with strong purpose.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who have been attending Monday evening meditation and received healing energy are aware of  how intensely powerful  and pure this regular group's loving energy can be. We welcome all who don't attend meditation on a regular basis to attend this healing ceremony and experience the benefits of this group, even if it is only this once to support your resolutions and intentions for the New Year. Those who have been coming on a regular basis are encouraged to bring guests who you  feel could benefit . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is suggested that you fast or eat very lightly before this very Sacred Ceremony, drink lots of water, and leave trivial and mundane conversation outside of this space. Dress warmly, with hats, gloves  and warm layers. The fire will provide comfort and warmth, but we will be outside for 20 minutes to a half hour. We will then proceed inside for a hot liquid refreshment, and conclude with a meditation inside the warmth of the inn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you cannot attend this powerful group invocation, but would like to play an active part in this incredible time of earth changes and healing energy, please contact us to schedule a private group healing ceremony at your convenience.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come into the house quietly via the left side driveway door, and we will quietly proceed outside after all are assembled.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sally Fiore</member_name><member_id>8203589</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263531128000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262539101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sacred Healing Circle and Fire Ceremony</name><id>12206138</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262649600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/12206138/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>