<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Patriot Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02035</zip><lat>42.093291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 543 1776</phone><name>Gilette Stadium</name><city>Foxborough</city><id>897737</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.263617</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>pair</description><amount>400.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>PLEASE READ CAREFULLY. I bought 4 tickets for the game. I am using 2. So that leaves 2 for someone else. Fantastic seats! 10th yard line on the visitor side. Section 128 Row 5. I opted to go for an early buy opportunity so I purchased these through ACE tickets. This game will sell out fast so do not wait. In past years, I have had no luck in buying tickets for a regular season game. They would go on sale and by the time I get through to ticketmaster, they are gone. Even via online. &lt;br /&gt;I will even save you the service and handliing charges. The cost is $400 for the pair. Get someone to go with you and it is $200 each. PLEASE make you plan to pay up front for the tickets before you RSVP yes. Last time I had to turn people down and reopen RSVP a few times, because people were not prepared to pay when saying yes. So lets cut down on the email traffic and think before you say yes. Much appreciated :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Agree to pay in full when before you RSVP yes, and I will mail you you.r tickets as soon as I get them from ACE Tickets</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285595074000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Funseeker</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>nefunseekers</urlname><id>1277691</id><group_lat>42.0299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>Funseekers!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272930477000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PATS vs Bills</name><id>13374208</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285520400000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nefunseekers/events/13374208/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/9/7/global_9919431.jpeg</photo_url></item>