<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Beginning at 6:00 PM we will have an organizational meeting. Please email 9-11-270@meetup.com for any ideas you may have on the agenda. Some possible agenda items are about nominating and voting for forthcoming films, events, actions. This event is being organized by Jonathan Mark. Stephen Goodale is stepping down as an organizer of this group, and we will be seeking another resource coordinator and treasurer. We will also be choosing another film to show for our April 30th meetup. One film that could be considered is a dramatic 9/11 film called &lt;a href="http://www.reflectingpoolfilm.com/" target="_blank"&gt;THE REFLECTING POOL&lt;/a&gt;. The group makes its decisions based on majority vote.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginning at 7:00 PM we will show the film, &lt;a href="http://communitycurrency.org/911TV/empirical.html" target="_blank"&gt;9/11: LET'S GET EMPIRICAL&lt;/a&gt;, which is a David Ray Griffin 's presentation based on his book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Debunking-11-Mechanics-Defenders-Conspiracy/dp/156656686X" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;Debunking 9/11 Debunking:&lt;/a&gt;: An Answer to Popular Mechanics and Other Defenders of the Official Conspiracy Theory.&amp;quot; This film was not shown at the February meetup due to weather problems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on empirical analysis, Dr. Griffin brilliantly shows that most objections to the alternative theory, according to which 9/11 was an inside job, are based on purely a priori arguments and a propagandistic use of the term &amp;quot;conspiracy theory,&amp;quot; showing that if we get empirical about 9/11, we can quickly see that the official story cannot be true. This film is of a David Ray Griffin presentation in Seattle, Washington in May 2007,  and illustrated with graphics and video clips.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film there will open discussions. At a previous meetup, Frank from Berkshire 9/11 Truth mentioned that their showing the History Channels put-down-film of the 9/11 Truth movement actually did more to convince attendees of Government complicity than the new Loose Change film. So, we will consider, if we get a copy, to screen this film too. Due to weather problems, these films were not shown during the February meetup.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The meeting for Valley 9/11 Truth begins at 6:00 PM in the community meeting space of the Media Education Foundation, which is the back of the building of the Woodstar Cafe.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205532306000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203029215000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11: LET'S GET EMPIRICAL - film &amp; discussion!</name><id>7332793</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205359200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/7332793/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/9/a/global_3047274.jpeg</photo_url></item>