<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>route 165</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02822</zip><lat>41.587753</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Arcadia Management Area</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1305681</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.709370</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;You better believe I’m heading back to Arcadia… &lt;em&gt;especially&lt;/em&gt; after getting my very first glimpse of the thing that has so successfully eluded me thus far; my Bigfoot, my Yeti, my Chupacabra… my White Whale!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;That’s right folks, you read it right. The last time out, I got a brief look of my ghost (meaning my fitness), and I intend to return this Wednesday to see if I can't steal another looksie. And should I be lucky, I might even get close enough to look into its eyes. But that’s a dreamer’s dream. Thou my head may be in the clouds, my feet will be on the ground, planted firmly on my pedals, as I race among the pines looking to corner that cunning shadow of mine.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Ahhh!!! But do not despair, I do have one thing going for me... "My Sighting." Over the last week, I took it upon myself to commission the talents of a local sketch artist to render a likeness of my ghost, and after hours and hours of exhaustive effort, I submit the following…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/5/c/event_146478012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As you can see my ghost is no fool. Notice the wily look on its face, the steely eyes, the crafty brows that hide a calculating wit. The bow tie. The suspenders. D&lt;em&gt;on’t let the “deer-caught-in-the-headlights” look fool you; that is part of its cunning.&lt;/em&gt; My ghost is no fool. Remember, it has been a very very long time since it was last seen. And that my friends, speaks volumes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Ride:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Once again, we'll meet at the Frosty Hollow Pond parking area &lt;em&gt;(a 3/4 mile drive up the dirt road from the intersection of Rt 165 &amp;amp; Frosty Hollow Rd),&lt;/em&gt; and once a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;gain we’ll assemble our rides, before heading out to ride some sweet sweet single-track.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The plan is to ride rings around Arcadia, keeping us out in the woods for up to two hours. Single track is our goal, but fire roads will be graciously accepted. And should our legs give out, or darkness settle in, we’ll take advantage of the trails or fire roads that will return us to our cars in the shortest amount of time and/or the least amount of effort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/d/6/event_143799382.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;On trail you can expect to experience a combination of fire roads and single-track, passing through forests and fields, over varied terrain, from smooth to rough, over rocks and roots, gravel and dirt which will require a bit of technical skill. But no worries, because we will be following The Unwritten Primary Rules of Mountain Biking: 1. We ride as a group; 2. We hike what we cannot ride; and 3. We wait at all major trailheads. Our pace will be moderate and accommodating (no speedsters here), but, you should know that the ride is filled with a number of short steep up and downs, and I ask that you believe yourself to be an intermediately skilled rider, or a fit beginner/intermediate rider willing to be challenged by the terrain. I will be riding a rigid single-speed (no shocks) w/ flat pedals, so my pace will not be blazing (thou my skills are pretty hot), nor will I be riding up every climb (I blame the single-speed); that my friends is for another time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;From the intersection of Rt 3 and Rt 165, follow Rt 165 east for approximately 2.75 miles. Turn right into Frosty Hollow Rd (dirt road @ the white church) and continue for .75 miles, turning right into a small parking area just after the small fishing pond.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Google Maps: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=41.587755,+-71.709374&amp;amp;daddr=41.587755,+-71.709374&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=41.587748,-71.709352&amp;amp;spn=0.004646,0.009162&amp;amp;sll=41.587716,-71.700554&amp;amp;sspn=0.148678,0.293198&amp;amp;geocode=FSuUegIdQs25-w%3BFSuUegIdQs25-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=17"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=@41.576874,-71.702774"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Coordinates: 41.587755, -71.709374&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Frosty Hollow Pond parking area (3/4 of a mile North of Rt 165 &amp; the white church); call if you can't find us. Cell: 860-460-1500</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>11024921</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344472611000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343947563000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike Arcadia: Again???</name><id>76085722</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344461400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/76085722/</event_url></item>