<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt. 102</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02830</zip><lat>41.965806</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crystal Lake Country Club </name><city>Burrillville</city><id>1193833</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.645019</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Burrillville RI:  The Rhode Isalnd Voter Coalition (RIVC) is pleased to announce our 4th Meet The Candidates Forum scheduled for FEBUARY 24, 2010.  This event will feature participants for state and federal offices.  The event will be held at the Crystal Lake Country Club Rt. 102 Burrillville, RI.  Doors open at 6:30pm and the Forum are scheduled to begin at 7:00pm that evening.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Rhode Island Voter Coalition is a non-partisan alliance of groups and individuals within the state that have entered into a compact to participate in the electoral process not merely by voting, but also by keeping in touch with their representatives throughout the year and to holding them accountable for actions taken or not taken in hopes of improving both the state and federal governments. RIVC is not a fund raising tool nor do they offer any endorsement.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The February meeting is intended as a forum wherein interested voter can vet the candidates who are campaigning for a wide array of offices in this year's election.  Candidates were invited regardless of their party affiliations or their status as either incumbents or challengers.  &amp;quot;We are a non-partisan group of citizens who have determined that our government and our political parties no longer represent us and we want a say in which candidates will be on the ballot in the primaries and in November 2010&amp;quot;  asserted Steve Wright, one of the group’s organizers.  “The object is to get started as early as possible so that voters have as many chances as possible to see and hear the candidates that wish to represent them”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Tassoni Jr. was invited but when he was told David Bibeault, his opponent would be there he said &amp;quot;not interested” and hung up.  Candidate for Secretary of State Leo Raptakis and Secretary of State Ralph Mollis were invited and both declined.  RIVC has also invited William Lynch, Patrick Lynch, Frank Caprio, and David Cicilline and is waiting for replies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Moderate Party participated in RIVC’s last forum and was invited to participate on the 24th.  “The Moderate Party has accepted our invitation and will be sending one or more candidates to meet with the Voters in Burrillville” said Wright.  “We welcome their participation and will provide an updated list of candidates participating in the forum later this week.   This has been a difficult event to plan due to the all of the recent announcements of candidates running for the 1st Congressional District, as well as today’s announcement that Ken Block of the Moderate Party will be joining the field of candidates in Rhode Island’s gubernatorial race.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For details contact Steven Wright by telephone at 401.615-9704, or E-Mail the Rhode Island Voter Coalition at steve@rhodeislandvotercoalition.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Running for US Congress, RI District 1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Loughlin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gubernatorial Candidates&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Robitialle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lincoln Chafee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And statewide seats &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; David Bibeault Dist. 22&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian C Newbury Dist. 48&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Crystal Lake Country Club&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rt. 102 Burrillville RI 02826&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: 7pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DATE: February 24th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RIVC events are FREE and open to the publi&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve</member_name><member_id>9369684</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347732910000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers</urlname><id>1425841</id><group_lat>41.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Oath Keepers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266460975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet the Candidates Forum February 24, 2010</name><id>12634218</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267056000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Oath-Keepers/events/12634218/</event_url></item>