<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Sorry this is extremely last minute, but I was surprised to see no other Film meetup this weekend.  Better a late post than none at all, right?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I heard good things about this one, if bleak and disturbing, and it won't be at Kendall for long, according to the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the official description about Gomorrah:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Matteo Garrone's epic, mesmerizing tour-de-force about Naples' infamous Camorra was a critical sensation at the 2008 Cannes Film Festival, where it won the Grand Prize. A sweeping drama with documentary-like realism, Gomorrah explores the mafia's vice-like hold on all aspects of life in the regions of Naples and Caserta (where the film was shot), as well as its creeping influence on international business and government. The film weaves together five stories of ordinary people forced to reckon with the heavy hand of the Camorra, where every decision, great or small, is a matter of life and death. Garrone's (The Embalmer) ambitious and powerful breakthrough film sheds light on a shadow organization that rules by fear and unsparing violence, tacitly fostered from above and abroad by greed, corruption and complicity. Based on Roberto Saviano's explosive international bestseller, which made him a target for mob threats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ty Burr, Boston Globe:  &amp;quot;When a man on a motorbike pulls alongside a moving sedan and opens fire, it's not the thrill of violence you feel. It's the awful shock, the immediacy of the disruption. Nothing sweet or serene in this movie stays that way for long.  As its punning biblical title suggests, &amp;quot;Gomorrah&amp;quot; is about decay and collapse. That besieged sedan goes careening into a garden of plaster casts of classic Roman busts and statues. The shattered pieces put a very fine point on the fall of Western civilization.&amp;quot;  Four stars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa Schwarzbaum, Entertainment Weekly: &amp;quot;Don't look for resolution, romanticism, or comic relief in this underworld tour, shot with a fast, you-are-there look and no pity; you won't find picaresque goodfellas or Sopranos-style ziti eaters here. Instead, there's the power of damning truth.&amp;quot;  Grade: A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK, not exactly a happy, care-free film, but it sure sounds good.  We'll go to an area restaurant afterwards for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the movie, I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236274385000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gomorrah</name><id>9888443</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236540600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9888443/</event_url></item>