<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Curzon Mill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.822050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-7223</phone><name>Maudslay State Park</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>848934</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.926670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This beautiful former millionaire's estate  is located along the Merrimack River in Newburyport, MA.  There are numerous trails for crosscountry skiing, showshoeing and hiking.  We will meet at the main entrance on Curzon Street at 10:00am.  It is difficult to predict the snow conditions now, we may be skiing/snowshoeing or hiking, we'll have to wait and see.  I'm looking over the trail map and will have a planned trip by then.  There's a trail that runs along the Merrimack Rive that's partially closed because of roosting Bald Eagles that I want to include in the trip.  I'll keep it to around three miles and two hours (low intensity).  There is a $2.00 parking fee, the rest of the park is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North and South: Take Rte. 95, exit 57 to Rte. 113 east. Follow 113 east for half a mile and turn left on Noble St. At stop sign turn left onto Ferry Rd., bear left at fork and follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From West: Take I-495 exit 55 to Rte. 110 east. Continue 1 mile to Merrill St., turn right at second light. Continue on Merrill St./Spofford St. for 1.5 miles. Turn right before stop sign onto Ferry Rd., follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the parking lot in my green Toyota 4runner.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234627174000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233028722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moudslay State Park Skiing, Snowshoeing and Hiking</name><id>9609600</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234018800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/9609600/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/d/global_6592605.jpeg</photo_url></item>