<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So many options: Jazz Brunch, Blues Jam, any of their wonderful concerts, but the best part of Johnny D's is their restaurant and at a moderate price. Ever since the smoking ban, it's really cleaned up. It's a great mix of good food and great music!  -  says BBLD fellow foodie, Diane &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over a dozen of you in agreement...it seems right that we should return to this Somerville institution for its amazing jazz brunch...both food and music receive rave reviews.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Here's a place that has it all: good food, cheap drinks, friendly surroundings, and a knack for booking the near great and the soon-to-be-great.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Best of Boston&amp;quot; - Boston Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reservations are not accepted, PLEASE BE PROMPT, so you can be seated with us.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For manageable conversations and bill paying, we'll sit at tables of six or less. You're welcome and encouraged to table hop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brunch Menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/menu_brunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.johnnyds.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.johnnyds.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metered Parking Lots:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ci.somerville.ma.us/CoS_Content/documents/Davis%20Square%20Parking%20Map.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ci.somervi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buena Vista Lot - Holland Street&lt;br /&gt;Herbert Street Lot&lt;br /&gt;Grove Street Lots&lt;br /&gt;Brooks Pharmacy Lot - Highland and Grove Street&lt;br /&gt;Cutter Street Lot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Steps from Davis Square subway station on the Red Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Before I list the Reservation Rules, please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to assure you I do understand if you've RSVPd YES and you have a sudden change of plans because you're lost, you don't feel well, you have transportation issues, you don't have the money, or you just don't want to be around people. My only request is for you to let me know as soon as possible so we don't worry about you and our reservation is adjusted. As long as you contact me you will not be considered a NO-SHOW.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rules for Events with &lt;u&gt;Reservations&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVPs are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the brunch and you have not attended, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update brunch confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW each will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the brunch, it is counted as a NO-SHOW if you do not contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events with reservations you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/suggestion/"&gt;Tonya&lt;/a&gt; about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be arrive at 10:30 to welcome you from Johnny D's bar.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295221715000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278583462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch With Background Music at Johnny D's</name><id>14038274</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278860400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/14038274/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/b/global_16273323.jpeg</photo_url></item>