<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>HC 32 Box 5000</address_1><state>ME</state><lat>44.965683</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rangeley lake state park</name><city>rangeley</city><id>7878612</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.642708</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/strong&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan is to spend the weekend in Maine at the Rangeley Lake State Park Campground.  I have a reservation for site 46 for up to six people Friday and Saturday night.  Both Saturday and Sunday hikes start early so it makes the most sense to drive up Friday and spend the whole weekend - the drive from Boston should take 4.5 hours assuming light traffic.  The parks website is &lt;a href="http://www.maine.gov/cgi-bin/online/doc/parksearch/search_name.pl?state_park=25&amp;amp;historic_site=&amp;amp;public_reserved_land=&amp;amp;shared_use_trails=&amp;amp;option=search"&gt;http://www.maine.gov/cgi-bin/online/doc/parksearch/search_name.pl?state_park=25&amp;amp;historic_site=&amp;amp;public_reserved_land=&amp;amp;shared_use_trails=&amp;amp;option=search&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The morning of the hike we will be at the trailhead at 8am to start the hike.  Should you not camp at the campsite please mail me about where to meet and make sure you understand how long it will take you to get to the trailhead - we will not wait long at the trailhead before starting off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan for the hike is to start from Caribou Valley road and then head down the appalatian trail to tag Sugarloaf and Spaulding mountains.  We will then head off and tag Abraham off the AT.   The total mileage will be 14 miles and will take a up a minimum of 10 hours on the trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan for the hike is to start from Caribou Valley road and then head down the appalatian trail to tag Sugarloaf and Spaulding mountains.  We will then head off and tag Abraham off the AT.   The total mileage will be 14 miles and will take a up a minimum of 10 hours on the trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; due to pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Maine Mountain Guide and the Internet. I have not done this hike before and have not been to the immediate area.  You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a day hike&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Appalachian Mountain Club&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As mentioned before it is likely the group will be staying at the campisite and then drive over the trailhead for a 8am start.  Should you not be camping please email me for trailhead directions. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris L</member_name><member_id>6602385</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343063090000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340561989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maine Weekend - Sugarloaf, Spaulding, Abraham mountains</name><id>70528592</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342872000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/70528592/</event_url></item>