<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I recently met a photographer that is having a Reception on April 6th to launch his new collection of images from two trips to Kyoto made in the Spring and Autumn of 2006. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The April 6th event is likely cocktail attire as the Rolly Michaux Gallery features onlt exclusive and high-end art. I will post up additional details as I get them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be at this reception so hope a few others will be going to check out the work and meet Robert and discuss photography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there are others going we can grab a bite or cocktails after to discuss the collection ... or other things photo ;-).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Eileen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://robertcastagna.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://robertcastagna...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;Rolly Michaux Gallery and artist Robert Castagna invite you to a special reception &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FRIDAY APRIL 6th from 5-7 PM&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an exhibition of new photographic work by Robert Castagna. Images will be on display from March 30 - May 7, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROLLY-MICHAUX 290 Dartmouth Street at the Vendome Boston, MA 02116 Tel. 617.536.9898 Gallery hours: Tuesday through Friday 11-4, Saturday until 5:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographs in this series will feature images from two trips to Kyoto made in the Spring and Autumn of 2006. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert's background is a Professional Certificate in Photography from the New York Institute and includes exhibitions in various venues, such as the Boston Public Library, Danforth Museum of Art, throughout the Harvard Square, Hynes Convention Center and the Western Gateway Heritage State Park. His work within the community has been consistent, teaching photography to all walks of life in a project deemed &amp;quot;Through their Eyes&amp;quot;. Currently his work is offered exclusively by Rolly-Michaux Gallery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awards include the Cambridge Arts Council Grant and the Award of Excellence from Photographer's Forum Magazine and the New York Institute of Photography. Robert's documentary work of Boston is a part of the Permanent Collection of the Boston Public Library. As well his work is included in the collections of Harvard University Archives, the Cambridge Historical Commission, the corporate collection of Randolph Associates, Inc and other private collections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.saatchi-gallery.co.uk/yourgallery/artist_profile/a/11351.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.saatchi-ga...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rolly-Michaux Gallery, known throughout New York and New England for its fine collection of Joan Miro, Henri Matisse, Pablo Picasso and other top 20th Century Artists, exclusively features the work of photographer Robert Castagna. A gallery exhibit is scheduled for April of 2007. The exhibition will will include limited editions prints of recent series entitled The Art of Mystery; Kyoto in its Season. &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541109000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173282895000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rolly Michaux Gallery: Kyoto in it's Seasons</name><id>5545634</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175893200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/5545634/</event_url></item>