<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Snyder Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06438</zip><lat>41.466972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Oar</name><city>Haddam</city><id>386567</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.477295</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The weather didn't cooperate for our solstice lunch, so we'll just have to try again! The Blue Oar is located in a marina, with a beautiful view of the river. There are no bad seats in the house! And speaking of seats, meals are served at picnic tables, so you may want to bring a cushion to sit on. Watching boats cruise up and down the river, while enjoying a casual and relaxing lunch, is the perfect way to celebrate the solstice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Oar offers salads, sandwiches, and burgers, as well as daily specials. They have soft beverages, but you can BYOB. Feel free to bring a pitcher of sangria, mojitos, or your favorite summertime drink to share. They do not take reservations - seating is as it becomes available. To find us, look for the Meetup sign on the table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From route 9 north or south, take exit 7 (route 154)&lt;br /&gt;- at the end, take a left onto rt 154 north&lt;br /&gt;- Blue Oar will be about 2-1/2 miles up the road, on the right, just past the Pilot House hot dog stand&lt;br /&gt;- there is a sign at the top of the road&lt;br /&gt;- follow the road down into the marina - the restaurant is on the left&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247945093000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>BBW/BHM and their Admirers.</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BigAttractions</urlname><id>667139</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Big Attractions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245620873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lunch at Blue Oar - Take Two!</name><id>10702561</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247414400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigAttractions/events/10702561/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/f/a/global_9028090.jpeg</photo_url></item>