<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A yes list will be provided as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TRAILHEAD LOCATION: For the north terminus, leave US 2 about 9 mi. east of Gorham, at the west end of an abandoned wayside area just west of the Maine–New Hampshire border; go about 0.1 mi. into this area, and take FR 95 (a rough gravel road) right for 0.9 mi. to a gate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance Time Elev Change Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude starting at Shelburne Trailhead - north 44° 22' 26" 71° 01' 33"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the north terminus, leave US 2 about 9 mi. east of Gorham, at the west end of an abandoned wayside area just west of the Maine–New Hampshire border; go about 0.1 mi. into this area, and take FR 95 (a rough gravel road) right for 0.9 mi. to a gate. 4.00 mi 3 hr 0 min +1906 ft on Shelburne Trail 4.00 mi 3 hr 0 min +1906 ft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trail begins on FR 95, near the Maine–New Hampshire border, passes through the col between Shelburne Moriah Mountain and Howe Peak, and descends to Wild River Rd. Most of the trail south of the ridgeline is within or adjacent to the Wild River Wilderness. The trail follows the continuation of FR 95 past the gate; this was an active logging road in 2006, with muddy footing, so hikers should be alert for changing conditions. The trail follows this road, then it turns left off the main road (sign) onto an older logging road and begins to climb moderately above the brook. This turn was difficult to discern in 2006; it is after the first bridge. The trail makes the first of four crossings of a branch brook and reaches the height-of land, where it meets the eastern terminus of the Kenduskeag Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(For Shelburne Moriah Mountain, follow this trail to the right.) to the junction of Kenduskeag Trail 44° 20' 58" 71° 04' 44" 1.40 mi 1 hr 16 min +969 ft on Kenduskeag Trail 5.40 mi 4 hr 16 min +2875 ft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ledges of Shelburne Moriah afford excellent views. The name of the trail is an Abenaki word meaning “a pleasant walk.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Mt. Moriah to the Rattle River Trail junction, the trail is part of the AT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Shelburne Trail, the Kenduskeag Trail climbs over two knolls with views—on the first knoll, one must scramble up a ledge on the left to obtain the fine view of the Wild River valley. It ascends steadily with rough footing from a sharp, narrow col. It runs across the summit plateau to an outlook east. to Shelburne Moriah Mtn 44° 21' 12" 71° 05' 56" 1.40 mi 47 min -969 ft on Kenduskeag Trail 6.80 mi 5 hr 3 min +1906 ft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail runs across the summit plateau to an outlook east, then descends steadily with rough footing to a sharp, narrow col. It then climbs over two knolls with views—on the second knoll, one must scramble up a ledge on the right to obtain the fine view of the Wild River valley –and ends at the Shelburne Trail. to the junction of Shelburne Trail 44° 20' 58" 71° 04' 44" 4.00 mi 2 hr 3 min -1906 ft on Shelburne Trail 10.80 mi 7 hr 6 min 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the height-of land, the Shelburne Trail meets the eastern terminus of the Kenduskeag Trail. (For Shelburne Moriah Mountain, follow this trail.) The trail makes the first of four crossings of a branch brook. The trail turns onto another logging road and descends moderately above Connor Brook. It turns onto a continuation of FR 95; this was an active logging road in 2006, with muddy footing, so hikers should be alert for changing conditions and ends at the gate. to Shelburne Trailhead - north 44° 22' 26" 71° 01' 33"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the north terminus, leave US 2 about 9 mi. east of Gorham, at the west end of an abandoned wayside area just west of the Maine–New Hampshire border; go about 0.1 mi. into this area, and take FR 95 (a rough gravel road) right for 0.9 mi. to a gate. 10.80 mi 7 hr 6 min 0 ft Totals&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER FOUR DOOR LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340585572000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339526336000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SHELBURNE MORIAH 52 WITH A VIEW</name><id>68867232</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340456400000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/68867232/</event_url></item>