<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We will meet at 8:30 at the parking area for the Willey House Station site, described in my WM Guide as &amp;quot;a parking area just below the railroad tracks, reached by a paved road .3 miles long that leaves the west side of 302 directly opposite the Webster Cliff Trail, about 1 mile south of the Willey House site.&amp;quot;  Please make sure you look at maps/GPS/whatever to be sure that you know where you are going ahead of time!! When I did this hike in July, I and 3 other people ended up at the WRONG trail head. We don't want that to happen to you!&lt;/span&gt; I do NOT know if this road is plowed in the winter, so be prepared for a .3 mile road walk at the end of our hike if it is not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a traverse, so we will be meeting at the Willey House Station Site/Ethan Pond trail head (described above) and carpooling to the Avalon Trail  trailhead (Crawford Depot Info Center).  We'll ascend to the summit of Tom via the Avalon and A-Z Trails to the Mt. Tom Spur Trail, double back to the AZ Trail and take the Willey Range trail to the summits of Field and Willey.  We will descend Willey via the Ethan Pond Trail (NOT KENDRON FLUME)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for winter cold and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This can be dangerous in cold weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. Come prepared to stay dry!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Traction and head lamps will be required.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunrise is at 7:20 am.  Sunset will be at 4:45 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This hike is mostly below treeline and unexposed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are no huts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is a full winter hike.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER.  If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I am not a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around.  The mountain will be there another day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog in cold weather and snow.  I will have my little dog (Loki) with me.  He does not have these peaks yet and is trying to &amp;quot;catch up&amp;quot; to me and my other dog! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike.  I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying being outdoors, SO if the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), I will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;  I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book time is about 7 hrs,  8.5 miles, excluding any road walk&lt;/b&gt;.  Plan on it taking 7 hours, possibly more in winter conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit &lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Avalon Trail (to the junction of the A-Z trail)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;1.3miles&lt;br /&gt;1hr  5min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail runs from the AMC's Crawford Depot infomration center on the west side of 302 to the Willey Range Trail....After .1 miles from the Crawford Notch Depot the Mount Willard Trail leaves left and the Avalon Trail ascends gradually and soon crosses a brook.  Just beyond this crossing, a loop path diverges left, passes by Beecher and Pearl cascades and shortly rejoins the main trail.  The Avalon Trail continues at an easy grade, recrosses the brook at .8 miles and begins a moderate ascent.  At 1.3 miles, the A-Z trail to Zealand Falls Hut diverges right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A-Z Trail to the junction of the Mt Tom Spur Trail and the Willey Range Trail &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;1 mile&lt;br /&gt;1 hour &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The A-Z trail diverges right of the Avalon Trail and and soon descends to cross a steep-walled gully then climbs steadily, anglnig up along the side of the brook valley that has its head at the Field-Tom col.  At .6 mi, the trail crosses the brook and soon begins to climb more steeply, reaching the height-of-land at 1.0 miles where the Mount Tom Spur diverges right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt Tom Spur Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; 1.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;1 hr (ROUND TRIP to the Summit of Tom and back to the Willey Range Trail)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Willey Range Trail (from the junction of the A-Z Trail to the junction with the Ethan Pond Trail) (NOTE: WE WILL BE DOING THIS SECTION IN REVERSE OF THE DESCRIPTION)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; 3.4 miles&lt;br /&gt;2hrs, 40 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail begins on the Ethan Pond Trail, 1.6 mies from the Willey House Station site then runs over the summits of Mt. Willey and Mt Field to the A-Z Trail in the Field-Tom col...The trail continues straight ahead where the Ethan Pond Trail turns left, crosses Kendron Brook in 100 yards and at .2 miles, turns sharp left and crosses a smaller brook.  At .4 miles, it crosses another small brook, then climbs a very steep and rough slope with several ladders, offering occasional outlooks.  The best view is from the east outlook, just before the summit of Mt. Willey, reached by an unsigned side path that leaves on the riht, 40 yards below the summit cairn.  The main trail reaches the summit at 1.1 mi and circles around to the south outlook which affords a sweeping view over the northeastern part of the Pemigewasset Wilderness.  It then descends gradually,  keeping mostly to the west side of the ridge and losing only 300 ft in altitude at its low point, then climbs to the summit of Mt. Field at 2.5 miles.  At 90 yards north of this summit, the Avalon Trail diverges right and the Willey Range Trail climbs over a small knob and descends gradually northwest to the A-Z Trail just below the Field-Tom col at 3.4 miles.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ethan Pond Trail (from the junction of the Willey Range Trail to the Willey House Station Site (Note:  We will be doing this section IN REVERSE)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; 1.6 miles&lt;br /&gt;1 hr, 25 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail begins at the Willey House station site in a parking area just below the railroad tracks, reached by a paved road .3 miles long that leaves the west side of 302 directly opposite the Webster Cliff Trail, about 1 mile south of the Willey House site.  The trail crosses th etracks and ascends on an old logging road and in .2 miles, the Arethusa-Ripley Falls Trail diverges left.  The Ethan Pond Trail climbs steadily, then becomes more gradual and at 1.3 miles, the Kendron Flume Trail enters on the right.  At 1.6 miles, the Willey Range Trail leaves straight ahead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;--------&lt;br /&gt;8.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;7 hours, 5 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY OR WINTER HIKING. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN  (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic with two dogs &amp; usually a Meetup Sign in the window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1295130149000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293056300000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tom, Field, Willey Traverse</name><id>15801837</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294579800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15801837/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/5/global_3608437.jpeg</photo_url></item>