<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/2/b/event_32660011.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
 I will be at the Broad sign by the main door of the Broad Institute by 5:30, we need to head in for seats by 6:15 or risk not being allowed in.&amp;nbsp; This is a very popular series. I have attended lectures in this series before, and they are always well done.&amp;nbsp; For those of you not familiar with the series:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Broad Institute's Midsummer Nights' Science is an annual lecture series that explores key advances in genomic research. This lecture series is held each summer, and is free and open to the general public. Midsummer Nights' Science at the Broad Institute takes place at 7 Cambridge Center, in Kendall Square in Cambridge. Come experience science!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seats in our auditorium for these lectures will be available on a first-come first-served basis, up until the capacity of the room is reached. &lt;strong&gt;Attendees arriving after 6:15pm will be seated at the organizers' discretion, based on the number of available seats.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Broad is located in Kendall Square on Main Street.&amp;nbsp; When you exit the Kendall Square Station, walk down Main Street towards Central Square.&amp;nbsp; There is parking in the area, but it is much easier to get there by T.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information on parking:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/facilities/transportation/parking/visitors/public_parking.html"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/facilities/transportation/parking/visitors/public_parking.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the lecture, there are usually refreshments in the lobby.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Some of you may wish to take advantage of this.&amp;nbsp; We can gather after the talk to see if anyone is interested in going to a nearby establishment for food and drink or if everyone wants to nosh at the Broad instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lecture Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wed, July 13th, 6-7pm: Engineering plastic chips for immunology research&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/lovelab/" target="_blank"&gt;Christopher Love&lt;/a&gt;, Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Your immune system is critical for protecting you from disease, and yet it can also let you down in diseases like cancer and autoimmunity. Christopher Love will discuss recent advances in fabricating small devices to be used for isolating and interrogating individual immune system cells. These devices provide new knowledge on how the immune system works, and how we can improve the manufacturing of biological drugs that mimic the natural mechanisms of protection afforded by the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside by the Broad Sign near the main entrance at 5:30 and I will be wearing a Meetup pin.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310650653000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308323002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Broad Lecture:  Engineering Plastic Chips for Immunology Research</name><id>22555141</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310592600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/22555141/</event_url></item>