<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ashes of Time is a lyrical, dream-like martial arts epic film!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hk.youtube.com/watch?v=Oos8-vS6Dz4" target="_blank"&gt;Watch Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Loosely based on the Chinese heroic literature classic, &amp;quot;The Eagle-Shooting Heroes&amp;quot; by prolific Wuxia author Louis Cha, ASHES OF TIME is conspicuous for the unusual and postmodern approach it takes to a genre so firmly entrenched in Hong Kong cinema.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;story&amp;quot; consists of interactions between various characters as they weave in and out of each other's lives, with a small village in a bleak desert wasteland as the crossroads. These vignettes are not always sequential, and we must gradually piece together the relationships and backgrounds of the protagonists, some of which contribute to a larger story, while others do not. The all-star cast portrays a varied palette of characters, perfectly flawed incarnations of fantastical beings, with performances teetering on the line between disarming humanity and iconic romanticism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thing to love about this movie is the way that director Wong Kar-Wai takes the reflective internal monologues and quirky, alienated losers from his other films and transposes them to the world of Chinese heroic fantasy. It's an interesting idea that both ennobles and deconstructs the genre. Martial-arts superheroes who can literally shear mountainsides with a wave of the sword, mired in their own personal conflicts and bouts with inadequacy, in the points of time that occur between the legend-worthy events. This unusual treatment lends these mythic characters a familiar dimension that is both poetic and banal. The cast and the desert are wrenchingly beautiful in the same starkly desolate way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ASHES OF TIME is a truly beautiful movie. The cinematography is a lush blend of stunningly arid vistas, iconic posturing, minute sensual gestures, grainy documentary-style camera-work, and stylish, impressionistic fight sequences. A visual metaphor for textiles and tapestry persists, with the various interwoven plots echoed in the camera's almost tactile attention to fabric and texture throughout... sometimes tightly bound like an inescapable net, others fraying apart like elusive memories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby at 7:20 on the wooden bench</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228952743000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226867053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ashes of Time</name><id>9173981</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228696200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/9173981/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/2/global_6332290.jpeg</photo_url></item>