<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>158 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02056</zip><lat>42.119259</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>TK Pet Supply</name><city>Norfolk</city><id>4447302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.327065</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us at TK Pet Supply in Norfolk, MA on Sunday, December 4th from 11-2 to have (you and) your pet's holiday photo taken by the talented Angie Tollefson of Kit Cat Photography (www.kitcatphotos.com) and help us collect donations for BayPath Humane Society! These will not be your typical department-store-Santa type holiday pictures... Angie specializes in beautiful pet photography and capturing our amazing animals' personalities on film; check out her work on her website or find Kit Cat Photography on facebook!..... Sessions will be $30 a sitting, to include TWO 5x7's (you'll be given a code to go on her website and order the prints of your choice, shipped right to you!) and the NEBBC will receive a portion of the proceeds! Bring the kids... bring the family!... Appointments will be booked every fifteen minutes. All you have to do to reserve your time slot is write it in a comment here! (I will then record/chart them... email justcassie101@gmail.com or call (508) 380-8853 with any questions!) The 2:00p event ending time will be extended if appointments book up!..... We would also like to take this opportunity to collect donations for BayPath Humane Society (www.baypathhumane.org), one of the only no-kill shelters in MA that routinely takes &amp;quot;pit bulls.&amp;quot; (See their wish list here: &lt;a href="http://www.baypathhumane.org/content/view/67/69/)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.baypathhum...&lt;/a&gt;. Simply bring your items with you to TK Pet Supply on December 4th! 'Tis the season! Leave this event with a free goodie bag! (As we are not hosting, NEBBC coupons will unfortunately not be accepted at this event.)..... Show your holiday spirit, help out some adoptable dogs, support the efforts of the NEBBC and leave with a holiday memory that will last forever! *Special thanks to Angie Tollefson of Kit Cat Photography and Keith Shelansky of TK Pet Supply specializing in premium pet nutrition for sponsoring this event!*&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323260604000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321369492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini Holiday Portrait Sessions to support the NEBBC &amp; BayPath Humane Society!</name><id>41240362</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323014400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/41240362/</event_url></item>