<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hynes Convention Center on the Green Line</address_2><address_1>intersection of Mass Ave and Boylston St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373419</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass Ave and Boylston St</name><city>Boston</city><id>929360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119422</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We declare our solidarity with the people of the Middle East who have the misfortune of living on top of the largest oil reserves on the planet which is the reason behind the current war on Iraq. We condemn all war makers and their accomplices in this criminal war of aggression.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We repudiate the so called “War on Terror” which amounts to a general assault on our rights: abuses, excuses, jailings, raids, lies, spies, xenophobia, torture, extraordinary rendition, and the police state that says we must support the victimization of the oppressed. We are no longer the silent generation but are now willing to stand apart and against the mass murdering villains who are doin' the real killin'.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in the DMZ!! On the first and third Friday of each month, we hereby declare the establishment of a new DeMilitarized Zone where all those who wish can congregate to denigrate and repudiate the war machine and celebrate the growth of a new movement from coast to coast that will oppose the war and oppression in this country and around the world. Bring your signs, and minds, let's chalk, talk, play music, paint art with caring and sharing and declaring that we are “chilling *against* the villains” in this zone of liberation and independence!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be holding signs, drawing, playing music, and handing out stickers.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>billie mulcahy</member_name><member_id>4120888</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244412518000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243828007000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston De-Militarized Zone (DMZ)</name><id>10540973</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244237400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/10540973/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/4/5/global_8110933.jpeg</photo_url></item>