<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Our Mindful Eating Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;br /&gt;Organizational Meeting on Thursday Sept 16, &lt;br /&gt;Cromwell, Ct @ 7 p.m.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are invited to help the BFF of Ct establish a new Buddhist group in Connecticut which will be dedicated to mindful and healthy eating and drinking using a holistic approach with Buddhist spirituality. There are a few books available on this topic but we will be using Savor written by Thich Nhat Hanh and Dr. Lilian Cheung. We highly recommend this book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Thursday, we will need to set up the Group’s meeting format, possible rituals, length and content of discussions, prayers, outreach etc. Also, we need to figure out a location for meetings, times, day of the week, web site, meet up group etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you interested? &lt;b&gt;Then, attend an organizational meeting in Cromwell on Thursday. September 16 at 7 p.m.&lt;/b&gt; If you can’t come, then look for future announcements on when it will be officially inaugurated in October. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a reminder: inspired by the book Savor, our Mindful Eating Group will focus on such things like: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) The Buddhist perspective on weight control&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Nutrition&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) How to really appreciate your food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) Actions plans for mindful eating and living&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) Helping create a more mindful world around us &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Contact us in order to attend Thursday’s meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in attending this organizational meeting, then e-mail the Buddhist Faith Fellowship at pam153@sbcglobal.net to get easy directions to meeting location in Cromwell. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Let’s make an idea happen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284752882000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284341499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mindful Eating Group's organizational meeting this Thursday</name><id>14747611</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284678000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/14747611/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/0/global_17917216.jpeg</photo_url></item>