<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>795 Central Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.213017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wentworth Home</name><city>Dover</city><id>5403062</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.875801</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;[Merci &amp;agrave; Jim qui organise les Soir&amp;eacute;es Cin&amp;eacute;ma &amp;agrave; la Wentworth Home ! This event is not a Meetup, but Jim and I both thought that group members might be interested in attending these public events. You certainly are encouraged to look for each other at the venue!]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All who are interested in the French language, good film, and an entertaining evening are invited to attend a new film series at the Wentworth Home. All films will be shown in French with English subtitles and will begin promptly at 6:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wednesday, June 13: &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1048171/"&gt;S&amp;eacute;raphine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;David Edelstein of New York Magazine calls &lt;em&gt;S&amp;eacute;raphine&lt;/em&gt; &amp;ldquo;one of the most evocative films about an artist I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.&amp;rdquo; It is the true story of S&amp;eacute;raphine Louis, a simple and profoundly devout housekeeper who, in 1905 at the age of 41, begins painting brilliantly colorful canvases. She is discovered in 1914 by a German art critic and avant-garde art dealer. The story is a testament to the mysteries of creativity and the resilience of one woman&amp;rsquo;s spirit. 2008, 125 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please park in front of or to the left of the building (as you face the building). If necessary, additional parking is available at Wentworth-Douglass hospital next door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be in the Gage Room, which is at the very back of the building on the first floor. Enter through the covered walkway and walk straight to the back (one jog left then right in the hall).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the the Gage Room (instructions in the description).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Verschueren</member_name><member_id>31053912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339637249000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastNHFrench</urlname><id>63967</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>Seacoast NH French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327790875000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Language Film Series at the Wentworth Home: Séraphine</name><id>50032732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339624800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastNHFrench/events/50032732/</event_url></item>