<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>ROOTS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ROOT of heritage is “heir” which means something that belongs to one by reason of birth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;October’s theme is ROOTS. Your recipe should relate to whatever meaning you give to that theme.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROOT words often set the meaning of a compound word whose meaning is augmented or altered by a prefix or suffix.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heritage can also suggest origin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROOTS are often edible (to ed i.e. to eat). Many ROOT vegetables are harvested in October (octo meaning eight).  October, oddly enough also means ale or beer because it is a traditional time of brewing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_culinary_vegetables#Root_and_tuberous_vegetables" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tooth and nail, hair and nerves all depend on roots to hold them embedded in their rightful locations. Toothsome (ROOT word tooth) may mean pleasing to the taste or sexually alluring. ROOT canals oddly are neither pleasing, nor for most of us sexually alluring even though a ROOT canal also starts with a tooth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROOTS, the book written my &lt;u&gt;Alex Hailey&lt;/u&gt; is a 914 page saga of an American family. It is almost as long as the current health reform bills and more people have actually read the Hailey book. It is unlikely that healthcare reform will be made into a TV miniseries movie. With the cost of healthcare continuing to rise we may all be eating TV dinners soon, so there is a connection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The ROOTS&lt;/i&gt; are a hip hop, soul, funk group that has been around at least since 2004. They have a sophisticated smooth style that may be the saving grace of hip-hop.  I have no idea what they like to eat but I bet they drink some sort of ale on occasion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/theroots" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are all the ROOTS I can think of at the moment; please note,  I am politely not mentioning the ROOTS that may mean it is time for a hair color job for Chris, Paul and sometimes Bill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now off you go to ROOT (meaning to rummage) around in your recipes for your magic making, yummy contribution to the October Cooking Club dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook onsite unless you dish takes more than 60 minutes to prepare.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>my home so you will notice me and the dogs, will send address a few days before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1258159806000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252713847000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes October Meetup</name><id>11351029</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255129200000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/11351029/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/2/global_10650418.jpeg</photo_url></item>