<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>971 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351646</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>701-331-0920</phone><name>Paradise Rock Club</name><city>Boston</city><id>512528</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/elvisperkinsindearland" target="_blank"&gt;Elvis Perkins In Dearland&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/bowerbirds" target="_blank"&gt;Bowerbirds&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/davegodowsky" target="_blank"&gt;Dave Godowsky&lt;/a&gt; @ Paradise&lt;br /&gt;Doors at 7 PM; 18+ show, &lt;a href="http://www.livenation.com/edp/eventId/411787" target="_blank"&gt;tickets&lt;/a&gt; $14 in advance, $16 day of show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two excellent folk-rock bands.  If you haven't heard Bowerbirds' &lt;a href="http://cdn.stereogum.com/mp3/Bowerbirds%20-%20Northern%20Lights.mp3" target="_blank"&gt;Northern Lights&lt;/a&gt; yet, you should listen to it immediately.  It's beautiful...one of my favorite songs of the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elvis Perkins in Dearland (from allmusic):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While Elvis Perkins' folk music has earned comparisons to the likes of Leonard Cohen and Bob Dylan, he is also known as the son of actor Anthony Perkins and photographer Berry Berenson. Raised in Los Angeles and New York, he started playing guitar in high school and took lessons from Prescott Niles of the Knack. Perkins played in rock bands and learned classical guitar, but his forte became folk, and the unexpected deaths of his parents (his father died of AIDS in 1992, and his mother perished in the 9/11 attacks nine years later) lent a weary, melancholic tone to his first album. Ash Wednesday was released in early 2007 via XL Recordings. To tour behind the album, Perkins assembled a full band and billed his shows as &amp;quot;Elvis Perkins in Dearland,&amp;quot; with bassist Brigham Brough, keyboardist/guitarist Wyndham Boylan-Garnett, and drummer Nicholas Kinsey rounding out the lineup. An album of the same name was released in 2009, and the Doomsday EP appeared before the year was up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bowerbirds (from allmusic):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bowerbirds sit on the dividing line between the freak folk contingent led by Devendra Banhart and Joanna Newsom and the more straightforward sunshine pop of Lavender Diamond: for all the self-conscious quirkiness of their lineup and instrumentation, there's an unfeigned positivity to their music that's refreshingly direct. The roots of the Bowerbirds lie in the Raleigh, NC, indie rock trio Ticonderoga, who were led by singer and guitarist Phil Moore. During the recording of the trio's second album, 2005's The Heilig Levine LP, Moore took a job tracking birds for the North Carolina Museum of Natural Sciences, which involved living in a cabin in the Carolina woods, far from civilization. Moore's girlfriend, a visual artist named Beth Tacular (born Beth Salmon) joined him in the cabin to work on her painting; at night, Moore began writing songs influenced by the couple's rustic, natural surroundings. When Ticonderoga split up on tour supporting their second album, Moore and Tacular started their own band, the Bowerbirds, with Tacular teaching herself how to play the accordion and acquiring a marching band-style bass drum to keep rudimentary time. In this stripped-down incarnation, the Bowerbirds recorded a six-song EP, Danger at Sea, in 2006. Drafting producer and multi-instrumentalist Mark Paulson to flesh out the duo's sound, the Bowerbirds released their debut full-length, Hymns for a Dark Horse, on the new indie label Burly Time Records in 2007.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call/text me on 617-549-8453.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>8828135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259802479000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257204263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Elvis Perkins In Dearland with Bowerbirds @ Paradise</name><id>11775608</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259629200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/11775608/</event_url></item>