<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Long Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.359778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-720-9200</phone><name>Boston Harbor Cruises</name><city>Boston</city><id>732009</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050870</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Codzilla&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Harbor Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborcruises.com/codzilla/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 Long Wharf &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02110-3602 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets:&lt;/b&gt; $25.00, for a 40 minute ride&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's try this again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to &lt;a href="http://secure3.gatewayticketing.com/BostonHarborCruises/Shop/Calendar.aspx?SalesChannelDetailID=16&amp;amp;Merchant=BHCOnline&amp;amp;CategoryGroupExternalID=EXCR&amp;amp;CategoryExternalID=CZ" target="_blank"&gt;http://secure3.gatewa...&lt;/a&gt; to purchase tickets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=====================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Boston Harbor Cruises:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborcruises.com/codzilla/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Get ready for more thrills, more laughs and more speed than you ever imagined as you zip across the ocean at up to 40 miles per hour. Don't worry, though; a ride on Codzilla is as entertaining as it is thrilling. The wind roars. The music blares. And the waves will splash during a wet and wild 40-minute ride of full blast, sensational fun. [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Before boarding Codzilla, secure all headwear, eyewear, wigs, toupees, and pitiful comb-overs. No refunds will be issued for bad hair days. Codzilla is a wet ride and bears no claims for wet feet, wet pants or wet t-shirts. Codzilla is also equipped with a state of the art sound system powering 30 marine-grade speakers. That’s about one speaker every 3 feet. So, if you're a fan of &amp;quot;easy-listening&amp;quot; stations be forewarned, we will not turn down our music- don't even think about asking. [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Codzilla is 70’ of marine aluminum and bad attitude. Codzilla seats (or was that &amp;quot;eats&amp;quot;) 135 people, so reservations are recommended. With two turbo-charged diesel engines driving state of the art waterjets, Codzilla roams the ocean with 2,800 horsepower. (We're not talking sea horses, my friend.) Plus with its unique hull design, Codzilla is capable of thrilling 360-degree turns and spinning on a dime. [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;======================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description From AllBostonTours:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.allbostontours.com/Body.asp?Page=TourDetails&amp;amp;tour=BOS-W0012" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.allbostont...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you ready for Codzilla? Hold on tight as you zip across the ocean at up to 40 miles per hour on Boston Harbor's high-speed thrill boat ride!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Get ready for thrills, laughs &amp;amp; speed aboard Codzilla! &lt;br /&gt;* Hop onboard this mighty beast at Boston Harbor's Long Wharf, conveniently located downtown. &lt;br /&gt;* Feel the wind whip and the music roar on this 40-minute thrill ride. &lt;br /&gt;* Zip across the ocean at up to 40 miles per hour! &lt;br /&gt;* Listen to the crew recount the legendary tale of how Codzilla came to Boston. &lt;br /&gt;* Watch out for splashing waves! &lt;br /&gt;* Roam the ocean with 2,800 horsepower. &lt;br /&gt;* Zoom through the water with 2 turbo-charged diesel engines. &lt;br /&gt;* You will get wet - so be ready for a great time! &lt;br /&gt;* Bring your camera for harbor photo opportunities! &lt;br /&gt;=========================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FAQ:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborcruises.com/codzilla/faqs.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) Do you recommend advance reservations for your cruises and ferries?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While reservations are not required, we strongly recommend you purchase your Codzilla tickets in advance if you know the specific day and time you want to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;2) What kind of boat is it?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Codzilla is Boston's first high-speed thrill boat ride featuring two turbo-charged diesel engines generating 2,800 horsepower and speeds of approximately 40 miles an hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3) Will I get wet?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although we can’t guarantee a good soaking, Codzilla is a wet ride and you may experience anything from a light saltwater spray to a shirt-wringing splash. As such we recommend wearing casual clothing and footwear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;4) Can I make a ticket reservation online?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes! Boston Harbor Cruises offers online ticketing for all Codzilla departures. Click on the link to purchase your tickets online. Tickets may also be purchased by phone, or in person at our Ticket Center on Long Wharf. If you do book online there is no &amp;quot;will call&amp;quot; window since BHC offers hassle-free dockside check-in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;5) What happens if I've reserved tickets but can't make it for the cruise?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, advance-order tickets for all Codzilla rides are non-refundable. But they may be transferred to another day and time depending on availability. Transfers cannot be handled online or over the phone – only in person at the BHC Ticket Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6) Where's the closest T station?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are located off the Aquarium Blue line stop. Follow exit signs to the Aquarium. Once you reach the exit, take a sharp left and you will see our white ticket office with a whale on top. (It's about a minute walk from the station exit.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=========================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, and will be wearing a &amp;quot;Hello, My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign on his messenger bag. He'll be there by 5:30 pm by the boarding gate in front of Legal Seafoods. Please mark your RSVP if you want to go to Legal Seafood's after. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Video:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Codzilla commercial: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NAFyYNsS3Nk&amp;amp;feature=related" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be off to the side of the boat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257958194000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250105102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Codzilla at Long Wharf near Aquarium </name><id>11096860</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251324000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11096860/</event_url></item>