<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing the Creative Industries of Massachusetts&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; Members: $20 in advance (with $5 back at check in) Non-Members: $20 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/2/0/event_231051232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Helena Fruscio, Creative Economy Industry Director for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, will give a presentation on the state of the creative industries and the statewide resources designed to actively support the growth of this sector at our next breakfast meeting on May 16, 2013 - our last breakfast meeting of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come find out about: &lt;br /&gt;

 • What are the Creative Industries and why do they matter? &lt;br /&gt;

 • Massachusetts’ statewide initiatives to support the Creative Industries. &lt;br /&gt;

 • Resources to help these businesses grow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Who is included in the creative industries? The creative industries include the many companies pushing the limits of creativity in the marketplace, including innovative video game companies, cultural non-profits, design, marketing and architecture firms, and also the people who are write books, design houses, shoot movies, make art and record music. &lt;br /&gt;

 The creative industries are an important part of the Massachusetts economy, with a $1 billion statewide impact and over 100,000 Massachusetts workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Helena Fruscio is the Creative Economy Industry Director for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. She has held the position since October of 2011 and in this role will help advance the state's $1 billion creative economy industry, which currently employs over 100,000 Massachusetts workers. Helena has been widely praised for her leadership as Director of Berkshire Creative Economy Council in western Massachusetts since 2009. She has also has provided excellent leadership and input into the work of the statewide Creative Economy Council and, more recently, as a gubernatorial appointee to the Economic Development Planning Council. That work also gives her a running head start into the issues that face creative businesses across the state.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368711950000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367350527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Breakfast Meeting: Growing the Creative Industries of Massachusetts</name><id>117003212</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>6300000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368704700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/117003212/</event_url></item>