<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Grafton St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.260447</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)400-7007</phone><name>Osgood Bradley Building</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1015377</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.793748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This educational workshop will focus on defining "Sustainable Development" and "Smart Growth" and how international land use policy is turned into enforceable law, right in our cities and towns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regional Planning Commissions, Green Non-profits and Land Trusts will not discus the horrific economic and property rights impacts of these comprehensive regional planning schemes, but we will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although this event is open to the public, we are making a special effort to attract political candidates AND current P...ublic Servants. Massachusetts and the nation are about to see a flood of proposed legislation focused on complete control of the land and a top-down government controlled "Green Economy" that will be absolutely crippling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using Federal, State and local documents, we will connect the dots that are NEVER covered. Land Trusts ARE banning tractors from farms. Industrial areas ARE being chased out of the country and replaced with low income mixed use housing! Water use IS being restricted! Roads ARE being discontinued! Regional Planners ARE using eminent domain to bulldoze homes! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.masslpa.org/sites/default/files/10_facts_you_should_know_about.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.masslpa.org/sites/default/files/10_facts_you_should_know_about.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Walkable Communities &lt;br /&gt;

* Viewsheds &lt;br /&gt;

* Environmental Justice &lt;br /&gt;

* Green Communities &lt;br /&gt;

* Corridors &lt;br /&gt;

* CLURPA &lt;br /&gt;

* Endangered Species &lt;br /&gt;

* Redevelopment Scams &lt;br /&gt;

* ICLEI &lt;br /&gt;

* Sprawl Myths &lt;br /&gt;

* Climate Change &lt;br /&gt;

* CPA / Open Space&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please reach out to everyone you know and try to get your elected officials to attend this important and very informative event. The speakers for the day will be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hal Shurtleff: &lt;br /&gt;

Hal in the northeast regional director for the John Birch Society and has been leading the charge against membership in the "International Counsel for Local Environmental Initiatives" (ICLEI) for years. Hal has traveled all over the country speaking to citizens and legislators alike. He will be covering the macro aspects of Agenda 21 and the historic philosophy held by the UN, as it pertains to "Comprehensive Land Use Planning" and development of global governance schemes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dave Kopacz: &lt;br /&gt;

Dave is the Chairman of his town's Conservation Commission &amp;amp; Open Space Committee. He's also a founding member of the municipal Agricultural Committee. Dave is also President of the Massachusetts Republican Assembly and contributed the language to the MFRA's recent anti-Agenda 21 Resolution that was the first national Resolution to be accepted, unanimously. Dave will provide the micro aspects of Agenda 21 that is prevalent throughout our communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is FREE but donations will gladly be accepted. Although the event is planned for two hours, the speakers will stay until every question is answered. Feel free to contribute a snack for the Potluck table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details to follow.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349550920000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347292545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UNsustainable development: Agenda 21, Regionalization and the New Soviet</name><id>81723552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349539200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/81723552/</event_url></item>