<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Sebethe Dr.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.606894</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 635-1001</phone><name>Courtyard Marriott in Cromwell</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>983528</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.706073</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>29.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>CT REIA, Than Merrill, and Patrick Precourt presents: Wholesale and Pre-Foreclosures (1 day, 2 great speakers)&lt;br /&gt;May 22nd. 9:00am – 5:00 pm. Marriott Hotel. 4 Sebethe Drive. Cromwell, CT&lt;br /&gt;$29 for CTREIA Members, $39 for Guests&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register and learn more at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=262" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=262" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;–&amp;gt; Patrick Precourt: Pre-Foreclosure Expert &amp;lt;–&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat Precourt is one of the most successful preforeclosure investors in the nation. He started in the preforeclosure business in the late 90’s. In 2002, he founded North Shore Enterprises, a professional real estate investment company specializing in preforeclosure and short sales. Since then his team has completed well over 700 short sales. Pat is quickly getting known across the industry as the quiet guru, the guy who speaks with his actions and documented results. He tells it the way it is…an unedited opinion of a self-made entrepreneur and insanely successful business owner with roots in preforeclosure investment. His beliefs lie in The Power of Team, the master mind concepts, and his refusal to empower the misconception that competition is opposition. These have founded and driven his unarguable and unequaled success in the business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat will cover the top key points you must be aware of if you are going to be competitive in the short sale arena and also what you need to do to stay out of trouble in today’s short sale investing world!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Patrick will cover…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* What properties, or rather loans, qualify for the HAFA program (Home Affordable Foreclosure Alternatives) and which lenders MUST participate.&lt;br /&gt;* The tiny direct effect HAFA will have on our real estate industry and the MASSIVE indirect effect it will leave us with.&lt;br /&gt;* How you MIGHT be putting your client(s) in harms way by directing them to sign the HAFA short sale paperwork.&lt;br /&gt;* The 3 “must know” requirements of the HAFA program that will indeed change the way we transact our short sales.&lt;br /&gt;* How to leverage the new guidelines to cut the short sale time line by 75%.&lt;br /&gt;* Which properties CANNOT be sold for 90 after a successful short sale transaction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;–&amp;gt; Than Merrill: Wholesale Expert &amp;lt;–&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than Merrill started in Real Estate career in 2003, after attending a CT Real Estate Investors Association meeting! From a modest beginning, CT Homes has grown quickly with a staff of seven plus 25 contractors and specializes in buying, rehabilitating, selling and leasing of investment properties in urban and suburban neighborhoods, particularly in New Haven. Than and Paul, and the other teammates currently, star in Flip This House, a reality show and contest that showcases what goes on behind the house flipping industry and the exciting aspects of today’s high-stakes real estate market. The show fuses the business side and real life drama, resulting in a hot business reality show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than will cover the top key points you must be aware of if you are going to be competitive in the wholesale market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Than will cover…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* The top 5 best ways to find deals at 40 to 65 cents on the dollar in the next 30 days.&lt;br /&gt;* Done for you marketing strategies you can put to use right away.&lt;br /&gt;* How to attract boatloads of qualified buyers with great credit score in today’s market.&lt;br /&gt;* The top strategies for finding buyers on the internet for FREE.&lt;br /&gt;* Which marketing strategies work and which strategies are a waste of time.&lt;br /&gt;* How to pre-screen all your leads and evaluate deals in 10 minutes or less.&lt;br /&gt;* How to build a business that will literally run itself.&lt;br /&gt;* Cutting edge technology you can use to match buyers with sellers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See a demo of the software you must use that will run your whole real estate business… believe me you will be blown away at everything it can do for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than currently wholesales over 50 properties a year and he is going to show you exactly how he runs his business and brings in an average of $15,000 dollars a deal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Learn how to find deals 30% to 60% below market value on properties in your area. You won’t believe how easy it is&lt;br /&gt;* How to find boatloads of qualified buyers and the 3 things you ABSOLUTELY must know to get your properties sold&lt;br /&gt;* Learn how to automate all of your marketing and lead generation efforts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;–&amp;gt; Who should attend this event &amp;lt;–&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* People who are looking for a proven system to buy and sell real estate&lt;br /&gt;* Anyone looking to profit from the foreclosure boom&lt;br /&gt;* People who are looking for a way to build wealth using limited capital&lt;br /&gt;* Anyone interested in a system to find buyers and get properties sold at lightning speed&lt;br /&gt;* Anyone interested in learning how to profit in one of the best buyers markets in history&lt;br /&gt;* Anyone interested in learning how to buy distressed property for literally pennies on the dollar&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274538252000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272976985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Than Merrill and Patrick Precourt: Wholesale &amp; Pre-Foreclosure Seminar</name><id>13379106</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274533200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/13379106/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/7/global_14829639.jpeg</photo_url></item>