<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>106 Prospect Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367650</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)354-5287 or (857)417-4021c</phone><name>Out Of The Blue Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>839245</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101909</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;PRE-AWP Dire&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;for more info&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.direreader.com&amp;amp;h=PAQFWXet_&amp;amp;s=1" target="_blank"&gt;www.direreader.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Kristen Tsetsi is an award-winning fiction writer and a feature writer and columnist for a Connecticut newspaper. Her semi-autobiographical debut novel about being left behind on the home front, Pretty Much True… (called “stark and beautiful” by Feministing and “living, breathing and absolutely engrossing” by NYT bestselling novelist Caroline Leavitt), has been featured on NBC, NPR, the Huffington Post, the Stars and Stripes, and in newspapers around the countr&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;y. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Mignon Ariel King is a third-generation New Englander who was born in Boston City Hospital. She holds a Master of Arts in English degree from Simmons College. King is the publisher of Hidden Charm Press; its first publication “Extra MoJo!” is an anthology of poems, flash memoir, and social commentary selected from the first ten issues of the online journal “MoJo!” Her blog is: Making Poetry. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Michelle Cheever is an Emerson College graduate with a BFA in Writing,Literature &amp;amp; Publishing, as well as a minor in Women and Gender Studies. Her work has appeared in InDigest, PANK magazine, Seventeen magazine, and Thought Catalog. She is a Pushcart Prize nominee and has recently published a book of stories, You'll Miss Me But That's Good with Wilde Press. She currently lives in Jamaica Plain, Mass.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362196955000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360868209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dire Literary Series: Tsetsi, King, and Cheever</name><id>104619722</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362186000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/104619722/</event_url></item>