<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>78 Olympia Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801   </zip><lat>42.498740</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 935-7325</phone><name>Boston Rock Gym</name><city>Woburn</city><id>812986</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.138599</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meetup at Boston Rock Gym in Woburn.  For some of us it's more convenient, and for some of us it's hardcore, but most of all, fun!  Whether you're a new or experienced climber, come join us for a solid workout :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet up at 7:00 PM by the benches in the central TV room/area, to make introductions and team up.  If arriving later, just come find us on the walls.  If you don't recognize me from my picture, just ask the staff at the front desk, they'll be able to point me out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRG has great variety, something for everyone, and a friendly community atmosphere.  Pure slab, vertical, and sustained overhanging routes, multiple cracks, dihedrals for stemming and laybacks, and more, for focused practice of many different techniques and strength-building.  Over 40 topropes, 3 bouldering areas including a full bouldering room and a large cave, and sport leading on overhung walls and the ceiling.  Leading the ceiling is a ton of fun, straight on or via the dark crystal, that moves!  High quality wall route and boulder problem setting (some of the best in the east) for fun and challenge.  From easy juggy speed routes to super hard 5.13 and V10+ problems, you'll find it here.  Let us know your interests!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've never climbed here before, you'll need to take &amp;amp; pass a belay test for rope climbing.  Call the gym or see the website below for more info.  Full-access Day Pass $16.  Bouldering-Only Pass $14.  If interested in regular workouts, I'd recommend checking out membership prices, definitely saves you money, and usually less expensive than other gyms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info and directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonrockgym.com/general_info.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonrock...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb</member_name><member_id>9443907</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290031309000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289850783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BRG Tuesday</name><id>15455193</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289952000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/15455193/</event_url></item>