<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Each week will have a 1 hour program on the Hcg weightloss program. If you are interested in losing weight you have nothing to lose by attending but potential weight.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally have lost 40 lbs. I have went from a size 18 to a 10. I have lost 25 inches!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did it all quickly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The motto is lose 20 lbs in 20 days or lose 40 lbs in 40 days.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am adding a study for you to read. I will have more information to come but in the meantime come to the meeting and hear about this new amazing program. I will doing some of the speaking and I look forward to educating many people about the life changing process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;HCG Clinical Study&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;Effect of human chorionic Gonadotropin on weight loss, hunger, and feeling of well-being &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;Authored by: W. L. Asher M.D. and Harold W. Harper M.D.  &lt;br /&gt; From the American Society of Bariatric Physicians Research Council, 333 West Hampden Avenue, Englewood, Colorado 80110 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;Twenty female patients on 500- to 550- kcal diets receiving daily injections of 125 IU of human chorionic gonadotropin were compared with 20 female patients on 500- to 550-kcal diets receiving placebo injections. &amp;nbsp;Patients in both groups were instructed to return for daily injections 6 days each week for a total of 36 injections (unless desired weight was achieved prior to this). &lt;em&gt;The HCG group lost significantly more mean weight, had a significantly greater mean weight loss per injection, and lost a significantly greater mean percentage of their starting weight. The percentage of affirmative daily patient responses indicating "little or no hunger" and "feeling good to excellent" was significantly greater in the HCG group than in the placebo group. &lt;/em&gt;Additional investigation of the influence of &lt;strong&gt;HCG &lt;/strong&gt;on weight loss, hunger, and well-being seems indicated. &lt;br /&gt; American Journal of Clinical Nutrition, Vol 26, 211-218, Copyright &amp;copy; 1973 by The American Society for Clinical Nutrition, Inc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301444412000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Losing weight can be a difficult thing to do.This program can kick start a considerable amount of weight loss which gets you back on the road to you best year ever!</why><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300660099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HCG Weightloss Program- Informational Seminar every Tuesday evening at 7:00pm</name><id>hwsrqypfbmc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301439600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/17102899/</event_url></item>