<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>UPDATE.... Huston We Have a Problem...&lt;br /&gt;In a message dated 6/10/2007 9:06:14 A.M. Eastern Daylight Time, jdeere16@hotmail.com writes:&lt;br /&gt;Hi Al oops,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry everyone..i possted this earlier..meetup sometimes dosnt update correctly...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sent blank message accidently, just wanted to let you know this is the day &lt;br /&gt;of the Litchfield road race. It starts at 1:00 pm so you might find some of &lt;br /&gt;the roads closed in town around that time. There should be detours set up &lt;br /&gt;but some people may get lost if they don't know the area. I will have my &lt;br /&gt;cell phone on and will try to be in Litchfield around 12:30 if anyone needs &lt;br /&gt;directions to the river by back roads. My number is  (860) 921-3512, any &lt;br /&gt;questions they can call me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi John, Thanks..&lt;br /&gt;Yes detours would be a problem for many...&lt;br /&gt;Im going to post it....as an update...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK EVERYONE LOOK AT YOUR MAPS....&lt;br /&gt;You might have to get there by rte 63 south from the town center and right (west) on Webster st, that runs into Whites...&lt;br /&gt;go right on whites a little way the parking area is then on your left...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was checking the tide table for Haddam, (Chapman Pond and Walebone Cove areas)&lt;br /&gt;High river tide is about 8:30 am and low tide is about 3:30..&lt;br /&gt;This is not good for our trip because the river current is higher on the outgoing tide and we would find it not as enjoyable in side the cove when its low in there?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO..another good place on my list is BANTAM RIVER.&lt;br /&gt;It?s a nice slow 15-20 foot wide river with many twists and turns..along with a few other features that I wont mention..its part of your exploration to find out when you are there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On a warm weekend there are quite a few people on this river because it?s a popular trip and one that collinsvill canoe and yak have tours on also so parking in the small lot may be difficult at times, If its filled, I will just drop off the yaks at the carry in spot and park a little ways down the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some snacks..&lt;br /&gt;Bantam Pizza and other places are nearby or we can just decide on food after the paddle..&lt;br /&gt;Hmm I can bring the portable gas grill and gas fire pit..well..maybe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;This is not real close but those who go will say it was a good trip and worth it.&lt;br /&gt;Besides, im getting you ready for the further great places on the list that are by the shore and one in Massachusetts..well provided you are not a wimp and cant drive a bit for something more exciting than a lake..lakes are good for some things..but wouldn?t you want to see something you wouldn?t see otherwise ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From most locations head towards Litchfield CT area.&lt;br /&gt;Its at the intersection of 202, 118, 63 and near 254 CHECK YOUR MAPS&lt;br /&gt;At the center of Litchfield get on 202 heading towards Bantam (west)&lt;br /&gt;On the left you will see Constitution Way at one of the traffick lights, keep heading toward Bantam for 1.4 miles.&lt;br /&gt;Look for the left and get on to Bissell Road.&lt;br /&gt;DO NOT take the right fork to some camp hall or something (white hall rd) stay towards the left staying on Bissell Road..&lt;br /&gt;Follow Bissell Road for 0.7 miles and veer right at the end on to Whites Wood Road&lt;br /&gt;Go 0.2 miles to the access on the right over the little bridge.&lt;br /&gt;I will have the trailer with a few yaks on them, not sure if I will drive the Red Blazer or blue Toyota Avalon.&lt;br /&gt;If you don?t know anyone from previous paddles, just say hi to everyone there and hopefully you will spot us first, check the site for our pictures and extra pictures..since I have a few of em..I wont be there with the pitch fork..thats for the Devils Hop Yard Event?.&lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS and other, use 176 Whites Wood Road, Litchfield CT to get you close enough. White Wood Road works too; it?s just a short extension of Bissell rd at the right veers?&lt;br /&gt;Again look at you maps and remember some of the roads?its along drive for some of you and I don?t want you to waste a trip because you got lost and were late?.&lt;br /&gt;Yeh we wait a bit, maybe till 1:30..but not that long if it seems most of you made it.?&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181668109000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181355246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPDATE,,,,Bantam River Kayak trip</name><id>5870938</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181494800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5870938/</event_url></item>