<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.1100006104</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SAT March 13 – 8pm Bus Stop at Cheney Hall with Little Theatre of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Little Theatre of Manchester &lt;br /&gt;at Cheney Hall &lt;br /&gt;177 Hartford Road &lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; by William Inge - Directed by Fred T. Blish&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stranded overnight in a roadside diner in Kansas during a howling snowstorm, four passengers – a cowboy and his sidekick, a nightclub singer and an alcoholic derelict spend the night. Together with the local sheriff, a bus driver and the owner of the diner and her pretty young helper, they each have a story to tell. Set in the 1950's, this wonderful comedy, that was both a Broadway hit and a top selling film, is filled with love and laughs. This was LTM’s very first production in 1961 – join us for the start of our 50th anniversary season!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast includes Alysa Auriemma (Cherie), Nick Demetriades (Carl), Michael Forgetta (Lyman), Sara Logan (Grace), Bob Pelletier (Bo), Trish Urso (Elma), Dave Walton (Will), Mike Zizka (Virgil).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $22.11&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HAVE A VERY LIMITED NUMBER OF TICKETS IN THE CT THEATRE GROUP SECTION&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT WILL SELL OUT - GET YOUR TICKET NOW &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location will be emailed to all CT Theatre Group Ticket holders &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pick up your ticket before the show with the CT Theatre Group, or at the will call window &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HAVE A VERY LIMITED NUMBER OF TICKETS IN THE CT THEATRE GROUP SECTION&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT WILL SELL OUT - GET YOUR TICKET NOW &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 84 East or West: Take 384 Eastbound to exit 3. Go right at end of ramp. Take a left at first light (Hartford Road). Cheney Hall is about 1/2 mile on Right. Go past building and take a Right on Pine Street into the parking lot. From 384 Westbound: Take exit 3. Turn left and continue straight through stop light (Hartford Road). Cheney Hall is about 1/2 mile on Right. Go past building and take a Right on Pine Street into the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet the CT Theatre Group before the show, or pick up your tickets at the will call window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Connecticut Theatre Group Events</member_name><member_id>8868299</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268702013000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266780305000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> SAT March 13 – 8pm Bus Stop at Cheney Hall with Little Theatre of Manchester   </name><id>12664723</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268528400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/12664723/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/a/global_13236698.jpeg</photo_url></item>