<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>~~&gt;Look for the Brown Boat Launch sign</address_2><address_1>1050 Boston Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06043</zip><lat>41.796425</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Across from South Road</phone><name>Lower Bolton Lake Boat Launch</name><city>Bolton</city><id>607397</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.428860</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;The weather is not good for a nice paddle, some of you want to play tennis and go hiking, or other.&lt;br /&gt;thats ok,&lt;br /&gt;but some of you need to know how to do a few things before i let all of you hit the ocean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE I DONT WANT TO HAVE A REQUIREMENT THAT YOU MUST SAVE YOURSELF LIKE ALL THE OTHER GROUPS DO..AMC, CONNYAK, AND SO MANY OTHERS..&lt;br /&gt;BUT SADLY I MIGHT HAVE TO..LIABILITY REASONS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok im scared about having some of you on the more advanced paddles that start in July.&lt;br /&gt;The CT river is not forgiving, some of you have not fallen in that river in the locations i plan to bring you,&lt;br /&gt;Ok the ocean has its problems too, but a few simple safety practice things will make my life and everyone else's easier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bolton lake is warm enoug now for me and you to go in and practice wet exits and how to get back in not complicated but something ya will remember and might just use someday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not Charging for the yaks either here, you being able to save your buddy is priceless.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The biggest thing here is to get some of you able to see some self rescue, Paddle float re-entry, empting a recreational boat, not as easy as you think, maybe a T rescue, or a few other things that work, test out your PFD and find out it isnt that good, etc, but then you know its all still ok, just know things limits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I havent got wet this year yet..so why not do it here..you really dont have to go in yet, Its still cold, but be prepared it happens when you dont expect it LOL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope some other experienced paddlers join also, they can help too..&lt;br /&gt;so far things have worked out ok over the years...but even the Farmington River has its hazards..those tree branches, some current, etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im not able to rescue most of you..for obvious reasons..some nearby but thats it..so i need a few others who can assist in rescues..Just in case.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE CT RIVER is not as forgiving as the Farmington..and i have a few more events planned there...and along the shoreline areas...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ocean coves are actually ok (most of the time) bad weather well its fun if you can handle it..., but out more than a mile (or less) in the ocean...ya better know how to get back in and fast.......and have some other stuff...spray skirt..I am mixed on them for close proximity to shore..or in tree branches areas..but they have their purposes as you learn the advanced stuff...no need to get one  unless you plan on ocean things, or learning rolls , bracing..etc.....but with rec yaks...i would rather have you in the water fast without impedance..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This isnt a far distance paddle, just around the lake and beach area till it gets dark doing practice things, YOU do a few of them if you like...they are GET wet things, the water is pretty clean here so dont worry..its not like the CT River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;practice here and ya wont get the CT river water in your boat or up your nose and mouth...then get worms growing in you that will eat you from inside to out..or worse...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring  some food..because we cook lunch right there, or if it looks like a thunderstormS, There is a real interesting tunnel a mile away..creepy creatures...If some of you that are interested..(last time it was pretty good), yep the old fire pit and grill work here too...&lt;br /&gt;bring a chair, maybe a few hot doggs, for a fast snack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steady rain cancels the event, thunderstorms at the site if its ok when we start, we are out of the water in in the cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a easy to reach boat launch right off of rte 44 in Bolton that has plenty of parking and PortaPotties at the parking lot . Further to the east on the lake is a beach area that would be an excellent place to sit on the sand to eat some snacks. And to practice paddle float entries...if you have not one of these things...its a real life saver.&lt;br /&gt;you will see why..oh yeh and a pump, sponge , bail bucket..is ok too..but no where near the capacity of a good pump.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reason 1..standing in the mud up to your waiste is not fun if you even make it that far to the shore..most likely you are going to die here like those stickey traps for mice. reason 2 :better to pop back in fast, pump out fast and get going...There is hungry LEACHES, EELS, and Frankenstein Fish in there....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 East to Bolton Notch (off of rte 84 in East Hartford / Manchester line area)&lt;br /&gt;Follow 384 to the end..&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) rte 6 is to the right, stay on 44&lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, (Quarry Rd off to the left).. you will pass vernon rd, lakeside and keeny also)  continue to the next traffic light.&lt;br /&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. (across from South Road, bolton)&lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mapquest, GPS and others use 1050 Boston Turnpike (rte 44) Bolton to get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LESS THAN 5 YES RSVP's  ALSO CANCELS THE EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Toyota Avalon with a Kayak Trailer and a few Orange Traffic Cones</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214851793000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><why>I dont think its a good idea for CT river or ocean if you cant save yourself</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214493870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddling safety practice on Bolton lake</name><id>8220122</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214670600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8220122/</event_url></item>