<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by Neuro-Linguistic Programming (NLP). Here are the details of the August meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month we will introduce &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time Line Therapy&lt;/b&gt; (TLT)&lt;/span&gt; which is similar to hypnosis regression therapy, only using specific modalities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLP has a concept called the Time Line.  the presupposition is that everyone's unconscious mind organizes memories in a temporal manner - from past to future and that most people perceive their past in a specific direction and their future in another a specific direction. TLT was designed to take advantage of that and create a scenario where negative emotions, limiting decisions, and many other issues could be eliminated by going back to the root cause, via the time line.  It is exciting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reference can be found in Time Line Therapy and the Basis of Personality, by Tad James.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, I should be there by 6:30 to answer any questions or have any discussions that won't be covered in the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Come and enjoy and evening For a Change.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Martin&lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner, Master Hypnotherapist&lt;br /&gt;Positive Effects&lt;br /&gt;kenda_assoc@msn.com&lt;br /&gt;978-273-5905&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be:&lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go straight back to the large studio (after 7pm)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282316991000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278998483000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP August Natick Meetup - Time Line Therapy</name><id>dlfdnynlbzb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282259700000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/14086257/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/0/global_11885328.jpeg</photo_url></item>