<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>170 State st.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Red Door</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>990720</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.755290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dance @ the Red Door&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday Dec. 28th. 9 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Door   170 State st. Portsmouth, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962   ob@tds.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join me, Steve Ob1. for an evening of music, dancing and drinks @ the Red Door. We will be dancing to my very favorite Dj "RGO". This is not your usual Bar. It is a martini club. The Dj is also not your usual Dj. He can not take request. Because, he has a sound show that we will dance too all night, as he rocks the house. This Dj made me understand and see for the first time. What, "Rocking the house" really meant, and felt like.  The seating is large sofas and lounge chairs, no tables. I will be there trying to hold seats around 8:45. But seats can not really be held. Unless you are sitting in it or have your coat there. Don't look for the usual sign for the place. They only have a RED DOOR. But, it is located on left side of the street, at the end of State St., near the river, and near the bridge being repaired, and Prescott Park.  This is a small place, and if you get there late? You may have to wait to get in. Tell the man at the door. That you are friends with the Dj, or the Dj's Dad. The Dj is better known as, Ryan Obermiller, or RGO. That may get you in easier. Once this place gets too full and packed, around 10:30- 11ish. We may move on. We may decide to stay, or to walk down the street and check out some other clubs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No dress code, but $5. cover charge may be charged after 9:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.reddoorportsmouth.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.reddoorportsmouth.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look 4 the Meetup signs by the Dj.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356758067000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356535911000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dance @ the Red Door</name><id>96544852</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356746400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/96544852/</event_url></item>