<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Landsdowne Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>888 693-2583</phone><name>House Of Blues</name><city>Boston</city><id>881127</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095720</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SOLD OUT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***-The original block of tickets has sold out! Additional seats have been reserved. Extension of Deadline to RSVP and purchase a ticket to this Gospel Brunch is now Monday, March 1, at 11 am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***The Date for this event has been changed to Sunday, April 18 with an RSVP and Ticket purchase Deadline of Friday, February 26 at 3 pm. All House of Blues Gospel Brunches have limited capacity and sell out well in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Sox Natives have reserved 8 tickets for the April 18 show because you have asked for it!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $45.00 and must be purchased from the Red Sox Natives on this site at the time of your YES RSVP. There are no refunds. Maybe RSVPs will not be accepted. Please follow all directions when you RSVP. We reserve the right to change the terms of this event, change the RSVP date or cancel the event for lack of interest and payment. A Wait List is not available.  If the event sells out in advance please E Mail me (Frank) only if you are prepared to RSVP and purchase a ticket immediately.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A portion of the ticket proceeds will be donated at a later date to a charity of the Natives choice.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Sox play the Tampa Bay Rays at 1:30 pm that afternoon and some people may want to hang out and watch the game afterward. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details &lt;a href="http://www.houseofblues.com/venues/clubvenues/boston/gospelbrunch.php" target="_blank"&gt;HERE.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gospel Brunch is a one-of-a-kind live music show and dining experience. Guests will enjoy a delicious all-you-can-eat southern style buffet that features breakfast favorites plus a host of southern specialties. Every week different gospel groups from around the region will perform live on stage. The music is uplifting and energetic and guaranteed to get the crowd standing on their feet! &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will contact you by E Mail after all Reservations are finalized.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271772861000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265910179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>House of Blues Gospel Brunch on Sunday, April 18</name><id>12580901</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271599200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/12580901/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/0/global_13047584.jpeg</photo_url></item>