<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Granite State Room in the Memorial Union Buildingg</address_2><address_1>83 Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.137985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UNH </name><city>Durham</city><id>1217875</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.934301</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Visit &lt;a href="http://ouramericainitiative.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://ouramericainit...&lt;/a&gt;  and watch videos describing Gov. Johnson's positions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MARCH 30th -- Granite State Room -- 6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gary Johnson - Former Gov. of New Mexico with a pro-marijuana legalization, pro-freedom vision for America&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Tommasi - Cop, Economist, Professor and member of Law Enforcement Against Prohibition tells us why &amp;quot;Cops Say Legalize Drugs&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GARY JOHNSON&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gary Johnson serves as the Honorary Chairman of the Our America Initiative. He has been an outspoken advocate for efficient government, lower taxes, winning the war on drug abuse, protection of civil liberties, revitalization of the economy and promoting entrepreneurship and privatization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1994, Johnson was elected Governor of New Mexico despite having little experience in politics. He defeated the incumbent Democratic Governor Bruce King in the general election as well as a former Republican Governor in the primary election.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1998, Johnson was re-elected as governor, defeating Democratic Albuquerque Mayor Martin Chavez by a 55% to 45% margin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Governor of New Mexico, Johnson was known for his common-sense business approach to governing. He eliminated New Mexico’s budget deficit, cut the rate of growth in state government in half and privatized half of the state prisons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While in office, Governor Johnson vetoed 750 bills (which was more than all the combined vetoes of the other 49 Governors in the country at the time ) and thousands of line item vetoed bills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JOHN TOMMASI&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Tommasi joined the Salem (NH) Police Department in 1979, and he was already a sergeant by 1983. By 1987, he had been assigned to the New Hampshire Drug Task Force. Part of his time there included two years in which he worked undercover for the state’s attorney general in order to apprehend individuals involved in the trafficking of illegal drugs. From this vantage point, he saw immediately that the “War on Drugs” can’t be “won.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John holds a BA in Psychology, an MA in Business Administration and an MA in Economics from the University of New Hampshire. “One of my Master's theses was on the cost of enforcing drug laws in New Hampshire,” he relates. “I specifically looked at monies that would be saved if just marijuana were legalized. It’s a staggering amount.” Since 1981, John has been a college and university professor and currently, he is a part-time professor at the University of New Hampshire, Whittemore School of Business (Durham, NH); and a full-time professor at Bentley College.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270159563000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268625224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Former Governor Gary Johnson comes to UNH!</name><id>12878553</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269986400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/12878553/</event_url></item>