<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>440 Greenfield Rd, </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01351 </zip><lat>42.537994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-367-9580 </phone><name>The Night Kitchen</name><city>Montague</city><id>1414966</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.537997</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Night Kitchen! We have had so many people ask us about The Night Kitchen and now we have an EatUp! there in a couple of weeks. Hoorray!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be $40.00 and that included both tax and tip, so really the only expense that night will by any wine or alcoholic beverage you'd like to order. A real bargain for this meal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also be preordering our food (as we have done in the past a few times), here are the menu choices for entrees (appetizer, salad and dessert are all the same): (no need to respond to this email, just register with the link below and you will be asked to choose an entree there)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mushroom &amp;amp; gruyere pudding with black trumpet &amp;amp; burgundy reduction&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maple - bourbon glazed quail with wild rice, cranberry &amp;amp; pecan stuffing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crab stuffed rainbow trout with pink grapefruit &amp;amp; stoli beurre blanc&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;here are some rave reviews from the 'net:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Yelp!&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;i&gt;I'm so happy to hear that the word is out about the Night Kitchen. This is the best restaurant in the Pioneer Valley - period. The food is sublime - a small menu consisting of local ingredients cooked to perfection - the waitstaff is friendly, accommodating, and professional, and the setting is beautiful for a date or a casual dinner out.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chowhound&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;i&gt;Excellent food, modest prices for the quality of ingredients and preparation, good wines without inflated prices, pleasant staff and beautiful location in an old mill building on the edge of a river. It shares the building with a great used book store, the Montague Book Mill, which makes for a swell extended afternoon-evening visit.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sounds like a great time, I know we are looking forward to the experience. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine &amp;amp; Jessica&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289655715000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288282479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Night Kitchen in Montague-the people's choice!</name><id>15259530</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289518200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/15259530/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/0/global_19137328.jpeg</photo_url></item>