<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup expenses</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>****SEE MAP IN FILES AREA OF THIS SITE****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month we meet at the home of Tom &amp;amp; Lee in Gorham.  The full agenda is TBD but it will be focused on green building with a chance to see one of the few LEED certified homes in the state of Maine (there will be slides/photos as part of the discussion of this house!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we don't do a specific narrow green building topic (check back in a couple of weeks) then we may do a green building roundup of what's going on across the state so people can &amp;quot;plug in&amp;quot; in whatever way appeals to them.  If you know of stuff going on with residential alt energy, straw bale, cob, earth berm, net zero, &amp;quot;mainstream&amp;quot; green bldg, etc. - please email me and let me know!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[A week earlier than normal to accomodate a special meetup on 11/14 and not have too many events in one week!  Sorry to conflict with voting day, but...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrive between 6 and 6:30&lt;br /&gt;6:30 potluck supper&lt;br /&gt;7:15 discussion w/photos.../tour/etc starts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*NEW* Don't forget to bring your own potluck kit of plate/bowl/cup/utensils/cloth napkin - we're trying to move away from disposable or even compostable stuff starting this month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potluck breakdown: &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with A-G bring whatever you want &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with H-M bring bread or beverage &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with N-S main or side dish to share &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with T-Z bring salad or veg or dessert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS NOTE:  This is a fairly new street so refer to the map in the FILES area of this site if needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CARPOOL:  Meet at Marginal Way Park-and-Ride at 5:45 to depart no later than 6:00 to head to Gorham.  If you want to carpool, start a thread on the message board and don't forget your phone or cell phone number if applicable.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194564775000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191972690000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Meetup:  Residential Green Building</name><id>6520625</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194391800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/6520625/</event_url></item>