<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>647 Broadway (Rt.1)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.501931</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781)-941-2220</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Saugus </city><id>1064209</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.014707</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Suzan Lindstrom, a fellow Law of Attraction practitioner and professional writer, has invited our group to take part in an exciting new book project!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She will be tapping into the vast knowledge of Law of Attraction practitioners around the world &amp;ndash; from Dubai, one of the richest nations in the world to India, Canada, London, Ireland, and the USA; in search of&amp;nbsp; identifying the most compelling questions newcomers ask about LOA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The answers will come with insights from the more seasoned practitioners. You might say this book is &amp;ldquo;for the people and by the people,&amp;rdquo; sharing globally our knowledge about the Law of Attraction. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Suzan is a long-time member of the Portland Oregon Law of Attraction for Happiness Meetup group and a professional writer with many years experience. She is authoring a book for those starting on their path to enlightenment using LOA and as a boost to the more experienced practitioners. She plans on gathering compelling stories from select individuals about &amp;ldquo;How the Law of Attraction has changed their lives?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to be a part of this exciting adventure, Please join us:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April 18, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panera Bread in Saugus, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located off Route #1 in the Marshalls parking Lot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;love &amp;amp; gratitude&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ellen Sklaver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;617-750-4830&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting in the back, closed off, room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>9941060</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334794689000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>northofbostonlawofattraction</urlname><id>567480</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The North-of-Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334066978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>You are Invited to Take Part in an Exciting LOA Book Project</name><id>59965822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334790000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/northofbostonlawofattraction/events/59965822/</event_url></item>