<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well my saga with my mother's health seems to be under wraps for now.  Just returned from Reading 2 weeks ago and am in AZ until our next meeting which will be&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;February 2nd, WEDNESDAY (not Tuesday) 2010 from 7 PM onward.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come with questions, concerns and help for our fellow sufferers.  I will be talking about the nature of our stress reactions and how to temper our brains reaction to stress so we can have less pain and stop stress related flareups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also be bringing my new &amp;quot;toy&amp;quot; for pain with me.  I am now using it in my practice.  I use the LaserOneTouch cold laser/micro-electro current wand.  This little item is the only thing that helped me when I fell down my stairs three months ago.  I have always thought cold laser and micro current therapies are fabulous for Fibromyalgia symptoms but coupled together and now available over the counter I want everyone to know about this.  So far there hasn't been anyone in my AZ meetup groups (both the FM support and Alternative Healing Group who haven't  found some benefit from it).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to experience a 2-4 minute session at the meetup call me and schedule a time after the meeting has ended and I will give you a chance to see how it works.  Call me at 623-251-7547.  I will only work on people who have preregistered for a session as it will be late when we get started so call me if you are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Betsy&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Timmerman</member_name><member_id>3507700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296704448000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People With Fibromyalgia</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fibromyalgia-301</urlname><id>586410</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>The Reading Fibromyalgia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294177840000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading Fibromyalgia Support Group Meetup</name><id>15918338</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296691200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fibromyalgia-301/events/15918338/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_1805463.jpeg</photo_url></item>