<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What better location in which to have a paranormal group's meeting could there be?  Molly Malone's ghosts have been written up a number of times in regional, national, and international literature and media.  In fact, BBC is filming there March 13!  (details of that are in a separate e-mail)  This meeting, like all our mothly 3rd Thursdays, is primarily a social gathering.  However, business is bound to come up (like details on the forthcoming Central Wave investigation, along with a recount of the &amp;quot;incident&amp;quot; that took place there during an impromptu attempt to map baseline readings). And Jill and the Gloucester people might be there, and fill the rest of us in on how their Houghton Manor TAPS investigation went.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS.  I've already spoken to Molly Malone's manager, and if enough people commit to attending, they'll open up the restaurant area for us and let us sit where we'd like (hint, hint: there are a number of phenomena reported coming from the tables in the far left corner from the State Street door).  Malone's might turn out to be a far more interesting place to hold a meeting than I initially thought!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a black fleece vest, and looking very much like my photo...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206227057000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203642358000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group March Meeting</name><id>7382289</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206054000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/7382289/</event_url></item>