<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>87 Perkins Row</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.631830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-887-9264</phone><name>Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>669386</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.925970</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>About the Hike&lt;br /&gt;This hike and social is designed for those who enjoy smaller groups and who have a lot of leisurely time to spend outside, without a day end deadline.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The focus of this hike will be enjoying the wildlife, in particular the birds around us.  We have spotted numberous birds  here such as the great blue herons, a northern flicker, double-crested cormorants, baby kingbirds, flycatchers, and cedar waxwings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave at 9:10. The hike and picnic lunch will be a minimum of 3 hours, but could go substantially longer depending on how people are feeling. We will probably hike anywhere from 3.5 to 4.5 miles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please note that the sanctuary does charge a $4 per person entrance fee. There are restrooms on site.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Bring&lt;br /&gt;B.Y.O.B.S. (Bring your own Bird Seed)  Just kidding!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;We will share!  At different points in the walk, you will be able to hand feed chickadees.   Sometime tufted titmouses and nuthatches will also be brave enough to eat out of your hand. Please also bring along &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;lunch&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, a camera, binoculars, bug spray and either sneakers or hiking boots.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails/Landscape&lt;br /&gt;Massachusetts Audubon's largest sanctuary, this property covers 2,800 acres of diverse habitats, including fields, vernal pools, forests, swamps, islands, eskers, and eight miles of the Ipswich River. Many species of animals make their home here either seasonally or year round. The Sanctuary offers an observation tower, a backyard-bird observation area and ten miles of trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to the Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Ipswich_River/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massaudubo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Boston and the south: Take Rt I-95 north to exit 50 and follow Rt 1 north. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97, turn right onto Rt 97 south (toward Beverly and Danvers). Follow Rt 97 south and look for a a very small, white Audubon sign.  Take the third left onto Perkins &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Row&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, not Perkins Lane. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for another small, audubon sign for the turn into the wildlife center, The address is 87 Perkins Row (not Perkins Lane). The street numbers are odd - they go up and then back down again!  Drive up the hill to sanctuary parking lot on the left.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Take Rt I-95 south to exit 53A and follow Rt 97 south. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97 in Topsfield, stay on Rt 97 south and look for a very small, white Audubon sign.  Take the third left onto Perkins &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Row&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, not Perkins Lane.  Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right&lt;br /&gt;Look for another small, audubon sign for the turn into the wildlife center. The address is 87 Perkins Row (not Perkins Lane). The street numbers are odd - they go up and then back down again!  Drive up the hill to sanctuary parking lot on the left.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting some of you and seeing others again! &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot with meetup stickers on.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1285515711000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283188595000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Birding Walk at Ipswich River with many stops and a picnic lunch</name><id>14592060</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284814800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/14592060/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/d/global_6592605.jpeg</photo_url></item>