<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.319171</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413.584.5848</phone><name>Pleasant Street Theater</name><city>Northampton</city><id>1073904</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.629255</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We'll meet in front of the theater before 7:15 and sit together; if we miss each other, we'll meet when the movie ends. After the movie, we'll go to Haymarket (or wherever the group wants to go).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SOLITARY MAN tells the story of Ben Kalmen, a fifty-something New Yorker and former successful car dealer, who through his own bad choices lost his entire business.  On the verge of a comeback, Ben finds some of the same motivations that led to his demise are threatening to take him down again. He's divorced from Nancy, his college sweetheart and the one person who knows him better than anyone.  Although he still finds the time to hang out with his daughter, Susan, and his adoring grandson, she cuts him off when she discovers him seeing one of her friends. His girlfriend, Jordan, is the daughter of a very influential businessman who's on the board of a major auto manufacturer.   If Ben can just keep his hubris in check for a little while longer, he'll be back as big as ever. But circumstances place him in very close proximity with the one girl he shouldn't touch, throwing everything into jeopardy.  Stars Michael Douglas, Susan Sarandon, Danny Devito and Mary Louise Parker and Jenna Fischer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check on Wed. as to who has RSVP'd, so you can see their pics, and find them at the theater.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathon Podolsky</member_name><member_id>9289550</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278610696000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>filmgroup</urlname><id>1279822</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Western MA Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278291582000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Solitary Man", Wednesday July 7 @ 7:15pm</name><id>14002380</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278544500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/filmgroup/events/14002380/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/1/9/global_14597145.jpeg</photo_url></item>