<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:45, so let's meet right outside the screening room at 7:15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1132620/" target="_blank"&gt;The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo&lt;/a&gt; was the first movie of the South By Southwest Film Festival I attended a few weeks ago in Austin, TX. And I couldn't get in because there weren't any seats left. As I talked to people over the course of the 5 days I was there, I was talking up my favorite movies and they were talking up theirs. Dragon Tattoo came up in conversation a lot. When you see 4 or 5 movies a day, you only talk about the really good ones. So I'm psyched to find this &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/node/2623" target="_blank"&gt;movie playing at the Coolidge Corner theater&lt;/a&gt;! Now I can get a seat!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets cost $9.75. Sorry, there's no discount to this theater! This movie has subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 6:30. The movie starts at 7:00. Everyone's responsible for getting their own ticket at this theater. We'll meet right in the lobby, in front of whatever theater is playing the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Forty years ago, Harriet Vanger disappeared from a family gathering on the island owned and inhabited by the powerful Vanger clan. Her body was never found, yet her uncle is convinced it was murder and that the killer is a member of his own tightly knit but dysfunctional family. He employs disgraced financial journalist Mikael Blomkvist and the tattooed, ruthless computer hacker Lisbeth Salander to investigate. When the pair link Harriet's disappearance to a number of grotesque murders from almost forty years ago, they begin to unravel a dark and appalling family history. But the Vanger's are a secretive clan, and Blomkvist and Salander are about to find out just how far they are prepared to go to protect themselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271892418000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269451475000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo</name><id>12980049</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270077300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12980049/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>