<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>381 Connecticut 80</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06419</zip><lat>41.362172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chatfield Hollow State Park</name><city>Killingworth</city><id>1191601</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.581165</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ragged Mountain Foundation picnic is Sunday August 12th at Chatfield Hollow. The RMF is a group of climbers and hikers who own Ragged Mountain in Southington CT. The annual picnic is our way of saying thanks to the people who have supported us throughout the year and introduce ourselves to new climbers. &lt;br /&gt;

All are welcome. We will be setting up ropes for climbing around 10:00 and firing up the grills around 2:00. &lt;br /&gt;

We will provide the basics - burgers, dogs, veggie burgers, drinks, etc. If you have a favorite item, chips, dip, side dish, salad, desert, or special dietary requirement, feel free to bring it along and perhaps a little extra to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;

Chatfield Holow is a state park in killingworth and charges admission – to avoid this you may park at the Chatfield trail head on rt 80 or in the public parking at the entrance but before the gate. (gets crowded) From New haven - take I-95 to exit 61 (rt 79 in Madison) . Take RT 79 north to Rt 80 ( circle) - turn right and follow rt 80 east to Chatfield Hollow . As you are heading east on rt 80 you will eventually head down a long hill. There will be a pullout on the right with parking for the Chatfield trail (climber's lot). If you miss the pull out you will reach the bottom of the hill and arrive at the main entrance to Chatfield. ( park there or go back up hill )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the pull out climber's lot parking area walk uphill until you arrive at the barrier on the right – drop down into the woods, take a left after about 50 feet and follow the climber trails to the cliff 100 yards or so orange trail nearby - the cliff can be seen from road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you choose to park inside the park - go around the lake to a field and park. It is close to the exit. I will arrive early and try to snag a table. From there Go to the road or take the orange (deep woods) trail for 15 minutes until you arrive at the cliff&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Loter</member_name><member_id>2298440</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345080676000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctrockclimbing</urlname><id>1388805</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>CT Rock Climbing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343610508000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ragged Mountain Foundation Picnic at Chatfield</name><id>75459212</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344780000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctrockclimbing/events/75459212/</event_url></item>