<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come help Noche Latina Dance Company celebrate its First Anniversary at Ryles tomorrow night, Tuesday January 29th. Even if you haven't visited Salsa Tuesdays lately, it would be great to see you come and enjoy what is expected to be a GREAT party! Please feel free to bring your friends as well. &lt;br /&gt;Two DJ's will be spinning the best of salsa for you tomorrow: DJ Hernan (you know him, no need to say more, come say hello) and DJ Guy (he will have you dancing like there's no tomorrow, you may know him from Fridays in the upstairs lounge @ Mojitos). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLDC is keeping regular class schedule that night so you will not miss out on the new combinations they teach each week.  If you haven't taken one of their classes lately, please come try it out.  If you are new to Salsa Tuesdays and are coming with a friend, one of you gets to take the class for free (so only $8 to get in, take the class, and stay for the night). Email nldcsalsa@gmail.com for this guest list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For $13, you get all the classes and the dancing afterwards.  If you can't make it to classes, it's only $8 for the dance party after 9.30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class schedule: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM ? 8:15 PM Beginner/Adv Beginner Salsa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:15 PM ? 8:30 PM Free Introductory Class (Check schedule for this month?s dance)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 PM ? 9:30 PM Intermediate/Advanced Salsa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 9.30 PM - the party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you all at our First Anniversary at Ryles Party tomorrow night (Tuesday February 29th).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you are not sure who I am or what I look like, as whoever is at the door for me :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Masha</member_name><member_id>2901990</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201824556000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>It's going to be a great big party and the more people come, the better it will be</why><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201549539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join Noche Latina in celebrating 1st anniversary @ Ryles!</name><id>7214644</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201651200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/7214644/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/3/global_522835.jpeg</photo_url></item>