<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Holland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397213</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Johnny D's Uptown Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1555567</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122986</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, October 5, 7:30 pm-12:45 am: &lt;br /&gt;

HONK! Kick-Off Concert &lt;br /&gt;

A showcase for the following visiting HONK! bands: &lt;br /&gt;

7:30-8:30pm: Church Marching Band (Sonoma, CA); &lt;br /&gt;

8:30-9:30pm: Brass Messengers (Minneapolis, MN); &lt;br /&gt;

9:30-10:30pm: Veveritse (Brooklyn, NY); &lt;br /&gt;

10:30-11:30pm: Young Fellaz Brass Band (New Orleans, LA); &lt;br /&gt;

11:30pm-12:30am: Pink Puffers Brass Band (Rome, Italy); &lt;br /&gt;

12:30-12:45am: jam session with all of the above. &lt;br /&gt;

Johnny D’s Uptown Restaurant and Music Club, 17 Holland St., Davis Square, Somerville, MA 02144 &lt;br /&gt;

[Conveniently located near the Davis Square stop on the Red Line and several MBTA bus connections.] &lt;br /&gt;

Ticket: $12 general admission, available at the door (cash only). &lt;br /&gt;

For information: 617-776-2004, www.johnnyds.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, October 7, 8 pm: &lt;br /&gt;

HONK! All-Band Blowout Concert: &lt;br /&gt;

A showcase for most if not all of the HONK! bands participating in the 4-day HONK! Festival. Those bands are: &lt;br /&gt;

AfroBrazil, Brass Balagan, Brass Liberation Orchestra, Brass Messengers, The Bread &amp;amp; Puppet Theater Circus Band, Caka!ak Thunder, Carnival Band, Chaotic Insurrection Ensemble, Chaotic Noise Marching Corp, Church Marching Band, Detroit Party Marching Band, Dirty Water Brass Band, DJA-Rara, EE-Environmental Encroachment, Emperor Norton's Stationary Marching Band, Expandable Brass Band, Extraordinary Rendition Band, Forward! Marching Band, Gora Gora Orkestar, Hill Stompers, Himalayas, Leftist Marching Band, Loyd Family Players, Lungs Face Feet, Minor Mishap Marching Band, Pink Puffers Brass Band, The Primate Fiasco, Rude Mechanical Orchestra, Second Line Social Aid &amp;amp; Pleasure Society Brass Band, Seed and Feed Marching Abominable, tint(A)nar, Veveritse, What Cheer? Brigade, and Young Fellaz Brass Band. &lt;br /&gt;

Sanders Theater, 45 Quincy Street, Cambridge, MA 02138 &lt;br /&gt;

[Conveniently located near the Harvard Square stop on the Red Line and several MBTA bus connections.] &lt;br /&gt;

Ticket: $15 general admission, $10 for students, available at the door (credit cards accepted). &lt;br /&gt;

Advance tickets (go on sale Tues., Sept. 25) can be purchased at the Harvard Box Office by calling 617.496.2222 (TTY 617.495.1642), online at www.boxoffice.harvard.edu/Online/, or in person: 1350 Mass. Ave., Cambridge, MA 02138 [hours: Tuesday-Sunday, 12:00-6:00 pm]&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349490845000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349111086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Honk!'s Two Ticketd Concerts</name><id>84954452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349479800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/84954452/</event_url></item>