<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I forgot to pin down the show time....sorry.   We will be seeing the 7:50 showing so lets all meet at 7:15.  The movie is showing upstairs so I will be in the area near the coffee/ice cream concession stand.  I will try to snag a table.  I will be wearing my usual badge so new folks can find me.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enchanted &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PGsome scary images and mild innuendoThe tale follows the beautiful princess Giselle (Amy Adams) as she is banished by an evil queen (Susan Sarandon) from her magical, musical animated land ? and finds herself in the gritty reality of the streets of modern-day Manhattan. Shocked by this strange new environment that doesn?t operate on a happily ever after basis, Giselle is now adrift in a chaotic world badly in need of enchantment. But when Giselle begins to fall in love with a charmingly flawed divorce lawyer (Patrick Dempsey) who has come to her aid ? even though she is already promised to a perfect fairy tale prince (James Marsden) back home ? she has to wonder: Can a storybook view of romance survive in the real world?Read More &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Amy Adams, Patrick Dempsey, James Marsden, Timothy Spall &lt;br /&gt;Director: Kevin Lima &lt;br /&gt;Genres: Fairy Tales &amp;amp; Legends, Comedy, Family-Oriented Comedy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197694713000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191087008000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enchanted</name><id>6451992</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196554500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6451992/</event_url></item>