<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>707 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02061</zip><lat>42.161495</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-659-0050</phone><name>Mount Blue</name><city>Norwell</city><id>833131</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.791390</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a Friday night of Dinner, Appetizers, Entertainment and Socializing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to your votes, we will be going to Mount Blue, which is located on Route 123 in Norwell and co-owned by members of the band Aerosmith.  Mount Blue offers a wide assortment of menu items with prices ranging from $6-$23.  Weekends include music, which starts at 9pm.  We'll arrive early enough to eat and socialize before the music begins.  All are welcome to stay and listen to the music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, February 9th @ 7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Mount Blue &lt;br /&gt;707 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Route 123 &lt;br /&gt;Norwell, MA 02061&lt;br /&gt;781-659-0050&lt;br /&gt;www.mountblue.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max:  There is no maximum at the moment.  Up to 2 Guests per person are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline:  Currently there is no registration deadline.  However, the Organizers reserve the right to cut-off &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; RSVP's one week or more in advance if the venue is in need of an accurate count more than the day before the event.  In addition, if &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; RSVP's are closed and the venue does need a head count more than the day before the event &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; RSVP's may not be included in the final count.  Therefore, it is important that you provide an accurate count and update your RSVP to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; if you do plan to attend the event and we close registrations for &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; RSVP's.  As always, please try to make any updates 24 hours prior to the event but be sure finalize your RSVP by Noon on the day of the event.  Any changes after that time may  not be received by the Organizer, thus they might not know of your changed.&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizers: Angela and Jen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash.  You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Mount Blue is located on route 123 in the village of Norwell, approximately 3 miles from either route 3 or route 3A.&lt;br /&gt;*Driving SOUTH on Route 3 (from Boston) Get off at exit 13, turn left off ramp. Drive less than a half mile to the first traffic light and turn RIGHT on route 123. Mount Blue is 3.2 miles on left. &lt;br /&gt;*Driving NORTH on Route 3 (from Plymouth) Get off at exit 13, turn right off ramp. Drive less than a half mile to the first traffic light. Turn right on route 123. Mount Blue is 3.2 miles on left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Driving From Route 3A: Take Route 123, in Scituate, west (toward Norwell). Traveling north on 3A, go left on 123 traveling south on 3A...you can figure it out... Mount Blue is approximately 3 miles on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171821702000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169420491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner, Appetizers, and Entertainment!</name><id>5413555</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171067400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5413555/</event_url></item>