<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Railroad Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06426</zip><lat>41.351651</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 767-0103</phone><name>Essex Steam Train &amp; Riverboat</name><city>Essex</city><id>1015069</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.405971</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's step back into time with a real steam train ride along the CT River, followed by a riverboat cruise on the river itself. Relaxing, serene and all with good company! Join us for this event which is sure to be loads of fun and I promise to make it this time...LOL!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the train ride and cruise, we are all heading over to The Blue Oar for a little dinner and alot of laughs. What a great day this promises to be. So hop on board to start the fun! Read on...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RIDE THE STEAM TRAIN!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two coal-fired locomotives are available to pull the collection of lovingly restored railroad cars. You will be swept away by the hiss of steam, the blast of the whistle, and the clickety-clack of the tracks. From the exciting &amp;quot;All Aboard&amp;quot; to the engineer checking the locomotive before the run, you will experience an authentic journey back to the days of steam. You will find forests and streams, beautiful vistas and nostalgic towns, and some gorgeous views of the Connecticut River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RIDE THE STEAMBOAT!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steam Train passengers who purchase tickets for the river boat ride disembark at Deep River Landing. Here, you board a riverboat for a relaxing and informative ride up the beautiful Connecticut River, from Deep River to East Haddam. Sit back, take in the fresh air, and learn about the history and natural wonder of the Connecticut River. In the heat of summer, the Connecticut River is alive with recreational boaters and vacationers. At other times of the year, the river boat ride is a quieter, more reflective experience. You will see more of the natural wonders that make the Connecticut River special - coves and inlets, islets and deep water, each home to fish, fowl, and river vegetation. Bald Eagles are seen during some seasons. You can also get a glimpse of man-made wonders - bridges, ferries, and river-front homes. Highlights include the historic Goodspeed Opera House and Gillette Castle. Throughout, we'll tell you about the history, natural wonders, and legends that abound in these waters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TASTE THE FOOD...THE BLUE OAR!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soak in stunning Connecticut River views from your colorful picnic table while you enjoy fresh seafood dishes cooked on a six-foot industrial grill. The Blue Oar, once a snack bar, has only outdoor seating. It's not like you'd want to sit inside with a setting like this. Seafood specials change daily, and there are plenty of land-roving options for the non-fish eaters out there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Hours:Daily, 11 a.m.-9 p.m. Cuisine:Seafood and American Meals ...Served:Dinner and Lunch... Price Range:$$$ ($16-$25)... Reservations:Not Required... Dress Code:Anything Goes... Alcohol:&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;BYOB ...    Specialties:Lobster Rolls ,Seasonal Seafood Menu, Steak, Ribs... Payment Methods:&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT INFO!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Steam Train leaves at 2pm ...from there we will go on the cruise. Both activities take approxamately 2 1/2&lt;br /&gt;hours. From there, onto The Blue Oar. Now, if I have 20 or more people, our cost for train and cruise is $22.00...if less than 20, it will be $26.00. Another point...The Blue Oar is BYOB and cash only!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whew!!!! If I forgot anything...let me know and I will  update...lol!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will meet at the train station!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1249603251000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247953560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Essex  Steam Train &amp; Riverboat followed by dinner at The Blue Oar Restaurant!!!</name><id>10905714</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249236000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/10905714/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/c/global_9725228.jpeg</photo_url></item>