<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pawtucket Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.643787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-459-0802</phone><name>Heritage Farm Ice Cream &amp; Restuarant</name><city>Lowell</city><id>1314481</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;- For all you folks that miss not having that FREE CONCERT ON THE RIVER every Monday night. It's been a great place to gather and enjoy some good times. So let’s keep it going! &lt;br /&gt;

 - For all you folks that didn’t have the opportunity to join us over the summer, we want to meet you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the concert series has ended for this year, let's keep this place and time special for our Monday evening gatherings. It can be a unique place to meet after work and get some exercise at the same time. We’ll do an easy ¾ to 1 hr walk along the river while enjoying the beautiful, changing foliage. &lt;br /&gt;

 Next we’ll stake out our piece of turf. So bring your chairs and snacks like you did for the concerts. We’ll gather around our new outdoor heater and have a fun social gathering. Let's share; up and coming events, exciting past events, personal experiences/adventures, or whatever. We’ll even have some “non-live” background music. Then, let’s brainstorm ideas for future Monday evening gatherings right here at our place along the river. Anything goes as long as it’s legal and can be done in public! I know I have a few crazy ideas and I'm sure you all can come up with some wild ones as well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll have a high powered heater to gather around and stay warm. But you may want to bring a blanket, jacket, gloves, hat, ear muffs, etc. Hot; coffee, cider, soup, and stuff like that are HIGHLY encouraged. If it gets too cold we'll say “forget this” and go for pizza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll meet between 5:30 - 5:45pm at the concert park benches just across the street from Heritage Ice Cream &amp;amp; Restaurant. For those that don’t know me, I’ll have a MEETUP pin on the back of my cap. If you come later, we’ll be the only group sitting around a heater with a blue light. You can also call me @ 603 204 -1657.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349141594000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349046377000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Walk &amp; Talk Along the River of the FREE Concerts!</name><id>84845462</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349127000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/84845462/</event_url></item>