<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;28 drafts, 8 bottled beers, classic cocktails and charcuterie.. what more can one ask for on a gorgeous summer night?&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On January 4th, 2007 Aaron Sanders, Max Toste and Josh Velazquez opened the doors to Deep Ellum, a collaborative venture born out of their shared appreciation of craft beer, classic cocktails, and wholesome cooking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trio agreed that paramount to their enterprise was creating a locale in which patrons could enjoy and explore the variety of tastes and flavors offered in a convivial and unassuming atmosphere. While feeling they have succeeded to this end, they regard Deep Ellum as an ever evolving concept and community and welcome those intrigued to join them in the experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And what does Deep Ellum mean, anyway? The name Deep Ellum refers to an area of Dallas known for its fabulous music, incomparable food and enticing nightlife since the early 1900’s. The area has produced some of the most influential names in blues and jazz and today it is considered one the United States’ touchstones for fashion, culture, art, food and above all, music. It is this same spirit Deep Ellum of Allston hopes to invoke among its guests.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leigh and Krisy </member_name><member_id>8616476</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247357220000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245941639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and Drinks on the Patio at Deep Ellum</name><id>10733509</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247184000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/10733509/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/9/global_9336729.jpeg</photo_url></item>