<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Northampton St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.260496</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-538-7431</phone><name>Summit View</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>722395</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.610911</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Summit View Meetinghouse and Banquet Facility provides for a quaint and charming gathering spot along rte. 5 across the Connceticut River.  On Friday evenings the Summit View holds free outdoor concerts at their Pavilion.  From 5:30 to 8:30p.m. a BBQ buffet is provided.  All food and drinks must be purchased on the premises.  Concerts begin at 6:30p.m.   Brass Attack, Southern New England's finest live dance band, is a nine piece band featuring four horns, a rythm section, and a lead vocalist, performing the hits of artisits like Tower of Power, Chicago, Frank Sinatra, James Brown, Glen Miller, Van Morrison, Blood Sweat and Tears, and classic hits from the 1930's through the 1990's.  The unique instrumentation and high degree of musicianship lend to the band's versatility and professionalism.  Members of the band have performed with prominent national acts such as The Tonight Show Band, Tavares, Ray Charles, The Four Tops, The Temptations, NRBG, Dizzy Gillepsie, Earth Wind &amp;amp; Fire and Aretha Franklin.  Brass Attack is the rage of Western Mass and a must for a cool summer night!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>4671887</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221608736000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1514</urlname><id>824401</id><group_lat>42.0999984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5899963379</group_lon><name>Single Mingle Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218163664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Outoor Concert:  Brass Attack</name><id>8501564</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221256800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1514/events/8501564/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/e/global_3300622.jpeg</photo_url></item>