<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This only meetup in Boston that brings together nonprofits and businesses to work on collaboration and partnerships in an informative and fun format. We will be having a short presentation on social media for nonprofits and how it can benefit your organization. Every month we bring one local nonprofit into the spotlight and all the donations go directly to the organization. The spotlight nonprofit is AFC Mentoring for our next meetup. Edelstein &amp;amp; Company will provide lunch for those who attend. Look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00-12:15pm - Networking with food and drink&lt;br /&gt;12:15-1:45pm - Short introductions, monthly nonprofit spotlight talk &lt;a href="http://www.afcmentoring.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.afcmentori...&lt;/a&gt;, followed by a presentation on Nonprofit Finances: It’s Mysteries Revealed by Alfonso Perillo of Edelstein &amp;amp; Company LLP.&lt;br /&gt;1:45-2pm - More Networking and collaborating&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nonprofit Finances: It’s Mysteries Revealed&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No one expects a Director or an Executive of a nonprofit organization to be a nonprofit accounting or finance expert.  However, you do need to know how to spot problems, ask the right questions, and have access to accurate information to make decisions.  Recent developments and trends in the nonprofit environment, including the new 990, require nonprofit organizations to be more transparent.  Here are some of the key things you’ll learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. How to judge the financial health of a nonprofit organization&lt;br /&gt;2. Fundraising: Do’s and Don’ts&lt;br /&gt;3. Why do I need to know the difference between the accrual and cash basis of accounting&lt;br /&gt;4. Simple steps you can take to prevent fraud&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alfonso Perillo, CPA, CFE, MSW -- Alfonso has worked in public accounting for 13 years. He specializes in providing auditing, review and taxation services to nonprofits, including private foundations and public charities.  He is a certified fraud examiner, and has worked with clients to conduct lost-profit analyses, internal control assessments and fraud examinations.  Prior to beginning his career in public accounting, he was a social worker where he worked with a variety of populations including children, the elderly and adults with brain injuries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alfonso received his Bachelor of Arts from Boston College, and his Master of Social Work from Boston University.  He is a member of the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, Massachusetts Society of Certified Public Accountants, and the Association of Certified Fraud Examiners.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Edelstein &amp;amp; Company LLP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.edelsteincpa.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.edelsteinc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edelstein &amp;amp; Company LLP has been providing high-quality services to nonprofit organizations for almost forty years.  Our nonprofit department is comprised of individuals dedicated to that sector.  We work exclusively with nonprofits and keep up to date with the industry’s best practices, accounting pronouncements and tax changes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our client base consists of over 150 nonprofit organizations including public charities, private and operating foundations, supporting organizations, and social welfare organizations. We service clients ranging from small start-ups to large multimillion dollar nonprofit organizations that are household names. Our clients are museums, foundations, public advocacy groups, education institutions, human service organizations and others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adoption and Foster Care Mentoring:&lt;br /&gt;In early spring 2002, AFC Mentoring made its first mentor/mentee “match.” AFC Mentoring became an independent 501(c)(3) in 2004 and continues to provide programs to serve both youth in foster care and those adopted out of care. Since its inception, AFC has enjoyed continuous growth and success in matching youth with highly committed volunteer mentors. AFC Mentoring continues to be among only a few mentoring organizations in the United States, and the only mentoring organization in the Boston area, that exclusively serves the unique, pressing needs of youth in the foster care system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Video Testimonials:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6b20_ZHxlJs" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PYiuQ8gFX24" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I met some great people who were willing to share ideas and thoughts. Everyone wants to help - it really is a win/win situation. ” - Danielle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“A good group of experienced professionals with diversified expertise but one thing in common: enthusiasm for social changes. Clear agenda, well organized meeting. People are genuinely willing to help each other. I can see great ideas forming and real collaborations happening. ” - Jing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PS. Remember to bring your own name tag this will help brand your organization more effectively.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsors of the event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Nonprofit Career Coach a division of Jobs In Nonprofits (&lt;a href="http://www.thenonprofitcareercoach.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thenonprof...&lt;/a&gt;) and Edelstein &amp;amp; Company LLP (&lt;a href="http://www.edelsteincpa.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.edelsteinc...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a name tag - Bring your own name tag please!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark McCurdy, NGO Career Coach</member_name><member_id>4242482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276013557000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Social Impact Community</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Social-Impact-Community</urlname><id>1383232</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Social Impact Success Community Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268115073000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Impact Circle April Meetup</name><id>xbqdnyngbrb</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271952000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Social-Impact-Community/events/12825817/</event_url></item>