<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Yes, it's still on, even though it's Patriot's Day in Massachusetts.  The topic will be &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Find Query Problems Proactively With Query Reviews&amp;quot; and here's the description (Sheeri will present):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wikipedia defines a code review as a “systematic examination (often as peer review) of computer source code intended to find and fix mistakes overlooked in the initial development phase, improving both the overall quality of software and the developers’ skills.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn’t it be great to do the same thing, but for the queries run against your databases? This presentation shows you how to do exactly that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;mk-query-digest is a Maatkit tool that can digest queries (similar to the output of mysqldumpslow) in a report. This can be a one-off report, or it can be stored in MySQL for a meta-database of queries. You can use this process to systematically go through every type of query that is sent by the code and set about approving or annotating each query type. For example, I have used this system to EXPLAIN each type of query, so that queries can be optimized before they show up in the slow query log.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation will show how to review the queries in your system on a one-time or ongoing basis. Being able to review new queries before code is released allows you to catch problematic queries before it goes to production. By saving the results in MySQL, you can take the large project of “make sure every query is optimized” and break it into manageable chunks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;Logistics&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's map with the building (E51) highlighted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's map with the Kendall square T stop highlighted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=L5&amp;amp;Landmarks=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(the stop is in red on that map, and you can see E51 in the bottom right)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's maps with parking lot information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P4&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P5&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that MIT lots are free to park in after 3 pm or so, even if it says &amp;quot;reserved for faculty&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free pizza and soda will be served, so please RSVP accurately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To RSVP anonymously, please login to the Meetup site with the e-mail address &amp;quot;admin at sheeri dot com&amp;quot; and the password &amp;quot;guest&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/calendar/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the third floor, make a right, and walk until you find room 372.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheeri Kritzer Cabral</member_name><member_id>2380684</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271891477000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Boston-Metro MySQL Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mysqlbos</urlname><id>212864</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268138222000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston MySQL April Meetup</name><id>qqddnyngbqb</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271718000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/events/12826893/</event_url></item>