<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>U.S. 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.226468</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Highland Center</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>1458574</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.417929</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please read the section on mandatory equipment carefully!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the same hike that some of us did last January. In fact, I copied and pasted most of Ron's original description (don't worry, I had permission!). I want to get a good winter hike before my busy season at work has me chained to my desk and I thought it'd be great if some RI Outdoors folks joined!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Highland Center in Crawford Notch and ascend to the summit of Mt. Avalon - not a 4000 footer - where there are some very nice views. From there we'll continue our ascent to the summit of Mt. Field. From Mt. Field we'll follow the Willey Range Trail to its junction with the A-Z and take the Mt. Tom Spur to the summit of Mt. Tom. Our descent will be via the A-Z trail and the Avalon trail, bypassing the summit of Mt. Avalon this time around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the goal is to hit both of these peaks, we will assess our time and energy levels before hitting the second peak. Last year we missed Tom, so it'd be nice if we did it this year.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The total distance will be 7.5 miles and we'll gain 3019 feet in elevation. Book time is 6 hours and 20 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This being winter, we will need to start promptly at 9:00 AM. We will also hike at a comfortable but steady pace. We will have lunch on either Mt. Field or Mt. Tom depending on the time. While we will take breaks, we won't generally stop for very long since the longer you stop, the colder you will get.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, please be aware that conditions are quite variable in the winter. Conditions may require us to forgo one or the other summit, or they may require us to alter our route. To quote Ed Viesturs,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;"Reaching the summit is optional. Getting down is mandatory."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that dogs are not permitted on this hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Mount Tom and Mount Field&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Distance:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;7.45 miles round trip&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Elevation Gain:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;3019'&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Moderate&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Pace:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Moderate.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Exposure:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Little to no exposure.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Book Time:&lt;/em&gt;6 1/2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike will be at a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;under winter conditions. Expect ice and deep snow. The trails are relatively sheltered however expect windy conditions on and near the summits. Expect several stream crossings. While there should be thick ice bridges this time of year, that's not a guarantee. Stream crossings can be tricky in winter. We will keep the group together throughout the hike. Therefore, please plan to hike at a pace that will be comfortable for everyone. We will gain about 3019' during the hike. Expect several steep sections both up and down. The views are very good from the summits. Weather conditions and time constraints will be monitored throughout the hike. Those conditions may result in a decision to turn back before the summits should safety become an issue. THIS IS NOT A HIKE FOR BEGINNERS. I would prefer that everyone who comes has had some experience with winter hikes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: If you do not have the proper equipment or you are wearing cotton, I will request that you not hike with us.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To participate you should:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable hiking UPHILL at about 1.5 to 2.0 miles per hour at a 15% incline for about 4 miles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable walking&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;at least 8 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on uneven terrain including ice and deep snow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have sturdy winter hiking boots suitable for cold weather.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;No Sneakers&lt;/strong&gt;!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have rain, snow, and wind protection.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;No Ponchos&lt;/strong&gt;!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to carry at least 2 liters of water. (Remember, 1 liter weighs 2 pounds!)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be in good physical condition.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather and Trail Conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microspikes and Snowshoes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- I fully expect to need some form of traction on this hike. At least Microspikes will be necessary. If you have snowshoes, you should bring them as well. While we will not know for certain if we need them, snowshoes should be a standard part of your winter pack this time of year. If you don't have them, you may rent them at EMS or REI. Last year we used snowshoes for the entire hike. As the date drawers nearer, I may update this to make snowshoes necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boots&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- A pair of winter hiking boots is mandatory. You will be hiking in snow for over 6-hours, so you cannot get away with your summer hiking boots in January or February. You do NOT need plastic boots for general hiking anywhere in NH, but you WILL need waterproof winter boots&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;comfort rated&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to at least -30 degrees. (No, we don't typically encounter those temperatures, but boots with that rating will keep you warm while you're having your lunch on snow or ice.) Remember, you will be spending some time standing or sitting around during brief breaks, summit views, taking pictures, or having lunch. Warm winter boots will keep you comfortable and safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- Finally, you see the note below that your water must be in wide-mouth plastic bottles. It is time to put your hydration systems - e.g. Camelbak's - away for the winter. While they do sell insulated tubes for the hydration systems, quite frankly they do not work. The entrance to the tube where it connects to the bladder still freezes, leaving you with a bladder full of inaccessible water. Therefore, unless it is unseasonably warm for this hike, you'll need to carry water the old fashioned way. Be sure to get wide mouth bottles and be sure to carry them upside down. (Water freezes from the top down.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mandatory Equipment List:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;This list could change based on trail conditions just prior to the hike.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microspikes or Hillsounds. (See note below.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synthetic shirt and waterproof pants.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;No cotton. No jeans.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sturdy Winter Hiking Boots suitable for cold weather.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;No Sneakers or summer boots.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rain / Wind Jacket with hood.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;No Ponchos.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Warm fleece layer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Warm gloves or preferably mittens. (2 pair is strongly recommended.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Warm fleece or wool hat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balaclava&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunglasses&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 liters Water in wide-mouth bottles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;No hydration systems!&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headlamp&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spare Lithium batteries for Headlamp. Bring Lithium, not Alkaline batteries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trail Snacks suitable for freezing weather. (You don't want something that turns into a rock when frozen.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lunch&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optional Gear:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiking Poles - strongly recommended&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snowshoes - strongly recommended&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gaiters&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera / Binoculars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toe warmers and hand warmers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible sled, yes, a sled. There's some spots that it would be super fun as long as we all decide&amp;nbsp;sledding down is a safe option. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Jeans, Sneakers, or Cotton clothing on the hike! Not even your skivvies! Since it is winter, this will be strictly enforced!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool Option&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use the comments to arrange any carpools. I will probably go up the night before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dining Options&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;nbsp;stopped at Fabians on Route 301 for dinner after the hike last year. I was a fan of the woodstove they had, but I'm open to suggestions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to Trailhead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Providence, RI:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please allow 4 hours travel time from Providence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Route 95 North.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Route 93 North to NH.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Exit 35 (Route 3 North) towards Twin Mountain.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn Right in Twin Mountain onto Route 302.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Highland Center will be on your right about 10 miles down.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Park near the exit from the Highland Center, ignoring the sign that says it's reserved for guests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trails and Other Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our route will be as follows:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avalon Trail to summit of Mt. Avalon&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avalon Trail to summit of Mt. Field&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willey Range Trail to jct A-Z Trail&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A-Z Trail to jct Mt. Tom Spur&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mt. Tom Spur to summit of Mt. Tom&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mt. Tom Spur to jct A-Z Trail&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A-Z Trail to jct Avalon Trail&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avalon Trail to Highland Center Parking&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will provide my cell phone number to all "YES" RSVPs the week of the hike. I strongly encourage you to call me or email me if you have any questions about the hike or the gear required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Note about Yak Trax&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yak Trax recently released a style of traction support similar to Microspikes and Hillsounds. Within the last week, however, I have received three separate reports of these new Yak Trax failing. Two of those situations resulted in falls. Since three separate hikers have recently found them unreliable, they are not considered suitable traction devices for hikes that I lead up north. Apologies to anyone that purchased Yak Trax, however your safety and the safety of the group as a whole is paramount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, the following devices are considered suitable traction options for hiking up north. Note that neither Hillsound Trail Crampons nor Katoola Microspikes are a substitute for full crampons in all conditions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hillsound Trail Crampons&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Katoola Microspikes&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

full Crampons (numerous brands)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Highland Center lot... Beige Saturn mom-mobile (aka station wagon)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle</member_name><member_id>11144032</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1326892023000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322440952000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Field and Mt. Tom take TWO!</name><id>42560242</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326548700000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/42560242/</event_url></item>