<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>59.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;Due to apparent demand, we are offering this course again.  This is a repeat of the earlier short course being held Jan 23/Feb 6.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested in learning about permaculture design but not sure if you can invest in a full-blown design course?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Greater Portland TBD (If you know of a suitable residential site &amp;lt;1 acre with inside space to accomodate up to 12 people seated for &amp;quot;class&amp;quot; time in the Greater Portland area, please let me know!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a new version of our popular Permaculture Design Seminar Series which we started in 2009.  &lt;i&gt;If, after taking this Intro Short Course, you are interested in proceeding to the full Permaculture Design Course (PDC) starting in May, your full fee for this event will be applied toward the PDC fee.  This is an affordable and accessible way to get your feet wet and decide if you would like to learn more about the potential for permaculture.&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants in this Intro to Permaculture Design Short Course will meet on two Saturdays (March 6 &amp;amp; 20) from 9:00 am to 2:30 pm at the home of our Portland-area &amp;quot;client&amp;quot; to work through a real, live design process.  With our client (who will have completed a questionnaire in advance) we will co-create a practical permaculture design based on their specific goals and the assets and challenges of their site.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will come away with a strong foundation for understanding and applying permaculture ethics and design principles.  You will have a framework and a process for approaching a residential property from a permaculture perspective.  You will feel confident about taking strides on your own property, if applicable, and will dispel that feeling of not knowing &amp;quot;where to start.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 10 students.  We may repeat this event if there is enough demand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Some student comments from the last iteration of this seminar:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“To my beginner's mind, the challenge elements of this property seemed to be overwhelming and complicated, but in the end Lisa began to bring together aspects of the property's challenges and assets and a design began to synthesize that was manageable and cohesive.&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I am impressed with the way Lisa teaches. It is great fun getting together in a small group like that and learning new things.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It was excellent!!! I left the gathering thrilled and excited by all I'd learned.&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It was a great experience to walk through the initial analysis phase of a permaculture design. I came away with a better understanding of how to approach permacluture design and some of the questions to ask. ”   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It was superb. Much more than I could have reasonably expected. I'm very excited. ”  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Details:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;By signing up for this event you are signing up for both days automatically; a total of 11-12 hours of class time.&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part I - March 6&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Permaculture Background, Ethics and Design Principles  &lt;br /&gt;Design Process and Goals Articulation  &lt;br /&gt;Reading the Landscape and Data Gathering  &lt;br /&gt;Analysis Techniques and Options  &lt;br /&gt;Strategies:  Food + Water  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[suggested online readings during the gap]  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part II - March 20&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Pattern Literacy  &lt;br /&gt;Strategies:  Energy + Shelter  &lt;br /&gt;Creation of Draft Design  &lt;br /&gt;Creation of Draft Implementation Plan  &lt;br /&gt;Bonus:  Top Permaculture Plants for the Northeast (slideshow for people who want to stay a bit later)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring boots and dress in layers for the weather.  We won't be outside alot but we will make a couple of short trips around this suburban property.  Please bring a notebook.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coffee/tea provided throughout the day.  Handouts and copies of all presentations will be provided.  Lunch will be potluck - please bring a dish to share.  A large selection of permaculture-related resources will be on display for reference and inspiration.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268099964000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263226752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intro to Permaculture Design - Short Course</name><id>12286792</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267884000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/12286792/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/e/global_8486014.jpeg</photo_url></item>