<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I'd like to cover 2-3 peaks in VT which are listed in NE HH (New England 100 Highest) on 11/6-7 weekend. This is Day-2 event which covers Mount Equinox (3840 ft) and Dorset Peaks , VT. After this 2days event, I'll be completed all the high peaks in VT in NEHH list. The rest of my remained peaks are either in NH or ME to complete the list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although I listed GMC book time below, &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;I'd like to hike much under book time with moderate to fast pace. (1.5-2.0 mph hiking pace in average) if possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Equinox (3825 ft) is located near Manchester which is the highest peak in the Taconic Mountains and the highest peak in VT not in the Green Mountain Range. There is a road to the summit and Skyline Inn (it's closed now) is located at the Equinox summit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hiking event uses Blue Summit Trail (blue blaze). This is 2.7 x 2 miles RT hike. Elevation change is 2730 ft. &lt;br /&gt;Book Time according to GMC Day Hiker's Guide to Vermont, hike in time is 3 hours and hike out is 1.5 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Meetup location:&lt;/u&gt; We'll meet at Equinox Hotel's Upper West Large Parking Lot at 7AM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;To The Trail:&lt;/u&gt; Parking for the Blue Summit Trail is available at the Equinox Hotel on VT. 7A in Manchester Village. Hikers should park their cars at upper(west) end of the large parking lot at the hotel. Park behind the hotel and follow the West Union Trail (blaze in green) to the top of West Union Street. Turn right onto a dirt road and follow the Red Gate Tr to the Blue Summit Trail. There are 3 other small parking lots for preserve. Please consult EPT(Equinox Preservation Trust) map for directions. ept@sover.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I estimate this Equinox hike will be done by noon time. If someone is interested in, we can peakbag Dorset Mountain as well which is 10min driving distance from Equinox. If we do, we'll start hiking to Dorset Mountain &lt;u&gt;no later than 12:30PM.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dorset Peaks (SouthWest peak (3730 ft) &amp;amp; NorthEast peak (3770 ft)) hike is 6.8 miles RT hike.  Elevation Change is 2320 ft. Hike-in time is 3 hours and hike-out time is 1 3/4 hour as book time.&lt;br /&gt;I'm planning to hike much under book time with moderate to fast pace. &lt;br /&gt;To the Trail: From Rt 30 on Dorset, VT, take Dorset Hollow Rd to NorthEast. This road is diverged to Upper Hollow Rd &amp;amp; Lower Hollow Rd. Keep driving on Upper Hollow Rd. It will be eventually dirt road. If you think you may not be able to drive further, then, that's the probably meetup location. I went there a several months ago. I start hiking on logging road by leaving car around there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Estimated Sunrise on 11/7 around Manchester is 6:34AM, sunset is 4:36PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather check point is 11/5, around 5PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to meeting/hiking with all of you,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer, &lt;br /&gt;Tomoko Nakajima &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Car is Honda CR-V (Blue)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289212656000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286552542000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Southern VT hike Day 2 - Equinox (and/or Dorset) Hike (NE 100 Highest)</name><id>15045966</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289131200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15045966/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>