<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Love beer? So do we!!! The 2012 Exeter Powder Keg Beer &amp;amp; Chili Festival will take place alongside the 14th Annual Fall Festival, a long standing Exeter tradition that includes local crafters, vendors and street entertainment. So pack up the family and come on down to experience all the fun Exeter has to offer! &lt;br /&gt;

We’ll keep you busy celebrating great beers and chili! Breweries and beer enthusiasts from the region will gather on a Fall afternoon for a sampling of fresh beers of all colors, styles and tastes. Vote for your favorite chili as local restaurants enter their house recipes in hopes of becoming the 1st Powder Keg Beer &amp;amp; Chili Festival fan favorite! &lt;br /&gt;

The Exeter Powder Keg Beer &amp;amp; Chili Festival will include great beer from breweries across the region, as well as live music all day long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can purchase your tickets to the Powder Keg Beer &amp;amp; Chili Festival directly online @ &lt;a href="http://www.powderkegbeerfest.com/tickets" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.powderkegbeerfest.com/tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each ticket includes a Exeter Powder Keg Beer &amp;amp; Chili Fest souvenir tasting glass, 8 beer sample tickets, 5 chili sample tickets and live entertainment!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional sampling and Designated Driver tickets will be available for purchase the day of the festival. &lt;br /&gt;

Price: $25.00&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350763620000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350271215000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 1st Annual Exeter Powder Keg Beer &amp; Chili Festival</name><id>87005322</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350748800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/87005322/</event_url></item>