<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If the weather has cooperated, we will be completing our 4th and final Golf Clinic Lesson this Tuesday night, August 11th.  Great Job Everybody!!!  I think we've all learned alot so what better way to utilize these newly found skills than to PLAY GOLF!!!  Let's get together out there and play a round of 9 holes at the Braintree Municipal Golf Course - 5:45 pm outside the pro shop Monday, August 17th.  Since the Clinic group is so large and in anticipation that others may want to join us, we'll begin T times at 6:00 and stagger each group out about every 10 minutes or so with 4 members to each group.  T-times would basically look like (give or take):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00 pm Group #1&lt;br /&gt;6:10 pm Group #2&lt;br /&gt;6:20 pm Group #3&lt;br /&gt;6:30 pm Group #4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone should arrive 10-15 mins before 6:00 so I can assign groups, clubs and get everyone started.  However, if there is someone that may have trouble getting there for the 1st T time or intend to borrow/rent clubs - indicate what you need - women/men's, left or right handed in the comment section upon RSVPing.  I'm working on getting a discount for the use of their clubs but the current rental cost is $15 - I'll keep you posted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members that did not participate in the Golf Clinic are also welcome to join us.  However, it may be worth noting that the majority of the group are at the beginner level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9 Holes of Golf&lt;br /&gt;Monday, August 17th @ 5:45pm&lt;br /&gt;Braintree Municipal Golf Course&lt;br /&gt;101 Jefferson Street&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-843-6513&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max:      Min of 4 by Noon on Thursday, August 13th.  Max of 16 members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests:        None. Members Only.  No Guests for this meet-up as demand is high and space is limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: Annual Members - FREE, All Other Members - $2pp&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;br /&gt;Greens Fees - $15 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Additional fee of $15 to rent clubs - working on discount rate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizers: Susan (AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadlines: The Final Deadline is Noon on Thursday, August 13th. Please be mindful if you change your RSVP to NO at the last minute that you may be taking a spot away from someone else that is serious about participating. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to arrive 10-15 minutes before 6:00 pm to get everyone organized to play.  If for some reason you cannot make it right at 6:00 pm but would still like to play or you need clubs, please indicate it in the comment section when RSVPing to the meetup.  &lt;b&gt;PLEASE ALSO NOTE in your RSVP COMMENTS:  if you intend to borrow clubs indicate what you need - women/men's, left or right handed.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SSFMG and its organizers are not responsible for any injuries to participants or damage to equipment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather Alternative:  None. This event will be canceled if it is raining or too foggy. We will do our best to cancel at least 6 hours in advance but we cannot control Mother Nature so we will do our best to notify everyone at least 3 hours prior to the event. Please do not change your RSVP based on weather forecasts. We check weather forecasts the night before and use those to determine if the event is canceled. Check emails Sunday night or Monday morning to determine event status.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool: There is no carpool for this event. Members should meet at the Braintree Municipal Golf Course. If you would like to carpool you may note where from in your RSVP comment and someone else may choose to contact you if they are also interested in carpooling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The course is conveniently located just minutes from four major highways &lt;a href="http://www.braintreegolf.com/golfcourse_directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet outside the Pro-shop</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>8338847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1250726489000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249750607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Golf - 9 Holes @ Braintree Golf Course</name><id>11065268</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250545500000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11065268/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/4/global_10082868.jpeg</photo_url></item>