<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;   On the Friday after Thanksgiving, we will be gathering to watch a powerful, award-winning film that looks into the heart and mind of the Dalai Lama. We will have popcorn and drinks, watch the film on a big screen, and have some time to talk about it afterward. If you like meaningful movies and meaningful conversation, come on over.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the description of the movie from the film-maker's website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;How do you reconcile a commitment to non-violence when faced with violence? Why do the poor often seem happier than the rich? Must a society lose its traditions in order to move into the future? These are some of the questions posed to His Holiness the Dalai Lama by filmmaker and explorer Rick Ray. Ray examines some of the fundamental questions of our time by weaving together observations from his own journeys throughout India and the Middle East, and the wisdom of an extraordinary spiritual leader. This is his story, as told and filmed by Rick Ray during a private visit to his monastery in Dharamsala, India over the course of several months. Also included is rare historical footage as well as footage supplied by individuals who at great personal risk, filmed with hidden cameras within Tibet. Part biography, part philosophy, part adventure and part politics, ?10 Questions for The Dalai Lama? conveys more than history and more than answers - it opens a window into the heart of an inspiring man.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you had only one hour, what would you ask?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196037479000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195427127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night: "10 Questions for the Dalai Lama"</name><id>6766160</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195864200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/6766160/</event_url></item>