<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 90</address_2><address_1>45 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 523 5260</phone><name>SunDo Mountain Taoist Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>489318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sacred Circle of Healers &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Energy Healers! Come and participate in the healing of the subtle energy body. We willl begin with brief introductions and healing breathwork meditation. During the meditation, each participant will have the opportunity for deep relaxed breathing to build Qi energy in the chakras.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Then, we will practice moving Qi Gong meditations designed to circulate Qi through the body and into the hands in preparation for partner and group Reiki sessions. Masters, students and newcomers to Reiki are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We invite you to establish a community with other healers in a safe and nurturing space. There is no cost for this event but donations are always appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We will all gather together on this night to connect, share, and grow through energy healing, and to remember that all physical, emotional or mental issues arise first on an energetic level in the field of consciousness, and so any healing of the individual must always address this dimension of our existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reminders &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Please be timely.&lt;/em&gt; Doors will be open at 4:15 before the circle begins - this is a great time to come in, socialize, get a cup of tea, settle your belongings, and start feeling grounded in the healing space. We won't be opening doors after the start of the event, which helps to create and maintain sacred space. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Please stay for the entire circle.&lt;/em&gt; So that we all have the opportunity to enjoy the magic of many healing hands, let's agree to stay for the entire time until 6 pm. The idea here is to share... receive with gladness in your heart, and then share back with the community who holds you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/7/a/event_17244698.jpeg" width="449" height="337" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333834163000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331159361000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sacred Circle of Healers</name><id>55414372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333829700000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/55414372/</event_url></item>