<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>An easy day all age hike to break in the colder weather hiking season. Good views, an easy to follow trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://img.groundspeak.com/waymarking/b96d0710-0acc-4587-a378-765f7a6c3f6f.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Pemigewasset is the official name given to the knoll containing the Indian Head profile, best seen from near the Indian Head Resort in Lincoln. Views up and down Franconia Notch can be obtained from ledges near the summit. The Mount Pemigewasset Trail is the shortest and easiest way up and starts at the Flume Visitor Center, while the Indian Head Trail that once started at the resort has been relocated to start lower down, or about 1.1 miles from the Flume.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: To summit of Mount Pemigewasset, about 1.6 miles one-way&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: About 1200 feet, nominal on return &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailhead: Upper (N) end of main parking lot at Flume Visitor Center (not the hiker parking lot for the Appalachian Trail which is further N), exit 34A off I-93/Franconia Notch State Park Parkway, elevation about 1400 feet&lt;br /&gt;N 44.101, -71.683 W (WGS84)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northbound, take exit 34A off I-93/Franconia Notch Parkway, about .2 miles from foot of ramp take second entrance for Flume Visitor Center on R, turn L to park in upper portion of lot&lt;br /&gt;Southbound, take exit 34A off I-93/Franconia Notch Parkway, then second L to Flume Visitor Center (not hiker parking lot), turn L to park in upper portion of lot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;High Point: Summit of Mount Pemigewasset, elevation about 2557 feet &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the parking lot, follow the wide paved multi-use trail (bike path) uphill about .1 miles. The Mount Pemigewasset Trail leaves L here and immediately takes an underpass under US Route 3. After a slight downhill jog, the trail passes under I-93 in two culverts and wanders uphill in the woods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 1.3 miles, the Indian Head Trail joins from the R and the two trails run together to the summit; be sure to take the correct trail on your way down. The trails follow the ridge to the top of the large cliff where there are expansive views to the S; exercise caution here particularly in windy or slippery conditions. From near the far end of the ledge, the trail turns sharp L into the woods and proceeds a short distance to a smaller ledge with a survey marker and views N into Franconia Notch. The trail ends here at about 1.6 miles.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227108726000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224201218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indian Head   </name><id>8976148</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226242800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8976148/</event_url></item>