<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Stata Center, Room 32-124</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8750602</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089844</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Product Serialization, Track &amp;amp; Trace and e-Pedigree for Pharma by 2015!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sept. 5, 2012 from 6:00 pm to 8:30 pm&lt;/strong&gt; at the MIT Stata Center in Cambridge, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT -- REGISTER for this event at the MIT Forum site:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-community-circle-event-preventing-counterfeit-medicines/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-community-circle-event-preventing-counterfeit-medicines/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us to hear the latest developments for e-Pedigree in pharmaceutical. After a delay of several years, serialization of pharma products at the item level is mandated by 2015. Speakers will discuss data collection approaches using 2D bar code and passive RFID, plus strategies for sharing and exploiting data and much more:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How best to achieve interoperability?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;End-to-end global supply chain traceability in healthcare — The GS1 Supply Chain model&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there a business case for RFID at the item level? At the case or pallet level?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barriers and limitations today? RFID tag costs, reliance upon inference, implementation difficulties, sharing data . . . . .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there resistance to serialization and enhanced visibility solutions? Why?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rfidjournal.com/article/articleview/221/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mark Roberti&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Founder and Editor of RFID Journal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Pizzuto&lt;/strong&gt;, Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/pub/bob-celeste/4/b62/977" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #647f4c"&gt;Margot Drees&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Director, Corporate Strategy at GHX&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/pub/bob-celeste/4/b62/977" target="_blank"&gt;Bob Celeste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, Director of Healthcare at GS1 US&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/pub/steve-tadevich/53/262/326" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Tadevich&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Director, Product Serialization Technologies, McKesson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/pub/tom-coyle/17/329/295" target="_blank"&gt;Tom Coyle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALSO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; -- on September 6, Check out &lt;a href="http://www.rfidjournalevents.com/healthcare/" target="_blank"&gt;“&lt;strong&gt;RFID in Healthcare”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at the Boston Park Plaza Hotel by RFID Journal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BIOGRAPHIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thomas Pizzuto, Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thomas has over 15 years of experience in the pharmaceutical industry.  Currently, he is responsible for End-To-End Traceability at Johnson and Johnson, where he is teaming with colleagues to deploy serialization and traceability as an enterprise solution.  Thomas was VP of Client Services with a leading electronic pedigree vendor and was at Wyeth Pharmaceuticals for almost 10 years, where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;he was Director, RFID Technology and Strategies, promoting supply chain security and regulatory compliance. He has served as the co-chair of the Item Level Tagging Joint Requirements&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Group for &lt;/span&gt;EPCglobal&lt;/span&gt; and was a member of &lt;span&gt;EPCglobal&lt;/span&gt; Healthcare Life Sciences Business Action Group; he was Steering Committee Chairman of HDMA's "RX Safe Track"; and was the Technology &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Team Lead for &lt;/span&gt;PhRMA’s Secure Supply Chain initiative. Prior to Wyeth, Thomas held management positions at several companies including General Electric and Andersen Consulting. Thomas holds a &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;BA from Williams College; an MBA from Fordham University; an MS from Temple University, School Of Pharmacy; and LEAN certification from Villanova University.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Margot Drees, Executive Director, Global Strategy, GHX&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Margot Drees leads strategy for an organization that brings together healthcare providers, manufacturers, distributors and group purchasing organizations in a collaborative and connected community to improve efficiencies, visibility and accuracy in the healthcare supply chain. In her current role, Drees is additionally responsible for development of an industry model in support of track and trace and e-pedigree. Drees joined GHX in 2005 with more than 15 years of experience in product management and marketing for healthcare and high-tech companies, including the Micromedex division of Thomson Healthcare Publishing. She received a BA in International Affairs from the University of Colorado, Boulder and an MS in Communication from the University of Denver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Tadevich, Director of Product Serialization Technologies, McKesson Pharmaceutical&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Tadevich is Director, Product Serialization Technologies and a Six Sigma Black Belt in the McKesson IT group for McKesson Pharmaceutical. His responsibilities include McKesson's initiatives in serialization, track and trace, e-Pedigree, RFID and supply chain security. He also works as a business technology liaison with Corporate Government Affairs. Steve has been at McKesson for 26 years in various operations and information technology positions. He is a member of several GS1 groups and represents McKesson on HDMA’s Business Technology Committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mark Roberti, Founder and Editor, RFID Journal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Roberti is a journalist with 25 years of experience covering business and technology. He launched &lt;em&gt;RFID Journal&lt;/em&gt; from a spare bedroom in his home in March 2002. Today, it is the leading source of news and analysis about radio frequency identification and its many business applications. More than 200,000 people around the world visit the &lt;em&gt;RFID Journal Web site&lt;/em&gt; each month, and RFID Journal LIVE!, the company's annual conference and exhibition in the United States, has become the largest gathering of RFID vendors and end users in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to launching RFID Journal, Roberti was a senior writer at the &lt;em&gt;Industry Standard&lt;/em&gt;. He has also served as managing editor of &lt;em&gt;InformationWeek&lt;/em&gt;, editor of &lt;em&gt;Asian Business&lt;/em&gt;. His work has appeared in &lt;em&gt;Business 2.0, Fortune, The Asian Wall Street Journal, International Herald Tribune, The New York Times&lt;/em&gt; and many other publications. He is also the author of a book about Britain's return of Hong Kong to China in 1997.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the founder of RFID Jounal, Roberti plays a unique role in the RFID industry. He is a though leader who regularly writes insightful columns about new applications and market adoption. He also travels the world evangelizing for RFID technology, meeting end users, technology providers and academics, which gives him unique insight into how and where RFID is gaining traction. He talks regularly with the heads of RFID programs at major companies from Airbus to Walmart. He informally advises many end user companies on RFID strategy. And he supports the work of groups such as the VICS Item-Level RFID Initiative, which are helping foster adoption of RFID technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Coyle, Moderator and co-chair, MIT Enterprise Forum Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For twenty years Tom has delivered RFID solutions as a senior executive at Texas Instruments, Savi Technology (now Lockheed Martin), Matrics (now Motorola), Mark IV Industries the producer of EZ-Pass (now Kapsch) and Avery Dennison. Tom was a helicopter test pilot and maintenance manager for 81 aircraft in the U.S. Army. Tom founded and was the president of the 501C3 non-profit Kendall Square Learning Project. He was named Volunteer of the Year in 1994 by the Massachusetts Coalition for Adult Education. He is a graduate of West Point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347546118000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345141840000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Preventing Counterfeit Medicines</name><id>78037452</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346882400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/78037452/</event_url></item>