<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>221 Daniel Webster Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.822351</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anheuser-Busch Facility</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>970305</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.483887</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW CARPOOL MEETING PLACE:&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;to make it convenient for everyone, we are changing the Carpool meeting place to Kmart in Billerica @ 484 Boston Road.&amp;nbsp; Meet in front of Kmart in the parking lot, we will decide then how many cars we will need to take.&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Reminder:&amp;nbsp; we will leave Kmart promptly at 10am.&amp;nbsp; if you have other plans later in the day, please do not include yourself in the carpool arrangements.&amp;nbsp; there is no plan on the time of the return trip, please be prepared to stay until everyone in the car you ride in is ready to leave.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Carpool Update:&amp;nbsp; We will be meeting at the Andover Park N Ride at Exit 42 Dascomb Road&amp;nbsp;at 9:45am.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;WE WILL BE LEAVING ANDOVER PROMPTLY AT 10:00 AM&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; If you &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;are interested in Carpooling from Andover, please let your organizers know by updating your RSVP no later than Friday June 17, 2011&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;____________________________________________________________&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Rock N Ribfest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;T &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;his just in......here's the link to purchase your ticket in advance when you do you will save 35%, hurry up this deal ends on June 11th!!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the link that will work:&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://www.rotaryribfest.org/contact/news/&amp;nbsp" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.rotaryribfest.org/contact/news/&amp;nbsp&lt;/a&gt;; when you get to that page on the right side you will see Buy your tickets on line, and go from there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are setting up a place to meet so we can car pool, if you are interested in doing that and haven't put that in your RSVP please go ahead and do so, stay tuned for an update of where to meet.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us for great food and entertainment on the beautiful and&amp;nbsp; spacious grounds of Anheuser-Busch. This family-oriented event will feature nationally renowned professional &amp;ldquo;ribbers&amp;ldquo; and local award-winning restaurants providing mouth-watering ribs for everyone to enjoy. Add great entertainment for children and adults and you have a recipe for fun and excitement. As the official New Hampshire State Barbecue Championships, you will experience some of the best grillers and BBQers in the northeast vying for title of New Hampshire Barbecue Grand Champion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;This event is open to Children of all ages &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission: $7.00 for adults, children under 15 Free. There are also amusement rides for the kids at $10.00 ride all day or .50 per ticket. Parking is Free. Bags, coolers, backpacks, and other containers are not allowed into the Rock 'N Ribfest except for childcare and medical needs. All bags will be checked prior to entering the event gate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets can be purchased soon online &lt;a href="http://rotaryribfest.org/"&gt;http://rotaryribfest.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note you are responsible for getting your own tickets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;, we thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We look forward to see you! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the admissions gate, we will be on the right side.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308414833000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Who doesn't love ribs and a brewery tour?</why><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303349954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rock N Ribfest</name><id>17380312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308409200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/17380312/</event_url></item>