<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Paddle/Skill Sharing Session at East Brimfield Lake near Sturbridge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and spend a couple of hours with other paddlers to share knowledge on paddling skills and rescues.  This is great for people who do, or want to, paddle larger waters and be able to self-rescue or get back in with assistance in case of a capsize.  Even if you only paddle flatwater, situations can arise, so it's still good to know how to handle a capsize and re-entry.  Whether you have knowledge to share or just want to improve your skills, come work informally with help from other paddlers on wet exits, paddle float re-entry, assisted re-entry and strokes and bracing.  Of course we will also paddle around the lake some as well!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come dressed for getting wet, and nose plugs are recommended for practicing rescues.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 9:00 at Long Pond boat ramp.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get there -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Mass Pike to Rt. 20 West - Stay on Rt. 20 through the center of Sturbridge.  About 1/2 mile after the intersection of Rt. 20 and 148 (stay on Rt. 20), there will be a brown sign saying &amp;quot;East Brimfield Dam&amp;quot;, and then shortly after that is another brown sign with a picture of a boat ramp, the entrance to the ramp area is on the right shortly after the ramp sign.  When you get down to the parking lot, the sign says &amp;quot;Long Pond / East Brimfield Lake&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 20 East - Go over the lake, and the entrance to the boat ramp is the  first left after you go over the lake.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4219141</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218673051000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218029742000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle/Skill Sharing Session - East Brimfield Lake</name><id>8488701</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218373200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/8488701/</event_url></item>