<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>380 Winter Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-7800</phone><name>Best Western</name><city>Waltham</city><id>746917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.258767</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>[url=&lt;a href="http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/EventDisplayNew.cfm?clubID=1762&amp;EventID=80110&amp;mo=3&amp;tDate=%7Bd%20'2009-03-20'%7D]All" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/EventDisplayNew.cfm?clubID=1762&amp;EventID=80110&amp;mo=3&amp;tDate=%7Bd%20'2009-03-20'%7D]All&lt;/a&gt; Day Intensive With Wendy Patton Register NOW![/url]

" Making Hard Cash in a Soft Real Estate Market Using Lease Options &amp; Subject To's ",   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
 
On Saturday, March 21, 2009, Discover How To Boost Your Real Estate Profits in By At Least Ten Thousand Dollars. . . &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

One of the Very Best

— and Least Known—Techniques,

Revealed By the Foremost Expert &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Today's real estate is different! Techniques that work in Miami may not work in LA!  That’s why—in order to be super successful in real estate investing—you need to know what’s working for real estate investors… &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

..in your town, right now, in this crazy economy &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
No one’s better suited to tell you that than Wendy Patton. Wendy is the nation’s foremost expert on how to uncover real estate profits where other investors see only problems, shake their heads, and walk away! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

For instance, Wendy will show you how to take a deal that looks mediocre, and get FOUR different profit streams into your pocket...with little or no money down on your part! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 

How could Wendy have perfected a technique that others don’t even know about? Wendy’s done more than 653 deals...she’s not only an investor, but a real estate broker, and a licensed contractor. Plus, she knows the nation’s markets inside-out! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Wendy will be sharing her secrets in a closed-door briefing on Saturday March 21, 2009. If you want to make your financial resolutions come true, clear your calendar for this event!


Here’s some of what Wendy will reveal: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 

• She’ll hand you a technique that works like gangbusters even in all markets,  where appreciation is sometimes flat or declining. She’ll show you how to profit from properties that both Realtors and investors avoid. You’ll be handing your impressed bank teller fat checks from these deals!

• How to get Realtors to put you on their “speed dial” list as a favorite person to send deals to.

• Tested and proven newspaper &amp; Internet ads—word for word—that attract sellers like a scrap yard magnet.

• When Realtors and other investors throw up their hands at obstacles in a deal, you’ll be clapping your hands at the money you know you can make on that deal.

• Five reasons why homebuyers will gladly pay more than the retail value of a home...IF you know Wendy’s secrets.

• Why your ethics and reputation are everything in this business, and how Wendy’s techniques are truly a “win win” for you and your customers.

“...in June I made $20,000, in July I made $18,000 and so far in August I have made $14,000...I currently have under contract two new properties that will net me at least $25,000 per deal. I used Wendy’s techniques in all but one of these deals. Wendy THANKYOU for all that you have done and the knowledge you’ve shared with us.” —-Scott Teerink, Phoenix AZ

Wendy Patton is widely recognized as one of the most inspiring speakers on "Little or No Money Down" real estate investing.  Her real estate savvy, great depth of experience and viable knowledge has helped her in orchestrating the most complete and easy to follow Lease Option &amp; Subject To Program in the country.

After graduating from the University of Colorado, Wendy went to work for EDS, (Electronic Data Systems).  Soon after, she had an enlightening experience in real estate (lease/option) and walked away from her corporate job to focus her efforts on real estate investing full-time.

Wendy is a licensed Real Estate Broker in 3 states and licensed Builder in Michigan. She is the former President and a current Board Member of D.O.L.L.A.R.S., a Detroit based organization comprised of real estate strategists.  Wendy has extensive experience in lease options, subject to’s, land development, property management, rehabs, foreclosures, new construction and pre-construction with lease options and new construction being her favorites.  With over 22 successful years in general real estate and hundreds of transactions using Lease Options, she is the country’s leading expert on lease options and working with Realtors to acquire lease option deals.  Wendy loves to teach others and assist them to achieve the same level of success that she has personally experienced.

 

Wendy Patton is a published author and well known public speaker. She also recently appeared on HGTV’s, My House IS Worth What? 
 
Event Details
8:00 - Begin checkin 
8:30AM-4:30 PM -All Day Intensive 
Location: Best Western Hotel, 380 Winter St, Waltham, Ma 
Members $29, Visitors $59 - includes lunch!!!


[url=&lt;a href="http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/EventDisplayNew.cfm?clubID=1762&amp;EventID=80110&amp;mo=3&amp;tDate=%7Bd%20'2009-03-20'%7D]All" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/EventDisplayNew.cfm?clubID=1762&amp;EventID=80110&amp;mo=3&amp;tDate=%7Bd%20'2009-03-20'%7D]All&lt;/a&gt; Day Intensive With Wendy Patton Register NOW![/url]</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239919928000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237392373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Low Down, Lease Option, Sub To Techniques with Wendy Patton</name><id>9980845</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237636800000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/9980845/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/b/global_1787963.jpeg</photo_url></item>