<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>177 Forest St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.480752</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Breakheart Reservation/Chris P. Dunne Visitor Center</name><city>Saugus</city><id>761790</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.026256</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;3 hour hike (approx) of 4.3 miles - I'm going to follow a trail I found online. I do not know these trails so bear with me and don't get grumpy if we get a bit lost..(: There will be some rocky trails and climbs to get views over Boston. It's going to be a great day for a hike!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open year-round, dawn to dusk. Breakheart Reservation is a 640-acre hardwood forest with jagged, rocky outcroppings, two fresh-water lakes, and a rambling section of the Saugus River. Seven rocky hills, over 200 feet high, provide vistas of Boston, southern New Hampshire and central Massachusetts. An extensive trail system through the woodlands guides visitors to various areas of the reservation. Fishing in Silver and Pearce Lakes, hiking the trails and birdwatching by the Saugus River are popular year-round activities. The supervised swimming area at Pearce Lake, one of the few fresh- water swimming spots north of Boston, draws crowds in the summer. In addition to its natural resources, the reservation has a rich cultural history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've been having a lot of no-shows lately - so please don't book a spot unless you really plan to come!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll send my phone number out to attendees. Dogs are allowed here, but I won't be bringing mine as she only does short walks these days....&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for red subaru with kayak holders on top in parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332153060000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332010164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakheart Reservation hike</name><id>56743862</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332081000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/56743862/</event_url></item>