<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone this is Rob :-)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My initial e-mail to everyone asking about interest in a ride for this Sunday drew enough interest....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So let's get out there and bike!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a nice 29 mile ride through the Towns of Weston, Sudbury, and Concord.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been on many rides and I REALLY enjoy leading the ones where everyone feels truly welcome and is part of a group of friendly people.  The rides that I've been on that I don't particularly like are the ones where people are primarily interested in just getting to the end first and we don't get a chance to really laugh and have fun.  Hey...what's the point?!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, I hope you'll join us for a fabulous day!  Let's pray for sun!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have a lunch stop in Concord center.  When we all get back to the beginning, we can decide if people want to go for ice cream etc...  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helmet is mandatory.  Water bottles and energy food highly recommended.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128, take exit 24, Rte. 30 West. The first traffic light west of Rte. 128 is at the end of the southbound off-ramp. Travel 2.3 miles on Rte 30 west to the fifth set of traffic lights (The fourth are blinking lights, in front of a firehouse.) Turn left onto Wellesley Street. Weston High School is on the left side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the cue sheet, the route is marked with a green line on the pavement at the turns:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, I admit it....I took the route from another ride I had been on earlier this season....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the link....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crw.org/cgi-bin/cues2htm.pl?id=261" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crw.org/cg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rob Fox</member_name><member_id>4368625</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184994775000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183513417000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weston, Wayland, Sudbury, Concord Ride - A chance to make new friends!</name><id>5972186</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183903200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/5972186/</event_url></item>