<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Runtime: ~2hrs 9min. | Rated PG for sequences of action, some violence and language.

Cast: Emile Hirsch, Christina Ricci, Matthew Fox, Susan Sarandon, John Goodman

Director: Andy Wachowski

More info: &lt;a href="http://imdb.com/title/tt0811080/" class="linkified"&gt;http://imdb.com/title/tt0811080/&lt;/a&gt;

Reviews: Not yet.

Trailer:
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/MQyYPP9zR7M&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

Description: Hurtling down the track, careening around, over and through the competition, Speed Racer is a natural behind the wheel. Born to race cars, Speed is aggressive, instinctive and, most of all, fearless. His only real competition is the memory of the brother he idolized-the legendary Rex Racer - whose death in a race has left behind a legacy that Speed is driven to fulfill. Speed is loyal to the family racing business, led by his father, Pops Racer, the designer of Speed's thundering Mach 5. When Speed turns down a lucrative and tempting offer from Royalton Industries, he not only infuriates the company's maniacal owner but uncovers a terrible secret-some of the biggest races are being fixed by a handful of ruthless moguls who manipulate the top drivers to boost profits. If Speed won't drive for Royalton, Royalton will see to it that the Mach 5 never crosses another finish line. The only way for Speed to save his family's business and the sport he loves is to beat Royalton at his own game. With the support of his family and his loyal girlfriend, Trixie, Speed teams with his one-time rival-the mysterious Racer X - to win the race that had taken his brother's life: the death-defying, cross-country rally known as The Crucible.

Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what your going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please buy your tix AHEAD of time! I'm going to watch this regardless of people coming, but it will more fun with people.

If it's downstairs, I'll be right behind the corded rope after ticket stubs have been ripped in front of the popcorn counter. If it's upstairs, I'll try to grab one of the tables in front of the coffee house near the large monumental windows.

I'll be there by 7PM, we plan to go into cinema and seat ourselves@7:15PM sharp. the movie begins@7:30PM. After the movie ends, we'll be outside of the auditorium waiting for people, look for the green trucker hat =D./</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front as usual. After the film ends, We'll be outside the movie exits. Pls wait for us.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212077739000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>We won't bite. Love to have discussions about the films after movie ends. The group often goes out afterwards and socialize.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198726964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Speed Racer</name><id>6974344</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210374000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6974344/</event_url></item>