<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In tribal cultures, the shamans are the ones who are responsible for interacting with the spirit world. They journey through meditation and dreaming to bring back messages from guides and ancestors.  But a shaman knows a secret.  If we are internally still and consciously aware, then there is no need to sleep or meditate to get those messages.  The world we inhabit is ever a waking dream with its own mysteries, symbols and portents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this class, we'll explore the symbology of the waking dream - what to look for, where to look, and the ways in which the mundane becomes sacred as it speaks to us. Learn to interpret the difference between coincidence and omen and how to be certain that you're getting the right message.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Students will be asked to look for messages from their lives in the last week before the program, so be certain to pay attention to your surroundings as you go through the week leading up to this program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kelle Sparta&lt;/b&gt; is a practicing shaman.  She has studied shamanic, mystic, occult, Wiccan, pagan, and metaphysical practices for 30 years.  She is a Reiki Master Teacher, a psychic and has led public and private ritual for over 10 years.  She runs a shamanic drum circle in Malden and takes on apprentices each year in shamanic studies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is welcome to attend and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/suggestion/" target="_blank"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 25 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions and other information about Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swedenborg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269452158000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264644924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Art of the Waking Dream</name><id>12445343</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268179200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/12445343/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/d/global_12828797.jpeg</photo_url></item>