<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Main Floor-North Entrance</address_2><address_1>404 Wyman Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02454</zip><lat>42.410244</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-781-895-1234 </phone><name>IBM Innovation Center</name><city>Waltham</city><id>893122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.256317</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This seminar is organized by our partner NECINA (&lt;a href="http://www.necina.net" target="_blank"&gt;New England Chinese Information &amp;amp; Networking Association&lt;/a&gt;).  It is to foster discussions on opportunities in two highly exciting transformations for technology firms, professionals and entrepreneurs: one is about opportunities in transforming China, and the other is on rapidly growing smart phone/devices and mobile applications world wide and in the US. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People have become increasingly aware that China has great aspiration of transforming itself from a global manufacture powerhouse into an innovation-driven enterprise.  “Internet of Things” has been identified as one of national interested areas to push the innovation effort.  Working with its sister parks within Wuxi, Z-Park Wuxi uniquely positioned itself to help high tech firms and entrepreneurs to launch their “Internet of Things” ventures in China.  At the same time, with all three major carriers in China – China Telecom, China Mobile and China Unicom opening offices here, mobile developers and firms could use Z-Park Wuxi as a launch pad to China market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Across the Pacific Ocean, the US wireless industry is undergoing a deep transformation itself with the introduction of more advanced mobile platforms, an influx of powerful smart phones, an accelerated roll out of 4G networks by carriers and more mobile users eager to take advantage of new applications.  The second part of this seminar, one of NECINA Wireless SIG series, will present Handheld Devices and Mobile Applications and Introduction to Verizon Verizon Developer Community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Registration&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please register at &lt;a href="http://www.acteva.com/booking.cfm?bevaid=211522" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.acteva.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Dinner will be provided&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt; 6:30 pm - 6:45 pm   Registration &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;6:45 pm - 7:15 pm   &amp;quot;Introduction to Z-Park Wuxi&amp;quot;, Zhongcheng Gao, VP of Z-Park Wuxi &lt;/b&gt;         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;7:15 pm - 7:45 pm   &amp;quot;Handheld Devices and Mobile Applications&amp;quot;,  Dr. Baoqing Ye, Verizon &lt;/b&gt; With the fierce competition of various handheld/mobile devices in the market, there are only a few running on the front row, including both long time champions and soon-to-be winners. Baoqing Ye will give an introduction of those mobile devices particularly on smart phones and tablets, and current market trends. To close on open source platforms, she'll demonstrate android development environment and live applications.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;7:45 pm - 8:30 pm   &amp;quot;Introduction to Verizon Developer Community&amp;quot;, Mr. Larry Rau, and Mr. Nick Katis, Verizon&lt;/b&gt;   Verizon Developer community is a Verizon wireless program to assist mobile application developers to bring innovative mobile applications and solution quickly and easily to the market. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;8:30 - 9:00            Networking &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner Sponsor - Z-Park Wuxi&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We thank Z-Park Wuxi for kindly sponsoring the dinner for participants of this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/1/c/600_19392572.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Z-Park Wuxi is located in Wuxi city that is about 80 miles west of Shanghai and is one of China's top ten fastest growing cities.  As the original Z-Park is famously called the Silicon Valley in China, Z-Park Wuxi will carry the same innovation spirit and seize the opportunities in building “Sense China” center.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Z-Park Wuxi is a key part of Wuxi New District (WND) that is a larger internationalized Hi-tech industrial zone and has been rapidly developed by the government.  It serves as a one-stop service center for high tech companies: state-of-art R&amp;amp;D facilities, intermediary services, human resource support and more.  Already, some of leading Chinese companies including China Mobile, China Unicom and prestigious multinational firms including IBM, Intel and Nokia Siemens have already opened up offices here.  It's partnerships with some of China's finest universities including Nanjing University and Shanghai Jiao Tong University ensures a steady flow of talented employees.  Firms in Z-Park Wuxi also enjoy special tax incentives, subsidies, and patent protection.   Because of these favorable factors, many winners of renowned 530 Project have chosen this area to launch their new ventures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Z-Park Wuxi Delegation Members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Zhongcheng Gao, VP of Z-Park Wuxi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Xiaojun Yang, GM of Wuxi  Tech-Park  Ivestment &amp;amp; Development Co. Ltd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Xia Qin,Vice Director Of Science and Economy Development Dept, Wuxi Tech-Park Administrative Committee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Bei Chen, Project Manager Of Science and Economy Development Dept, Wuxi Tech-Park Administrative Committee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speakers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Mr. Zhongcheng Gao, VP of  Z-Park Wuxi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/2/2/600_19398722.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Dr. Baoqing Ye, currently Sr. Software Engineer and System Architect at Product Design and Development Division of Verizon Information Technology Organization, is responsible for the design and development of mobile services and applications. She previously served as Distinguished Member of Technical Staff at various divisions within Verizon Technology Organization, including Network Security, Network Architecture, Network Design &amp;amp; Integration. Baoqing received her MS and PhD in Computer Engineering from Syracuse University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Mr. Larry Rau jointed Verizon wireless in 2009 as a director managing developer community, earlier he co-founded SavaJe technology and served as CTO in Sun' s consumer solutions division.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Mr. Nick Katis is current in Verizon Wireless' application ecosystem group. Nick has over 12 years of experience driving the definition, development and launch of innovative new consumer products in the wireless industry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ning An</member_name><member_id>10728354</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289864007000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288894224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>[Partner]NECINA: Mobile Platforms and Apps &amp; Opportunities in Z-Park Wuxi China</name><id>15339802</id><headcount>53</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289518200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/15339802/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/3/global_19384739.jpeg</photo_url></item>