<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108-2406</zip><lat>42.374218</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 742-2121</phone><name>Hennessey's</name><city>Boston</city><id>668979</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At this month's meeting, we will hear about the Secure Communities program From Jessica Vaughan of Center for Immigration Studies. She will explain the program and how important it is that we, as activists, attend the Forum in Brockton on Saturday, May 14th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Secure Communities?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secure Communities is a program of the federal Bureau of Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) designed to help them find and remove foreign nationals (usually illegal aliens) who commit crimes in the United States. &amp;nbsp;Launched in 2007 as a pilot program in Boston and Houston, it is now activated in more than 1,000 counties in 39 states. &amp;nbsp;As a result, ICE has identified and charged more than 150,000 criminal aliens nationwide, including about 700 in Boston. &amp;nbsp;The Secure Communities system works by linking DHS and DOJ databases so that every person who is arrested and fingerprinted for criminal charges will have their immigration status checked, and ICE is notified to take action if appropriate. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;ICE has requested that this program be extended to cover more jurisdictions in Massachusetts, and has announced that the program will be mandatory by 2013. &amp;nbsp;After more than a year of delay, Governor Patrick announced in December that he would sign the agreement with ICE to allow other cities, towns, and county jails to join, but he has yet to move forward. &amp;nbsp;He and his spokespersons have cited concerns that the program is used to remove not only violent criminal aliens but also illegal aliens who have been convicted of lesser crimes. &amp;nbsp;In addition, immigrant advocacy groups have protested that the program breaks up families and spreads fear in immigrant communities. &amp;nbsp;The Governor recently announced a series of public meetings to take place over the next several months, featuring opponents of Secure Communities exclusively, to discuss the program. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us to hear about how you can advocate for the continuation of this program!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christen Varley</member_name><member_id>9247789</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305247093000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's time for another get together in Boston!

At this meeting, we will hear about the Secure Communities program From Jessica Vaughan of Center for Immigration Studies. We'll also be reviewing current pending legislation on Beacon Hill.</why><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304688258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston May Meeting - Greater Boston Tea Party</name><id>17566838</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305243000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/17566838/</event_url></item>