<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Day I Saw Your Heart Jennifer Devold&amp;egrave;re 2011 Categories: Art, Comedy, Drama, Family Relationships, Fiction, Romance, Women, Young Adults Average Rating: My Rating: 1 2 3 4 5 Run time: 105 min. | aka: Et soudain, tout le monde me manque | France | Language: French with subtitles | Film Format: 35mm Note: Trailer is in French without subtitles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This lighthearted comedy offers poignant reflections on family life. Eli Dhrey&amp;rsquo;s news that his third wife is pregnant unsettles his grown daughters. Dom, trying to adopt, is indignant. Justine, her unmoored twentysomething half sister, responds by making stunning X-ray art from images acquired during her day job. Enjoy delightful performances by Michel Blanc (The Girl on the Train, 2009 Festival) as Eli and M&amp;eacute;lanie Laurent (La Rafle, Le Concert, Inglorious Basterds) as Justine. New England Premiere Sponsored by: Solomon Schechter Day School Introduced by: Christophe Guilhou, Consul General of France in Boston (Nov 5) 1 video Videos 4 pictures Pictures buy tickets related links official film site &amp;gt;&amp;gt; facebook &amp;gt;&amp;gt; film details screenings reviews&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;more info on BJFF website re: prices and buying tickets online&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320538267000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317773808000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Jewish Film Festival</name><id>36174232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320534000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/36174232/</event_url></item>