<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Nicole suggested that we do a meet-up here.  I had wanted to go to this event this year myself anyway.  I think this looks like lots of fun.  We will meet in front of  the main door of the State House .  I will post my cell phone # closer to the date so that people can contact me if they have questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;2008 Flames of Hope...A Celebration of Life at Waterfire &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join us on October 11, 2008 for the 3rd Annual Flames of Hope™…A Celebration of Life at WaterFire Event in Downtown Providence. This year’s festivities begin at 5:30 PM at the RI State House with the enormously uplifting Flames of Hope Torch Parade and the lighting of the RI State House in Pink to celebrate National Breast Cancer Awareness Month. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pink Ribbon VIP Party will be held in the Flames of Hope Village beginning at 6:00 PM. The Flames of Hope Village will showcase the Cotton Candy Boutique featuring clothing, jewelry and accessories, the exciting Flames of Hope Art Gallery featuring Berge’ Zobian, a fabulous Wine Tasting event, and live and silent auctions with some of the most sought after sports memorabilia.  Don’t forget to visit with our generous sponsors and breast health care providers. There is plenty of food at our food courts located throughout the event, featuring many of your WaterFire favorites. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local radio personalities from Clear Channel Radio, Citadel Communications, WEEI, WBRU and WCTK will also be on hand to help out in the fight against breast cancer. For more information on event festivities or to purchase tickets for the VIP Party, visit www.gloriagemma.org or call 491-861-HERO (4376). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss this extraordinary event! Remember…It’s your fight too!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gloria Gemma Breast Cancer Resource Foundation was established in 2004 in memory of our mom and in honor of her courageous fight against breast cancer. Our mission is to raise breast cancer awareness, increase breast health education, and generate funding for critical breast health programs that are in desperate need of being brought to fruition. Our promise is that 100% of the net proceeds will remain right here in our local community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shortly after our mom’s death, we realized that if we didn’t do something quick to help fight this horrific disease, it could steal more of our loved ones. We also knew that more awareness, more education, and more funding for critical breast health programs could help women and men detect breast tumors earlier and ultimately, save lives! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As it turns out, our quest would be a journey none of us ever thought we would have to take. Not only did our mom Gloria suffer from breast cancer, but our sister Gloria was recently diagnosed with this horrific disease. Our sister, like most of you, is married with four young children under the age of 10. She works and maintains a home. Never could we have imagined that this horrific disease would strike twice in our family. Never did we imagine we would have to go through this torment again. My sister is only 41 years old…far too young to have to deal with this horrible disease! Because of our strong message, our sisters’ breast cancer was diagnosed early. She will undergo surgery and treatments, and she will survive! Her courage and determination will prevail, and her strength will carry her through. My sister was lucky…she found her cancer early. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As time passes on, we continue to miss our mom terribly, but we get through each day, knowing that her inspiration lives on. For all of you that have lost a loved one to breast cancer, you know this pain…this indescribable feeling of sadness. Our mom was the wind beneath our wings.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will meet in front of  the main door of the State House</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer Lamontagne</member_name><member_id>7358665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224961372000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218466132000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Water fire with Jazz to support Gloria Gemma Breast Cancer Resource Foundation</name><id>8520612</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223758800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/8520612/</event_url></item>