<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Boat Launch: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-84, south on rte 195 (exit 68) through Storrs to Mansfield ctr (about 11 miles from 84)&lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. (licquer store at the intersection too)&lt;br /&gt;Will see a picknick area on left go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-384, follow rte 6 to toward Willimantic. &lt;br /&gt;6 and 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6. &lt;br /&gt;Follow ths highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte633 or s. frontage rd.) it is acually a parallel to rte6 connector to rte 195, &lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too, &lt;br /&gt;Go north on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, same info from here as above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue Toyota Avalon with the kayaks on a old sailboat trailer. maybe even one kayak with a 55 horsepower motor on it and a torpedo prop... &lt;br /&gt;The RedNeck Jet....runs on pure moonshine...&lt;br /&gt;That will get that mother in law over the dam in no time...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For users of GPS or Mapquest..&lt;br /&gt;use 300 Bassetts Bridge Road, Mansfield Center, CT&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179250407000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178806084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mothers Day Paddle at Mansfield Hollow/Dam Area</name><id>5763716</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179077400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5763716/</event_url></item>