<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>680 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02601</zip><lat>41.648232</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brazilian Grill</name><city>Hyannis Port</city><id>10448762</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.292694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets have a feast! And I know just the place. The Brazilian Grill in Hyannis. Here's how it works, we leave KFIT for the short flight to KHYA. Take a taxi or whatever the 1.5 miles to the best feast you've ever had. This is a whole different dining experience. And they know how to do it right! Don't miss this one and bring your appetite!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daylight savings time will help make the trip down easier, but no sleeping on the way home!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.braziliangrill-capecod.com/index.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.braziliangrill-capecod.com/index.php&lt;/a&gt; ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/1/8/event_182328152.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OUR MENU We offer an authentic Brazilian dining experience as we serve you various cuts of slowly grilled meats over natural wood charcoal and seasoned to perfection. We also offer a buffet of soups, fresh salads and side dishes. And remember to save room for our homemade Brazilian deserts. Take Control... Manage all your food by just turning the cards on your table. Want to start with a salad? Just keep your card on the red side. Not a vegetarian? Flip to the green side and the meats will be brought to your table...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Brazilian Grill, The Brazilian Grill Churrascaria offers an authentic Brazilian dining experience as we serve you Churrasco a Rodizio, which means “Rotisserie Barbeque.” We also offer a full buffet of soups, fresh salads, cheese, hot entrees, and side dishes. And the best part? &lt;strong&gt;It’s all you can eat!&lt;/strong&gt; Come hungry and enjoy your dining experience here with us. Tender morsels are brought to you on skewers and carved at your table. You may enjoy as much as you like, all for one fixed price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start with a light salad course, and then signal the Gauchos that you are ready to begin the Rodizio by turning the card on your table to the green side. After you have enough, simply turn the card to the red side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget there are many other meats to follow and you may request as many servings as you like. The Rodizio includes unlimited visits to our fabulous buffet with a wide variety of salads, vegetables, cheeses, pasta, imported prosciutto and delicious Brazilian hot dishes. (Vegetarians may enjoy the buffet only). For dessert try Chocolate Cake and Banana Flambada. Bon Appetit!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charley V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, need a seat, find a seat, but get your tail with us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364140957000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358311853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blast down to The Brazilian Grill Churrascaria on the Cape.</name><id>99842182</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364072400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/99842182/</event_url></item>