<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We'll hike (or snowshoe)&amp;nbsp;for&amp;nbsp;+/-3 hours to refresh our bodies, then head to the Holy Grail Pub in Epping to, um, refresh our spirits...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet at the parking area just inside the main gate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Bring snowshoes if it snows and your microspikes in case of ice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/5/b/event_20487739.jpeg" width="337" height="251" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Pawtuckaway State Park offers&amp;nbsp;5,500 acres in a variety of landscapes, with something to do and see for everyone. There are many opportunities for hiking, with trails leading to numerous points of interest, including a mountaintop fire tower, an extensive marsh, and an unusual boulder field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Hikers walking the 2.4 miles to the 908&amp;rsquo; summit of South Mountain will be rewarded with a spectacular panoramic view from the fire tower. Mountain Trail begins at the sign on the left just past Mountain Pond.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;A walk on the Fundy Trail, bordering Burnham&amp;rsquo;s Marsh can be very enjoyable, especially in the early morning or evening when the beavers, deer, and great blue herons are most apt to be active. Fundy Trail begins across the road from the entrance to the group picnic and camping areas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Boulder Field is a geologically unique area where many large boulders, called glacial erratics, were deposited when glacial ice melted near the end of the Ice Age. They are so large that rock climbers practice different climbing techniques on them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portsmouth/Dover: 40 mins.&amp;nbsp;Newburyport: 45 mins&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Pets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/7/8/event_11798776.jpeg" width="165" height="143" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Holy Grail Pub - 64 Main St. Epping, NH&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The old St. Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Church was built in 1896 by William J. O&amp;rsquo;Connor and was established as a Parish in 1898. In simpler times long past, this structure served the local residents as a gathering place to worship, to meet people, listen to music and socialize among friends and family. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Except for the worshipping part, and the addition of 21 beer taps, &amp;nbsp;nothing's changed&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;(Native killer rabbit below)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/6/6/event_13317702.jpeg" width="217" height="189" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.&amp;nbsp; Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving&amp;nbsp;home.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327356014000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326082776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike for the Holy Grail</name><id>47283022</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326558600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/47283022/</event_url></item>