<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Attend the Annual SOUTH END OPEN STUDIOS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrating 22 years of art in Boston’s vibrant South End, the South End Open Studios are &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 20 and Sunday, September 21 this year from&lt;br /&gt;11am to 6pm both days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South End Open Studios is your chance to meet over 250 artists…explore work that is both familiar and new to you...purchase work directly from the artist who created it...start your own list of artists you would like to learn more about or visit again after Open Studios.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you have come to South End Open Studios for a number of years or this will be your first visit, you will be impressed by the incredible range of work you will see. Each stop along the self-guided route will introduce you to artists working a in range of media…oils, watercolors, photography, sculpture, jewelry, mixed media, fiber arts, ceramics, wood, glass, and metal as well as other types of visual and performance arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors to South End Open Studios can walk easily from building to building (or those who prefer can take the free shuttle buses.) There are 3 information areas within our Open Studios area where volunteers can assist you with directions and questions. We also are able to provide free parking at the areas indicated on the map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the event website for maps, contacts, and additional details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.useaboston.com/open_studios.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.useaboston...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: there will be shuttles and parking available throughout the days.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alyson</member_name><member_id>5616452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223124310000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219870825000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South End Open Studios</name><id>8634446</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221922800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/8634446/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/4/global_5313428.jpeg</photo_url></item>