<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>152 Commonwealth Ave Unit M-1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.458334</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(877) 578-4777</phone><name>Lens Pro To Go</name><city>Concord</city><id>1066094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.396617</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Tim Tadder Monday January 9th 2012, 7:30&amp;ndash;9:30pm 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.cipne.org/CC_Postcard/assets/TT02.jpg" width="249" height="200" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commercial advertising photographer &lt;a href="http://www.timtadder.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tim Tadder&lt;/a&gt; will walk us through the dynamics of two drastically different styles of brand advertising campaigns shoots. We will first explore an &amp;ldquo;all hands on deck approach&amp;rdquo; where budgets are stretched razor thin and crews are pushed to the brink in order to bring great creativity to light. Sometimes clients have a desire for more than they can afford. Tadder will explain how to temper unrealistic expectations and deliver great images on thin budgets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tadder will contrast this with a &amp;ldquo;no stone left unturned&amp;rdquo; approach, where clients budget for perfect production, every detail is debated, call sheets go on for pages, and pre=production meetings run for hours. Sometimes more is less, and while big budgets make productions easier, they also can create overall complications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us as Tadder provides insight into his mistakes and successes and discusses his approach to creating successful shoots no matter what the budget or approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.cipne.org/CC_Postcard/assets/TT03.jpg" width="273" height="200" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim Tadder is a visual communicator who produces award-winning campaign work for top consumer brands including Adidas, AT&amp;amp;T, Duracell, Budweiser, Coke Zero, Craftsman, Gatorade, McDonalds, and more. His passion for photography began at age seven while assisting his father, a sports photographer for the Baltimore Orioles and Colts. The desire progressed while living in the Ecuadorean Andes. The full blown commitment developed while earning an MA in Visual Communications from Ohio University. The refinement is happening now in southern California as he works with top consumer brands to create award-winning campaigns. He creates highly-stylized action shots that draw viewers into the moment. Tadder has always been active in sports, exploration, and adventure and believes that being familiar with shooting live action makes it easier to recreate the look for advertising shoots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LOCATION &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.lensprotogo.com/" target="_blank"&gt;LensProToGo&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 152 Commonwealth Ave., &lt;br /&gt;

 Unit M-1, C, &lt;br /&gt;

 Concord, MA 01742&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We recommend that you check out the &lt;a href="http://www.lensprotogo.com/directions/" target="_blank"&gt;directions&lt;/a&gt; for the alternate (much larger) parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Registration:&lt;/span&gt; 6:30&amp;ndash;7:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Program:&lt;/span&gt; 7:30&amp;ndash;9:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; CIPNE Members, Free; Non-members*, $35; Full-time Students**, $5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Non-members - there is still time to join CIPNE or renew a lapsed membership at our specially discounted Membership Drive rate and attend this program for FREE, just &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org/membership.php"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Full-time students will be required to present their photo-IDs at registration.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Join in! If you have any interest in Commercail Work- you should see this program...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326240005000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324395017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tim Tadder: On Assignment- A lecture about production of ad campaigns</name><id>45015792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326153600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/45015792/</event_url></item>