<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Stevens Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.691586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Weir Hill</name><city>North Andover</city><id>922750</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110088</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Trace the western shoreline of a sparkling lake or enjoy a woodsy ascent to scenic views of the Merrimack Valley.   The two-mile-long lake and Weir Hill (&amp;quot;wire hill&amp;quot;) are the dominant natural features in the northeast part of town and easily its most scenic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring bug spray and wear hiking boots, as a small portion of the trail will be steep&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/u&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Water, a snack and sunscreen are also a good idea.  Some of you may wish to bring swimsuits for after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Hike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THERE ARE &lt;u&gt;NO&lt;/u&gt; RESTROOMS ON SITE, so leave enough time to stop before the hike!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave promptly at 9:40.  The hike will be about 3 to 3.5 miles.   We will follow the Edgewood Farm Trail to reach the meandering shore of Lake Cochichewick, which dominates the east and south edges of this reservation.  We will then follow the lake shoreline to Stevens Pond.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this point we will be about 2/3rd of the way through our hike.  Some of you may wish to stop and swim at the town beach at Stevens Pond.  I won't be stopping to swim but I can point you in the direction of your car.  Or you may prefer to take your car to the town beach after the hike for a swim.&lt;br /&gt;It looks like the $12 per person daily fee can not be avoided for swimming at Stevens Pond, unless you are a North Andover resident who has paid for a sticker.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last stretch of the hike, we will take Stevens Trail up the spine of Weir Hill to where a scenic overlook opens on the left. Enjoy a broad panorama of the Merrimack Valley spreading below. On days of good visibility, you can see Mount Wachusett rising in the distance beyond Worcester, and northwest of Wachusett, New Hampshire's Mount Monadnock.  (I must admit that the view is a little better when the leaves on the trees are gone).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the Hike&lt;br /&gt;I thought we might go out for lunch in the area.  I'm open to suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails/Landscape &lt;br /&gt;Four miles of trails, easy to moderate hiking, strenuous in places.&lt;br /&gt;Generations of agricultural use, a history of fire, and cutting and mowing regimes have created a patchwork landscape on Weir Hill that supports ten different types of plant communities, from a 60-acre oak-hickory forest to hillside seeps, intermittent streams, and wet meadows. Several threatened state-listed and watch-listed species can be found on Weir Hill, including the white bog orchid (Habenaria dilitata), violet bush clover (Lespedeza violacea), butternut trees (Juglans nigra), although we have not yet seen any of these.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you want to learn more about Weir Hill or print out a trail map, here's the link: &lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/weir-hill.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;If you type any address between 54 and 90 Stevens Street in North Andover in to your GPS, this should work.  When I used street view, I could see the trail head at 62 Stevens Street.  Park on the side of the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93 Exit 41, take Rt. 125 North 7.3 mi. Merge left onto Rt. 114 West and then right back onto Rt. 125. Follow for 0.2 mi. and turn right onto Andover St. Continue for 0.6 mi., bear right at fork, and continue 0.2 mi. to intersection. Proceed straight for 0.1 mi., turn left onto Stevens St., and continue for 0.8 mi. to entrance and roadside parking on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-495 Exit 42, take Rt. 114 East 1 mi. Turn left onto Rt. 133 East and follow for 0.2 mi. to traffic light. Proceed straight onto Andover St.  Continue for 0.6 mi., bear right at fork, and continue 0.2 mi. to intersection. Proceed straight for 0.1 mi., turn left onto Stevens St., and continue for 0.8 mi. to entrance and roadside parking on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing some of you again and meeting some of you for the first time. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the trail head with Meetup Stickers on. </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1281304982000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278907265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weir Hill Walk-slower with a number of stops- followed by Lunch</name><id>14073489</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281187800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/14073489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/6/6/global_8499174.jpeg</photo_url></item>