<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>41.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Bretton Woods got two feet of snow on Saturday night and may potentially get some more during the week!  The mountain is just about 100% open...what a great start to the season!  Come get some discounted turns in at Bretton Woods this weekend, Jan 8th-Jan 10th and stay at The Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors Club!  If you've never been to the house, it offers dormitory-style accommodations with full living room, kitchen and dining room areas, as well as 6 private full bathrooms.  Check it out at www.wedeln.com.  More importantly, it offers easy access to many Mt. Washington ski areas and lots of friendly faces!  We welcome you to come up and spend this weekend with us!  Here's a tentative itinerary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday night:&lt;/b&gt;  BYOB and get to know the others staying at the lodge for the weekend and find some ski buddies too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday:&lt;/b&gt;  Breakfast (optional, $5, must pay in advance...payment details to come).  Then head to Bretton Woods.  Many Wedelns will be taking part in their first race of the season, which means everyone staying at the house will get a substantial discount on their lift ticket for the day!  Tickets will be available for purchase at the mountain saturday morning, cash only and before 8:45 a.m.  We pay $45 (give or take a few bucks) instead of the usual $74!  This in an amazing opportunity to ski/ride on the cheap!  Of course, if you want to ski a different mountain in the area, there are many to choose from, including Wildcat, Attitash and Cranmore, or you can take a ride to Sunday River, which is an hour from the house.  Sunday River is doing a Facebook friend promotion for this Saturday.  If you are a Sunday River friend, you can ski for $39.  You have to sign up in advance.  Check out the details on their website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday afternoon/evening:&lt;/b&gt;  Apres ski fun and then full turkey dinner at Wedeln (optional, $15, must pay in advance...payment details to come), and perhaps some more fun by night.  If turkey's not your thing, check out one of the many fine establishments in North Conway for dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfast (optional, $5, must pay in advance...payment details to come). Then, go for some more skiing/riding at local mountains, or snow shoe nearby the house, cross country ski in Jackson, or check out the outlets in North Conway.  See what others are up to, or do your own thing, before heading home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prepayment will be required:&lt;/b&gt; The two night stay at Wedeln is $40 ($20 per night).  Meal package is $25 for both breakfasts and Saturday night dinner.  Payment info will be posted shortly.  Meals are contingent upon meeting minimum numbers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apprehensive about coming up not knowing anyone?  Then come to our Prime Season Kickoff Party at the La Verdad Taqueria, 1 Landsdowne Street, Boston, on Wednesday night this week.  Here are the details: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/calendar/12140786/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you have any questions!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you come into the house ask  the first person you see for Darlene.  If I'm not there yet, ask for Flounder (yes, that says Flounder).  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263230394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262660437000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ski Weekend at Wedeln Ski &amp; Outdoors Club</name><id>12224320</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262995200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/12224320/</event_url></item>