<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.361595</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 227-2098</phone><name>Bell In Hand</name><city>Boston</city><id>766411</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057058</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Hello,&lt;br /&gt;The Awesome and Fun Meet Up group is hosting this event along with other meet up groups. You can check their site out at: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/theawesomeandfungroup/calendar/11239679/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are attending, please look for Katie, the awesome and fun group organizer, as I will not be able to attend- most likely.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Note: This is not strictly an Awesome and Fun Group Meetup Event. People from other Meetup groups, the Red Cross, the Boston Young Professionals Society, and other friends not related to any of these groups will be attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AS COPIED FROM AWESOME AND FUN MEET UP GROUP EVENT DESCRIPTION!&lt;br /&gt;BOO!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us on the spookiest night of the year for A Haunting at the Bell in Hand. Join us on All Hallows Eve for lots of treats...and perhaps a few tricks along the way! Dressing up in your scariest (or cutest!) costume is not required, but strongly suggested. There will even be fun prizes for Best Overall Costume, Most Creative Costume, Spookiest Costume, Best Couples Costume, and Craziest Costume.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are doing this to raise money for the Red Cross. Don't worry...you do not need to give blood (only to the vampires in attendance). However, we are asking each person to pay $20.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What do you get for $20.00 (besides the kindness and joy in your heart from donating to a very worthy cause)? Well, food for one thing (pizzas, chicken tenders, potato skins, mozzarella sticks, etc.). Additionally, the Bell in Hand is mixing up some creepy drink specials at a discounted price just for us! We're also getting a DJ to play your favorite songs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUT WAIT, there's more! It also includes Trick or Treat Bags filled with goodies for each person. Games will be played...and a pinata or two will also probably make a guest appearance. It also includes the chance to win some amazing raffle prizes! We also reserve the right to throw a few surprises your way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on the number of people, we will either be upstairs or downstairs at the Bell in Hand, but either way we'll have the room to ourselves. Check your email closer to the event date and we will let you know exactly where we will be located.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because the food and Trick or Treat Bags need to be ordered ahead of time, we won't be able to take any RSVPs at the door or after October 15th. We also can't take money at the door, so please pay ahead of time. We set up a PayPal account ([masked]).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite a few...or 50...friends (just make sure they pay ahead of time as well). We want to raise as much money as possible for the Red Cross! Hope to see you there :).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trick or Treat?!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please Look for Katie, Awesome and Fun Meet Up group Organizer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257203471000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255058807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Haunting at the Bell in Hand.   Awesome and Fun Meet Up Group Event</name><id>11586483</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257030000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/11586483/</event_url></item>