<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>34 Bedford Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.662575</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lee Hall in the Wishcamper Center at USM Portland</name><city>Portland</city><id>1448835</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.273759</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/f/2/event_76331762.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We are extremely lucky to be able to take advantage of a last-minute opportunity to host &lt;strong&gt;Nicole Foss&lt;/strong&gt; (a.k.a. "Stoneleigh" from The Automatic Earth) for a timely talk on "The Century of Challenge" ahead of us and what is happening in our world and how it will play out globally, nationally and locally. &amp;nbsp;Nicole is a world renowned financial analyst with expertise in financial bubbles. &amp;nbsp;She has the ability to explain in very straightforward terms a complex system that affects us all regardless of our interest in economics. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;She will help us understand the big picture much more clearly as well as suggest ways that we can personally prepare ourselves and our community for continuing economic volatility and upheaval.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meetup is ideal for anyone watching the economy, the financial markets, people who are confused about what to do with their money/investments (if they still have some!) and anyone who needs to understand the ramifications of a growth economy on the brink of something unprecedented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://efc.muskie.usm.maine.edu/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://efc.muskie.usm.maine.edu/"&gt;This event is generously co-sponsored by the University of Southern Maine and the New England Environmental Finance Center.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donations will be accepted at the door to defray the cost of travel for our speaker.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/215138/2012_Nicole_Foss_PWM.pdf"&gt;Feel free to print/post/share event flier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More About Nicole:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nicole M. Foss is co-editor of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://theautomaticearth.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Automatic Earth&lt;/a&gt;, where she writes under the name Stoneleigh. She and her writing partner have been chronicling and interpreting the on-going credit crunch as the most pressing aspect of our current multi-faceted predicament. The site integrates finance, energy, environment, psychology, population and real politik in order to explain why we find ourselves in a state of crisis and what we can do about it. Prior to the establishment of TAE, she was previously editor of The Oil Drum Canada, where she wrote on peak oil and finance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Foss runs the Agri-Energy Producers' Association of Ontario, where she has focused on farm-based biogas projects and grid connections for renewable energy. While living in the UK she was a Research Fellow at the Oxford Institute for Energy Studies, where she specialized in nuclear safety in Eastern Europe and the Former Soviet Union, and conducted research into electricity policy at the EU level.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Her academic qualifications include a BSc in biology from Carleton University in Canada (where she focused primarily on neuroscience and psychology), a post-graduate diploma in air and water pollution control, the common professional examination in law and an LLM in international law in development from the University of Warwick in the UK. She was granted the University Medal for the top science graduate in 1988 and the law school prize for the top law school graduate in 1997.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://efc.muskie.usm.maine.edu/images/neefclogoREV.jpg" alt="neefc" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://usm.maine.edu/image/images/vertical_usm_logo.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>PARKING:  You can park for free in the garage (36 on map) attached to Abromson Center, next door to Wishcamper (41 on map).  Printable campus map: http://usm.maine.edu/sites/default/files/About%20USM/portland_map_color_locator.pdf</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323893000000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322772776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Making Sense of the Economic Crisis in the Era of Peak Oil</name><id>43067852</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323734400000</time><rsvp_limit>80</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/43067852/</event_url></item>