<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.360067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Suites</name><city>Boston</city><id>968618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Folks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The seating for this event is very limited!&amp;nbsp; In order to assure that you have a seat, I need for you to RSVP ASAP.&amp;nbsp; RSVP via the meetup, however, also, send me an email at &lt;a href="mailto:dette101@gmail.com"&gt;dette101@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, please include your email so that I can add you to a special distribution list for attendees.&amp;nbsp; I need to make sure that I have enough materials and samples for everyone.&amp;nbsp; This will be a phenomenal event...also, check out my latest blog entry -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="https://traftonbernadette.wordpress.com/2011/11/04/do-you-have-traits-that-are-killing-your-chances-to-succeed/"&gt;Do you have traits that are killing your chances to&amp;nbsp;succeed?&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Also, please note that this event is taking the place of the event we normally have in Windham, NH.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I have updated that meetup, I hadn't realized it was still listed.&amp;nbsp; I apologize!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Make it a great day and in the words of Wayne Gretsky - "100 percent of the shots you don't take, don't go in!"&amp;nbsp; So, take your shot today!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Folks this event is launching the Boston area of FDI Youngevity! Folks this is an ALL-STAR event! Million Dollar earners abound! VP of Training Steve Schulz, VP of Leadership Development Mike Randolph, #1 Rep of FDIY Sheryl Morley , PMD Maxandra DesRosiers, VPMD Annie Trajlinek and VPMD Bernadette Trafton will ROCK THE HOUSE! BOSTON will not know what hit them! Self-motivated, positve, high-powered people to network with! An opportunity presentation followed by the BEST training the industry has to offer! BE AT THIS EVENT!!! I haven't seen this much star power in a room since the National Convention!! Contact Bernadette at 603-505-8683, dette101@gmail.com for free entrance! Refreshments will be provided. ACT NOW, There is limited seating at this event RSVP today!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette Trafton</member_name><member_id>12413116</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321190660000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Health/Wealth Builders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>yourbridgetowealth</urlname><id>403924</id><group_lat>42.7999992371</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3000030518</group_lon><name>Your Bridge to health and wealth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>91</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317934128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SAVE MONEY!  GET HEALTHY!  CREATE WEALTH! - Must RSVP TO Guarentee seating</name><id>36442462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321106400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/yourbridgetowealth/events/36442462/</event_url></item>