<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>978 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02120</zip><lat>42.337193</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>SLADES BAR &amp; GRILLE</name><city>Roxbury</city><id>1414870</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084212</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/8/event_168901912.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/b/4/event_161873172.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;TOSOB  Steppin Set at Slade's theme 'Steppin In Pink'  TOSOB's contribution to Breast Cancer Awareness Month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a fundraiser for the under served communities of Roxbury, Dorchester and Mattapan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A raffle will be held with mystery gift baskets for men and women&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breast Cancer Awareness Month is an annual international health campaign organized by major breast cancer charities to increase awareness of the disease and to raise funds for research, information and support to those affected by breast cancer as well as a reminder to women to be aware for early &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/5/0/event_161876912.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;detection. Men also have been diagnosed with Breast Cancer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;American Cancer Society &lt;a href="http://www.cancer.org/index"&gt;http://www.cancer.org/index&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NATIONAL CANCER INSTITUTE FACT SHEET&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prostate cancer occurs more often in African-American men than in men of other races. African-American men are also more likely to be diagnosed at an advanced stage, and are more than twice as likely to die of prostate cancer as white men. Prostate cancer occurs less often in Asian-American and Hispanic/Latino men than in non-Hispanic whites. The reasons for these racial and ethnic differences are not clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PSA -  prostate-specific antigen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PSA test has been widely used to screen men for prostate cancer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The higher a man’s PSA level, the more likely it is that he has prostate cancer. However, there are additional reasons for having an elevated PSA level, and some men who have prostate cancer do not have elevated PSA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The PSA test has been widely used to screen men for prostate cancer. It is also used to monitor men who have been diagnosed with prostate cancer to see if their cancer has recurred (come back) after initial treatment or is responding to therapy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some advisory groups now recommend against the use of the PSA test to screen for prostate cancer because the benefits, if any, are small and the harms can be substantial. None recommend its use without a detailed discussion of the pros and cons of using the test&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cancer.gov/"&gt;http://www.cancer.gov/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TOSOB COMMUNITY FUNDRAISER $5.00 MINUM PER PERSON PROCEEDS AMERICAN CANCER SOCIETY AND SUSAN G. KOMAN FOR THE CURE</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>valerie wales</member_name><member_id>5133027</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351996732000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Original Steppers of Boston</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Steppers-of-Boston</urlname><id>1340809</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Original Steppers of Boston Inc. 2006</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347414465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>STEPPIN IN PINK - BREAST CANCER AWARENESS MONTH</name><id>81987262</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351366200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Steppers-of-Boston/events/81987262/</event_url></item>