<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey all, this is an invitation to a community event on the South Shore that is a great opportunity to meet some friends and volunteer to support a very local cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South Shore Habitat for Humanity is looking to get a new project going in the Braintree area. A group of local volunteers have stepped up to lead the Local Partnership Committee, and we are looking for all the helping hands we can get!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are not yet at the actual building phase for our project, but there is no shortage of volunteer opportunities. At our community meetings we set the agenda for the next month, develop fund raising strategies and events, and sign on volunteers to help plan and staff those events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We meet the 2nd Wednesday of the month @ 7-8:30pm.  We have a fun time and you are welcome to bring your dinner if you need to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are in the South Shore area, please come by, we'd love to meet you and get you on board as we develop this project!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Overview&lt;/em&gt;: The BCYC is located on Pond Street, approximately 1 mile from Braintree High School and the T and highway. It is one of two brick buildings next to a cemetery across from Sunset Lake. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;From North of Braintree&lt;/em&gt;: Take Route 93/95/128 to Route 3 South. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;From Route 3&lt;/em&gt;: Take Exit 17/Union Street, Braintree.  Exit the Rotary heading towards the T and Bickford's and South Braintree.  Go straight through the 1st light keeping the T on your left.  Go up the hill and take a left at the next light onto Washington Street.  Follow straight thru 2 sets of lights passing Town Hall on your right.  At the next set of lights take a right, which is still Washington Street.  (Rite-Aid is at this intersection.  It will be to your left at the light and behind you after you make the turn.)  Take a left at the next light (onto Route 37S) keeping Braintree Cooperative Bank on your left.  Take a right at the next light onto Pond Street.  74 Pond Street is 1/4 mile up on the left next to a cemetary.  It is one of two brick buildings.  Park on the side. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;From the Braintree T&lt;/em&gt;: Follow directions above on foot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352948583000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350644366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Habitat for Humanity, Braintree Community Meeting</name><id>87662712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352937600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/87662712/</event_url></item>