<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>169 main st</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02895</zip><lat>42.002617</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harris hall</name><city>woonsocket</city><id>10105682</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.513786</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to curb the city’s population of pit bulls and other “fierce, dangerous or vicious” dogs, City Council President John F. Ward has proposed an ordinance that will prohibit any new pit bulls in the city after the ordinance is passed. &lt;br /&gt;

 Existing pit bulls would be permitted to register prior to passing the ordinance, allowing them to remain within the city limits, but owners would have to obtain $100,000 liability policy as well as meet additional requirements to legally own the dogs. &lt;br /&gt;

 This knee-jerk reaction comes at the heels of an incident last month that involved an alleged pit bull in which three people were injured with bite wounds. &lt;br /&gt;

 According to Council President Ward, the police department has requested repeatedly that Woonsocket officials enact breed specific legislation because ‘we have pit bulls all over the city’. Ward says “They think it would make it safer.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the registration requirement and liability insurance, the new ordinance would require mandatory spay/neutering of ‘pit bulls’, “escape-proof” containment on the owners property, and muzzled and leashed or in a temporary enclosure when off the owners property. &lt;br /&gt;

 The proposed ordinance is structured on the near-by Pawtucket ordinance that was passed several years ago. Ward states that while the matter is on the agenda for the Council’s Monday night meeting, it will likely be tabled for sometime in effort to provide council members time to discuss the proposal, gather feedback from police, pet owners and Animal Control Officer Doris Kay, as well as invite Pawtucket Animal Control Officer John Holmes to talk with council about how the law is working in his city. &lt;br /&gt;

 “Pit Bull” is defined as American Pit Bull Terrier, American Staffordshire Terrier, Staffordshire Bull Terrier, or any dog of mixed breed displaying the majority of physical traits of any one or more of the above breeds.” &lt;br /&gt;

 To send your POLITE, PROFESSIONAL and INFORMATIVE correspondence to Woonsocket Officials: &lt;br /&gt;

 Woonsocket Council Agenda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 John F. Ward, CPA &lt;br /&gt;

 President&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;jfwardcpa@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Daniel M. Gendron &lt;br /&gt;

 Vice President&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dangendron1@verizon.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Roger Jalette&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(401) 597-5790&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Christopher Beauchamp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;chrisbeauchamp@nicori.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Robert Moreau&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;rmoreau462@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Albert Brien&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;albertgbrien@yahoo.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Marc Dubois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;mdubois6@cox.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 PLEASE JOIN US ANY SPEAK OUT &lt;br /&gt;

 HERE ARE LINKS TO FACEBOOK SITES WHO ARE ORGANIZING A RESPONSE. THE MEETING IS OPEN TO PUBLIC SPEAKING, 3 MINUTES. WE HAVE SRENGTH IN NUMBERS, SIMPLY STANDING THERE WITH A POSTER OR A SHIRT SHOWING YOUR SUPPORT WILL MEAN THE WORLD. THANK YOU!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/#!/events/110075625817963/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/#!/events/110075625817963/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/#!/StopWoonsocketBsl" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/#!/StopWoonsocketBsl&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 come early if you can for a peaceful protest...5pm&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352169172000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351794700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Help fight WOONSOCKET B.S.L., no matter where you are!</name><id>89505932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352158200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/89505932/</event_url></item>