<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello all.  Our February meetup brings us back to our regular scedule of first Friday of the month.   Every month our meetup is growing by leaps and bounds!  It is so exciting that people are wanting to take more control over their health and well being.  Getting back to basics.  Not only do we learn a lot from each other but the food is amazing. If you are raw or interested in making better food choices in your diet this is the place to be.  Bring a raw organic dish enough for 6-8 people.  If you are new to raw and not sure what to bring a nice organic fruit or veggie salad is always good.&lt;br /&gt;I have had several members ask that we have an evening where people share their stories of how and why they chose a raw diet.  This is that evening.  If you have a story to share shoot me an email and we will get you in the spotlight.  We are the buzz of the raw food meetups!  No one can understand how we are so successfull!  I know why we are successful....we have the most amazing members!  If you have not yet attended a meetup come and join us and you will instantly know what I am talking about.  $2 for adults, children free.  See you soon!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KO Bisson</member_name><member_id>4565632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265649999000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawfood-ManchNH</urlname><id>1292928</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Food Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263602110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Food February Meetup</name><id>ljqclyndbhb</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265412600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawfood-ManchNH/events/12332400/</event_url></item>