<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>326 Main Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01354</zip><lat>42.640845</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 863-9006</phone><name>Gill Tavern</name><city>Gill</city><id>1247153</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.499772</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Gill Tavern is such a cool place! The weather will be gorgeous, the food will be wonderful and it's another chance for us to come together and laugh and enjoy life with people we like. Started by the owner of the People's Pint, the Gill Tavern ooozes with genuine charm. I know it's a hike for many of you, but come on! We are foodies! Nowhere is too far for a good meal, right?  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what they say about themselves:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;In the spirit that good food makes good company, The Gill Tavern aims to nourish the dining and gathering needs of Gill and its neighboring towns. The Tavern serves fare made from fresh, locally produced ingredients whenever possible in an atmosphere that fosters friendship, community, and respect for our environment. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Right up our alley! And guess what we HAVE to HAVE based on the reviews below?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a review from The Republican last week (thanks Rosemary!):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.masslive.com/entertainment/index.ssf/2010/04/restaurant_review_the_gill_tav.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gill Tavern Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and some testimonials from around the 'net:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Gill Tavern is a small and absolutely charming restaurant in an old country store in the middle-of-no-where. It has a really sophisticated bar with all of my favorite beers (especially Farmer Brown from The People's Pint). They have great seafood, soups, salads, and vegetarian options. My mother went there for Oyster Night late this summer and said it was fabulous (I am not a fan of oysters). My husband went out for &amp;quot;a beer&amp;quot; with friends and ended up gorging on lamb chop &amp;quot;lollipops&amp;quot; with shaved fennel and goat cheese and bacon wrapped scallops over a spinach salad. Plan on getting there early (especially if you are feeding kids) or making reservations. There can be a line out the door.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chow.com/restaurants/44949/gill-tavern" target="_blank"&gt;Chow.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Gill Tavern is cute -- especially in the front room (though it can also be loud). It's the sister to the People's Pint. It does, unlike the People's Pint, take credit cards. Food is very good, and the atmosphere and service are lively and friendly. I highly recommend the gorgonzola garlic bread -- chewy and not too blue cheesey for those who don't usually love blue cheese.&lt;br /&gt;##&lt;br /&gt;The Gill Tavern is a quaint yummy secret, hidden in the small town of Gill.  The night I went, seemed like I was walking onto the set of a movie.  The atmosphere is darling.  Small tables filled with bright, happy people, covered in great food and drinks.  Local beer is served along with a short menu of delicious entrees.  &lt;br /&gt;##&lt;br /&gt;The Gorgonzola garlic bread is delicious, hot and crunchy with delicious cheese.   I tried the prime rib and it was cooked perfectly and the spices were delicious.  A fresh peach cobbler for dessert with local ice cream finished off the meal to stuffed bliss.  &lt;br /&gt;##&lt;br /&gt;The first time there we started with the Gorgonzola garlic bread, which is incredible.  I'll never eat plain garlic bread again.  For the main dish, I got the Alfredo pasta, which was average, but it came with a mixed green salad, with the best sun dried tomatoes I've ever had.  I never used to like sun dried tomatoes, and now I have to get the salad just so I can get the tomatoes!  Luckily the salad comes as a side with many of the main dishes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another interesting thing about the food, it's mostly (if not all) locally grown.  &lt;br /&gt;They have a full bar and their own beer.  The beer is under the People's Pint label, since the owners of the Gill Tavern own the People's Pint in Greenfield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the Alfredo had been as wonderful as everything else, they'd have gotten 5 stars. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-gill-tavern-gill" target="_blank"&gt;Yelp.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can't wait to taste the...you guessed it: GORGONZOLA GARLIC BREAD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jessica, Christine and Kirsten&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will be the ones laughing the loudest</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277678162000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271387349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gill Tavern Sunday, May 16th!</name><id>13197483</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274047200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/13197483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/e/3/global_14399347.jpeg</photo_url></item>