<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Essex Way</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05452</zip><lat>44.501583</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>888-802-7364</phone><name>The Essex Vermont’s Culinary Resort &amp; Spa</name><city>Essex</city><id>1139263</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.078732</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Check out Traveling Singles Meetup group to see who is attending: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/TravelingSingles/calendar/15064628/?action=detail"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;WE STILL HAVE ROOMS AVAILABLE AT THE $237 RATE!  &lt;b&gt;Also, we have a room share available - pay only $135 total for both two nights.  Email me if you are interested: jackierg@comcast.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: black"&gt;Attend our very first trip!&lt;/b&gt;Enjoy a fabulous weekend doing whatever you want.  Relax at the spa, participate in activities, shop, or visit some great attractions.  This 4 star resort has an indoor pool, outdoor hot tub, fitness center, and gorgeous new spa (voted best in Vermont).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arrive any time on Friday depart any time on Sunday.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;b]Cost is $15 to hold your spot - payable through this site.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once your $15 deposit is received, you will receive an email on how to pay the balance directly to the Essex with your credit card.  Scroll to bottom to see rates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpool&lt;/b&gt; - arrangements will be made as soon as reservations are made and we see who is going.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We get 20% off of culinary classes, spa services, and more...&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vtculinaryresort.com/"&gt;Essex Resort &amp;amp; Spa Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stuff to do at the Essex and in the Burlington area:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Friday night&lt;/b&gt; we’ll have dinner at the resort and hang out in their tavern for a casual dinner and an evening of fun socializing.  If you plan on getting there early, consider a spa treatment, browse the outlett shoppes across the street, take a walk, or just relax in the comfy lobby area while sipping on hot cider.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday and/or Sunday&lt;/b&gt; – walk along Lake Champlain, browse the shops downtown, spend time at the spa, take a swim, visit the outlet stores, relax, read a book, visit Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s or the Vermont Teddy Bear Factory.  These are just a few of the things you can do.  See below for more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday night&lt;/b&gt; – relax and socialize at the hotel Tavern after enjoying the bonfire with s’mores (weather permitting).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spa at the Essex&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Voted best in Vermont.  Offers several spa services from manicures to massages to several different body treatments and relaxation rooms. One service (or $25) gets you full use of the spa including relaxation rooms, saunas, etc. Spa treatments need to be booked at least 3 days in advance. Visit the website for a menu of services and call the resort to schedule your services.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bonfire&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every Saturday night the resort has a bonfire with s’mores (weather permitting).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cooking Classes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://atyourschool.youritdept.com/vcr/jsp/Calendar.jsp?TYPE=M&amp;amp;YEAR=2010&amp;amp;MONTH=11&amp;amp;DAY=1&amp;amp;SESSIONID=1287886363211"&gt;Check the schedule to sign up for a cooking class.  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bicycle Rentals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For leisure, recreational riding. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Northern Lights Rock and Ice&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;High Ropes, Low Elements, Zip Wires, Rock &amp;amp; Ice Climbing, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernlightsvt.com/nlri/index.php/rates.html"&gt;http://www.northernli...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lake Champlain&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a walk or bike ride along the largest and most beautiful lake. I will be organizing a group walk on Saturday or Sunday along this magnificent Lake. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shopping&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit down town Burlington and walk the cobblestones while browsing the shops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.essexshoppes.com/Welcome.asp?Key=1"&gt;Essex outlet shoppes including Polo, Reebok, Bogner, OshKosh, Carters) &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Attractions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit Vermont Teddy Bear Factory, Lake Champlain Chocolates, Magic Hat Brewery, Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Room Rates&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$237.00 per person, single occupancy for two nights.  &lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;(You may share a room with a cot and pay only $119.00.)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Room Availability Options - price per room is $237 plus...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traditional Room (1 bed) with gas fireplaces @ $20 p&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;lus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Traditional Room (2 beds) with gas fireplaces @ $20 plus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Minisuite (1 bed) @ $30 plus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Minisuites (2 beds) @ $30 plus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Luxury Room (1 bed) @ $30 plus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Studios (1 bed) @ $30 plus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Deluxe One Bedrooms (king and full-size pullout) @ $50 plus tax per night&lt;br /&gt;Luxury One Bedrooms (queen and full-size pullout) @ $60 plus tax per night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacki</member_name><member_id>6777705</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290438202000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287961086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vermont Weekend Getaway at the Essex Resort &amp; Spa</name><id>15214713</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290196800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/15214713/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/3/global_13367603.jpeg</photo_url></item>