<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every now and then this happens... I have to change movies 2 days before the meetup. Prince of Persia's been out for a few weeks and it looks like it's getting bumped for the 8-hour Twilight-athon that AMC is planning (all 3 movies starting at 6:30 on Tuesday night for $30). I would have been totally into this (natch!) if I hadn't already scheduled a meetup for this Tuesday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prince got bumped to one showing that day -- at 4:20. Most of you will still be in work at that time, so I think that won't work out so well! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810115368/details" target="_blank"&gt;Knight and Day&lt;/a&gt; with Cameron Diaz and Tom Cruise, however, will show lots of times since it's a new movie. So we're gonna head for the 7:20 show, let's meet at 6:50 either right inside or right outside the ticket lobby. Here's the summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;A woman is caught between a covert agent and those he claims set him up. As their globetrotting adventure erupts into a maze of double-crosses, close escapes, false identities, and head-spinning romantic snafus, they come to realize that all they can count on is each other.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to see the Twilight trifecta, you're more than welcome to do that, too. I cannot, however, offer discount tickets for it, as it's a special promotion by the theater and they won't let me. Sorry!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Knight and Day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810041991/details" target="_blank"&gt;Prince of Persia&lt;/a&gt; looks like a good ol'-fashioned summer blockbuster. Don't get caught up in the accents, but the special effects should be incredible. Come be blown away by Jake Gyllenhaal, Ben Kingsley and Alfred Molina!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set in the mystical lands of Persia, a rogue prince reluctantly joins forces with a mysterious princess and together, they race against dark forces to safeguard an ancient dagger capable of releasing the Sands of Time - a gift from the gods that can reverse time and allow its possessor to rule the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat). I'll bring the coupons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Prince of Persia!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279919297000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276108029000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Knight and Day, was Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time</name><id>13750337</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277851500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/13750337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>