<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Get the feeling, get the feeling, get the feeling!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first time I have ever done this! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you practicing the Law of Attraction for a while I have a special class just for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 4am this morning I had a "download" I was told to get a pen and start writing. I did and I am very happy to share it. This process will be taking you to the "feeling" of abundance like you have never experienced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class is not for a beginner, this is for those persons practicing for a while and understand the importance and the depth of vibration. We will travel the vibrational scale but in an experintial way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All particpants must be experienced at sitting quietly for mediation, not necessarily at a long amount of time, have practiced some form of Law of Attaction for at least 6 months to a year, be comfortably versed in&amp;nbsp;the concept of manipulatoing energy&amp;nbsp;and be open to a new deep meaningful experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All newer students, I appologize but in order to raise the conscienousness of the more experienced students I have to seperate the class for this particular program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The class will start promptly at 7:00. The class will end at 8:00. Anyone wanting to stay and talk after is welcome to until 9:00. If you want to share a snack or beverage after it is welcomed and appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.thehsccenter.com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312244301000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311589810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Get the Feeling, Get the Feeling, Get the Feeling!!</name><id>26925731</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312239600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/26925731/</event_url></item>