<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/6/a/event_191715722.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This looks like a fun, fairly mindless action flick.  Lets start the new year by watching people blow and shoot things up.  :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Showtime is at 7:30.  I will be at the theater by 6:30 and we will head in for seats by 7. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, I arrive at the theater an hour before the show to start gathering people, and we head in for seats about 30 minutes before the show, so we can sit together. This also allows us to take turns getting snacks, etc., before the previews start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;Because the group usually sees movies opening weekend, it is a good idea to buy your tickets in advance, especially if there is a lot of buzz about the film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after. We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after.$$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; January 25, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; FilmDistrict &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Taylor Hackford &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; John J. McLaughlin &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Jason Statham, Jennifer Lopez, Michael Chiklis, Wendell Pierce, Nick Nolte &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Crime, Thriller &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; R (for strong violence throughout) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://getyourcut.com" target="_blank"&gt;GetYourCut.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Jason Statham and Jennifer Lopez team up to get their cut in the crime thriller, "Parker," based on the series of bestselling novels by Donald E. Westlake. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Parker (Jason Statham) is a professional thief who lives by a personal code of ethics: Don’t steal from people who can’t afford it and don’t hurt people who don’t deserve it. But on his latest heist, his crew double crosses him, steals his stash, and leaves him for dead. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Determined to make sure they regret it, Parker tracks them to PalmBeach, playground of the rich and famous, where the crew is planning their biggest heist ever. Donning the disguise of a rich Texan, Parker takes on an unlikely partner, Leslie (Jennifer Lopez), a savvy insider, who’s short on cash, but big on looks, smarts and ambition. Together, they devise a plan to hijack the score, take everyone down and get away clean.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359764346000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356987455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Parker (7:30PM Show)</name><id>97236662</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359243000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/97236662/</event_url></item>