<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>92 Waltham St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01754</zip><lat>42.429348</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-361-7978</phone><name>Victoria's house</name><city>Maynard</city><id>948502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.440777</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We've had a good long break from the last book club discussion.  So, let's start up again with one that's still on the hot list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Safran Foer spent much of his teenage and college years oscillating between omnivore and vegetarian. But on the brink of fatherhood—facing the prospect of having to make dietary choices on a child's behalf—his casual questioning took on urgency. His quest for answers ultimately required him to visit factory farms in the middle of the night, dissect the emotional ingredients of meals from his childhood, and probe some of his most primal instincts about right and wrong. Brilliantly synthesizing philosophy, literature, science, memoir, and his own detective work, Eating Animals explores the many fictions we use to justify our eating habits—from folklore to pop culture to family traditions and national myth—and how such tales can lull us into a barbaric forgetting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A review on the book from Amazon:&lt;br /&gt;The book is like nothing else ever written on the food industry. It reads like a novel, is funny, incredibly well documented, and lets factory farmers and animal activists speak in their own words. I've read a lot of books on the food industry and this is by far the best.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come prepared to talk about what you've read.  &lt;br /&gt;Light refreshments will be provided.  : )&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277726555000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272337255000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club: Discussion of "Eating Animals" by Jonathan Safran Foer</name><id>13302184</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277665200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/13302184/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>