<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 Buckland Hills Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.806870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-648-0730</phone><name>Bertucci's</name><city>Manchester </city><id>1321542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.545900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The movie starts at 830 so let's meet for dinner at 630. For anyone going straight to the movie we'll meet you in the Libby by chatters at around 8. If we're running late and you can't find me give me a call. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's start with dinner at Bertucci's in the Buckland mall. The address is listed above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie will be at Rave Cinemas (formerly showcase) at 99 Redstone Rd, Manchester, CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Inception, this is opening weekend so it will be crowded and probably sell out.  &lt;b&gt;You will need to purchase tickets in advance. &lt;/b&gt; We have the option to see it in IMAX.  IMAX will cost a little more and require reservations.  If the majority say they prefer IMAX in their RSVP, I'll post it that way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inception:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dom Cobb (Leonardo DiCaprio) is a skilled thief, the absolute best in the dangerous art of extraction, stealing valuable secrets from deep within the subconscious during the dream state when the mind is at its most vulnerable. Cobb’s rare ability has made him a coveted player in this treacherous new world of corporate espionage, but it has also made him an international fugitive and cost him everything he has ever loved. Now Cobb is being offered a chance at redemption. One last job could give him his life back but only if he can accomplish the impossible—inception.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Leonardo DiCaprio, Ken Watanabe, Joseph Gordon-Levitt &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://inceptionmovie.warnerbros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://inceptionmovie.warnerbros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://inceptionmovie...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll grab a drink somewhere afterward so we can discuss.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Bertucci's - meet at the hostess stand.  If skipping dinner, meet at the theater near the restaurant.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279665347000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279035537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inception - Dinner and a Movie</name><id>14089154</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279405800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/14089154/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/a/global_16406810.jpeg</photo_url></item>