<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Grafton St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.260447</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)400-7007</phone><name>Osgood Bradley Building</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1015377</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.793748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Farmagedon is a documentary film that illustrates, in no... uncertain terms, the all out assault on local farmers by big government and their partners in corporate agribusiness. YOU WILL NOT BELIEVE WHAT GOVERNMENT AGENCIES ARE DOING TO INNOCENT FARMERS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Kristin is brave enough to create this informative film, WE should be brave enough to help spread the word.....and that's just what we're going to do on Saturday July 21st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1:00 p.m. - Doors open. Guests are encouraged to meet and mingle with other guests and venders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3:00 p.m. - The Red Pill Politics radio show will be filmed LIVE with special guests "Farmageddon" filmmaker Kristin Canty and Matt Thibodeau of "Luckyfoot Ranch"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4:15 p.m. - Screening of FARMAGEDDON with introduction by Kristin Canty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:45 p.m. - Q&amp;amp;A Session&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:15 p.m. - Break...mingle...potluck...exhibitors...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 p.m. - BAND "Farmstand".....and others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a day long event designed to educate people on critical food and agriculture related issues that effect all of us. Here are a few other things that will be going on throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Venders - Organizers are seeking to include a variety of agriculture related groups. They will be offered vending tables to share their information, product or service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Fresh Produce - Luckyfoot Rance will be providing a huge selection of ultra-fresh seasonal garden items from the Ranch. ALL Organic....NO GMO's!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Farmageddon DVD's - Guests will be able to meet filmmaker Kristin Canty AND get a signed copy of her groundbreaking film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* FOOD - We're going to have a massive potluck table set up so guests can sample and nibble throughout the day. This will be a group effort so please bring your favorite dish, beverage or appetizer to contribute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Entertainment - Farmstand is just one of the bands that will be rocking us into the evening. Stick around as we showcase some local talent, well into the wee hours of the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come for the show or come for the whole day, but DON'T MISS THIS EVENT! Please blast this important event out to your friends and family. help us promote awareness of this critical issue everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Farmageddon Trailer: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/16513455" class="linkified"&gt;http://vimeo.com/16513455&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luckyfoot Ranch: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/LuckyfootRanchRI" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/LuckyfootRanchRI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: There is no ATM at the venue so please be sure to have the appropriate funds you need for any purchases and donations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342900927000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341504589000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Farmageddon screening and Q&amp;A with filmaker</name><id>72059382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342890000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/72059382/</event_url></item>