<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our July pick is &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Three Cups of Tea&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; by Greg Mortenson and David Oliver Relin.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a brief synopsis from Barnes and Noble of &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Three Cups of Tea&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One day in 1993, high up in the world's most inhospitable mountains, Greg Mortenson wandered lost and alone, broken in body and spirit, after a failed attempt to climb K2, the world's deadliest peak. When the people of an impoverished village in Pakistan's Karakoram Himalaya took him in and nursed him back to health, Mortenson made an impulsive promise: He would return one day and build them a school. Although he was a homeless &amp;quot;climbing bum&amp;quot; living out of his aging Buick in Berkeley, California, Mortenson sold what few possessions he had to launch one of the most remarkable humanitarian campaigns of our time.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Three Cups of Tea traces Mortenson's decade-long odyssey to build schools, especially for girls, throughout the region that gave birth to the Taliban and sanctuary to Al Qaeda. While he wages war with the root causes of terrorism - poverty and ignorance - by providing both girls and boys with a balanced, nonextremist education. Mortenson must survive a kidnapping, fatwas issued by enraged mullahs, death threats from Americans who consider him a traitor, and wrenching separations from his family.&amp;quot; Today, as the director of the Central Asia Institute, Mortenson has built fifty-five schools serving Pakistan and Afghanistan's poorest communities. And as this real-life Indiana Jones from Montana crisscrosses the Himalaya and the Hindu Kush fighting to keep these schools functioning, he provides not only hope to tens of thousands of children, but living proof that one passionately dedicated person truly can change the world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim G.</member_name><member_id>7110146</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250031995000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244592232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club July Meetup - Three Cups of Tea</name><id>10616729</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247612400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/10616729/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/e/global_9076750.jpeg</photo_url></item>