<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Lexington Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.460152</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish In Concord</name><city>Concord</city><id>1591498</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;David Niose is the president of the American Humanist Association and author of the new book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Nonbeliever-Nation-Rise-Secular-Americans/dp/023033895X/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1337026202&amp;amp;sr=1-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nonbeliever Nation: The Rise of Secular Americans&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Dave will be speaking to us about his new book and how how secularism is gaining momentum in American culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books will be signed and for sale, with help from the Concord Bookshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/1/4/event_154569492.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/8/2/event_154569602.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The Library Journal says of the book" . . .A calm, informative, and positive portrait of the rapidly growing secular segment of the American population."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Dawkins writes: " ...David Niose lays bare the whole dismal history of how the Religious Right hijacked America and betrayed the secular intentions of the Founding Fathers. ...decent Americans are now fighting back, and the book ends on an uplifting &lt;br /&gt;

 note of hope.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From AHA description: “Today, nearly one in five Americans are nonbelievers - a rapidly growing group at a time when traditional Christian churches are dwindling in numbers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Niose concludes his introduction with: “Given the state of affairs after several decades of Religious Right dominance, we should all be hoping that Secular Americans win their place at the table.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;David Niose has been President of AHA since 2009, an organization that promotes Humanism and defends the separation of Church and State for all Americans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has practiced law in Massachusetts since 1990, taught both history and law, and written on a wide array of issues. Upon joining the AHA board in 2005, he initiated and helped develop the AHA's media campaign. He has appeared in national media and spoken to groups around the country, emphasizing importance of utilizing mass media &lt;br /&gt;

 to inject Humanist ideas into the public dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an attorney, Niose is currently involved in implementing a legal strategy to enforce non-believer rights via the avenue of equal protection law. He has worked with the Secular Coalition for America to help advocate for the rights of Secular Americans, and has served &lt;br /&gt;

 on the boards of Greater Worcester Humanists and Greater Boston Humanists. Come and hear him on September 5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more about Dave at his biography page at AmericanHumanists.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting will start at 7:00 with socializing and a few announcements. The program will start at 7:15, after which we will have open discussion with the presenter followed by more socializing. At 9:00 we usually have an open steering committee meeting which anyone is invited to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through the door at the lower level, at the back of the building, on the right side as you're facing the church.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347078401000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346532772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>David Niose talks about "Nonbeliever Nation" with the Concord Area Humanists</name><id>80418352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346886000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/80418352/</event_url></item>