<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Self Sabotage: The Myth of the Victim Mentality&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare Watts&lt;br /&gt;Friday, April 24 • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Within us, there is a great desire to grow in consciousness and progress toward the soul’s goal, which is union with God. The soul is aware of where we are internally not yet aligned with functioning to our fullest potential and does everything it can to reach that potential. When we have the opportunity to commit to something that will change our level of consciousness and our lives, the saboteur arises within us. He wants us to slip into unconsciousness, failing, and proving we are worthless. Unconsciousness may look like sleepiness, procrastination, or fear, to name a few. However, the saboteur can make you stronger, more convicted in your action and more ready and alert to act. It gives you the opportunity to stand for the change you want and make it solid in your whole being. Come and learn from Mother Clare Watts, Christian Master, how to turn around and make your relationship to this force in your life be one of empowerment and strengthening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Donation: $25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the location of this meetup has changed.  It's now in Providence Rhode Island at MOTION CENTER.  Details below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;111 Chestnut Street &lt;br /&gt;Providence, Rhode Island 02903&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or, visit Motion Center's website for directions and parking suggestions:  &lt;a href="http://motioncenter.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://motioncenter.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Through the lobby on the first floor.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240789066000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238522792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar:  Self Sabotage:  The Myth of the Victim Mentality * Providence RI</name><id>10080068</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240615800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/10080068/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/9/global_5804905.jpeg</photo_url></item>