<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be an awesome short hike of low to low-moderate difficulty. Purgatory Chasm on this 900 acre reservation is a deep feature created from a break in an ice dam in the last ice age about 14,000 years ago. There will be cliffs, interesting rockforms, and small caves to see. This is the first of a set of two hiking events located near each other. Optionally, you can join us on the second longer hike at a nearby location or just head out on your own after this hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall, we'll hike no more than 2.25 miles in two loops for this first hike. The first loop (Chasm Loop Trail) will be of about .75 mile with the first .25 mile in the chasm where we will see up to 70 ft. cliffs at close quarters above us, Lover's Leap, the Devil's Pulpit, and the Devil's Coffin. The .5 mile return will take us to features such as the Fat Man's Misery, and the Devil's Corncrib. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second loop of 1.5 miles will use part of Charlie's Loop, Little Purgatory, part of the Forest Road Trail, and part of Old Purgatory Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please meet at 9 AM at the parking lot near the Visitor's Center and bathrooms on Purgatory Rd. in Sutton, MA. There is a playground, picnic areas, and a playing field as part of the Reservation where you can optionally eat and relax after the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should complete hiking by no later than 11:15 AM giving time to look over the sights and natural wonders. We'll take a little time to fuel up, relax, and hit the bathrooms before those that wish to head off to the second hike (leave by 12:30 PM, 2nd hike meetup starts at 1 PM). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; for meetup location via MapQuest (Purgatory Rd., Sutton, MA):   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Purgatory+Chasm&amp;amp;city=Sutton&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.127318&amp;amp;longitude=-71.716179&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=14307366" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;(Lat=42.127318, Long=-71.716179)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail map: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/PurgatoryChasm.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More about Purgatory Chasm: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/purg.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Short Wikipedia article on Purgatory Chasm: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Purgatory_Chasm_State_Reservation" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some photos of the chasm: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gweep.net/~lizzie/purgatory/chasmpics.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gweep.net/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A rough topographical map of the area about Purgatory Chasm: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=190+purgatory+rd.,+sutton,+ma&amp;amp;sll=42.132922,-71.719952&amp;amp;sspn=0.020528,0.028925&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.130376,-71.719308&amp;amp;spn=0.020528,0.028925&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===    &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at event location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246367434000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244522711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Purgatory Chasm State Reservation in Sutton MA</name><id>10610052</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246194000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10610052/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/c/global_9062636.jpeg</photo_url></item>