<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Unfortunately, I won't be able to make it there in time to herd nerds for this Double Feature of Sam Raimi's Evil Dead 2: Dead By Dawn and Army of Darkness at 7:30 pm and 9:45 pm. I will be at &amp;quot;Boston By Foot's Beacon Hill with a Boo&amp;quot; from 5:30 pm to 7:00 pm and couldn't head to the Brattle until after I'm done with the Beacon Hill tour. I wouldn't be able to get to the Brattle Theater until 7:45 pm the earliest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe a few people could volunteer to hold up a red MEETUP sign at, say, 6:45 pm outside the theater lobby to meet-and-greet people, acting as a human landmark? People could then grab seats together as a group at 7:10 pm. I'm thinking people should try to get there at 7:00 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to sign up &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;MAYBE&amp;quot;... red MEETUP signs in Adobe Acrobat format can be printed out on a color printer from &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/661701/Table-top%20Sign%20-%20T.J.%20Maher.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; ... just print it out, fold it in half, and hold it up in front of you when you get to the lobby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets&lt;/b&gt;: $9.78, can be purchased online from the site&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Brattle Website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/101031.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;King of Cult&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;Sam Raimi&lt;br /&gt;Fri 10/29 – Sun 10/31&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Since this is the 10th anniversary of the Brattle Film Foundation, and one of our signature events has been an annual Halloween screening of the cult favorite EVIL DEAD 2, we’ve decided to pay tribute to the man behind the mayhem, Sam Raimi. Undoubtedly, a “king of cult”, Raimi has created a distinctive style over the years – his appreciation for the Three Stooges really sets him apart. Of course there’s also the Raimi-cam – a dizzying dolly-shot – that is as distinctive as a fingerprint. And, just to be sure we’re paying attention, he even directed a serious drama about baseball (no, we’re not showing it)! We are showing his latest, DRAG ME TO HELL and his big-budget successes SPIDER-MAN 1 &amp;amp; 2. Plus two overlooked gems: the weirdo DARKMAN and American spaghetti western THE QUICK &amp;amp; THE DEAD. And, of course, EVIL&amp;#8200;DEAD&amp;#8200;2:&amp;#8200;DEAD&amp;#8200;BY&amp;#8200;DAWN!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Evil Dead 2:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/101031.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Happy Halloween! Come to tonight's 7:30 show in costume and you just might win a prize in this year's costume contest! (1987) dir Sam Raimi w/Bruce Campbell [84 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It just wouldn’t be Halloween without our annual screenings of this perennial favorite. Raimi pits bosom buddy Bruce Campbell against a forest full of demons from hell with typically maniacal results. Strap on your chainsaw, get out your boomstick and say it with us… GROOVY!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Army of Darkness:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/101031.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(1992) dir Sam Raimi w/Bruce Campbell [81 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The finale to the EVIL DEAD trilogy finds our totally unlucky but resourceful hero Ash (Campbell) stuck in medieval Europe. With his trusty chainsaw strapped to his left arm, it isn't long before Ash leads his fellow knights into battle against a band of marauding, undead skeletons. Will Ash defeat the Deadites and find his way back home? You'll have too much fun watching Bruce Campbell chew the scenery and vanquish his enemies to care&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288572342000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288453023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Double Feature: Evil Dead 2: Dead By Dawn and Army of Darkness @ Brattle Theater</name><id>15278970</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288567800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15278970/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>