<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A Henna Art &amp;amp; Design Party is a creative gathering to practice the art of henna or mehndi tattoos. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free and open to all ability levels!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Henna is a shrub that thrives in warmer climates all over the world. The shrub's leaves are harvested, dried, and ground into a fine powder. This powder is used for the ancient eastern art of mehndi. Henna contains a dye that bonds with the collagen in skin cells, leaving behind a red coloring. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mehndi is the Hindi word describing the process of painting patterns on the body with henna paste and the resulting stains left on the skin. Using henna paste, intricate patterns are applied to the skin, traditionally on the hands and feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Henna/Mehndi tattoos are completely temporary and pain free. The henna plant is one of the oldest cosmetics ever used and is extremely safe. Tattoos usually last for about 2-3 weeks before fading.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be hands-on so come prepared to do henna. If you don't feel comfortable working on another person, you can practice with paper and pencil. Also, free mehndi drawing lessons will be given for beginner's basic designs. &lt;b&gt;ANYONE can do it and we really do mean anyone!!! No experience necessary!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a snack or beverage item to share. Before the Henna Party, join us for the Tantric Yoga class at 4:30 pm (cost $5). Or join us after the party for a Meditative Sound Healing Concert at 6:30 pm (cost $20). Green Vibration members can attend all three events for only $20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265754972000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262041220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Henna Art &amp; Design</name><id>12162929</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265581800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12162929/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/0/global_12411152.jpeg</photo_url></item>