<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Hopkinton State Park &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a 2 hour walk and lunch afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Info:&lt;br /&gt;www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/hpsp.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopkinton State Park is located in the towns of Hopkinton and Ashland and includes the picturesque Hopkinton Reservoir.  The park offers a variety of year round recreational activities including 2 life guarded swimming beaches, stocked fishing, 1 reservable group picnic site (see Split Rock below), 12 tree shaded, first come first served, picnic areas (300 picnic tables and 165 charcoal cooking grills), 10 miles of marked trails, open field space and a concrete boat launching ramp for non-motorized watercraft. Outdoor Recreation of Hopkinton Inc. provides seasonal boat rentals (508) 435-3965.  Environmental Educational programming is offered during the summer.  Public restrooms are available during the spring, summer and fall months.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Hopkinton State Park is located in the greater Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rte. I-495 (north or south) to exit 21A, Main Street Hopkinton. Travel on Main Street until the third traffic light located at the heart of downtown Hopkinton. Turn left, traveling North on Route 85. Proceed approximately 2 miles to the Hopkinton State Park entrance on the right (do not enter the Field Office on the left).  To locate Main Entrance by MAPQUEST:  268 Cedar Street, Hopkinton, MA 01748&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch location:&lt;br /&gt;Carbones Restaurant - 280 Cedar St, Hopkinton, MA - (508) 435-3465&amp;#8206;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy M</member_name><member_id>3233594</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213034369000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211244268000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hopkinton State Park</name><id>7971502</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212847200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7971502/</event_url></item>