<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In 1986 Byron Katie, a 43 year old wife and mother living in California, checked herself into a halfway house to address her addictions and a debilitating suicidal depression.  One morning two weeks later she awoke in a mystical state of complete joy that has never left her.  In recognizing it was her thoughts that caused her suffering, she developed a simple inquiry process for questioning stressful thoughts which has helped many thousands of people over the past two decades to question and let go of their suffering.  In Integral Spirituality, Ken Wilber says that Byron Katie's book Loving What Is offers &amp;quot;...a wonderful new set of techniques for spiritual intelligence and glimpsing causal emptiness...&amp;quot;  In this presentation, Ben Cohen will provide participants with a brief introduction and experience of Byron Katie's Inquiry process.  He'll then show how the method can be understood more fully, and it's strengths and weaknesses seen more clearly, by examining it using the elements of the Integral model -- quadrants, levels, lines, states and types.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ben Cohen&lt;/b&gt; became a certified Kripalu yoga teacher in 1992, and has been teaching Kripalu yoga in the Boston area since that time.  He was introduced to the Work of Byron Katie about a decade ago, and for the past year has shared her Inquiry process with groups and individuals on a volunteer basis.  A student of Ken Wilber's Integral Theory for the past five years, Ben recently attended the &amp;quot;Integral Incubator&amp;quot; in Boulder, Colorado to explore Byron Katie's process through the lens of Integral.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284117024000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281547683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Work of Byron Katie: An Integral Perspective</name><id>14391507</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284074100000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/14391507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>