<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry I have been out of touch, but I’ve been occupied with food poisoning, the Holidays, &amp;amp; traveling.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A somewhat separate musical opportunity from the meetup, are two performances at the Hynes on Fisrt Nite -&lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Dec. 31st (New Years EVE day&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;/i&gt; of our band Brock &amp;amp; Roll Earth Revival, at 1PM (1/2 hr) and 4:30PM. (up to 1 hr).  This is kind of a follow on from playing environmental songs at the Boston Greenfest at City Hall Plaza last year.  If you go to First Nite Boston site, then Fedex Family Festival, you can see us on the schedule.  The site is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.firstnight.org/FirstNight2010/Events/Family.aspx&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you scroll down past the Bombay Cinema section, you will see us (Brock &amp;amp; Roll Earth Revival).  This is a good example of how you can put together a band for a gig in a very short time (two weeks) that sounds good (hopefully).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon in January we will be having meetups, breaking down into subgroups to arrange our songs, record them, play out, put on performances and hopefully create our own (monthly?) open mike type show, where we can feature everyone's talents.  I will try to set up the group website so we can input the type of music we are interested in, and the songs we like, so as to facilitate &amp;quot;sub group&amp;quot; formation for song arrangment based on common interests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a 7 piecs band and bunch of fun songs for Fisrt Nite.  Here is the probable song list for First Nite.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 Jeremiah was a bullfrog extra environmental verse&lt;br /&gt;2 IN The Jungle the Mighty Jungle extra environmental verse&lt;br /&gt;3 birthday - regular or beatles kids  +/- 1 week also world's birthday&lt;br /&gt;4 Over the Rainbow &lt;br /&gt;5 Future Flood environmental  - original fm Greenfest&lt;br /&gt;6 yellow submarine &lt;br /&gt;7 let it be &lt;br /&gt;8 &amp;quot;Earth Blues&amp;quot; Blues jam with environmental words&lt;br /&gt;8 Just my imagination &lt;br /&gt;9 Beatles songs  &lt;br /&gt;9 puff the magic dragon in  G - Bm - C G - Em - A7 - D7&lt;br /&gt;10 aug lang zine at end&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Holidays    - Bill&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262455764000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262159083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Nite Performance</name><id>12174628</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262282400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/12174628/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>