<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Seven Sisters is a really popular collection of peaks in and around the Hadley, MA area. The name comes from a string of peaks that stretch from Joseph Allen Skinner State Park to Mt. Holyoke Range State Park. Together the parks offer over 3000 acres with about 40 miles of trails. The summits range between 800 and 1100 feet above sea level, which doesn't sound like much but the total elevation gain will add up as we wind our way from peak to peak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm proposing to start hiking on the Two Forest Trail from the parking lot off of route 47 in Skinner State Park (map below.) An historic hotel and restaurant (1851) can be found at the summit of our first peak, Mt. Holyoke. We'll continue on the Metacomet-Monadnock Trail (MM: White blazes) to Bare Mountain. Looks like about 3 miles one way. If our minds, bodies and wills allow we could stop down to the visitors center on route 116 or shoot for the next peak, Mt. Norwottuck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm including notes here that I emailed to hikers confirmed for the Seven Sisters Hike. The Plan is to hike from the west end of Skinner State Park to the Visitors Center on route 116. If we have enough cars we'll spot cars at the Visitors Center to shuttle hikers back to the start point. If not we'll do an out and back hike and judge the distance based on the clock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WEATHER: As of Tuesday, January 3 the Weather Channel forecasts a high of 47 degrees and a low of 31 degrees with 10% chance of rain. Go to www.weather.com and enter zip code 01035 for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joseph Allen Skinner State Park Tail Map&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/skinner.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/skinner.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Route 47, Hadley, MA 01035 413- 586-0350 (They don&amp;rsquo;t answer the phone much)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt. Holyoke Range State Park Trail Map &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/holyoke.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/holyoke.pdf&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EQUIPMENT CHECKLIST Cold Weather/Fall Essentials (required): &amp;bull; Synthetic Quick-drying Pants &amp;bull; Synthetic Quick-drying L/S Shirt &amp;bull; Sturdy Hiking Boots/shoes (preferably waterproof) &amp;bull; Synthetic/Wool Socks &amp;bull; Insulated/Fleece Jacket &amp;bull; Light/Mid-weight Insulating Layers (undershirt/underpants) &amp;bull; Extra pair of Socks &amp;bull; Hat/Gloves &amp;bull; Rain/Soft Shell Jacket/Pants &amp;bull; Water (2-3L insulated containers for sub freezing conditions (no camel backs) &amp;bull; Headlamp/Flashlight &amp;bull; Map/Compass/Whistle &amp;bull; Lunch &amp;bull; Snack/Energy Food (extra food) &amp;bull; MICROspikes, STABLicers, ect... (a must when there's snow or ice on the trail) the&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remaining Essentials: &amp;bull; Medications/First Aid Supplies &amp;bull; Emergency Blanket (so small &amp;amp; light, there's hardly a reason not to have one in your pack) &amp;bull; Fire (waterproof matches, lighter, starter) &amp;bull; Repair Kit/Knife Optional: &amp;bull; Sunscreen/Sunglasses &amp;bull; Light-weight Wind Jacket (if your insulated or rain jacket isn&amp;rsquo;t windproof) &amp;bull; Hand Warmers &amp;bull; Trekking Poles &amp;bull; Gaiters &amp;bull; Light-weight Emergency Shelter &amp;bull; Camera/Binoculars&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important: NO JEANS, NO SNEAKERS, NO COTTON CLOTHING (They get wet, They stay wet &amp;amp; They won&amp;rsquo;t keep you warm). ALSO, LET'S NOT UNDERESTIMATE ANYTHING, so come prepared for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LIABILITY WAIVER: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru sedan w/RI Lic 6730</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis </member_name><member_id>8755592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326054830000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325651277000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seven Sisters</name><id>46567262</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325944800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/46567262/</event_url></item>