<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Winter from MDog has invited our members to attend this event along with them.  We will be having the hike in Groton for  the members in that area and for people in the area of this event they can attend with MDog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is the write up she sent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mdoghikes/calendar/13165484/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a 45 minute hike through the Nathan Hale State Forest and stay for the Coventry Regional Farmers' Market's Dog Days event, if you'd like!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike will begin and end at the Nathan Hale Homestead. The trail will follow old logging roads and bridle paths, with an easy grade. There is a small woodland pond for dogs to explore. Dress for deep woods and possibly muddy paths.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Coventry Regional Farmers' Market fifth annual Dog Days event runs at the Hale Homestead from 11-2, and includes a full farmers' market plus dog service groups, a dog cookie give away, toy swap, K-9 Good Citizen test, demos including freestyle dance, agility, RALLY, blessing of the animals, and much more...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every year, the Dog Day event is among their most popular days, drawing dog-aficionados from around New England! You may want to return, as the market welcomes leashed, friendly dogs every Sunday, June through October, 11-2.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Winter will be hosting this hike</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Winter (Annie &amp; Sage)</member_name><member_id>11830736</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280745800000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dogs and their People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hikingwithdogs</urlname><id>496525</id><group_lat>41.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.2300033569</group_lon><name>Hiking with Dogs</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280407408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cross Posting an MDOG Hikes! meetup I am leading on Aug 1:</name><id>14250940</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280671200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hikingwithdogs/events/14250940/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/3/global_13566835.jpeg</photo_url></item>