<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your Home</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.373188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Your Home</name><city>Boston</city><id>1000833</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120766</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/male-mystique-teleclass/dietcoke-2/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/dietcoke1-300x199.jpg" width="243" height="161" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 27 &amp;ndash; Teleclass 6:00 pm Eastern  Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$20 REGISTER HERE &lt;a href="http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/male-mystique-teleclass/"&gt;http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/male-mystique-teleclass/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Believe it or not, men are pretty simple to figure out. Sounds    crazy, but it`s true. So why do so many of us find ourselves spending    hours, days or even weeks trying to decipher their behavior? &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Here are some short cuts that we`ll discuss and myths we`ll dispel in this teleclass: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Men rarely believe us when we can say we can handle the truth &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Men heavily rely on common sense, not manipulation &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Men aren`t being lazy or cowardly by relying on text messaging &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Men usually don`t go on a date looking for a relationship.  &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Men love a woman who can express her opinions and concerns and are not threatened by a strong woman &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * What men value or are impressed by in a partner is not what we value/are impressed by&amp;nbsp; in a partner&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; We`ll also discuss some common types of men we`ve all, at one time or another, fallen far like: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The Crash &amp;amp; Burner? &lt;/strong&gt;You   know, the guy who pours it on thick on  the first couple dates, starts   talking in "we" over cocktails on your  first date, that emails you   hello and goodnight every day and  then...disappears?&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The Emotional Vampire? &lt;/strong&gt;He`s   the guy that breaks things off with you,  but checks back in regularly   inquiring if you`re still seeing someone?  He tells you how much he   cares for you, wishes he could be the person  you want him to be..but   yet never actually tries to do so? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The Chimpanzee? &lt;/strong&gt;This   man is taken, but flirts endlessly, usually via  text or email, but   never makes a move. Only after you`re attached doe  she reveal he   "kinda" has a girlfriend "but things aren`t going so  well." He`s trying   to set up his next relationship before he even ends  his current one.   He won`t let go of one branch till he has a firm hold  on another.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The Svenagli? &lt;/strong&gt;His   words and his actions don`t match up. You believe  everything he says,   even though your gut and your girlfriends tell you  he`s full of it.   This guy brings out your worst side - the needy, over  analyzing,   insecure side. You do things that normally you wouldn`t. It`s  almost   like he has you hypnotized. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; These are the men we`ll be   discussing tonight, along with how to spot  them, how to avoid them and   how to find someone healthy, loving and  available. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; OTHER TOPICS DISCUSSED &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;*Common myths women tell themselves and each other to explain why relationships fail &lt;br /&gt; *What red flags men look for when dating someone new &lt;br /&gt; *How to know if a man is available or looking for a relationship &lt;br /&gt; *Decoding common male behavior &lt;br /&gt; *How to have important conversations with men&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; REVIEWS FROM PREVIOUS WORKSHOPS: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; "Not sure you get to read these. Well, if you do, Thanks for giving me    the confidence to get back out there. After being married for many    years, it was strange to get out and attempt to meet someone. I attended    your dating group Q&amp;amp;A about reading signs etc and right after the    meeting had dinner with someone from the group. After that I had the    confidence to follow through with some other women. It has resulted in    being with my girlfriend for over 3 years now. We have a great    relationship. Thanks for helping me bring out the best in me. - C from    NY" &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Mariann &lt;br /&gt; &amp;ldquo; i really enjoyed this workshop as it was   definitely insightful. i was  ready for the constructive criticism to   get my dating profile up to par.  chris had great advice and a gave us   all a handbook on how to perfect  our profile. looking forward to   improving mine and getting more hits  from quality men! &amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &amp;ldquo;   This was a very worthwhile event, it was very interactive, everyone    felt at ease and the discussion was very animated.Well done! &amp;rdquo; - Jyothi &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; "Hey Chris-Just wanted to let you know that maybe it`s a coincidence but &lt;br /&gt; I feel like I`m already getting more responses to my profile since I    changed some things you told me to change :) Thanks for all your advice!    - DeDe"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301267420000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialnetworking</urlname><id>251346</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300646124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Male Mystique - Understanding &amp; Attracting Men Teleclass</name><id>16987900</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301263200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialnetworking/events/16987900/</event_url></item>