<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Get ready to dance up a storm! Showtime's performing!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a multigroup meetup.  There are at least 2 other groups that I know of that are scheduled to be there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a new place for us and a new band.  It looks like a really fun place.  So lets check it out!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People from all over Fairfield and Westchester Counties are making Route 22 Stamford a one of a kind destination for a fun night out! Take a healthy helping of American comfort cuisine at great prices, toss in excellent service, an arcade for the kids, a dash of nostalgia and you have the perfect recipe for Route 22 American restaurant and bar! They have quite a few pub tables and you can order some of their very tasty appetizers to go along with your drinks, if you so choose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard LaPerchia is the founder and leader of the Showtime Dance Band. Richard had a vision of starting a band which would perform inspirational music that combines the sound of Motown, Soul, R&amp;amp;B, Funk, Old School Disco, Dance Rock, and Jazz with the priority that IT MADE THE CROWD MOVE!! Showtime Dance Band has been performing at the Holiday Inn Hotel (MT Kisco), Empire City Yonkers Raceway, New York Life, Chat 19 Restaurant and Lounge, Route 22 Restaurant &amp;amp; Bar, (CT), La Lanterna Restaurant, 12 Grapes Restaurant &amp;amp; Grill, The Arthur Ave Feast and many other premier venues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.showtimedanceband.com/menuindex.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.showtimeda...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be in the bar area!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247882680000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246047040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's Showtime @ Route 22 in Stamford</name><id>10742949</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247358600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/10742949/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/0/global_8204688.jpeg</photo_url></item>