<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 College Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396847</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Davis Square-right in front of JP Licks</name><city>Somerville</city><id>2465461</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122116</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Most of our rides start pretty far outside of Boston/Cambridge, so let's start this one in Davis Sq. From Davis Sq. we'll follow the minuteman trail out to Bedford then onto Concord. In Concord we can get a snack and then head back. Back in Davis square, let's hit Sacco's Bowl Haven for Pizza, Wine, Beer etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We'll meet at Davis Square proper, in from of JP Licks, at the corner of Elm and College, across from the T station.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The total distance of this ride is about 32 miles. We'll be traveling at 10-15 miles per hour on average. We'll stop at major turns and intersections to let everyone catch up. If we get a big turn out perhaps someone will volunteer to help me split the group up and lead half. I anticipate this ride taking 4 hours give or take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyndi will co-lead a shorter ~20 mile ride within this ride, turning around in Bedford, MA.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Helmets are required!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Road bikes are recommended. &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring also layers of bike clothing, those funny looking bike shorts, sun glasses, sun screen, water, energy food, water, drink, bike repair kit, spare bike tube, etc. etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy and looking forward to meeting you out there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the corner of Elm and College, across from the T station on the square in front of JP Licks.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Douglas M.</member_name><member_id>9031252</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335027920000</updated><rating><average>4.23000001907</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333239664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>City to Country ride (Davis SQ. to Concord, MA)</name><id>58707172</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333818000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/58707172/</event_url></item>