<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>166 Broadway </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821278</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Grange </name><city>Providence</city><id>12368002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422539</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and event scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: The GRANGE!!! on Broadway over on the West Side&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, so The Grange is the NEWEST place to hit the Broadway strip! It's very exciting, not only because we've been watching it for the last 9 months and anxiously awaiting its opening, BUT its also the third new restaurant by the owners of the Garden Grille Cafe! Yes, its vegetarian, but believe me, regardless of your propensity for either side, and if the Garden Grille, and Wildflour Bakery is any indication, I am confident this is going to quickly become a favorite spot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Grange can be described as boho meets county-chic (which is probably the same thing). The bar is a nice size and with a large, long table behind it for additional mingling. Perfect for us! So, come on over to the West Side and check out the latest addition to the restaurant scene at the corner of Dean St and Broadway. Look for the place on the corner with the clock at the top! You can't miss it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy and NYE 2012!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're hard to miss!!! Just in case, I'll be wearing the brown and pink scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367167325000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366246493000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - The Grange!!!</name><id>114895002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366668000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/114895002/</event_url></item>