<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>-</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>43.979238</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>-</name><city>North Conway</city><id>1288405</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120348</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>150.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like last year and earlier this summer, we will be making a trip up to the White Mountains in New Hampshire to enjoy a few days away from the city. If any of our Japanese members or local Bostonians have not yet seen the beauty of New Hampshire and the White Mountains, now would be a great time to join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be staying in a large condo (condominium) in North Conway, and will have plenty of opportunities to relax and explore. Last year we went hiking and swimming in the White Mountains, and this year we will be able to do the same.  White-water rafting is one possible activity.  Another attraction will be the peak of Perseid Meteor Shower on the night of August 12 (there will still be meteors on Friday night for those of you who cannot make it up on Thursday).  The moon will be a waxing crescent (just 2 days after the new moon) on August 12, making it perfect stargazing time.  The Perseid meteor shower has been observed for about 2000 years and has a higher rate of meteors per hour than many of the other meteor showers visible here during the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few more details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip Length:&lt;br /&gt;We will all meet up at our condo on Thursday night, August 12th OR Friday night, August 13th, and will return to the Boston area by 9 pm on Sunday night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transportation:&lt;br /&gt;We will need other drivers to volunteer to help transport members to and from the White Mountains. The drive to our condo will be about 3-4 hours from Boston, depending on traffic. Drivers will be fully compensated for gas (please keep your receipts). We would ask that all drivers be cautious when they drive in New Hampshire - there's many deer and moose that will occasionally cross the highway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Passengers will need to do their best to meet at a location convenient for the driver, and this may require passengers to take public transportation to a destination close to the driver. Passengers should also be on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food:&lt;br /&gt;Rob will be buying a bunch of groceries before all of you arrive at the condo. Last year, we had more than enough food to keep everyone full during the trip. The cost of any food bought for the condo is already included in your trip payment. If you have any dietary needs (vegan/vegetarian, allergies, etc.), please let Rob know so that we can make sure you are also well-fed on the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sleeping Arrangements:&lt;br /&gt;Rob is currently working to secure a condo with a large number of beds, and will of course do his very best to make sure everyone has satisfactory sleeping arrangements. However, please feel free to bring a sleeping bag as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests:&lt;br /&gt;Because of the limited number of spots available, please e-mail Rob if you would like to bring a guest. For anyone that wants to bring a guest not affiliated with our group, please remember that you are responsible for your guest's behavior.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone:&lt;br /&gt;- At least two days of clothes (please)&lt;br /&gt;- A warm fleece (it can occasionally get cold at night or when hiking in the White Mountains)&lt;br /&gt;- Rain gear&lt;br /&gt;- A sleeping bag, if you have one&lt;br /&gt;- A flashlight&lt;br /&gt;- Anything you will need for the bathroom and shower.&lt;br /&gt;- A bathing suit&lt;br /&gt;- Sunblock&lt;br /&gt;- A towel&lt;br /&gt;- A camera&lt;br /&gt;- A good water bottle (1 liter)&lt;br /&gt;- bug spray (optional)&lt;br /&gt;- Any food or drinks you would like to share with the group (but remember that we will have plenty of food!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hikers, please bring everything above plus:&lt;br /&gt;- Hiking boots&lt;br /&gt;- Wool socks (very important for hiking!)&lt;br /&gt;- A hat for the sun&lt;br /&gt;- An extra 1 liter water bottle (two total)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Required Information:&lt;br /&gt;Hua will be e-mailing a questionnaire to all of our attendees asking for their contact information, as well as the contact information of someone I can contact in case of an emergency. Also, if you have any special medical needs that I should be aware of in case of an emergency (for example, drug allergies, heart condition, etc.), please let me know. This information will be kept private, and all references to medical information will be destroyed after the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost:&lt;br /&gt;The cost of the entire trip will be roughly $150 (&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;white water rafting will be an additional fee&lt;/span&gt;). This covers cost of food, our condo, travel expenses for our drivers, and admission to some state parks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For now, the trip is open to 12 people, but we will do our best to open it up to more people if there's interest.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282329219000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275528981000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Weekend Trip to White Mountain Trip</name><id>13679270</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281744000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/13679270/</event_url></item>