<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Jfk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.491.9851</phone><name>Redline</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692091</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; The RSVP list got too big for me to reasonably handle at the restaurant tonight, so I closed this to new RSVPs.  But now that you know that we play Trivia every Monday at Redline, come sign up over at Social Fun in the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There was some call for attending a trivia night at a local bar in the &amp;quot;meetup ideas&amp;quot; section.  Well, it's a known fact among some of the Nerds that there is a popular, nerd-friendly, weekly trivia Meetup event in Harvard Square on Monday nights.  But to call it to your attention more distinctly, Heather has permitted me to cross-post it here.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you attend other Nerd Fun events regularly, you'll probably see lots of familiar faces at Trivia.  We've been regulars at Redline on Monday nights since early last summer.  While the size of our crowd varies from week to week, it's a rare week that one of our teams doesn't take one of the top two prizes.  And we've only earned the booby prize once.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you've got a hankering to answer questions and psych yourself out about whether you actually know the right answer, come on down.  There's a good dinner menu and we have a blast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special Note:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's edition of Trivia is being cross-posted to both Social Fun and Nerd Fun for those Nerds who haven't found us at Redline yet.  The cross-post won't be a regular thing, just an FYI kind of posting.  Please only RSVP to one of the two so I can maintain an accurate head count for the reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The fine print:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trivia starts at 8:00pm and I will be making a reservation for 7:00pm for dinner under my name, Amy Hughes. Show up earlier to be guaranteed a seat with our group and a place on a team.  We are usually seated at the tables along the wall opposite the bar - to the right past the hostess stand.  We can have teams of up to 6 people. Trivia ends around 10:00pm.  Just ask for us, everyone at Redline knows who we are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP if you think you will be coming - showing up unannounced makes it difficult for me to make a decent reservation with the restaurant.&lt;/b&gt; Please indicate in your RSVP when you think you'll show up. Also, please bring cash with you to facilitate paying the group bill. Making change is never a problem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Redline is located in Harvard Square on JFK Street underneath the Staples. Parking can be tricky in Harvard Square so come early to find a space or take the T (Harvard Square Station). Redline currently validates parking on weeknights, in the lot directly above the restaurant, access on Eliot St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be seated along the wall to the right, ask for Amy Hughes or Meetup.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267661341000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266352696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and Trivia at Redline in Harvard Square </name><id>12620818</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267488000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12620818/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/f/global_13154015.jpeg</photo_url></item>