<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>645 Boylston St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350106</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-536-1970</phone><name>Old South Church</name><city>Boston</city><id>855376</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.078323</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a People's Celebration of the Life and Work of Howard Zinn&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, 15 May, 2-4 pm&lt;br /&gt;The Old South Church&lt;br /&gt;Corner of Dartmouth and Boylston Streets, Copley Square&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world.&amp;quot; --Howard Zinn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring letters, songs, short videos, poems, speeches, and manifestos of rebels, dissenters, and visionaries from our past and present.  Presentations by anti-war veterans, labor and union workers, civil rights and political activists and many others.  These moments from our history are brought to life by remarkable everyday artists, musicians and young people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The People's Celebration will feature the extraordinary possibilities for creating social change that ordinary people have realized throughout the course of our long, but often ignored, history of dissent and protest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What most of us must be involved in -- whether we teach or write, make films, write films, direct films, play music, act, whatever we do -- has to not only make people feel good and inspired and at one with other people around them, but also has to educate a new generation to do this very modest thing: change the world.&amp;quot;  --Howard Zinn&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273951268000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272034955000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>People's Celebration of Howard Zinn</name><id>13268726</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273946400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/13268726/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/7/global_13014871.jpeg</photo_url></item>