<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 State St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076996</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-9715</phone><name>The Rosa Restaurant</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>260717</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.754150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our May pick is &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Book of Vice: Very Naughty Things (and How to Do Them) &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; by Peter Sagal - the host of &amp;quot;Wait, Wait...Don't Tell Me!&amp;quot; on NPR. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a brief synopsis from Barnes and Noble of &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Book of Vice: Very Naughty Things (and How to Do Them) &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Somewhere, somebody is having more fun than you are. Or so everyone believes. Peter Sagal, a mild-mannered, Harvard-educated NPR host—the man who put the second &amp;quot;L&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;vanilla&amp;quot;—decided to find out if it's true.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;From strip clubs to gambling halls to swingers clubs to porn sets—and then back to the strip clubs, but only because he left his glasses there—Sagal explores exactly what the sinful folk do, how much they pay for the privilege, and exactly how they got those funny red marks. He hosts a dinner for three of the smartest porn stars in the world, asks the floor manager at the oldest casino in Vegas how to beat the house, and indulges in molecular cuisine at the finest restaurant in the country. Meet liars and rich people who don't think consumption is a disease, encounter the most spectacular view ever seen from a urinal, and say hello to Nina Hartley, the only porn star who can discuss Nietzsche while strangers smack her butt. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a sharp wit, a remarkable eye for detail, and the carefree insouciance that can only come from not having any idea what he's getting into, Sagal proves to be the perfect guide to sinful behavior. What happens in Vegas—and in less glamorous places—is all laid out in these pages, a modern version of Dante's Inferno, except with more jokes.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273678066000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271211996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup May Meetup - The Book of Vice</name><id>ckldnynhbpb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273618800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/13176824/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/6/global_14366470.jpeg</photo_url></item>