<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Weybosset Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.823981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>331-9217</phone><name>DownCity</name><city>Providence</city><id>861774</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409440</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Happy Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: DownCity on Weybosset Street in Providence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DownCity has been a Providence culinary institution for a long time and changed a lot over the years. Most recently, (they were ASKED t o participate, I might add) it has been featured in the Food Network's Kitchen Nightmares. The Collective has been to DownCity several times and honestly, in my humble opinion, I always liked and enjoyed the food as it was. And yes, I LIKED the meatloaf......Truthfully, and again in my humble opinion of course, I'm not sure that Gordan's adjustments to the menu have been so wonderful. BUT - you be the judge! Let's check out the changes and one thing I'm sure hasn't changed is that the drinks are still great! DownCity has a trendy and hip decor with a tasty and diverse menu (prior to Chef Ramsey), but while we're there make the comparison for yourself if you've been before...... DownCity is a favorite of many Collective members and its been over a year since we've been, so let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.   &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf, but we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301367619000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Its fun!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301095687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup  - DownCity</name><id>17058773</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301349600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/17058773/</event_url></item>