<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;Closing to New RSVPs 7/2/11&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==============================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you trying to peakbag your NH or NE 4000 footers? Have you been putting off those last, long, pesky&amp;nbsp;hikes&amp;nbsp;until the end? Come join us in peakbagging one of the more remote of them all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Owl&amp;rsquo;s Head Mountain (4,025 feet), occupies a narrow valley created by Pemigewasset Range to the east and the Franconia Range to the west. More than ten 4,000s surround Owl&amp;rsquo;s Head. Needless to say, it is one of the more remote major summits in the White Mountains. We will be starting at the Lincoln Woods Trailhead. The round trip mileage is 18 miles. The trail route is about 9 miles each way, and begins with an easy walk up the old railroad grade on the 
&lt;a href="http://hikenh.netfirms.com/TDLincWd.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Lincoln Woods Trail/Wilderness Trail&lt;/a&gt; to just beyond a bridge crossing Franconia Brook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Lincoln Woods Trailhead and continue for 2.9 miles on that trail to Franconia Brook Trail. We will continue for 3.4 miles to the junction of Owls Head path and climb to the summit. Round trip total mileage is 19 miles with approximately 3300 feet in elevation gain. The book time for this trip is aproxiamtely 12 hours.&amp;nbsp;I expect that we will meet or beat book time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although&amp;nbsp;I have hiked to Owls Head several times, my research has been done online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We expect all participants to bring a map &amp;amp; compass, and be familiar with the planned route. You are responsible for your own safety!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group.&amp;nbsp;Please know you ability&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;To sign up for this hike, you should be an intermediate/moderate hiker who has recently completed trips of at least&amp;nbsp;10-14 miles and 3,000 feet of elevation gain - at book time/average pace or faster. Please answer all RSVP questions.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;================================&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions (steady rain and/or thunderstorms) will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Footwear: Sturdy hiking boots/trail runners. (Be prepared for water crossings with waterproof boots, or water shoes, or change of socks. Poles are also helpful.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip (2-3 Liters recommended).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Bug Spray. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;======================================&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>White or Green Toyota Highlander with MA plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1310587963000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309204562000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Owls Head (Intermediate/Advanced)</name><id>23710311</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310297400000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/23710311/</event_url></item>