<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>366 Gulf Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06071</zip><lat>41.961651</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Soapstone Mountain - Somers</name><city>Somers</city><id>923728</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.408183</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a nice mild hike at Soapstone Mountain in Sommers CT. We can meet in the main parking lot. After words perhaps we can do for ice-cream or a lite lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Soapstone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soapstone Mountain will take your breath away and is definitely  worth a visit. It's an easy walk up or a great bike ride on the paved road  to the top. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So don't let your mind wonder any longer as to where you want to unwind this weekend; just come here and leave your worries behind. Enjoy the fresh, clean noise pollution free air. Spring has arrived and it will slowly change the landscape, and this is certainly the place to see it happen. With great vistas, and &amp;quot;Fifty Mile&amp;quot; views, some days when it really clear you can see a mountain top far north in the state of New Hampshire. The open well marked trails here are easy to get to.  The trails and the road from the lower parking lot are a good start for hardy hikers and walkers, as they climb the mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's an easy walk to the tower from the upper parking area as well, straight up to the left of the telephone tower and also to the right  are clearly marked trail's.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274026899000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273014695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social: Hike Soapstone Mountain Somers</name><id>13386588</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273932000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/13386588/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/9/e/global_15021998.jpeg</photo_url></item>