<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Alright bitches, it's finally happening. I know that it's short notice and I'm sorry about that but my house just became available. This is what needs to happen: Everyone should bring an iPod, laptop, music listening device, singing voice/growl/scream (I'm talking to YOU, Casey) and we are going to have a crazy metal listening party. I have an iPod stuffed with music and a laptop with speakers to play it on. I only have one other set of speakers that you can plug an iPod right into but it would be best if you brought a laptop or speakers so you can play what you want, when you want. I want at least 4 different types of metal to be playing in different rooms. Even the bathroom dammit. Bring your favorite beer, alcohol, blood of a virgin, whatever. If there is food, it will be very little so make sure that you come with a full belly. We'll be partying from 7pm into the wee hours of the morning so don't worry about coming late. Anytime is fine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I live in Waltham right off of 95. If you can't find a ride you can always take the red line to Harvard and then the 73 bus to the very end. Call me and I'll come grab you from the bus stop. If you are driving, please note that I live across the street from a business park and that Party Needs is DIRECTLY across from my house. It's a big grey and white place with a large gravel driveway. Park anywhere in the driveway, no one will be coming/going all night, besides us. I will start a message board thread so that people can start a discussion about carpooling, etc. Also, if you need to crash, that's totally cool. I have plenty of floor space and 2 air mattresses. One is a queen and one is a twin. Be sure to bring a sleeping bag and pillow if you are going to stay. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can't think of any other details, I hope this is everything. If you have any questions, please call me on my cell phone (below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;METAL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Erin&lt;br /&gt;(339) 206-6700&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call my cell if you have any trouble getting here!!! (339) 206-6700</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erin Gallagher</member_name><member_id>2907555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267488202000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Metalheads</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonmetal</urlname><id>235213</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>The Boston Metal Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267124445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>METAL HOUSE PARTY</name><id>12707363</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267315200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonmetal/events/12707363/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/a/global_8268666.jpeg</photo_url></item>