<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard University</address_2><address_1>45 Quincy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sanders Theatre at Memorial Hall</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1021665</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114285</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update: 8/26/2009:&lt;/b&gt; It appears this event is sold out! Sorry about that. And Carol mentioned that the line to get in will probably be wrapping around the street with this speaker so sit where you can. We can meet up -after- the event, on the sidewalk in front of the auditorium. I'll hold up an 11 x 14 inch red MEETUP sign, and we can figure out where we want to go for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;quot;Reservations are required from the Harvard Museum of Natural History. Tickets will be available beginning on &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 28&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt; through the Harvard Box Office in Holyoke Center (Harvard Square) or by calling 617.496.2222&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Harvard Museum of Natural History Presents:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Looking Back, Looking Forward: A Conversation with James D. Watson and Edward O. Wilson&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/press-room/looking-back-looking-forward.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(Cambridge, MA) Harvard Museum of Natural History will present  &lt;i&gt;Looking Back, Looking Forward: A Conversation with James  D. Watson and Edward O. Wilson&lt;/i&gt; on Wednesday September 9, 2009 at 5:30 pm. The event will be held in Sanders Theatre at Memorial Hall, Harvard University, 45 Quincy Street, Cambridge, Massachusetts.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;James D. Watson, a Nobel Prize winner for his role in the discovery of the of the structure of DNA, and Edward O. Wilson, a pioneer in the study of biodiversity and two-time Pulitzer Prize winner, will reflect on their storied careers, including their time together at Harvard, and look ahead to the key challenges for biological sciences in the 21st century. Moderated by Robert Krulwich, award-winning journalist and correspondent for National Public Radio.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Advance tickets are required. Admission is $10 for the public, $8 for Harvard Museum of Natural History members and current Harvard University ID holders; and $2 for Harvard University students. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Watson-Wilson conversation is included as part of Harvard Museum of Natural History’s longstanding and successful public lecture series. These lectures, on a range of topics, including climate change, conservation, evolution, and the origin of life on earth, are attended by over 3,000 annually. The museum’s fall 2009 lecture series will commemorate the 150th anniversary of the founding of the Museum of Comparative Zoology at Harvard. A later series will explore the natural history of food. Upcoming speakers include primatologist Sarah Blaffer Hrdy, paleontologist Michael Novacek, and Cristián Samper, Director of the National Museum of Natural History, as well as numerous members of the Harvard faculty&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like I will have to get out of work early for this one! I was going to try to be there at 5:00 pm to wait for people, but this sounds like it is going to be impossible. It's going to be packed. Let's meet up -after- the event. Just get there where you can and sit where you can. After, let's exit the place and meet up on the nearest sidewalk outside. I'll be holding up an 11 x 14 inch red MEETUP sign. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About James D. Watson (Wikipedia):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_D._Watson" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;James Dewey Watson (born April 6, 1928) [81 yrs old] is an American molecular biologist, best known as one of the co-discoverers of the structure of DNA. Watson, Francis Crick, and Maurice Wilkins were awarded the 1962 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine &amp;quot;for their discoveries concerning the molecular structure of nucleic acids and its significance for information transfer in living material&amp;quot;.[3] He studied at the University of Chicago and Indiana University and subsequently worked at the University of Cambridge's Cavendish Laboratory in England where he first met his future collaborator and personal friend Francis Crick.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In 1956 he became a junior member of Harvard University's Biological Laboratories until 1976, but in 1968 served as Director of Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory on Long Island, New York and shifted its research emphasis to the study of cancer. In 1994 he became its President for ten years, and then subsequently served as its Chancellor until 2007, when he was forced into retirement by controversy over several comments about race and intelligence. Between 1988 and 1992 he was associated with the National Institutes of Health, helping to establish the Human Genome Project. He has written many science books, including the seminal textbook The Molecular Biology of the Gene (1965) and his bestselling book The Double Helix (1968) about the DNA Structure discovery&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;E. O. Wilson bio, from his Biodiversity Foundation:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eowilson.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=43&amp;amp;Itemid=69" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eowilson.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Early in his career, Wilson conducted work on the classification and ecology of ants in New Guinea and other Pacific islands, and in the American tropics. In 1963 his work and his conception of species equilibrium led him to the theory of island biogeography, which he developed with the late Robert H. MacArthur of Princeton University. In their theory, immigration and extinction, the determinants of biodiversity at the species level, were tied to area (distance of islands from source regions) and the basic properties of ecology and demography. The work culminated in their 1967 book The Theory of Island Biogeography, which has been a standard reference work ever since. The theory greatly influenced the discipline of ecology and became a cornerstone of conservation biology. Applied to “habitat islands,” such as forests in a sea of agricultural land, it has influenced the planning and assessment of parks and reserves around the world. In the late 1960s Wilson, with Daniel Simberloff, conducted experiments in the Florida Keys that documented the basic principles of island biogeographic theory. [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;While continuing his research on the systematics and biogeography of ants, Wilson has become increasingly involved in the global conservation movement. In addition to authoring other books and articles on the subject, and lecturing in many countries, he has served on the boards of directors of the American Museum of Natural History, Conservation International, The Nature Conservancy, and World Wildlife Fund, and has been a key consultant of the New York Botanical Garden, Columbia University’s Earth Institute, and many other environmental and scientific organizations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In 1971 Wilson published his second major synthesis, The Insect Societies, which formulated the existing knowledge of the behavior of ants, social bees, social wasps, and termites, on a foundation of population biology. In it he introduced the concept of a new discipline of sociobiology, the systematic study of the biological basis of social behavior in all kinds of organisms. In 1975 he published Sociobiology: The New Synthesis, which extended the subject to vertebrates and united it more closely to evolutionary biology. The foundational discoveries of sociobiology are generally recognized to be the analysis of animal communication and division of labor, in which Wilson played a principal role, and the genetic theory of the origin of social behavior, which he helped to promote and apply in his 1971 and 1975 syntheses. Sociobiology: The New Synthesis was later ranked in a poll of the officers and fellows of the international Animal Behaviour Society as the most important book on animal behavior of all time, and is regarded today as the founding text of sociobiology and its offshoot, evolutionary psychology. [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The more than 100 awards received by Wilson from around the world in science and letters include the National Medal of Science, two Pulitzer Prizes for Non-fiction (for On Human Nature and, with Bert Hölldobler, The Ants) [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Wilson lives in Lexington, Massachusetts, with his wife Irene. A daughter, Catherine, and her husband Jonathan, reside in nearby Stow&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Robert Krulwich:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=5194672" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.npr.org/te...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Robert Krulwich is a correspondent for NPR's Science Desk, reporting on the intersections of science and technology with culture, politics and religion. His specialty is explaining complex news — economics, technology, science — in a style that is clear, compelling and entertaining. &amp;quot;I like talking about 'invisible ideas' and trying to find a way to explain what you've learned so people can grasp it,&amp;quot; he said.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Additionally, Krulwich co-hosts WNYC's NPR-distributed scientific documentary series Radio Lab with host/producer Jad Abumrad and serves as substitute host on NPR news magazines and talk programs including Morning Edition, All Things Considered and Talk of the Nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Krulwich first joined NPR in 1978 and served as economics reporter until 1985 when he joined CBS News. Since 1994, Krulwich has been an ABC News correspondent, appearing regularly on Nightline, World News Tonight and Good Morning America. He contributed to NPR occasionally until his recent return to NPR&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions from Harvard Square (on the Red Line):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fas.harvard.edu/~memhall/webpages-current/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fas.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sanders Theatre/Memorial Hall is located at 45 Quincy Street, between Cambridge and Kirkland Streets in Cambridge, a 5 minute walk from Harvard Square&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fas.harvard.edu/~memhall/webpages-current/parking.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fas.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sanders Theatre is located inside Memorial Hall at 45 Quincy Street in Cambridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There is NO PARKING at Memorial Hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;For those traveling to Sanders Theatre by car, parking will be available from one hour pre-performance to one hour post-performance. The Broadway Garage is located on Felton Street, between Broadway and Cambridge Street. Patrons need to tell the attendant that they are attending a Sanders Theatre event. They will receive a swipe ticket, which they will use to get back into the garage after the show, and which they will use to exit&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252705279000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248672539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Conversation with James D. Watson and Edward O. Wilson w/ Robert Krulwich</name><id>10965672</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252531800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/10965672/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/b/global_7445755.jpeg</photo_url></item>