<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>So, I'm back from the Advanced Mastery Training (AMT) in Colorado.  An amazing week, with Steve Andreas, Steve Watson, and especially Andrew Austin (referred to by some as the British Milton Erickson) (see &lt;a href="http://www.toolsfortransforming.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.toolsfortr...&lt;/a&gt; for more info on the training).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We learned a number of new, submodality-based techniques from Steve A, got some practice with hypnotic inductions from Steve W, and got a whole new approach to working with clients from Andrew (hint: never let the client get in the way of achieving their outcomes).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obviously, I can't impart an intense week of training (9am-9pm for 6 days) in one evening, but what I CAN do is to teach you a couple of very useful techniques that I learned, and tell you some of the more interesting, more impactful, and more humourous events of the week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to learn how to &amp;quot;spin&amp;quot; feelings to get rid of/let go of them, and how to slow down internal (negative) voices to transform them into allies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few notes:&lt;br /&gt;1) The meetup date has changed: instead of this Thursday (Sept 24) we're meeting next Thursday (Oct 1)&lt;br /&gt;2) The location has changed.  We'll now be meeting at the Wayland Wellness Center (15 E Plain St, Wayland), which is a much nicer meeting space than our old Newton digs&lt;br /&gt;3) The fee for the meetup is $20 (and as always, no one will be turned away for inability to pay)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, my website is finally up (NewLightNLP.com), my blog is imminent (newlightnlp.wordpress.com), and my new office is almost ready! (whew!  Enough change yet?).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you all next week!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256250066000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245368255000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP September Meetup - Latest &amp; Greatest Tools from Colorado</name><id>10684102</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254436200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/10684102/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/8/global_3512920.jpeg</photo_url></item>