<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>William has left the NEPN group please go to &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Newenglandphoto/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; to RSVP for this event. This is not a NEPN even rather a NEPE event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Hello Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, Welcome to all the new members of NEPE and NEPN. Coming up on November 19th we will be hosting a Meet and Greet so you can learn what NEPEand NEPN is all about. This meetup is not only geared towards new members but also members who have not yet been able to make it to one of our events. But of course are veteran members are also encouraged to attend and share their experiences with the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The East Coast Nikon Rep will also be on hand to show us the new line of Nikon products from DSLR's to the New point and shoot cameras.  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will consist of a Review of our meetups of 2008. We will talk about which trips were successful and which ones members would like to see repeated in 2009. A portfolio of our 2008 trips is being put together and will be passed around for members to view.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also go over how our events work. Included will be how to use the Website, how to check a event, when a event gets cancelled, contact info, posting of photos to the group site, the message board..ect..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also go over trips that are being planned for 2009. Here is a short list of New Trips we are looking at - Winter Lighthouse Trip, Waterfalls of NH, Boston at Night, Acadia National Park, Shelburne Farms, Cogg Railroad... Also, as stated above we will be looking at some of our 2008 trips and reviewing which ones we may want to repeat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And of course, and most importantly we will get a chance ot meet all of our new photographers.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have booked the function room and will be meeting there.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227995294000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225762511000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet and Greet - 2009 photo season info night. </name><id>9088675</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227139200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/9088675/</event_url></item>