<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>41 Branch Point Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.935875</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 1-508-746-5644 </phone><name>Billington Sea Kayak</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>1287839</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.676124</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Kayaking in Plymouth Bay isn't happening - not enough rentals on the waterfront and too many beginners. 
&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ THIS ENTIRE ENTRY !&lt;/strong&gt; So we are going to Billington Sea ....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Cindy..-- I talked to Doug at Billington Sea Kayak and he can handle a large group rental for us on the original date of Sat. August 20th. They open at 10 am so everyone should meet there at that time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Rental cost&lt;/strong&gt;: single kayak - $25.00 double kayak: $40.00 The cost is for use for the entire day 10 am - 5 pm and includes the PFD (life jacket).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is not room at Billington Sea Kayak for people to launch that have their own kayaks. Therefore, I will meet this group at the rear entrance to Morton Park (there's room to pull over) between 10:15 and 10:30 to lead them to the public boat ramp in Morton Park. There is a $15.00 park fee without a Plymouth Beach sticker. (It's a very short paddle from the boat ramp over to the rental site.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those attending need to indicate if they have their own boat or will be renting. They should bring sunscreen, a towel and a lunch and wear clothes (bathing suit) and shoes that can get wet. There are places to pull up the boats and swim. Directions to Morton Park - rear entrance and Billington Sea Kayak:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From Route 3 South:&lt;/strong&gt; Take Exit 6A (Plymouth Center, Route 44 East/Samoset St). Once on Route 44 East/Samoset St., take 2nd street on right (Oak St.). Follow Oak Street to end and turn right (Summer Street). Go 200 yards on Summer St. until a diagonal left (Billington Street). Turn left on Billington St. and go approximately 1/2 mile. You should be just going under Route 3. Look for a large sign saying "Morton Park - Rear Entrance" at the stone entrance. Go into the Park through the stone entrance. The road turns to dirt, but don't worry. Take the first left on the dirt road at the Canoe/kayak sign. Then just follow Canoe/Kayak signs to our shop. Travel time from Exit 6A is approximately 5 - 10 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From Route 3 North:&lt;/strong&gt; Take Exit 6 and turn right on Route 44 (Plymouth Center - Route 44 East/Samoset St.). Once on Route 44 East/Samoset St., take 2nd street on right (Oak Street) and then from that point follow directions above. 
&lt;strong&gt;Address for mapping:&lt;/strong&gt; Billington Sea Kayak 41 Branch Point Rd Plymouth, MA 02360&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Cindy or ask for our MEETUP GROUP</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314235542000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275392397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking in Billington Sea</name><id>16232827</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313848800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/16232827/</event_url></item>