<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>South End</address_2><address_1>539 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.344296</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>212.242.2566</phone><name>Boston Center for the Arts - Cyclorama</name><city>Boston</city><id>714089</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070992</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Taste wines from all over the world, enjoy tasty food pairings, and enjoy mini &amp;quot;Crash Courses&amp;quot; to expand your wine expertise. The Crash Courses are about 20 minutes long and will be hosted by sponsors throughout the Riot! sessions, zeroing in on specific grapes, regions, growing trends, and lots more. While the $45 event charge isn't cheap, you get a lot of bang for your buck and I will save the group the $5 service fee by buying tickets at a local wine store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting for coffee first will allow us to get to know each other briefly and target areas of common interest. Then we can walk down the street to the Cyclorama and explore the various pieces of the event in pairs or small groups -- or just follow your own wine muse wherever it leads you. We can regroup at a predetermined location later in the afternoon to share our findings and decide whether to continue our investigations. If there's interest, we can also move on to an early dinner at one of the many great restaurants in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: If you want me to buy your ticket, please contact me by email to let me know! I'll need you to send the ticket fee by check or PayPal. I'll go buy the tickets on Thursday night; any last minute RSVPs will have to buy their own tickets online.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet first at the Starbucks at 627 Tremont Street -- look for Meetup sign there!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241833714000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239546798000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taste up to 250 wines at Boston's Wine Riot!</name><id>10168977</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240075800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/10168977/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/c/global_8116044.jpeg</photo_url></item>