<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>246 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 629–4963</phone><name>Diva Lounge</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1037817</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122147</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The second annual New Years Eve Masquerade Ball, a classy, affordable, adult alternative to the downtown bar scene. If you were at last years event then you know how amazing it was. We sold out over a week in advance and threw one of the best New Years Eve parties Boston has ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Years party is Invite only and very Exclusive. It is All Inclusive: Which means free drinks and it is Open bar for 4 hours 10pm - 2am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only thing you need to bring is cash to Tip the bartenders. That also means shorter lines, better service, more drinks, and more partying. No paying $12-$18 per drink. You have an Actual OPEN BAR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: The Open Bar is only with the VIP Admission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The $25 General Admission does not include the Open bar. On top of all this, you still get to help out a great cause, as a portion of the event proceeds benefit Sane. You can't go wrong! So RING in the New Year with us once again. Get dressed up, have a couple cocktails, let loose, and dance the night away with friends and family all while supporting a great charity. Admission includes 4 hours of open bar that includes premier liquor, bottled beer, wine, a champagne toast at midnight Early Bird Tickets are almost SOLD OUT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is talking about this event. General admission tickets are only $55 each which includes the Open bar. General admission seating is available on a first come first serve basis, rest is standing room. If you want to guarantee seating then the VIP ticket is the way to go. If you would like to Reserve a table or section that is an extra $30 and seats groups of 5-8ppl. For $40 extra as a group you get reserved seating for drinks. A limited amount of VIP tickets will be sold so get your's before they're gone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this you would have to Purchase the $40 Table reservation option Doors open at 9:30 pm | Open bar 10:00pm - 2am | 21+ Admitted with I.D. Bostons best DJ's will be playing all your favorite hits from from the 80's - today. Top 40/ Hip Hop/ Mashups/ Latin remixes / House etc. FREE parking all across the area in Davis Square. Divas Lounge is Located at 248 Elm Street, Somerville 02144 Diva Lounge has entered its fifth year as the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s premier nightspot. Its mesmerizingly modern d&amp;amp;eacute;cor has been featured in several design magazines. Bring your own fancy Masquerades and feel free to get creative. Our photographer will be snapping away. Dress to Impress. As always, thank you for your continued support. Without you these events wouldn't be possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tix at www.Highrollerboston.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325387569000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Lifers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonnights</urlname><id>860845</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Nights</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324780413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years Eve Masquerade Ball (ALL INCLUSIVE)</name><id>45417142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325383200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonnights/events/45417142/</event_url></item>