<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of State and Pleasant Streets</address_2><address_1>26 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Richdale Food Store</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1126642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://chambermaster.blob.core.windows.net/images/events/1189/2426/EventPhotoFull_EventPhotoFull_springfest_weblogo.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some helpful hints on where to park.....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For parking: I would say basically where ever you are able to find a spot, in any of the parking lots or on street, but remember that you have to pay the meter if you are in a lot. There are 5 lots surroundingdowntown: 1 on each side of the Fire House/Not Your Average Joe's (East lot/West lot), when you are coming down Water Street There is the one behind all the stores next to Green St behind the Unitarian Church (big white one on Pleasant Street), this is the lot that is near Inn Street. 1 is off of Prince Place which is the street before the library 1 after the Library on State Street (which is the smaller lot, maybe 15-20 spots) IF you park on the street there is a 2 HOURminimum and you will get ticketed if you do not move your car! Also if you want to bring a lawn chair to sit in if there isn't room on the bench's...........&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come celebrate the season in downtown Newburyport! Come and enjoy great live music, art, fine crafts, and food from Newburyport's best restaurants. On this date Don't Call Me Shirley will be playing, let's go cheer them on while enjoying the sites and sounds around town.  The festival is from 10-5pm, and DCMS is playing 1-4pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, give me a call:  978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember if you have not paid your dues this year, this event would be a good opportunity to do so.  Thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be outside if you can't find us or you are running late call the Meetup phone.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338254564000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336619904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Newburyport Spring Fest</name><id>64191222</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338134400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/64191222/</event_url></item>