<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 minutes from Lexington, MA</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>42.742516</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Private Home</name><city>Hollis</city><id>6712602</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.589531</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>525.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/2/4/event_102890212.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/0/0/event_102891712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Fully Alive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Y&lt;/strong&gt;our sexuality is one of the most powerful spiritual awakening forces in your life, yet a great deal of your sexual potential lies untapped, unexplored.  Learn ways of accessing this potential, freeing it, as you open your body, heart and soul to the experience of being fully alive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;U&lt;/strong&gt;sing breath, movement and awareness, in this two day weekend workshop, you will learn how to access the heart of Kundalini - your sexual energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Y&lt;/strong&gt;ou will discover what it means to be fully alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Fully Alive . Weekend Tantra Immersion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 20th - 22nd . 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hollis, New Hampshire  (approx. 45 minutes from Cambridge, MA)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$525 per person . residential including all meals&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;includes workshop, meals, shared sleeping accommodations, outdoor pool, hot tub, walking trails&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will experience . . .&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the breath of ecstasy .&lt;/strong&gt; The heart is the center of our body, it is where physical reality, known as Shakti, meets pure awareness, known as Shiva. You’ll learn one of the basic elements of Tantric union, The Breath of Ecstasy, a pranayama practice that opens the heart to universal love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;purification .&lt;/strong&gt; This dynamic bio-energetic practice unlocks the body at a cellular level, purifying consciousness and freeing energetic blocks that limit our perception of reality. Something extraordinary happens when all patterns are erased. Somehow, it's only then that the true self within us emerges and we experience, for the first time, the limitless potential we carry as human beings. We see the mind-blowing truth of this world we inhabit yet rarely touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sacred spaces .&lt;/strong&gt; The spaces we live in are vessels for our spirit. This shamanic practice will inspire and instruct you in creating sacred Tantric space in your home, your life and in your body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;inquiry .&lt;/strong&gt; Have you ever taken a good long look at how you relate to your sexuality? Have you ever wondered how to bring the sacredness you know is possible into your sexual expression? Through inquiry, you’ll discover how to bring the love you know is possible into your life - now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the inner path to awakening .&lt;/strong&gt; You’ll learn to channel your life energy through your body in ways that will awaken these aspects of Being within you. Each of these 7 themes reflects the path taken by the kundalini as she moves through the human body on her journey to unite with her beloved. Root. Dwelling Place of the Self. Lustrous Gem. Unstruck. Purity. Beyond Wisdom. Thousandfold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ritual of the tattvas .&lt;/strong&gt; One of the most popular expressions found in the Upanishads is Tattvamsi which means . . . Thou art That. The 36 tattvas describe the Absolute, its internal aspects and the creation including living beings, down to the physical reality. In our final ritual of the weekend, we will experience the Shakti Tattvas - doors of perception - revealing your true nature as the Absolute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;what to expect .&lt;/strong&gt; All the processes are done fully clothed, singles and couples are welcome and you may choose to work alone or with a partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;your instructor .&lt;/strong&gt; Dawn Cartwright is a Tantric visionary, sacred writer, world traveler, and innovator in bio-energetic Tantra fusion. During her 18 years of teaching, she has integrated the Vigyan Bhairav roots of Tantra, Alexander Lowen’s teachings, the wisdom of Osho, and a&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;microcosm-macrocosm approach to the body. She is also creator of the Chandra Bindu Tantra Institute, dedicated to the realization of human potential through direct experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Fully Alive . Weekend Tantra Immersion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 20th - 22nd . 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hollis, New Hampshire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$525 per person . residential&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;includes workshop, meals, shared sleeping accommodations, outdoor pool, hot tub, walking trails&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chandra Bindu Tantra Institute&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.chandrabindutantrainstitute.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;508.380.9254&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344138479000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>new-england-tantric-meetup</urlname><id>804252</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>New England Tantric Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332189776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Be Fully Alive - A Weekend Tantra Immersion</name><id>57007352</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342825200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/new-england-tantric-meetup/events/57007352/</event_url></item>