<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2nd Floor</address_2><address_1>21 Main Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.611560</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-309-8448</phone><name>Cape Ann Community Cinema</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1434347</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.665501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning on seeing the award winning documentary Chasing Ice at the Cape Ann Cinema Theater. It is a small theater so I would recommend getting tickets in advanced. I will plan on being at at the theater lobby at 5:30 and head into the theater no later than 5:45. I will be wearing a black coat, bluish/green scarf and jeans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADULTS: $9.75 * STUDENTS &amp;amp; SENIORS (60+): $8.25 &lt;br /&gt;

CINEMA MEMBERS: $6.75 (IN DISCOUNT BLOCK)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://capeanncinema.wordpress.com/advance-tickets/" class="linkified"&gt;http://capeanncinema.wordpress.com/advance-tickets/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description &lt;br /&gt;

In the spring of 2005, acclaimed environmental photographer James Balog headed to the Arctic on a tricky assignment for National Geographic: to capture images to help tell the story of the Earth’s changing climate. Even with a scientific upbringing, Balog had been a skeptic about climate change. But that first trip north opened his eyes to the biggest story in human history and sparked a challenge within him that would put his career and his very well-being at risk. &lt;br /&gt;

Chasing Ice is the story of one man’s mission to change the tide of history by gathering undeniable evidence of our changing planet. Within months of that first trip to Iceland, the photographer conceived the boldest expedition of his life: The Extreme Ice Survey. With a band of young adventurers in tow, Balog began deploying revolutionary time-lapse cameras across the brutal Arctic to capture a multi-year record of the world’s changing glaciers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information: &lt;a href="http://www.chasingice.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.chasingice.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trish O'Flynn</member_name><member_id>3013556</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359338959000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359080411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chasing Ice Movie at Cape Ann Cinema Theater</name><id>101272432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359327600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/101272432/</event_url></item>