<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our next Meetup will be the first in a series which I'm calling 'Mini Presentions' or 'Mini-Topics'. We've discussed the idea before, and I'm excited to see it begin. At each one of these meetings, several of us will present a topic and discuss it for 20-30 minutes. I hope to cover a wide variety of subjects at all skill levels. Please don't be shy to suggest or volunteer for topics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have three presentations lined up for this meetup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bob Herrmann will present a &amp;quot;A Quick Start to Griffon. &amp;quot;  He will give an overview of Griffon and dive in develop a small sample project. Griffon is a Grails like application framework for developing desktop applications in Groovy.  Inspired by Grails, Griffon follows the Convention over Configuration paradigm, paired with an intuitive MVC architecture and a command line interface.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave Fox will give a presentation on using Subversion, the Hudson Continuous Integration Server, the Archiva Maven repository, and the new Grails dependency DSL to support a productive development workflow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Ressler: &amp;quot;On the Trail from Rails to Grails. My journey porting a good sized application from Rails to Grails.  I'll be discussing why we're doing this and many of the potholes I found on the trail.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been spending weeks trying to get in touch with Microsoft about using their meeting space again, but have been unable to get a response from them. Therefore, this meetup will be held at the Cantina office.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, I realize that this is the same day as St. Patrick's day. If you're planning on not coming specifically because of this, please keep in mind that a) we'll have beer and b) we'll be done by 9&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>the bottom floor of the building has a large hair salon named "Phia". Look for the sign. We're on the second floor, the first door on the right at the top of the stairs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Pember</member_name><member_id>9587085</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269040243000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Grails-Boston</urlname><id>1458975</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Grails Users' Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267818439000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grails Mini Presentations I</name><id>12794451</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268866800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Grails-Boston/events/12794451/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/global_9810037.jpeg</photo_url></item>