<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>238 Deer Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.077565</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Portsmouth VFW Hall</name><city>Portsmouth </city><id>883909</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.761881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Trailblazers, join us for a rocking scary night for a Halloween Dance Party.  Jumbo Circus Peanuts will be playing in the  Portsmouth VFW International Ballroom.  You get the best freakin' party in the Seacoast. Doors open at 8, musical orgy at 9. $5 is all... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costumes are encouraged!  It'll add to the fun and many people will be wearing them.  Show everyone your hidden demon (or angel or . . . ).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll try and get there early to grab a table, come early if you can.  &lt;br /&gt;My cell phone is: 603-312-6735 if anyone needs directions. &lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;Peter &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the (Amazing) Jumbo Circus Peanuts &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on who you talk to, this 12-piece band is either a Seacoast institution or should be confined in one. Others have observed that the group is merely a collection of professional drinkers with a music problem. Debate aside, one thing is clear — the Jumbo Circus Peanut philosophy starts and ends with fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like any great musical organization, the band was born one night in a tiny smoky kitchen when two trombonists, a clarinet player and an alto saxophonist collided over a case of beer and a couple of sheet music fake books. Collectively, at that time, the founding musicians had not picked up their respective instruments in something like 60 years.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the later addition of a rhythm section and even more melody instruments (not to mention two more trombones,) the Jumbo Circus Peanuts outgrew their kitchen home, performing in local bars and street events for the benefit of friends, family and those who came to confirm the existence of what one observer described as a &amp;quot;musical Loch Ness monster in drag.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, after nearly 15 years of Seacoast performances, the Jumbo Circus Peanuts are the area's top-drawing musical group with an ever-expanding repertoire that sails around the musical worlds of pop, funk, swing and rock — with stops that include Hollywood, Broadway, Detroit, Latin America and Hawaii.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although the Peanuts' present members are veterans of a wide variety of Seacoast bands and have performed everywhere from a Presidential inauguration (trumpeter Mark Weatherby as a member of the West Point band) to a state prison (bass player Chip Brindamour and saxophonist Curt Mackail as members of a UNH jazz big band) they all admit they've never been part of anything like the Peanuts.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We refuse to take ourselves and our purpose too seriously,&amp;quot; said saxophonist and the band's music director, John Prendergast. &amp;quot;This band is all about poking a fun at life and musical pretension. How else do you explain a college-educated male onstage wearing a pink prom dress, green high-top Chuck Taylor sneakers and playing Brock House on the xylophone?&amp;quot; he said. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When asked to name their musical influences by a reporter recently, members of the band agreed on: the Neville Brothers, Tower of Power, New Orleans' brass bands in general, Spike Jones, Tom Jones, both Sinatras (Nancy and Frank,) Disney, the Surfaris, Carmen Dragon, Count Basie, Sly Stone, Sarah Vaughan, Dusty Springfield, Perez Prado, Antonio Carlos Jobim, Mitch Ryder, Alvin and the Chipmunks, Hank Williams and Otis Redding. For that moment, it was apparent, the Jumbo Circus Peanuts were serious about something. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the tall scary guy in a mask!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288655919000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284512075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween Dance Party</name><id>14773558</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288486800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/14773558/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/6/f/global_4711903.jpeg</photo_url></item>