<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Boston Common</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.328947</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common</name><city>Boston, MA</city><id>972585</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=122033607896354" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; The constitution does not grant the federal government authority to conduct a war on drugs. Alcohol prohibition, for example, required its own constitutional amendment. Whereas &amp;quot;powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the States, are reserved to the States respectively, or to the people&amp;quot; via the tenth amendment, then it's up to us decriminalize the possession of small amounts of m...other nature. and say what you want about taxachusetts, but via a ballot initiative, we the people have elected to decriminalize! Join us at high noon on the Boston Common as we celebrate CONSTITUTION DAY and persuade these pot heads (some of whom are die hard political activists themselves) [not necessarily to change political affiliation but] to vote for Ron Paul and vote for freedom! NOTE: this is the second largest hempfest in the country. so don't come if you get paranoid in large crowds. Bring signs if you got 'em. If you don't have any then come anyways and will give you one or give you cards to hand out more info about the event rally: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=122033607896354" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316280023000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315599558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Republican outreach at Boston Freedom Rally</name><id>32928742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316275200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/32928742/</event_url></item>