<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397423</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Au Bon Pain</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669351</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Another Scrabble meetup. As always, these happen every second Sunday, same time, same location. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recent Meetups have lasted 2-3 hours, with some folks staying for two, three or even four games, and some folks leaving after just one. Turnout has been great the last few months, around 10-20! Skill and experience has ranged too, from novice players to tournament players. One thing has stayed the same, and that's everyone's fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a board if you have one, but you are welcome to come even if you don't have one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've put up several tips for improving your Scrabble play at this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston/pages/Tips_for_Improving_Your_Play/"&gt;page&lt;/a&gt;. The first tip may be to take a peak at the Cross Tables &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.cross-tables.com/download/CHEAT_PRO.pdf"&gt;cheat sheet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;--a list of two letter and other highly playable words. It's very helpful to memorize the two letter words. From now on I plan to provide a list of two and three letter words for folks to use as they are comfortable at the Meetup. Some folks may be okay using this &amp;quot;open&amp;quot; during the game--ask first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A note on the space: Au Bon Pain has been very accommodating of us. Usually they are not very busy on Sundays and I think they appreciate our business. However, they have asked that we stay in just one corner of the restaurant, and try not to move furniture around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, the dollar is voluntary--it goes to cover Meetup's monthly fees, and nobody will be turned away for not having funds. I ask that you bring a dollar once a month, which will cover you for the whole month even if you come to more than one game. Hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Quinten</member_name><member_id>9980941</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272384673000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Word Freaks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston</urlname><id>1385528</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Scrabble Enthusiasts of (Greater) Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271629696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bi-monthly Scrabble Meetup (Sunday April 25)</name><id>13218576</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272211200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston/events/13218576/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/e/global_7376798.jpeg</photo_url></item>