<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Rashomon&lt;/b&gt;  Japan 1950 83 min.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In both artistic achievement and historical importance,&lt;b&gt; Rashomon&lt;/b&gt; remains one of the masterpieces of cinema.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The simplicity of the idea disguises its serious intent. What is truth? In medieval Japan, a wealthy traveller is killed in the forest. A local bandit is picked up and charged with his murder. Four separate versions of the incident are shown, each with an opposing outcome. Which is right? Who is guilty? &lt;br /&gt;This is the film that introduced the West to Japanese cinema in 1950. It caused a sensation at Cannes, where it collected the top prize, and later went on to win Best Foreign Film at the Oscar ceremony.  Eye for Film&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Akira Kurosawa masterfully combines the testimony of four witnesses/participants in a rape/muder occuring in the woods in the era of feudal Japan. It all sounds straightforward at the start, but by the end, we're left to wonder exactly who's telling the truth, or even if the participants know what the truth is. The exploration of subjectivity has never been so thrilling, and Kurosawa is at his pinnacle as a filmmaker, framing testimony shots in earnest close-up and staging the flashbacks with inimitable grace. But of course it's not just a beautfully constructed movie, it's also a biting commentary on deceit, gender roles, and due process (not to mention Japanese culture). And every viewer is given the opportunity to draw his own conclusions.  Filmcritic.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to the NY Times Review written in 1951 when the film was first released in the U.S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/review?res=EE05E7DF1730A42CA44A4CC2B7799D8E6896" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free screening presented by the VES department at Harvard and since this masterpiece has a running time of only 83 minutes (sweet!)  we should be in round-table discussion mode by 9 PM- which is a good thing on a weeknight. Since it is free, you might want to get there a bit early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the film's conclusion Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to discuss at a nearby restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207350365000</updated><rating><average>4.13000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204767245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Akira Kurosawa's Rashomon at the HFA</name><id>7473555</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207177200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7473555/</event_url></item>