<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;PADDLE the Essex River, HIKE Choate Island, and EAT on the Salt Marsh!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/4/2/event_127108482.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Essex River Basin is one of the most beautiful places for kayaking in Massachusetts north of Boston. We'll paddle around Choate (Hog) Island and hike its trails. We'll see the 700-acre Crane Wildlife Refuge and possibly Crane Beach. We can stop for a picnic or wait until we return to eat at Farnham's Seafood on the salt marsh or at the original Farm Bar &amp;amp; Grill pub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/b/e/event_127103742.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We begin&lt;/strong&gt; at the Essex town boat ramp. Heading out of Essex and toward the sea (but not into the sea!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll paddle down the Essex River and out to protected Choate Island, which is completely surrounded by salt marsh and other islands. We'll land at Choate, stopping for a hike. There are many tributaries to explore and the area abounds with wildlife. Herons, egrets, terns, and even eagles may be encountered. The water is not deep and this attracts many birds that hunt in the shallows.  The entire trip is in salt marsh - protected waters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/1/a/event_127108442.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With its ever-changing skies and tides, and shifting sandbars, the Essex River Basin is never the same twice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length/difficulty&lt;/strong&gt;: Easy to moderate depending on conditions. From 6 to 8 miles in protected water. There will be some tidal current but it's not likely to be too severe. Figure on being out 3-5 hours total before we return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portsmouth Carpool: 11:30am&lt;/strong&gt; @ &lt;a href="http://www.ridecj.com/new-hampshire/portsmouth.html"&gt;Portsmouth Bus Station&lt;/a&gt; - 185 Grafton Ave. Meet in the the overflow lot - the lot farthest from the main bus terminal building. Meet at the back of the lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Newburyport Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;Noon @&lt;/strong&gt; Storey Ave Park &amp;amp; Ride&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choate Island &amp;amp; Crane Refuge:&lt;/strong&gt; Protected and overseen by The Trustees of Reservations, people can now paddle to Choate Island, also known as Hog Island, to view the Crane Wildlife refuge and historic Choate Farm and experience an abundance of nature, sightseeing and bird watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/8/0/event_127109312.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A bird-watcher's delight&lt;/strong&gt;, Choate Island is the major landscape feature of the more than 700 acres of islands, salt marsh and sand dunes that compose the Cornelius and Mine S. Crane Wildlife Refuge located in the Essex Bay estuary. The abundant plant, fish and invertebrate food attracts many different species of birds, including sandpipers, plovers, terns, heron, egrets and songbirds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some of the island's&lt;/strong&gt; distinguishing features are the dark spruce forest, planted in the 1930s, which can easily be seen by boat, and the Choate House, an architectural wonder built by the Choate family, who inhabited the island for 300 years, sometime around 1730. It has stayed virtually intact for more than 250 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/2/6/event_127109222.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Lo:9:46-Hi:3:30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Unless otherwise specified, refunds for timely cancellations will be processed the day after the event.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/messages/boards/thread/13601461"&gt;Click here for a note on event fees.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1340844958000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339084726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle, Hike, Eat!</name><id>68167782</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340555400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/68167782/</event_url></item>