<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;No rest for the weary! &amp;nbsp;We finished our 48 NH 4Kers this weekend and now are pushing on towards the NE100 with 
&lt;strong&gt;Sandwich Mountain. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Sandwich Mountain is on the list of 100 New England Highest and 52 With a View&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We'll ascend to the summit of Sandwich Mountain via the Algonquin Trail and descend via the Sandwich Mountain Trail, passing Jennings Peak along the descent. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The Algonquin Trail is steep and rough. &amp;nbsp;Both trails are supposed to have some great views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cool and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. &amp;nbsp;Come prepared to stay dry!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This IS a traverse, so we will need to carpool to another location.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;We will meet in the Sandwich Mountain Trail Parking lot on Route 49 and carpool to the Algonquin Trail Head on Sandwich Notch Road. &amp;nbsp;We will traverse the mountain by ascending via the Algonquin Trail and descending via the Sandwich Mountain Trail.&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sunset will be at &amp;nbsp;about 8:07pm.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I do not know how exposed this hike will be.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will not pass a hut or a shelter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Water sources appear to be *very* limited on this trail - bring enough for a hot summer day.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Headlamps are not required but strongly suggested as a safety precaution. &amp;nbsp;Always be prepared to come out in the dark if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you. &amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;strong&gt;I require participants to wait at trail junctions, major water crossings and summits so that the group can exchange information and reset their pace.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I am NOT a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace. &amp;nbsp;I'm doing about book time, maybe a little slower, these days.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day. &amp;nbsp;I would like you to be around for another day too.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog &amp;amp; bring plenty of water for the summer heat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors. &amp;nbsp;If the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule to Sunday if possible. &amp;nbsp;Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;RSVP Questions are NOT optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
     &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Book time is about &amp;nbsp;8.4 miles, 6 hrs, 45 &amp;nbsp;minutes&lt;/strong&gt;. Plan on it taking about this long &amp;amp; possibly a little more since we intend to spend some time at the summit and take the paths to the ledges for views. &amp;nbsp;My climbs have been averaging a little faster than book time these days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Plagerized" Trail Descriptions &amp;nbsp;from the AMC Guide will follow shortly
 &lt;br /&gt; ----------------------------------------------------------&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt; Copyright &amp;copy; the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summit of Sandwich Mtn via Algonquin Trail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;4.5 miles&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;3 hours 30 minutes&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summit of Sandwich Mountain to parking lot via Sandwich Mountain Trail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;3.9 miles&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;3 hours and 15 min&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Totals&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt; --------&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;8.4 miles&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;6 hours, 45 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THIS PEAK AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic, usually a Meetup Sign in the window &amp; 2 dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312756670000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311008953000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NE 100 &amp; 52 With a View:  Sandwich Dome &amp; Jennings Peak</name><id>26151511</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312635600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/26151511/</event_url></item>