<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>underside of Boston Bed Company</address_2><address_1>386 Lindedlof Ave (Rt 139)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02368</zip><lat>42.162600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 341 8800</phone><name>Judy's School of Dance</name><city>Randolph</city><id>1169179</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.041159</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ZUMBA CLASSES FOR ADULTS!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets face it, working out can be healthy, rewarding, beneficial… working out can be lots of things, but its never been known to be much fun… UNTIL NOW! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zumba fuses hypnotic Latin rhythms and easy to follow moves to create a dynamic workout system that will blow you away. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our goal is simple: We want you to want to work out, to love working out, to get hooked. Zumba Fanatics achieve long term benefits while experiencing an absolute blast in one exhilarating hour of caloric-burning, heart-racing, muscle-pumping, body-energizing, awe-inspiring movements meant to engage and captivate for life! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The routines feature interval training sessions where fast and slow rhythms and resistance training are combined to tone and sculpt your body while burning fat. Add some Latin flavor and international zest into the mix and you've got ZUMBA! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the past years Zumba has become nothing short of a revolution. Coining the concept of &amp;quot;fitness-party&amp;quot; and making fitness fun, Zumba has spread like wild-fire, and has positioned itself as the single most influential movement in the industry of fitness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As of July 08, Zumba has a rapidly growing community of over 20,000 trained instructors in thirty-five countries, sold over 3.5 million DVD's, and changed the lives of an estimated 4 million Zumba Fanatics. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why? Because it's the best party around. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $10 per person (cash, payable to the studio)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No minimum... I'm going either way to have fun at my friend Jess's class. The space is huge and Jess said, the more the merrier so no max either. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadlines: Wednesday the 3rd at 5pm. After that time please email or contact an organizer directly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Judy's School of Dance &lt;br /&gt;386 Lindedlof Ave. (Rte 139) underside of Boston Bed Company &lt;br /&gt;Stoughton/Randolph, MA 02368 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://danceinrandolphma.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://danceinrandolp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will meet inside the studio</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4336960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267930758000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265938003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ZUMBA!</name><id>12585036</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267745400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/12585036/</event_url></item>