<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Pocahontas Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03905</zip><lat>43.071270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fort Foster </name><city>Kittery Point</city><id>845838</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.686638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/b/e/event_101783742.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Gerrish Island Lane, turn right onto Pocohontas Road and proceed 1.1 miles.  You will pass Whaleback Drive on you right and then keep right at the fork (the left fork is a driveway for private houses).  Proceed about another 330 feet or so.  You will come to a gate house and the road will be gated closed.  At this time of year you will have to simply park on the side of the road and walk past the gate.  We can congregate just past the gate house so we don't have to worry about the dogs running lose in traffic..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tides for Kittery Point October 21, 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon
           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible

Su  21     High   4:07 AM     9.0   7:04 AM    Rise  1:26 PM      35
    &lt;strong&gt;
   21      Low  10:13 AM     0.5&lt;/strong&gt;   5:50 PM     Set 11:38 PM
    21     High   4:23 PM     9.9
    21      Low  10:59 PM    -0.3
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This outing/hike is set so we will get there close to low tide rather than high tide so that more of the beach will be exposed and the water will be lower compared to if we went there closer to high tide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip isn't so much about going on a longer hike to get more exercise as it is about going on a shorter hike and enjoying the views along the seacoast/beach.  Of course there is always the possibility of any one wanting more exercise to walk the route twice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For those who might be interested we could set up a car pool near exit 1 off of Rt. 101 in Manchester if enough people show an interest in doing so in the comment section below.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/c/7/event_19027111.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Drive past the indicated address.  At this time of year the park gate will be closed.  Simply park on the road near the park gate/toll both.  We can gather just inside the park gate away from the cars</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350941428000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348950834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fort Foster - Kittery Point, ME</name><id>84701402</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350828000000</time><rsvp_limit>29</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/84701402/</event_url></item>