<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10253922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/3/a/event_189764602.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Please join the Red Sox Natives and other invited groups from North of Boston for A Third Wednesday After Work Happy Hour at Laurie's 9:09 Steakhouse and Raw Bar in Wakefield on Wednesday, January 16 at 6:00pm. Red Sox Native Maria and her North Shore Groups will also be Co-Hosting with us.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be occupying both the Penny Lane and Raw Bars at Laurie's so invite your friends. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for appetizers, dinner, a cocktail or two or three, socializing and more. $1.00 Oysters are available from 5-7pm while they last. If you have a group of people that want a table reservation for dinner please call Laurie's at 781-246-1909 and make a reservation. For information on Laurie's 909 and the menu go to &lt;a href="http://www.lauries.com/"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get there when you can and stay as long as you are able. You are more than welcome to show up for all or just part of the event. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participating Groups include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Red Sox Natives (Frank &amp;amp; Jon)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Boston Happy Hour (Tonya)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. North Shore Womens Group (Maria)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. North Shore Separated &amp;amp; Divorced Group (Maria)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this will be your first time meeting the Red Sox Natives Crew and the other groups check out the photos of those who RSVP Yes so you can find the group. All RSVPs are required to have a real face photograph as their main profile photo. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay as you order and tip your servers. However, if you sit at a group table a group bill may be provided so please communicate with your server when ordering. Credit Cards will be held by the servers at Laurie's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar is Wakefield's newest restaurant and Bar with live entertainment several nights per week and Tuesday night Trivia with Morgan White Jr. from WBZ Radio. Laurie's is located at the Wakefield Commuter Rail Train Station in Wakefield. The Reading and Haverhill Commuter Rail trains stop at Laurie's. Trains leave North Station Boston at 5:15, 5:35, 5:55, 6:20 and 7:20pm. It's a 20 minute ride to the Wakefield stop in front of Laurie's. Trains depart from Wakefield to Boston at 8:05, 9:09, 10:19 and 10:59pm. Laurie's is easily accessible within 10 minutes from Routes 128, 93, 28 and 1. Free parking is available in two lots on Tuttle Street, in the Church parking lot if there are no activities there, and on street after 5:30pm. Check out the MBTA or Hop Stop for additional public transit options including the less reliable/frequent 136 and 137 bus lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Say hello to Laurie and Bob when you visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the "Penny Lane" Bar, the 9:09 and Beatles references.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information at http://&lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask For The Red Sox Natives and All of Maria's North Shore Groups Occupying the bar</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359234676000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357415410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Third Wednesday After Work Happy Hour at Laurie's 909 Steakhouse/Raw Bar</name><id>98079792</id><headcount>16</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358377200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/98079792/</event_url></item>