<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>199 Cabot St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.651110</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-937-2690</phone><name>The Brewery Exchange</name><city>Lowell</city><id>797911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.316459</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Free pool at a nice establishment.  They have 10 tables and it is rarely very busy.  They have a full bar, food and many TV's.  2 TV's are huge 10' wide!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will give free pool lessons to anyone who desires (beginning through advanced).  &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;This time I will have a sign-up sheet&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; so you can sign up for time with me directly and I will do whatever you want to work on.  We can do everything from 1) play a game or 2) work on english 3) work on breaks, etc.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll teach you how to pull the ball or follow the ball or freeze it on the spot or whatever you want to work on.  However, instead of just showing you using this format you will actually do it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website &lt;a href="http://www.thebreweryexchange.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Menu  &lt;a href="http://www.thebreweryexchange.com/pubmenu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thebrewery...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lowell Beer Works is right next door as well if you want to eat or try some cool microbeers &lt;a href="http://www.beerworks.net/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.beerworks.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beerworks....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also a great French restaurant (and expensive but worth every penny) about 1 mile away called La Boniche &lt;a href="http://www.laboniche.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.laboniche.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.laboniche....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info:&lt;br /&gt;Where is the Brewery Exchange located? &lt;br /&gt;The Brewery Exchange is located at 201 Cabot Street in Lowell, MA. We are 25 minutes North of Boston and 30 minutes south of Manchester, NH. For directions to The Brewery Exchange visit our Find Us page. Website link &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is there parking available? &lt;br /&gt;Yes. There is plenty of free parking.  The Brewery Exchange parking lot is located directly across the street in the Notini Parking lot. Parking is safe, convenient and free during non event days.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be upstairs by the pool tables</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241910378000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238631320000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free pool at the Lowell Brewery Exchange and free pool lessons!</name><id>10093066</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239145200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/10093066/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/3/global_7755251.jpeg</photo_url></item>