<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 1A</address_2><address_1>675 Ocean Blvd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03870</zip><lat>43.041522</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-7406</phone><name>Odiorne Point State Park</name><city>Rye</city><id>1004721</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.715843</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>DUE TO A CONFLICT in my schedule I cannot make the original date of April 11.  Since I don't wish to miss this event I'm going to reschedule for 2 weeks after the original date.  Thanks and hope to see you all there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot.  After the walk we'll gather for lunch at a local restaurant for those interested. Carpooling is suggested.  Just post whether or not you need a ride or can provide a ride to someone.  My cell is 617-775-0045 if you are running late that day.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Odiorne Point State Park offers one of the most beautiful natural settings along New Hampshire's 18-mile coastline. Within the 135-acre seaside park, visitors can enjoy a wooded picnic grove with a modern playground and miles of walking trails. Most trails are handicapped accessible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the park is an ideal location for seaside outdoor recreation, the property is also renowned for its diverse natural history. Seven distinct natural habitats can be visited in a leisurely hour's walk. Although the spectacular rocky shore is the most popular, the woodlands, uplands, salt marsh, freshwater and salt ponds, and sandy beach (non-swimming) combine to create one of the region's most diverse nature walks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New Hampshire Division of Parks and Recreation operates the park; the Center adds interpretive and educational components to the experience. Call 603-436-1552 or visit www.nhparks.state.nh.us for more information about Odoirne Point State Park or any of the state parks in the seacoast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;From 95 North or South&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 5 on Interstate 95 North or South to the Portsmouth Traffic Circle. From the Circle take Route 1 By-Pass South to Beaches/Hampton. After 1 mile the road connects with Route 1 South. Follow Route 1 South for approximately 1 mile. At the third traffic light (sixth from traffic circle), take a left onto Elwyn Road. Pass the Urban Forestry Center (on your left), go approximately 1.3 miles to the roundabout at Foye's Corner. Go half-way around the roundabout onto Route 1A South. Continue for 1.8 miles, past the Odiorne Point State Park boat launch parking area (on left), to the main entrance of Odiorne Point State Park (on left).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272380811000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269277389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ODIORNE  POINT STATE PARK  DATE CHANGE</name><id>12956742</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272207600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/12956742/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>