<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1904 Canton Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.223400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 333-0690</phone><name>Blue Hills Trailside Museum</name><city>Milton</city><id>669267</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116940</lon></venue><fee><label>event</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: chocolate"&gt;The Blue Hills Reservation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; stretches over 7,000 acres from Quincy to Dedham, Milton to Randolph, providing a green oasis in an urban environment. Rising above the horizon, Great Blue Hill reaches a height of 635 feet, the highest of the 22 hills in the Blue Hills chain. From the rocky summit visitors can see over the entire metropolitan area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: chocolate"&gt;&lt;b&gt;NE Dynamic Sports Fan member Cliff has offered to be our hike leader - thank you Cliff.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; The hike will run about 2 to 3 hours. We will hike to summit which is moderately challenging at times but plenty of places to rest and enjoy the view and the foliage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: chocolate"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Take Route 128 to exit 2B  (Milton, Route 138 North).  Proceed straight through the first set of lights and make a mental note of the parking lot on your left in case you need to use it. About one-half mile further on the right, just after the Blue Hills Ski Area, are two large parking lots in succession. Park in the first one, marked “Trailside Museum Parking”.  If the lot is full, move on to the next.  We’ll meet at the entrance to the Trailside Museum, which is basically the only building you’ll see, and is accessible from both lots.  Please Note: that day there is an open house at the summit weather observatory, along with a kite flying contest. Both will be pretty cool to see, but will probably make parking a bit more of a challenge, so carpooling and/or arriving early would be wise. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: chocolate"&gt;Sturdy sneakers or hiking boots, water and snack required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Camera suggested. &lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;No dogs allowed - boo hoo&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After well head for relaxation and rest at local pub for refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb</member_name><member_id>5999051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257268824000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Funseeker</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>nefunseekers</urlname><id>1277691</id><group_lat>42.0299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>Funseekers!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251569594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills Hike</name><id>11232825</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257094800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nefunseekers/events/11232825/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/3/global_10439155.jpeg</photo_url></item>