<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Does Integral Reject New Age?: Deciding What to Believe in a Post-Metaphysical World&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ken Wilber describes his latest work as All Quadrants/All Levels (AQAL) plus post-metaphysics.  Post-metaphysics has something to do with what we take as &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; (metaphysics), and integral theory values tell us to avoid &amp;quot;confusing the map with the territory&amp;quot; and avoid &amp;quot;the myth of the given&amp;quot;.   What is the place of mythic/magical thinking in integral or second tier thinking?  Can we, and do we really want to, avoid metaphysical thinking?  Is New Age thinking too metaphysical?  What aspects of New Age beliefs should we reject, and what should we include yet transcend?  We will start with a group activity involving mythic/magical thinking, and then explore the above questions, and see if we can invoke the spirit of Habermas and the pragmatists! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this meetup, Tom Murray will lead us through a provocative presentation on these ideas.  We will then integrate these ideas in to our own being, and engage in a collective group discussion.  This is our last Boston Integral Commons meetup until the fall, so please do come!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tom Murray, Ed.D. is an independent scholar who's day job involves research in adaptive learning environments, online communities, and cognitive tools: &lt;a href="http://www.tommurray.us" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tommurray....&lt;/a&gt;.  In addition he is an Associate Editor at Integral Review journal and has published papers on integral theory as it relates to education, dialog, leadership, ethics, knowledge building communities, and epistemology: &lt;a href="http://www.perspegirty.com/papers" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.perspegirt...&lt;/a&gt;.  He has held positions as visiting/adjunct faculty member at Hampshire College and the University of Massachusetts, where he continues to do most of his consulting work.  Tom also occasionally teaches classes in improvisational movement and communication skills.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273361275000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271365812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Does Integral Reject New Age?: What to Believe in a Post-Metaphysical World</name><id>13194379</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273187700000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/13194379/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>