<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harborside Learning Lab</address_2><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.358925</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New England Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>735569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050636</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the New England Aquarium website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;On June 23, 2000, a cargo ship sank off the coast of South Africa, spilling 1,300 tons of oil and putting 75,000 African penguins at risk. Some 12,500 inexperienced volunteers descended upon Cape Town to help save the imperiled birds. &lt;b&gt;Dyan DeNapoli&lt;/b&gt;, at the time a senior penguin aquarist at the Aquarium, was one of 100 penguin experts who helped supervise the volunteers during the rescue effort. After three months of grueling labor, 95 percent of the affected penguins were successfully released back into the wild in what has been heralded as the largest and most successful rescue of animals ever undertaken. DeNapoli tells this story in &lt;b&gt;The Great Penguin Rescue: 40,000 Penguins, A Devastating Oil Spill and the Inspiring Story of the World's Largest Animal Rescue&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New England Aquarium would like people to register with them at &lt;a href="http://support.neaq.org/site/Calendar?id=103068&amp;amp;view=Detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://support.neaq.o...&lt;/a&gt; . Their event is free and is open to the public, and is held at their Harborside Learning Lab. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside the Harborside Learning Lab, which is down the alley between the IMAX theater and the parking garage, past the dolphin sculpture starting at 6:00 pm. We should probably grab seats at 6:40 pm for this 7:00 pm lecture, since the lecture hall is kinda small. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Talks at the New England Aquarium's Harborside Learning Lab are usually an hour long. Anybody want to grab a bite to eat at Legal Seafood after?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the author, Dyan deNapoli&lt;/b&gt;, according to her website &amp;quot;The Penguin Lady&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thepenguinlady.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thepenguin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Dyan deNapoli&lt;/b&gt; is a recognized penguin expert, educator and author. After working closely with the penguin colony at Boston’s prestigious New England Aquarium for nine years, she founded her company, The Penguin Lady, to teach audiences worldwide about the biology, behavior, and conservation of these fascinating seabirds. She has been the guest lecturer on nature cruises to Antarctica and the Galapagos Islands, and has presented her penguin programs at numerous libraries, grade schools, colleges, museums and assisted living facilities. She donates 20% of the proceeds from every appearance to penguin rescue groups. Praised for her engaging presentation style, Dyan has shared her passion for penguins with approximately 250,000 people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dyan has appeared as the guest expert on CNN's Situation Room, BBC Radio 5 Live, ABC Radio Australia, WSCA Radio Portsmouth, Wild Moments and several other television and radio shows. She has been the content reviewer for three books about penguins, and in 2007, she authored the Penguins chapter for Scholastic Publishing’s New Book of Knowledge encyclopedia. Her forthcoming book, The Great Penguin Rescue, vividly chronicles her participation in the largest and most successful rescue of oiled animals ever undertaken. Scheduled for release by Free Press on October 26, 2010, it is currently available for pre-order wherever books are sold. Dyan is donating 20% of her proceeds from The Great Penguin Rescue to penguin rescue groups and to Gulf oil spill relief efforts&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Review of &lt;i&gt;The Great Penguin Rescue&lt;/i&gt; by The Daily Beast:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Book was released Tuesday, October 26, 2010.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/galleries/2238/11/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thedailybe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It’s hard to imagine a silver lining coming out of a story about an oil spill, but if there ever were one, it would be The Great Penguin Rescue. Ten years before the disastrous BP oil spill still plaguing the Gulf Coast, another massive spill off the coast of South Africa put the local population of 75,000 penguins – 41 percent of the world’s penguin population – at serious risk. Without missing a beat, animal expert Dyan deNapoli (understandably known more often as “the Penguin lady”) jumped into action, eventually gathering a team of 1,250 volunteers who individually scrubbed the oil from and nursed back to life nearly all the 40,000 affected birds in what became the world’s biggest ever animal rescue. For those still hoping for a March of the Penguins sequel this is the perfect, adorable solution, as well as another stark reminder of the dangers of environmental irresponsibility&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dyan deNapoli's &amp;quot;The Penguin Lady&amp;quot; blog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://thepenguinlady.wordpress.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://thepenguinlady...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Sept 20, 2010&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Well, the last few months have been extraordinarily busy, but I’m finally back and ready to get blogging again. In one of my last posts, I had mentioned that I was heading to the Gulf of Mexico to assist with the bird rehabilitation efforts there. The IBRRC (who I had worked closely with during the Treasure oil spill rescue in South Africa) had taken me on as a consultant – my bags were packed and I was ready to go. Then, frightening reports began emerging from the Gulf. The dispersant (Corexit) being used to break up and submerge the oil from the Deepwater Horizon well had been applied in massive quantities – close to two million gallons were sprayed on top of, and injected into, the waters of the Gulf. Virtually the entire world supply was dumped into the region. Ironically, this particular formulation of Corexit was banned in the UK ten years ago because it is extremely toxic and damaging to the environment - despite this fact, BP had no compunction about using it in US waters. They even continued using it after the EPA told them to cease and desist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What was most alarming, however, were the reports about the impacts on human health after this same dispersant was used during the Exxon Valdez oil spill in Alaska 20 years ago. Dr. Rikki Ott, a leading marine toxicologist who lived in the region at the time of the Exxon Valdez spill, was on the front lines during the months following this event. Check out her website and books (including Not One Drop), in which she discusses the devastating effects on the health of the clean-up workers who were exposed to Corexit. She and other scientists have conducted a great deal of research in the years since that spill, and their findings are chilling. Many of the clean-up workers who were on the front lines are now dead – all dying before the age of 51. Those who survived have been left with chronic respiratory illnesses and other crippling health problems including blood disorders, and liver and kidney damage. This last one is where my antennae went up. [ &lt;b&gt;MORE&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://thepenguinlady.wordpress.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://thepenguinlady...&lt;/a&gt;  ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Aquarium Lecture Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Aquarium has been providing free lectures and films by scientists, environmental writers, photographers and others since 1972. The Aquarium Lecture Series is presented free to the public through the generosity of the Lowell Institute, which has been providing funding for free public lectures at universities and museums since 1836.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lectures are free and open to the public. Registration is requested. All programs start at 7 p.m. in the Aquarium's Harborside Learning Lab, unless otherwise noted below&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;General Directions to the Aquarium:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/visit_planning/maps_directions_and_parking/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map to to the Harborside Learning Lab:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/documents/harborside_learning_lab.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290082339000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288805544000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dyan deNapoli talks about "The Great Penguin Rescue" @ Harborside Learning Lab</name><id>15325927</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289952000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15325927/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/e/global_19365454.jpeg</photo_url></item>