<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi, Everyone!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us this Sunday for a hike in and around York Beach (including the Nubble) and York Village followed by a great brunch at nearby York Harbor Inn!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jane and I will be co-leading this hike together.  Some of you met Jane on my previous hikes.  She mapped out a route on a previous walk and estimates this hike to be around 5 – 6 miles.  See the directions to the meeting location below.  Following our hike, we will head up to York Harbor Inn for a great brunch!  Here is their website:  www.yorkharborinn.com (just copy and paste into your browser), click on “Fine Dining and Pub” on the first page - then on “Sunday Brunch Menu” in the left column.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike will start at 10:30.  Estimate 2 hours or so for the hike.  We’ll get to York Harbor Inn by around 1:00 and enjoy our brunch (the dining room closes at 2:30).  We may need a reservation if more than eight people sign up, so please be reasonably sure that you will be able to join us for both the hike and brunch, which will run from about 10:30 - 2:00 or so for both.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As to dress:  we all know at this time of year, the direction of the wind can make all the difference in the world!  If the wind is off the water, it could be in the 40s, breezy, and chilly enough for a heavy jacket and hat.  If off the land, it will be pleasantly mild.  My advice would be to throw a heavy jacket and hat in the car but dress with a light jacket or heavy sweater – that way you’re prepared either way!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll look forward to seeing you then!  &lt;br /&gt;Randy  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 95 North over the big bridge to Exit 7 just before the toll booths.  (NOTE:  There are two Exit 7s -one in Portsmouth, NH that is currently under construction and one in Maine; it’s the second Exit 7, the one in Maine, that we’re looking for).  Take a right at the end of the ramp.  Go to the lights – another right – then left at next set of lights (this is York Street also called Route 1A).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the village – the road will fork in the village – bear right at the fork.  The road will turn and bend in a couple of places.  The road name eventually changes to Long Beach, but it’s the same road.  In fact, you will pass York Harbor Inn, which will be on the left.  Keep going until you come to the beach.  Look for the general area of the Sun and Surf restaurant on the right and Anchorage Inn on the left.  We will meet in that general area.   &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the general vicinity of Sun and Surf Restaurant on the right and Anchorage Inn on the left.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1273338334000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271887678000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>York Beach and York Village Hike and Brunch!</name><id>13252255</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272205800000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13252255/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/b/global_11008251.jpeg</photo_url></item>