<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187114</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>Richard Tosti Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>826225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236877</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The location will be my residence. 36 Woodridge Road, Westwood, MA. You can bring your favorite CD. Yes, we will dance, laugh and have Fun! I will supply the pizza and wine/beer on this one occasion for the holidays. We will determine if it is more convenient for everyone that I cover the food-get feedback after the party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The warm, cozy, friendly, secure atmosphere of my home will be more appropriate for the holiday season and smaller groups. It will be more intimate and more conducive to meeting everyone.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I just like being with friendly, warm, and caring singles during the Holiday season. I hope you feel the same. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It continues to happen at everyone one of my home parties. People get connected and they meet someone they think is special. Reason: These parties are more relaxing, less intimating and people are generally more receptive to communicating with everyone.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;INVITE SOMEONE YOU KNOW - I’d be especially pleased if you’d invite a wonderful male friend. Our objective is always to achieve a 50-50 ratio of men and women. So let’s redouble our efforts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Values&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE ARE PRINCIPLE-CENTERED - We are high integrity, are honesty, reliable, positive, non-judgmental, gentle, kind, cheerful, friendly, and respectful toward everyone. We use private Singles Home/Dinner/Dance Parties as a vehicle to meet other singles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our purpose is to socialize with other principle-centered people in our age range (30-65) who are also searching for a lifetime partner.  Let’s have fun meeting old and new friends. Circulate, and talk to everyone. If someone is alone, introduce yourself and say hi!  Please be Friendly, Positive, and Optimistic to everyone.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• THE YES DANCE - Please be respectful and dance at least one time with anyone who asks you.  This is our No. 1 value.  If you’re willing and able to say yes, then this will be a great event for you to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•  INVITE OTHER FRIENDS, PARTICULARLY MEN - Our objective is to have an equal amount of men and women.  Our Singles Dinner/Dance Parties are always close to equal numbers of men and women. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it a truly memorable home/dance party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fees - $25.00- I will supply the pizza and open bar this one time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DRESS CODE - Professional casual&lt;br /&gt;DATE - Saturday - Nov. 27th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;TIME - 7:00PM - 10:30pm (agreement with neighbors not to have parties too late)&lt;br /&gt;PLACE - My home- 36 Woodridge Road, Westwood, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MAXIMUM ATTENDEES – 30 People&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MUSIC - CDs supplied by guests and some of mine&lt;br /&gt;PIZZA BUFFET - 7:30PM- supplied my me- you bring no food or drink&lt;br /&gt;OPEN BAR - Wine &amp;amp; Beer - supplied by me&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location &amp;amp; Directions&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road &lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128-Exit 16B/Route 109 toward Westwood&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles left on Pond Street, just past the middle school on left. If you go by Dunkin Donuts on right, you missed it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go 1 mile, then left on Oak Street (Google search says go right; this is wrong.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go 1.5 miles to end and turn right on Brook Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 100 feet, take a right on Woodridge Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My home is the 3rd house on the left, cream colored, number 36.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon. The best is yet to be!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;Your Organizer/Host/Coach&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;President&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti Associates&lt;br /&gt;36 Woodridge Road&lt;br /&gt;Westwood, MA 02090&lt;br /&gt;781-551-3307&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290967556000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283819830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Private Singles Dance Party 30-65</name><id>14677882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290902400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/14677882/</event_url></item>