<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello, Java Meetup members!&lt;br /&gt;this month, Renaud Richardet from Wyona, agreed to introduce Apache-Cocoon. Cocoon is a great framework to build dynamic websites. It is XML based and transforms xml based files and data streams into HTML output, using XSLT. Cocoon is implemented in Java, off course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For sample Cocoon websites look at&lt;br /&gt;- Apache XML parser Xerces, which uses Forrest, a documentation framework based on Cocoon or&lt;br /&gt;- Apache Lenya, a CMS system build on Cocoon or&lt;br /&gt;- at my very own website for Conficio, which is a static output of Cocoon input.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Renaud will cover the following topics&lt;br /&gt;* The Apache Cocoon project: goals and history&lt;br /&gt;* 10'00 ft overview&lt;br /&gt;* Pipelines: where it all starts&lt;br /&gt;* Common components: generators, transformers and serializer&lt;br /&gt;* A minimal helloCocoon application&lt;br /&gt;* Advanced components&lt;br /&gt;* Lenya, an example of a complex Cocoon application &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Meetup will be hosted in the SupraShere office space (thanks, David!) at 87 Wendell St. in Post Office Sq., Boston. The closest T stations are South Station and Government Center. It's about a five minute walk from either Faneuil Hall or South Station.  From South Station in particular, you must walk up High St. toward the water, and the office is adjacent to International Place in between Franklin and High St. at the intersection of Batterymarch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=87+Wendell+St,+Boston,+MA+02110&amp;amp;spn=0.019794,0.028131&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to David: &amp;quot;there is no street sign. It's a small street in between High St. and Franklin St. between Broad St. and Battery March. If you are coming from South Station, you walk up High St., take a left on to Battery March, and it's the first street on the right.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kaj Kandler</member_name><member_id>1142521</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1124150937000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Java September Meetup</name><id>4749502</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1127170800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/4749502/</event_url></item>