<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>88 Beach St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.350986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6173388813</phone><name>Hei La Moon</name><city>Boston</city><id>669068</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059044</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Are you ready for dim sum? I am so let's enjoy good cheap eats. You can also order from the menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll gather outside at 10:45 then we'll head inside at 11:00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a helpful dim sum primer written by fellow BBLDer Pam Phillips; &lt;a href="http://home.comcast.net/~pam_phillips/TCC4335/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://home.comcast.n...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.heilamoon.com/menu_dim_sum.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hei La Moon Dim Sum Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: Call Hei La Moon 88 Beach Street 02111 (617) 338-8813 for advise, otherwise here are a few options.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Central Chinatown Garage * 86 Beach Street 02111 (617) 542-1549 above restaurant with validated parking though a little confusing.  You pay the parking garage attendant $11 upon entry and then take your parking ticket to Hei La Moon, where you pay another $3 to get your ticket stamped. As you exit the parking garage you give your stamped parking ticket back to the parking garage attendant who refunds your original payment....at least that is how it worked a few months ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Super 88 Market lot 8 AM til 7 PM  * 85 Essex St $10 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stanhope Garage lot 617 262 0691 * 33 Essex Street  (entrance corner of Essex St and Harrison St) $22 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bradford Auto Parks lot 617 423 2375 * 125 Essex Street (entrance on Kingston St) $10 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INTERPARK Shoppers Garage 617 426 7717 * 40 Beach St $10 cash &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Common Garage 617 954 2098 * 0 Charles St (bet Boylston St and Beacon St) $11&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hyatt Regency Hotel Parking (Pilgrim Lafayette Garage) (617) 723-1488 * 1 Av de Lafayette bet Chauncy St and Washington St) $14 credit card or cash (take your ticket to get validation stamp from Macy's gift wrap in basement for $4 discount pay cashier before you return to your vehicle)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION: Create your own train and/or bus route here &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Subway Stations are South Station and Chinatown&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POST DINING ACTIVITY OPTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1)  Burn off a few calories by walking around Chinatown and/or the Common.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2)  Check out a movie at AMC Loews - Boston Commons 19 located at 175 Tremont Street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RULES of Engagement:&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly. &lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis. &lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option. &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment explaining your situation. &lt;br /&gt;If the meal is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.* &lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event. &lt;br /&gt;If I change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied by final update event confirmation email deadline, it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event. &lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event. &lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event. &lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for THREE (3) events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST email me at snowrover@yahoo.com or call or text me at 617 445-7549. &lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining. &lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so, &lt;b&gt;rate the event and venue by completing surveys&lt;/b&gt; afterward. &lt;br /&gt;I will arrive at Hei La Moon by 10:45 AM to arrange seating as well as welcome you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292546169000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291607516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hei La Moon Dim Sum</name><id>15653060</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292169600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/15653060/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/b/global_20069371.jpeg</photo_url></item>