<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>351 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.767490</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 247-0998</phone><name>Mark Twain House &amp; Museum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>664323</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.701324</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well so what if I AM a Mark Twain fanatic?  Okay, but at least this one, as far as I can tell, has nothing to do with Tom Sawyer! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taken from the Mark Twain House Website, which also gives directions and more info: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.marktwainhouse.org/newsworx_published/newsworx_story_1242.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.marktwainh...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JULY 6, FREE!: WRITERS ON THE HARTFORD CIRCUS FIRE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Mark Twain House &amp;amp; Museum will mark the anniversary of Hartford’s tragic 1944 circus fire on Tuesday, July 6, at 6:30 p.m., with an airing of a CPTV documentary on the Big Top tragedy, followed by a panel at 7:30 p.m. made up of those who have written about the event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The authors taking part in the panel, &amp;quot;Telling a Tragic Tale: Writers on the Hartford Circus Fire&amp;quot; include novelist Mary-Ann Tirone Smith (Masters of Illusion); poet Paul Janeczko (Worlds Afire); and non-fiction authors Don Massey and Rick Davey, who traced the mystery of “Little Miss 1565,” a girl whose body had never been identified, in A Matter of Degree.  The program moderator will be Kathy Maher, Executive Director of the Barnum Museum in Bridgeport. There will be a book signing after the program. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An exhibition of circus fire artifacts curated by Curatorial Assistant Jeff Mainville will be on display in the Great Hall during the program and through July.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entire evening will be free to the public as part of a grant-funded program series collaboration with the Barnum Museum that jointly commemorates the centennial of Mark Twain’s death and the bi-centennial of P. T. Barnum’s birth.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278866994000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277933947000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WRITERS ON THE HARTFORD CIRCUS FIRE Mark Twain House</name><id>13964430</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278455400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13964430/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/6/global_16106886.jpeg</photo_url></item>