<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 Green St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810625</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 463-9009</phone><name>Mission Oak Grill</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>706310</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.873033</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The comedy event is hosted by Friar’s Club semi finalist Susan Alexander and will feature performances by Bethany Van Delft from the Boston comedy festival, Maria Ciampa, Jesse Baade and Ellen Moschetto. The tour brings a line up of five women having varied ethnic backgrounds and comedic types. The tour is refined yet quirky. These laugh inducing women show off their unique points of view as they engage the audience with their offbeat life stories and opinions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “The 5 Funny Females Comedy Tour is a perfect concept to raise funds for the YWCA, as their mission is to empower women and eliminate racism”, says show producer Lisa Knight. “The tour has partnered with the YWCA several times within the last year as a fundraiser for the organization. The comedienne’s look forward to another great show.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5 Funny Females take the stage on Saturday, May 9th at 8 PM. Doors will open at 7 pm. There will be a cash bar is available. Mission Oak Grill is located at 26 Green Street in Newburyport, MA. Tickets are general admission and cost $25.  They can be purchased online today at www.drinkwaterproductions.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340338371000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>women-303</urlname><id>472102</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Girls Night Out Shopping Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239677502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5 Funny Females Comedy Tour</name><id>10180153</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241910000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/women-303/events/10180153/</event_url></item>