<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>29 Upham St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.529000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>812-240-3236</phone><name>Liv and David's House</name><city>Salem</city><id>1130885</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.902600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Unwind from your work day with some word games. We'll have Scrabble, Lexigon, Word on the Street, Boggle, Quiddler, and Snatch-It. If you have another favorite, please bring it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With an 8:00 start time, this Meetup starts a little later than most  of our events. We're trying to figure out what time works the best now  that we have two little ones in the house. We're hoping the big one will  be on her way to bed as people are arriving. Because of the late start  time, we'll make sure we have a game out ready to play right away (as  normally, if we start a Meetup at 7:00, with all of the chatting, we  don't start playing a game until nearly 8:00 anyway).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to bring a favorite snack for    the evening. We'll have plenty to drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who have never  attended a traditional game night, we   usually split up in different  rooms or areas to play smaller games of   players' choice and then come  together for a larger game or two at the   end of the night. However,  sometimes we just play large party games  for  the majority of the  evening. It depends on the mood of the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You should know  that we are a household with cats (one of whom is   the  Official Cat of Salem!), but they will be locked up for the   evening. The  house is also home to a hopefully well-behaved 2 year old,   who will  obviously not be locked up for the evening, but she will be   in bed for the later part of the Meetup. We also have an infant, who   isn't much of a game player, as he just eats and sleeps all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it  is tight. There is   generally more parking available toward Orne St., and  more parking is   available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306194832000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303074297000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Word Game Night</name><id>17337780</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305936000000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/17337780/</event_url></item>