<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Pre-Registration</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for members, $15 non-memb</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Self Storage Profits&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turning the Key Monthly Meeting by ForeclosuresMass.com.  Thursday, March 5th at 6:30  pm in Dedham, Mass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/blog/2009/03/why-is-self-storage-being-touted-as-the-hottest-sector-of-commercial-real-estate.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Check out this sneak peak interview with Scott!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If all of the books, tapes, CDs courses, seminars, boot camps that all of the Real Estate Investing gurus sell actually worked, then why are you still not making the kind of money you want to make? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Meyers asked himself that same question when he was teetering on the verge of bankruptcy while managing a portfolio of over 400 tenants and toilets.  Scott went on to discover Self Storage and why it's the hottest sector in Commercial Real Estate that almost no one has ever heard about. He now owns several properties and thousands of units located several hundred miles apart, and he manages them all remotely with the aid of the internet and self service kiosks!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott is living proof that you can start with no experience, credit or cash using his 6 steps to creating wealth with self storage system. It truly is a turn key real estate investing business in a box! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Specifically, Scott is going to cover: &lt;br /&gt;His Top 10 reasons why he chose to dump all of his tenants and toilets&lt;br /&gt;How he developed a system that made him a Self Storage Millionaire&lt;br /&gt;What technology he uses to automate his Self Storage Empire&lt;br /&gt;The techniques and processes he uses to streamline his operation&lt;br /&gt;How he put together his first Self Storage deal&lt;br /&gt;What he did to grow his portfolio. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our March 5th Turning the Key meeting, Scott will be joining us for a content-packed education event and sharing his 6 steps to creating wealth with self storage systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seating is Limited; Pre-registration is HIGHLY recommended&lt;br /&gt;$45 at the Door (no exceptions)•$15 for Pre-Registrations&lt;br /&gt;•$10 for Pre-Registered Members&lt;br /&gt;FREE for TTK Pass Holders and TTK Auto Pay Subscribers&lt;br /&gt;Call 617.275.4800   or   visit www.ForeclosuresMass.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3372062</member_name><member_id>3372062</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kirsten, ForeclosuresMass</member_name><member_id>6575727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238712908000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233880643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ForeclosuresMass' Turning the Key Networking/Education Event March Meetup</name><id>9683334</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236295800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/9683334/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/3/c/global_791180.jpeg</photo_url></item>