<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20, newman avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02916</zip><lat>41.841282</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>avenue n american kitchen</name><city>rumford</city><id>3465242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Avenue N, located in East Providence (Rumford area) in the Rumford Center complex&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, I admit it. Uncharacteristically I've been here twice and really like it. Not that I don't &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; places, but that I've been here twice BEFORE making it an official MNM. Avenue N has great food and drinks, and is always a little crowded which is why I've hesitated. However, the last time I was here I spoke with the owner/chef and he assured me that on Mondays the bar is mostly open. SO here we go, its time to share!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avenue N is one of the only bistro restaurants in Rumford. As a matter of fact it probably IS the only one which is why its so popular. It has a great contemporary bistro atmosphere and a large marble bar which is perfect for the MNM. The food is diverse so there is something for every palette, and truthfully, I LOVE the Bourbon Hayride cocktail. Also Chef Nick Rabar is&amp;nbsp; host of &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Chef 2 Go"&lt;/em&gt; on the Cox network, which you may have seen as you've perused the channels&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; Its a great show that highlights local restaurants and fresh food suppliers. If you've been already, then you know, and if you haven't, then here's your chance and let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328404193000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327176641000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Avenue N!!!!!</name><id>49051622</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327964400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/49051622/</event_url></item>