<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Middlesex Fells WEST side walk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:30 in the Sheepfold parking located on Route 28. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the south on 93 take exit 33 to 28 North. Go about 1 mile on 28 N and look for the Sheepfold sign on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North on 93 take exit 35 to Rte 28 South. From the exit ramp you will turn left and go under 93, then make an immediate right. Go about 1200 ft and turn Right on to 28 South. Go about a half mile on 28 S and look for the sheepfold sign on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See the map on this link:&lt;br /&gt;lot.&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/maps/fells.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will go for lunch at:&lt;br /&gt;Felicia's of North End&lt;br /&gt;423 Main St (Rte 28)&lt;br /&gt;Stoneham 02180&lt;br /&gt;781-438-9399&lt;br /&gt;(I have a reservation for 12)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need a ride please ask for one in your rsvp, saying what area you are in.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Middlesex Fells Reservation's 2,575 acres offer a welcome retreat for city dwellers and a suitable terrain for hikers, horseback riders, rock climbers, cross-country skiers and picnickers as well as natural and cultural history buffs. &amp;quot;Fells&amp;quot; is the Saxon word for rocky, hilly tracts of land - an apt name for this scenic area which is rich in local history. This picturesque area was once favored for timber, granite quarrying, ice industry, and water power for the many mills including one that manufactured some of the first vulcanized rubber products.&lt;br /&gt;The Botume House at 4 Woodland Road is the Middlesex Fells Headquarters and will soon house the Middlesex Fells Visitor Center.&lt;br /&gt;Special features for visitors include the Sheepfold picnic area, Bellevue Pond, Virginia Wood, and Spot Pond. The Sheepfold is 10 acres of open field, ideal for picnics, frisbee playing and informal games. Bellevue Pond is a seasonal pond surrounded by trails and wide fire roads, some leading up to Wrights Tower which looks out over the Boston Basin. Virginia Wood, the site of a vanished mill village called &amp;quot;Haywardville&amp;quot; is now a dense hemlock enclave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spot Pond&lt;br /&gt;Spot Pond is a picturesque body of water, centrally located in the Middlesex Fells, just east of Routes 28 and 93. With a surface area of 340 acres, and a capacity of 1.8 billion gallons of water, it serves as a backup reservoir to the Quabbin, located in central Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;The area was first explored by Governor Winthrop and his men in the winter of 1632: &lt;br /&gt;...they came to a very great pond, having in the midst an island of about one acre and very thick with trees of pine and beech and the pond had divers small rocks standing up here and there in it, which therefore called Spot Pond.&amp;quot; (quote from Gov. Winthrop's private papers) &lt;br /&gt;Spot Pond Boating offers sailing, kayak, canoe and rowboat rental from Memorial Day through Labor Day. Sailing lessons are provided throughout the season as well&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185201080000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183684278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middlesex Fells WEST side walk</name><id>5980783</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185028200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5980783/</event_url></item>