<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 Sumner Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.152466</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lucky Dogs Day Care</name><city>Milford</city><id>4046092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.519142</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Channeling that famous boxer exuberance into a super-fun ALL Boxer Basic Obedience Class!....... This is a formal, 7 week course beginning Saturday, November 5th at 10:00a at Lucky Dogs Day Care in Milford, MA. (Week one: handlers ONLY. Bring your dog to all consecutive classes)............. Topics to include ALL of your basic obedience cues - loose-leash walking, focus, sit, down, wait, stay, drop it, leave it, come - PLUS specific coursework geared toward this playful, goofy, energetic and fun breed! Ways to channel that exuberance &amp;amp; energy; games; play-training........... Cost is $250, paid up front in advance, and space is limited. Price includes access to private practice workshops............... Open to dogs 16 weeks and up. Whether they have never been in a formal class before or are brushing up on their obedience/distraction work, if you have a boxer or boxer mix, this is the class for you.............. Call April at (508) 634-3037 to sign up. Email justcassie101@gmail.com with any questions............... See my listing here: &lt;a href="http://www.thumbtack" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thumbtack&lt;/a&gt;..... Also available for private in-home training and other group classes. (&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/cassiestock" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/cassiestock&lt;/a&gt;). Barbara Jean Crehan, our executive director, is also NEBBC endorsed, a 12-year veteran dog trainer, and can be reached at bjcrehan88@hotmail.com for private in-home consultations/training. Find her on facebook here: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.c" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.c&lt;/a&gt;.... We are also preparing to welcome our very own Lorena Lacasse, vice president of the NEBBC to our training staff! She can be reached at newenglandbullybreedclub@gmail.com............ Hope to see you on November 5th!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321114781000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boxer Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boxer-340</urlname><id>1175534</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Massachusetts Boxer Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318983613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ALL Boxer Basics Obedience Class w/Cassie-Leigh Stock at Lucky Dogs Day Care</name><id>37894042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321110000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boxer-340/events/37894042/</event_url></item>