<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;What: Driving Range - Golf - Fore Seasons Driving Range&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: August 30, 2009 @ 11:00 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:&lt;br /&gt;Fore Seasons Driving Range&lt;br /&gt;306 Whiting Street&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA &lt;br /&gt;781-741-8305&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 4, Max of 16 members &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: NONE, members only&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2 event fee &lt;br /&gt;Annual Members - FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bucket of Balls:&lt;br /&gt;   Medium          $7.50&lt;br /&gt;   Large             $10.50&lt;br /&gt;   Extra Large    $12.50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   $2.00 for grass T&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Everyone - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In keeping with the golfing theme, let's try out the golf range this time and wack some balls.  This meetup let's head off to Hingham and the Fore Seasons Driving Range.  Maybe others will be able to join us with this event being on a weekend or Sunday, August 30th @ 11:00 am meeting outside the pro shop.  If anyone needs to borrow clubs, the range can provide them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How many?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a minimum of 4 Participants (Non-organizers) by noon on Thursday, August 27th.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Susan (AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadlines: The Final Deadline is Noon on Thursday, August 27th. Please be mindful if you change your RSVP to NO at the last minute that you may be taking a spot away from someone else that is serious about participating. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to arrive about 5-10 minutes early to get everyone situated.  No Guests for this meet-up as demand is high and space is limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SSFMG and its organizers are not responsible for any injuries to participants or damage to equipment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather Alternative: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;None. This event will be canceled if it is raining or too foggy. We will do our best to cancel at least 6 hours in advance but we cannot control Mother Nature so we will do our best to notify everyone at least 3 hours prior to the event. Please do not change your RSVP based on weather forecasts. We check weather forecasts the night before and use those to determine if the event is canceled.  Please check your email (or the Event Page) Saturday night or Sunday morning to determine event status.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool: There is no carpool for this event. Members should meet at the Fore Season Driving Range. If you would like to carpool you may note where from in your RSVP comment and someone else may choose to contact you if they are also interested in carpooling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.yahoo.com/info-10138912-fore-seasons-golf-hingham" target="_blank"&gt;Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the Pro-shop</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>8338847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251935192000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250113330000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Driving Range - Golf</name><id>11098088</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251644400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11098088/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/2/global_10166418.jpeg</photo_url></item>