<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>560 Albany Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.338455</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Future Chefs</name><city>Boston</city><id>10104482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066521</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Want to bring healthy, local foods into your kitchen, and stay on-budget, too?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the cooler weather and shorter days upon us, you might think there are no fresh veggies available at farmers markets, but instead, they're bursting with colorful greens, root vegetables and winter squashes. Learn to make the most of the abundant produce available in New England!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The workshop will cover time-saving ways to prepare delicious meals with recipes from The Farmer’s Kitchen. We’ll talk about how to store your produce and basic cooking techniques to get the best flavor. Join Julia for a discussion and Q&amp;amp;A, complete with recipes, ideas and a healthy dose of delicious fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instructor Julia Shanks received her professional training as a chef at the California Culinary Academy in San Francisco. She is the co-author of “The Farmer’s Kitchen,” a localvore cookbook that details preparing, storing, and eating local food throughout the four seasons. Her book was cited as a reference in Michelle Obama’s “American Grown.” She is a local Cambridge, MA resident, and current board member of Future Chefs, a non-profit that prepares urban youth in Greater Boston for quality early employment and post-secondary education opportunities in the culinary field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register Here: &lt;a href="http://www.nofamass.org/events/perennial-chef-cooking-healthy-and-local-all-year-round#.UJKzx4a0z8k" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.nofamass.org/events/perennial-chef-cooking-healthy-and-local-all-year-round#.UJKzx4a0z8k&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produce for the event will be generously donated by Boston Organics, a local Boston based business that delivers organic produce right to your door!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Costs: &lt;br /&gt;

$30 NOFA Members &lt;br /&gt;

$40 General Public&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or comments, please contact Drew Love by email at drew@nofamass.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>6980975</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355083734000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351791679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Perennial Chef: Cooking Healthy and Local all Year Long with Julia Shanks</name><id>89497042</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355076000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/89497042/</event_url></item>