<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>121 Essex St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522367</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 745-5656</phone><name>The Old Spot</name><city>Salem</city><id>870689</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.890700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Forget those expensive dinners and red roses....let's get together for a tasty pub dinner at the cosy Old Spot pub in Salem at 6 pm followed by a great Celtic music concert starting at 7.30 pm at the Tabernacle Church on Washington St (in Salem a short drive or maybe a walk away) where we'll hear a range of talented Celtic musicians including singer Michael O'Leary and David O'Docherty(whistle), Jen (fiddle) and Bob Strom(guitar) and many more.  This evening which is called Shamrock for HAWC is also an annual fundraiser (HAWC is the excellent organization which provides services for abused women and children) and last year the music was so good they put out a CD after the event. Be a part of the action this year! Entry to the concert is by donation and suggested minimum is $15. Have fun and support a good cause at the same time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: If you'd rather skip the pub and meet at the concert, you can do that..if you'd rather go to the pub and skip the concert you can do that instead! Let me know your plans!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Table in the restaurant - red scarf</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238885916000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>North Shore Brits &amp; Euros</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Brits-Euros-Singles-group</urlname><id>1354184</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Brits &amp; Euros</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233806608000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celtic UnValentine's night: guinness and live Celtic concert!</name><id>9677458</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234652400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Brits-Euros-Singles-group/events/9677458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/6/9/global_6885433.jpeg</photo_url></item>