<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1904 Canton Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.223400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 333-0690</phone><name>Blue Hills Trailside Museum</name><city>Milton</city><id>669267</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Why not start your weekend off great with a workout in the beautiful Blue hills instead of on the Stairmaster machine? &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll start on the red dot trail - challenging rugged, rocky loops over hilly terrain - until we reach the Observation Tower.  Here we will stop for a short break and take pleasure in some fantastic views of the Boston city skyline and surrounding area.  We’ll finish up on the woodland green dot trail to enjoy the natural beauty of the reservation.  The hike will take approximately 2 hours, depending on the pace.  This event is for advanced beginner/moderate hikers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Blue Hills Trailside Museum – 1904 Canton Ave, Milton, MA 02186&lt;br /&gt;Take Rt I-93 to exit 2B (Milton, Rt 138 North). Follow the exit ramp to the first set of traffic lights. Go straight through the lights and the parking lot is 0.5 miles ahead on the right. The museum is at the end of the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough water (very important) and wear sturdy sneakers/hiking boots.  Also, consider bringing a snack, sunscreen, bug spray, sunglasses and a hat.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer O</member_name><member_id>8579834</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280153251000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279505633000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday morning hike in the Blue Hills</name><id>14141779</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279976400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/14141779/</event_url></item>