<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This movie will be hosted by Susan and will be shown at the MFA.  The following is a description from their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Private Fears in Public Places by Alain Resnais (Coeurs, France, 2006, 120 min.). Collaborating once again with British playwright Alan Ayckbourn, French new wave director Alain Resnais sets this film against a snow-laden Paris, where six lonely souls suddenly find there lives interconnecting. Thierry, a real estate agent is smitten with his dutiful assistant Charlotte, who moonlights as a home-care attendant for the hell-raising father of a widowed bartender named Lionel. Lionel, who works at a stylish modern hotel bar is frequented by an embittered recently discharged army vet, who takes refuge in alcohol to escape life and a troubled relationship with his fiancée, Nicole. Resnaisâ??s film explores how these situations evolve over the course of a few days, ultimately leading these characters to confront their personal fears as they connect with those around them. French with English subtitles.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MFA members, seniors, and students $8; general admission $9.  Tickets may be purchased ahead of time at mfa.org; click on &amp;quot;tickets&amp;quot; and scroll to Events and Classes Tickets and click on &amp;quot;click here to purchase tickets;&amp;quot;  then in the drop down box select &amp;quot;film&amp;quot; and click on &amp;quot;Private Fears in Public Places&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;If you are planning on driving to the museum, you can get info on directions and parking by clicking on &amp;quot;visit&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;getting here.&amp;quot;  Just to let you know, the museum parking lot will close at 10:30 that night which will only give you about 45 minutes after the movie ends.  So perhaps street parking might be a better choice unless you don't plan to go out with the group after the movie.   Public transportation can solve the parking problem, of course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will hold up the &amp;quot;Meetup&amp;quot; sign at the front right side of the theatre after the film.  Then we'll go somewhere nearby to discuss where you can enjoy some refreshments too.  I'm looking forward to meeting up with the group and having some intriguing conversation.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180457214000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179341157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French film "Private Fears in Public Places"</name><id>5784967</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180136700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5784967/</event_url></item>