<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's been awhile since we've had an early morning eye-opener at the MFA!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Three Gorges Dam when complete will be the world's largest hydro-electric power station in the world. 1.5 million people will be relocated, many from small villages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Still Life&lt;/b&gt; by Jia Zhang-Ke (The World, Unknown Pleasures, and Platform) was shot on location during the flooding of the Three Gorges Dam. A meditative work merging documentary with fiction, the film produces a painterly narrative. Jia's digital camera lingers on the dangerous exploits of the workers and incredible terrain, but also follows the stories of a man who returns to look for the wife he abandoned, and a woman looking for the husband who forsook her years ago. Alternately apocalyptic and otherworldly (watch for an unexpected space encounter), this massive construction zone?the hydroelectric project will relocate 1.2 million people?has become an emblematic site of sacrifice where nature is forced to make way for a technocratic China.  MFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Still Life&lt;/b&gt; is a dazzling addition to a series of films contemplating the state of contemporary China. Shot in crystalline high-def, the movie tracks the progress of two lost souls through the rapidly altering landscape of Fengje, a town that has literally been swallowed up by progress. Philadelphia City Paper&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gradually vanishing under rising water levels as a result of the nation's mammoth Three Gorges Dam project, it is a transitory landscape that beautifully evokes the existential malaise?the helpless feeling of spiritual drowning?that so many of Jia's characters find themselves locked in. The film's stunning opening shot, a capricious lateral sprawl aboard a ferry slogging down the Yangtze River, challenges the English title's suggestion of painterly gentility. Despite Jia's superb compositional skills and the characters' stalled lives, this is less a film of static poses than one of mysterious movements, aware of the impermanence of connections and the ruthless push of time.   Slant Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those unconvinced, here is a link to a complete review: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.villagevoice.com/film/0803,hoberman,78844,20.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.villagevoi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film's conclusion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202779125000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Still Life from China</name><id>7313285</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204990200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7313285/</event_url></item>