<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01373</zip><lat>42.477718</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-397-2190</phone><name>Alina's Ristorante</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>1430476</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.608934</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Everyone I know who has gone to Alina's Restaurant in Deerfield has raved about the food. I have been there for appetizers and I can truly say they were melt in your mouth delicious!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chef Martin is a wonderful, caring man who is very excited to host us that evening and it's a great way to kick off the upcoming holiday season with friends old and new.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nestled in the center of South Deerfield, former location of Sienna’s Restaurant, Alina’s offers Italian Cuisine with a Mediterranean flair.  Head chef and owner, Martin Amaya, formerly executive chef at &lt;br /&gt;Carmelina’s, has opened his own restaurant. “I wanted to have a place of my own, where I can create and serve my favorite dishes and incorporate my family with me”, says Amaya.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An interesting little piece from Russelnod.com [local food blog]: &lt;a href="http://www.russelnod.com/2010/05/14/alinas-ristorante-in-south-deerfield/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.russelnod....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and here from the reviews:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TripAdvisor: &lt;i&gt;I have enjoyed numerous dinners at Alina's and it is always a delight to the senses! From the delicious Martinis to the exquisite entrees I can't wait to go back again to try yet another creation from Chef Martin. The servers have always been friendly and the atmosphere is elegant and warm. I continue to be a devoted fan and now measure other restaurants' offerings against Alina's stellar fare - however, few have met my expectations. My recommendations: Lobster Ravioli or stuff aged sirloin &amp;amp; the Michelangelo Chianti.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;bon apetit...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jessica &amp;amp; Christine&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291823010000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289916501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Fabulous and Underrated Alina's in Deerfield!</name><id>15463911</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291764600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/15463911/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/c/global_19686828.jpeg</photo_url></item>