<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Kingston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353630</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 482-6282 </phone><name>Kingston Station </name><city>Boston</city><id>705312</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059048</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The big winner is Petropolis, by Anya Ulinich.  I knew nothing about this book prior to its being suggested, and I'm very interested to get started on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Petropolis-Anya-Ulinich/dp/B001G8WRWO/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1269802814&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION:  Kingston Station&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Amazon.com / Booklist:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;When a coming-of-age novel is truly different, it can send shock waves through unsuspecting readers. This brave blend of satire, farce, and heart-wrenching realism delivers the necessary voltage to do just that. First-novelist Ulinich sets out as if she intends to lampoon the whole idea of coming-of-age. Teenager Sasha Goldberg, a pudgy parody of the archetypal outsider, is a mixed-race Russian Jew living with her mother in a mining camp called Asbestos 2, once a Stalinist model town but now a postglasnost embarrassment. When your entire universe, internal and external, needs escaping from, the very notion of escape becomes a bad joke. So it is for Sasha (&amp;quot;For a Jew, you sure look like a Negro,&amp;quot; one of her friends tells her), whose every attempt at escape leads to an even more absurd reality than the one she left behind. A furtive romance results in pregnancy, but when her mother usurps the baby, Sasha decamps to America as a mail-order bride, landing in Arizona with an old-school husband whose Crown Victoria &amp;quot;is as long as Sasha Goldberg's whole life.&amp;quot; From there it's off to Chicago, where, as the &amp;quot;pet Soviet Jew&amp;quot; of a rich Orthodox couple, Sasha trades one kind of servitude for another. One more escape lands our heroine in Brooklyn, in search of her father, who abandoned the family when she was an infant. Ulinich plays this absurdist immigrant's journey for all its black-comedic potential, but she never loses sight of Sasha's bedrock humanity. Her triumphs are attenuated at every turn by lingering levels of despair, but her ability to find a pulse of life in even the most outrageous turns of fortune lifts the novel as far beyond parody as it is beyond convention. Bill Ott  Copyright © American Library Association. All rights reserved --This text refers to the Hardcover edition.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272580781000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266779354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston readers: April meeting:  Petropolis, by Anya Ulinich</name><id>12664614</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272407400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/12664614/</event_url></item>