<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>345 Somerville Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.381008</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>PA's Lounge</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1213917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099039</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;STARTING&lt;/i&gt; OPEN MIC AGAIN, Live Music, Networking&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;STARTING OPEN MIC AGAIN&lt;/b&gt;.  We have found a place to restart the OPEN MIC.  Party with Free Live Music in Union Square at PA's Lounge  - 345 Somerville ave, Somerville MA - across and down a little towards the Square from Bull McCabes.  This will be for next Wed.  There are a few other possible places for the OPen Mic and we are working out the details.  We may change days.  Please send your feedback if Sunday late afternoon to mid evening is a good time for you, or if not when.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention Party goers,  Musicians, &amp;amp; Singers!!  Come join the party at the Wed Night Open mike! Everyone Welcome. No cover charge - Play music solo or with backing band. All instruments and styles welcome.  Originals, covers, blues, jazz, classic rock, R&amp;amp;B, Motown, folk, etc.   Back up band with drums, bass, guitar, and Songlist for singers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great opportunity to further your music experience and career, jam with other musicians, play solo, play originals, and network.  The goal is to have everyone play as much as possible.  &lt;u&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please come to check this out, have a drink and support this for your Music Guild even if you don't play tonight.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  This is a combined meetup of 3 music groups and sometimes 1, 2 or more other social groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can bring song sheets for your songs on one page that will facilitate playing.  SINGERS WELCOME!!  If you want to be play with accompanying bass /lead/harmony try to come early at 7PM and bring about 4 copies of 2 or 3 songs you want to play on 1 sheet per song if possible, so we can all play it.   If you are playing at semi-professional level and are playing solo or don't need to rehearse, just come to the open mike.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285200775000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277923548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RESTARTING OPEN MIC </name><id>jwnxnynmbdc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285196400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/14822199/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>