<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>26 Beacon Street</address_2><address_1>Clubhouse</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.504818</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beacon Village Apartments</name><city>Burlington</city><id>867158</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.195610</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>FOR BEGINNERS wanting to learn the basics of your digital camera and digital photography! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Digital cameras have an intimidating array of features and controls which can be confusing.  Professional photographer &lt;a href="http://www.splainephotography.com/biography.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dan Splaine of Test of Time Studios in Nashua, NH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will be leading two BEGINNER workshops designed to get you familiar with your digital camera, help you make better pictures and provide an overview of your camera controls and how they impact your photographs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dan has been offering workshops in his Nashua studio for a while and has agreed to come down to our neck of the woods to offer these workshops for our group.  He has a teaching style which presents the topics below in a way that makes them easy to understand and apply to your photography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Beginner - Part TWO&amp;quot; is the second of two workshops being offered in November. &lt;i&gt; (See November 11th for Part ONE info)&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;In this class&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, we dig a little deeper into camera functions and picture taking situations. The emphasis is to give you more control over your results and to help you become more deliberate in your shooting technique. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics discussed will be:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- Exposure compensation&lt;br /&gt;-- Equivalent exposures&lt;br /&gt;-- Metering techniques&lt;br /&gt;-- Focus control and DOF (Depth of field)&lt;br /&gt;-- White Balance&lt;br /&gt;-- Perspective control/optical effects&lt;br /&gt;-- Understanding resolution/file formats&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once we cover the role of these topics we will show how to apply them to general subjects and common shooting situations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Techniques we will cover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- Camera holding methods&lt;br /&gt;-- Camera supports&lt;br /&gt;-- Lens selection / zooming&lt;br /&gt;-- Timing your shot/anticipating action&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come to class with your camera, owner's manual, memory cards and charged batteries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;PAYMENT INFORMATION:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workshop fee for a single session is $35.00.  We will offer a discount of $10 if you sign up and pay for both at once.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow the Paypal payment link below to pay for one workshop at $35.00 or both workshops at $60.00.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you choose to sign up for both sessions, &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;please also visit the other workshop date (see November 11)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to send your RSVP through for that workshop as well.  We'll match the payment on our end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;PAYMENT via Paypal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Please contact the organizer (Dianne) for a link to make your payment via Paypal. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;REGISTRATION NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to keep the workshop slots filled and to clear anyone potentially on the wait list, all payments must be received at least two days before the workshop date - &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;deadline November 16th&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  Unless other arrangements are made with the organizer, any reservation not paid for by the deadline date is subject to being dropped and replaced.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are on the wait list, please keep an eye on your email between November 16-18 to see if you're cleared from the wait list.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on the success of these two workshops, we will consider running them again throughout the winter months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CLASS NOTES:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This class if for BEGINNERS shooting with a DSLR or Point-and-Shoot cameras.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Digital Photography for Beginners - Part Two is scheduled for November 18, 2009 - Enroll for both to cover all of the basics for making digital photos.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on the success of these two workshops, we will consider running them again during the winter months.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions and contact will be sent out to "yes" RSVPs by November 9th</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>5274985</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258760351000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256669164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Digital Photography Basics:  Beginner - Part TWO</name><id>11725004</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258587000000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/11725004/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/3/global_11491139.jpeg</photo_url></item>