<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Cambridge Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>588384</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Testing is tightly integrated with the Grails experience, and rightfully so. Most users may only ever use JUnit, unaware of the useful alterntives out there. To that end, three of our members will give presentations that focus on some of these alternatives:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bob Hermann will discuss geb, a browser automation testing framework based on WebDriver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Jeff Winkler will show us continuous testing with Grails - running unit tests for changes automatically in the background&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Dan Durkin will present Spock, the specification testing language&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each talk should last 20-30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, due to massive interest, our next meetup will be held in Kendall Square, instead of our usual location in Newton. I'm pretty excited about this... we'll be in the auditorium of the Broad Institute. The Broad Institute is on Main St between Vassar and Ames streets. You can see it on a map at this location. The meeting will be in the Auditorium which is on the ground floor near the entrance. Special thanks to Dan Durkin who secured the space for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you all there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Pember</member_name><member_id>9587085</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337304457000</updated><rating><average>4.26999998093</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Grails-Boston</urlname><id>1458975</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Grails Users' Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331909694000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Groovy Testing: Beyond JUnit</name><id>56602852</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332974700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Grails-Boston/events/56602852/</event_url></item>