<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Richard S. Lindzen, Alfred P. Sloan Professor of Atmospheric Science at MIT, member of the National Academy of Sciences. Sunday, April 22 - 6:30 p.m. to 8:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Old South Meeting House &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our planet has become warmer in recent decades, and there is a growing chorus claiming that the consequences will be disastrous. However, some still remain unconvinced that carbon caps and similar regulatory measures will help the situation. Does the cost of regulation outweigh the damage of inaction? Should the United States government take dramatic public policy steps? Should we brace for stronger hurricanes, invasions of tropical diseases, and significant increases in sea levels, or is the danger overstated? &lt;br /&gt;Prof. Richard Lindzen steps into the fray to offer his view that irrational alarm may be clouding our judgment. Join us for tonight?s discussion as we explore what the future holds for our planet and what we should do about it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This program is part of the Ford Hall Forum?s continuing series on environmental issues. It is presented in collaboration with the Old South Meeting House as part of the Partners in Public Dialogue Series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion afterward; Location TBD &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177454255000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176848718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Is Global Warming a Cause For Alarm? Lecture and Discussion</name><id>5680814</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177281000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/5680814/</event_url></item>