<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(2009) Director: Duncan Jones, Screenplay by Nathan Parker, based on a story by Duncan Jones. Cast: Sam Rockwell, Kevin Spacey, Dominique McElligott.&lt;br /&gt;First time director Duncan Jones, son of futuristic rocker David Bowie, tells that his father introduced him early on to the novels of George Orwell and great science fiction classics from Alien to The Man Who Fell to Earth. It's no wonder that Jones' new vision of humans in space, which was filmed at Britain's Shepperton Studios with models instead of CGI animation, would turn out to be haunting, unique, and unforgettable. Sam Rockwell (Confessions of a Dangerous Mind) plays an astronaut who toils on the dark side of the moon, mining materials that have solved our energy problems on earth. It is a lonely existence, with only his computer (voiced by Kevin Spacey) for companionship...until he is greeted by what appears to be a younger version of himself. Moon was not only a hit at the recent Sundance Film Festival, it was screened by enthusiastic scientists at NASA. &amp;quot;The beauty of science fiction is its open canvas. It doesn't have to be laser battles and things exploding...&amp;quot; Duncan Jones. 97 min. Admission is $8, or $7 for Friends of Cinestudio, Seniors over 60, or students or faculty with ID.&lt;br /&gt;____________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there around 7:15 pm in the front entrance.  I have glasses,, a ponytail and a smile.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250206515000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249350707000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moon</name><id>11028516</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249860600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11028516/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>