<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will ride for a couple of hours each day, doing the western end on Saturday and the eastern end on Sunday. Both rides will begin and and in the parking lot at the entrance to Nickerson. &lt;br /&gt;The Staruday ride will begin at 11:00 since many people will be arriving from &lt;br /&gt;Boston. The Sunday ride will begin at 10:00. You may join us for any portion &lt;br /&gt;of the weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to camp at Nickerson for the weekend you should try to make reservations now. Some of us will opt instead for a nearby bed and breakfast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nickerson State Park&lt;br /&gt;Rte. 6A, Brewster &lt;br /&gt;508 896-3491&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/d.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions &lt;br /&gt;Nickerson State Park is located in southeastern Massachusetts on the mid-Cape, near Brewster. &lt;br /&gt;From Boston: take Rte. 3 south to the Sagamore Bridge, then Rte. 6 to exit 12 in Orleans, turn left off the ramp onto Rte. 6A West towards Brewster. Continue for about 2 miles. Park Entrance is on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cape Cod Rail Trail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cape Cod Rail Trail follows a former railroad right-of-way for 22 miles through the towns of Dennis, Harwich, Brewster, Orleans, Eastham and Wellfleet. Its paved surface, few hills, and well-marked automobile crossings make it ideal for cyclists. The trail has a wide unpaved shoulder on one side to accommodate horseback riding, walkers, and runners. &lt;br /&gt;There are many opportunities to get off the trail and visit a beach. Food and water are also readily available and public restrooms can be found at Nickerson State Park, Salt Pond Visitors Center at Cape Cod National Seashore and the National Seashore Headquarters. If you do not have a bike, bike rentals are available at many points along the way. For people with disabilities, a limited number of hand-cycles are available for rent at specific bike concessions. For more information call Nickerson State Park at 508-896-3491.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/d.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/d.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248706333000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238329862000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Cod Cycling weekend</name><id>10061128</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248533100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10061128/</event_url></item>