<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please note the start time is 7:25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Page Turner&amp;quot;  is a psychological thriller, which the French seem to do so well. A tale of revenge  set in the Parisian world of classical music performance, a young working-class girl's audition for a prestigious school is ruined by a careless slip by one of the judges. The story picks up ten years later. Most of the favorable reviews note how understated this film is. The director, Denis Dercourt, was solo viola with the French Symphony Orchestra from 1988 to 1993.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dercourt's cool, extremely elegant and often witty film remains admirably ambiguous until the very final scenes, and even then the script wisely forgoes tying up too many loose ends. It's a meticulous piece of work, beautifully shot by Jérôme Peyrebrune, and assembled with a proper understanding of music and the important role it can play in people's lives&amp;quot; London Time Out &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;a fine example of the excellence of French genre film right now: A dark tale of revenge with an inscrutable heart, ice in its veins and an electric undercurrent of eroticism, it also might be the best-photographed picture I've seen so far this year.&amp;quot; Salon.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, as is the custom,  I will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177533420000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176159891000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Subtle French Thriller- The Page Turner</name><id>5653579</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177198200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5653579/</event_url></item>