<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This program has 2 shorts and one feature length film. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Short One is an animated tale of adultery between a beetle and a grasshopper.  (shot in 1912).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Short Two (shot in 1924) is a sci-fi animation, ridiculing the &amp;quot;Martian proletariat&amp;quot; - can't make this stuff up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The feature, &amp;quot; A Spectre Haunts Europe&amp;quot; , is a Soviet interpretation of Poe's &amp;quot; The Masque of the Red Death&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A bit obscure- yes! A bit fun- definitely! Plus the live piano accompaniment is always magnificent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And yes, here is a review of the 1922 feature:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Europe&lt;br /&gt;( Prizrak brodit po Yevrope ) &lt;br /&gt;USSR 1922. &lt;br /&gt;Director: Vladimir Gardin &lt;br /&gt;Cast: Zoya Barantsevich, Oleg Frelikh, Vasili Kovrigin, Iona Talanov &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revolutionary politics and a classic horror tale mix in this rare 1922 silent feature, which takes its title from the opening line of Marx's The Communist Manifesto but actually adapts (rather loosely) Edgar Allan Poe's The Masque of the Red Death. Facing the threat of revolution, the emperor of an imaginary country seeks exile in a distant corner of his realm. He meets and falls in love with the beautiful Elka, daughter of a revolutionary who has been banished there due to his political activities. The empress, meanwhile, embarks on a love affair of her own, while the emperor begins to have nightmares in which murder-minded revolutionaries are storming his palace. A Spectre Haunts Europe was directed by Vladimir Gardin, a leading actor and filmmaker who was also active in the pre-Revolutionary period, and who founded the VGIK, the Soviet Union's renowned state film school, in 1919. &amp;quot;This beautifully atmospheric film was shot in Crimean locations by the great cameraman Boris Savalyev, who would later shoot Dovzhenko's Zvenigora&amp;quot; (Film Society of Lincoln Center). B&amp;amp;W, 35mm, silent with English intertitles. 94 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've made it so far, I'll be holding  a Meet-Up sign near the front row afterwards and then we'll discuss these films at a cafe in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540770000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1164830771000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3 Early Russian Fantasies with Live Piano Accompaniment</name><id>5297411</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165190400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5297411/</event_url></item>