<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>These repo men don't take cars... they take your heart! Or your liver, or your eye, or whatever other mecahanical organ you have purchased to extend your life...

I always enjoy Jude Law's performances, and he was pretty good as a sinister killer in Road to Perdition. 

[b]Details[/b]

The time of the movie is 6:10. That's a little early but the other times won't work out if we're going to eat dinner afterwards.  I will be in the theater lobby by 5:40.

I strongly encourage folks to buy tickets ahead of time at fandango.com.

I will be wearing my red meetup hat. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be in the lobby by the tables by the giant window. If the movie is downstairs, I'll be behind the rope is across from the first floor refreshment stand. I'll be at the theater 30 minutes before showtime, we'll head in to get seats 15 minutes before showtime. If you miss the group before the movie, no worries, we gather outside the theater that showed the movie, and then we all go out for some munchies and a beer, or two.

[b]Synopsis[/b]

In the futuristic action-thriller "Repo Men," humans have extended and improved our lives through highly sophisticated and expensive mechanical organs created by a company called The Union. The dark side of these medical breakthroughs is that if you don't pay your bill, The Union sends its highly skilled repo men to take back its property... with no concern for your comfort or survival.

Jude Law plays Remy, one of the best organ repo men in the business. But when he suffers a cardiac failure on the job, he awakens to find himself fitted with the company's top-of-the-line heart-replacement... as well as a hefty debt. But a side effect of the procedure is that his heart's no longer in the job. When he can't make the payments, The Union sends its toughest enforcer, Remy's former partner Jake (Academy Award® winner Forest Whitaker), to track him down.

Now that the hunter has become the hunted, Remy joins Beth (Alice Braga), another debtor who teaches him how to vanish from the system. And as he and Jake embark on a chase across a landscape populated by maniacal friends and foes, one man will become a reluctant champion for thousands on the run.

The film is based on the novel "The Repossession Mambo" by Eric Garcia. 

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="470" height="264"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/jl9Nvg4yuus&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275960702000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267237531000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Repo Men</name><id>12721247</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269035100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/12721247/</event_url></item>