<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When:  Oct 31st&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Orange, NH &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt. Cardigan Fire Tower&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Orange, NH&lt;br /&gt;State Owned&lt;br /&gt;Elevation: about 3121 feet&lt;br /&gt;1.4 miles (each way)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the fifth in a series of short hikes and trips to various fire towers in NH.  On this date, the foliage is predicted to be PAST PEAK in the Region.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday, October 31st, I am going to climb the Mt. Cardigan Fire Tower.  The trail is 2.8 miles round trip, making it a &lt;b&gt;very&lt;/b&gt; manageable climb. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the Trailhead&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-89. Get off of exit 17 and head east on Route 4 towards Enfield and Canaan. Once in Canaan make a left onto Route 118 towards Orange and Rumney. At roughly a half mile north of Canaan make a right at the Cardigan State Park sign. Bear right after crossing over a stream roughly two and a half miles. The road to the parking area will be on your left, roughly a mile past the creek (closed in winter and early spring).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will take the Westside trail 1.4 miles to the summit.  We may take the South Ridge trail down - if anyone has info about that trail, please pass it on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Planning Details:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet us at the trail head at 9:00 AM.&lt;/b&gt; Orange is  is a little over 1 hour northwest of Concord.  I am happy to meet up with anyone who wants to carpool from the Souhegan Valley area.  After the descent, we can decide if we want to stop for late lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a dog friendly hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional.  If you do not provide a phone number for follow-up (to contact you on the morning of the hike if necessary) I will not wait for you at the trailhead. &lt;/span&gt; I will only use your contact information for this meetup.  I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the NH Fire Tower Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So there are  the 48 White Mountain 4,000 footers and the NE 4,000 footers and then there are the New England 100 Highest....oh and there are the &amp;quot;52 With A View&amp;quot; in NH too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But what if you aren't quite ready for all that time and elevation gain? Or what if you just need some small worthwhile hikes and inspiring views in-between those trips to the Whites?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why not climb our State's fire towers for a little exercise?  The State of NH has a program to &amp;quot;increase the public's recognition of, and appreciation for, the critical roles that our fire towers play in the protection, stewardship and sustainable use of New Hampshire's forests.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who doesn't appreciate that?  And with all hikes less than 2 miles (and many less than 1 mile!), who wouldn't be willing to get a little workout for a guaranteed view?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There are 15 Fire Towers currently in use on public land in New Hampshire.  Ascending just 5 of these towers, some of which are accessible from State Parks and auto roads, qualifies you for a Tower Quest Patch.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Information about the Fire Tower program can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.nhdfl.org/fire-control-and-law-enforcement/fire-towers.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhdfl.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a series of short trips and hikes to visit these locations.  I'm hoping to do most of them in the fall, when the foliage will make the payoff even better. I hope you'll join me!  And if not, I hope you'll pass on the word about this program to others who might be interested!&lt;br /&gt;------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE.  I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.  YOUR PARTICIPATION IN THIS HIKE SIGNIFIES THAT YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THE ABOVE TO BE TRUE.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda with two dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289074697000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286997987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Fire Tower Series:  Mt. Cardigan in Orange, NH (Day Hike)</name><id>15099060</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288530000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15099060/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/5/6/global_18719718.jpeg</photo_url></item>