<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Just two blocks from Haverhill Public Library.</address_2><address_1>across from post office</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.793591</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>9784764989</phone><name>Washington Square</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>1190483</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us at Washington Square in Haverhill for the Team Haverhill's River Ruckus.&amp;nbsp; This is a full day and night of events put on by Team Haverhill.&amp;nbsp; There are free activities for all ages all day with the night ending with a Fantastic Light show on the River.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy browsing the Artisans Market that will be in Washington Square and on Wingate Street,&amp;nbsp; be part of the Essex Gateway Mural- you can paint a piece of history in the building next to the tap, take a Pontoon Boat ride down the Merrimack River or participate in the many different activities throughout the day.&amp;nbsp; Plus you can meet Sammy the Sturgeon....the River Ruckus mascot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is an old car parade starting at&amp;nbsp; 11:30 am which will travel from Academy Lanes to Washington Square.&amp;nbsp; We will not be attending this but if anyone is interested, the cars will also be on display in Washington Square Noon-3pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As more festival scheduled are posted we will update the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this event brings in lots of people to Haverhill, so please come prepared....carry the Meetup cellphone number with you in case you get lost, can't find us or we get separated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you all at the Ruckus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of the Post Office in Washington Square</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313977382000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310695649000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Team Haverhill's River Ruckus</name><id>25806801</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313859600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/25806801/</event_url></item>