<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 6:50, so let's meet right inside the ticket lobby at 6:20. Then we'll get tix, snacks, and seats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Edge of Darkness!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Mel Gibson's still got it, even when he's &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810041005/details" target="_blank"&gt;on the edge. &lt;/a&gt;Okay, okay, so now he's playing a dad, but I dare ya to cross him! He's part of a plot to uncover his daughter's murderer (so don't get too attached to her in the beginning of this flick) and something tells me he's gonna get his revenge. Maybe a little like Taken, but still a promising movie. Come join me in the action!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides, HELLO!!, filmed right here in MA. We'll talk after about how many landmarks we recognize!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Craven is a veteran homicide detective for the Boston Police Department and a single father. When his only child, 24-year-old Emma, is murdered on the steps of his home, everyone assumes that he was the target. But he soon suspects otherwise, and embarks on a mission to find out about his daughter's secret life and her killing. His investigation leads him into a dangerous looking-glass world of corporate cover-ups, government collusion and murder -- and to shadowy government operative Darius Jedburgh who has been sent in to clean up the evidence. Craven's solitary search for answers about his daughter's death transforms into an odyssey of emotional discovery and redemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Edge of Darkness!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267022277000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264966612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edge of Darkness</name><id>12475339</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266796800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12475339/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>