<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>539 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.353896</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 259-3400 for tickets</phone><name>Boston Opera House</name><city>Boston</city><id>746686</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062154</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>39.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A night at the ballet!  Since we have 10+ we get 50% off orchestra seats for this fantastic ballet.  A real bargain! Performance is at 8pm on Friday evening, April 8 - so there is some time beforehand to get a bite to eat or have a drink.  Seats will be in the "B" section of the orchestra - these are in the front section of the orchestra, on the side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Ballet presents George Balanchine&amp;rsquo;s A Midsummer Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream, a lucid and inventive telling of Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s play. A Midsummer Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream was Balanchine&amp;rsquo;s first original, full-length ballet. Called by critic Clive Barnes, &amp;ldquo;a fantasy spectacle of love,&amp;rdquo; this work is a masterful combination of storytelling and choreography danced to the exquisite sounds of Mendelssohn. The ballet tells a story of love, illusion and adventures of two pairs of mortal lovers and the kind and queen of the fairies. A Midsummer Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream was choreographed for New York City Ballet and premiered in 1962. The production includes a large cast complete with 25 students from Boston Ballet School and sets and costumes designed by Tony Award-winner Martin Pakledinaz. The last time A Midsummer Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream was danced by Boston Ballet it was called, &amp;ldquo;a winner, a gorgeous, spirited production given strong performances throughout the ranks, including the excellent orchestra led by Jonathan McPhee&amp;rdquo; by The Boston Globe.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a wonderful way to spend a spring evening in Boston!  The opera house is a spectacular place to see a ballet, and Mendelssohn music along with Balanchine's choreography will be a real treat.  Don't miss out&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be be in the front lobby by 7:30pm with the tickets in hand! My cell phone is 774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302795621000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294936084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ballet - A Midsummer Night's Dream at the Opera House</name><id>16035694</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302307200000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/16035694/</event_url></item>