<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually provide handouts and have appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up.  Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************* &lt;br /&gt;Hope everybody’s soaking in all this beautiful sunshine and enjoying the summer.  As September rolls around, there is generally a collective &lt;i&gt;(perhaps, subconscious)&lt;/i&gt; mood shift –“Darn it, back to the grindstone, the fun is over.” ;o(&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As LOA practice-tioners, we know we can deliberately choose how we want to feel.  &lt;b&gt;Ann Ide, BostonLOA member and New Possibilities Life Coach,&lt;/b&gt; will share with us how we can live in a relaxed, vacation frame of mind &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; day, experiencing greater harmony, happiness and success. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you Ann for sharing your gift of time and wisdom with us.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Living Every Day in Vacation Mode&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;from Ann:&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Summertime...and the livin' is easy.&amp;quot;  Know that song?  It's got a slow, relaxed mood about it.  You know that feeling?  How'd you like to feel this way &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; day?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As soon as summer rolls in, my mood shifts.  I'm more relaxed each day; and &lt;i&gt;even though I may have just as much to do as any other day of the year&lt;/i&gt;, it doesn't &lt;i&gt;feel&lt;/i&gt; the same.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recently I became even more aware of this mood when we went away for 5 days to Cape Cod.  In my relaxed state of mind, I allowed myself to just go with the flow.  Even when it rained (and it did plenty of that), we still gracefully found something to do &lt;i&gt;and had lots of fun&lt;/i&gt;.  Every day ended up being perfect -with an easy unfolding and &lt;i&gt;delightful manifestations&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was so wonderful, that I set an intention to live every day in a vacation mood; and it has been wonderful ever since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I mean, after all, it's not like there's a formal summertime edict that gives you permission to relax more!  &lt;i&gt;You give this permission to yourself.&lt;/i&gt;  So why limit it?  Why not do it every day, year round?  I'm sure you'll agree, there are many benefits to be had!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can, for a moment, recapture how you feel inside when you're on vacation.  For me, it's an inner calm and an anticipation of good times and feeling good.  I'm less attached to a schedule and &amp;quot;have to's&amp;quot;; and instead am aware of the freedom of &lt;i&gt;choosing&lt;/i&gt; moment to moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, if you were to pick up almost any book on spirituality, I bet you would find suggestions that what I just mentioned is an enlightened state to aim for - an attitude towards life worth trying, to create a life worth living. &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Real harmony and happiness is created from within.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not only have I been feeling great, but more good things are happening for me.  Additionally, work is easier. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do you think maybe you sometimes struggle harder than necessary?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on at our Tuesday, September 1st meetup.  Learn &lt;i&gt;and experience&lt;/i&gt; how you can live in a vacation mood &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; day – feeling that happy, harmonious, relaxed feeling and be productive and successful as ever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Ann Ide&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;www.NewPossibilitiesCoaching.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann is a certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming (NLP) and Hypnotherapy, and a certified NLP Life Coach with over 15 years experience. She has trained and consulted people nationally.  Her passion is helping people move beyond suffering and mere survival, and creating “New Possibilities” in their lives for greater harmony, happiness and success. She provides personal and group coaching, guided meditations, and business workshops.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252976820000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249471917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Living Every Day in Vacation Mode </name><id>11040473</id><headcount>49</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251846000000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/11040473/</event_url></item>