<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt Auburn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365641</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga Studio</name><city>Watertown</city><id>752617</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183571</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>My Dear Women,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like to invite you to awaken your subtle body and become a channel of pure love during our next community event - White Tantric Healing Circle. The white color symbolizes the purity of consciousness, connection to the source, balance and unity of all colors. The circle is a structure in which we all come together, as one; it is a place to see and be seen, to speak and be heard, to touch upon the souls of others and be touched by their presence. It says in Upanishad:  &amp;quot;Who sees all being in his own self, and his own self in all beings, loses all fear&amp;quot;. Practice in a circle is a way to develop that higher vision.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to create a solid foundation and develop a solid spiritual practice of our own before we are able to build successful relationships, learning how to transform our emotions into wisdom, judgment into acceptance, attachment into unconditional love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the White Tantric Healing circles we will work on:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Clearing mental noise &lt;br /&gt;- Achieving Emotional Balance&lt;br /&gt;- Cleansing suffering from the depth of our being&lt;br /&gt;- Releasing body memories&lt;br /&gt;- Purifying the Nadis (energy channels)&lt;br /&gt;- Sharpening the senses&lt;br /&gt;- Enhancing intuition and creativity&lt;br /&gt;- Activating the chakras&lt;br /&gt;- Restoring the body's natural sexual charge&lt;br /&gt;- Transmuting sexual energy into honeywaves of bliss&lt;br /&gt;- Disappearing as self into love&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be using a series of tantra tools including: silent, guided and active meditation, kundalini yoga kriyas, various types of therapeutic exercises, breathwork, partner yoga, Para-tan ancient healing method as taught by Shri Param Esrawan , chanting and mantra, yoga of touch, emotional release techniques, dancing, ritual and sharing.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will learn how to practice without necessarily having a partner, finding the polarity within yourself, connecting to all feminine and all masculine in the universe. It is a powerful and truly liberating way to be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you come to the circles, you will start feeling an on-going ecstatic connection between your body, your mind and your soul, which will radiate in every aspect of your life.  As a great yogi Sri K Patthabi Jois says &amp;quot;Do your practice and all is coming&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Tantric Circle is a community event, which we are planning to repeat as regular practice to maintain the blazing of your inner fire which purifies the soul. The time you spend on spiritual practice is the only time which would have a long lasting effect on your being in your awakened state, in your dreams, and as tantric believe, in your other lives to come. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am happy that we can offer this wonderful practice for our community. All genders are welcome to this event. If you would like to participate in a women only event, please email me at luba.evans@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Meditation:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two men meet on the street.&lt;br /&gt;One asks the other: &amp;quot;Hi, how are you?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;The other one replies: &amp;quot;I'm fine, thanks.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;And how's your son? Is he still unemployed?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Yes, he is. But he is meditating now.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Meditating? What's that?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I don't know. But it's better than sitting around and doing nothing!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luba Evans</member_name><member_id>7320465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290926533000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258169916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>White Tantric Healing Circle - Friday  Night</name><id>11871109</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259973000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/11871109/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/8/global_11792312.jpeg</photo_url></item>