<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>; see directions below</address_2><address_1>182 Memorial Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building 6, Room 120</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>408704</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP! If you have friends you talk stocks with, bring them and add them to your RSVP!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guest Speaker Meeting: Take Charge of Your Money with The Market Guys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that AJ Monte will be presenting; Rick Swope will not be able to appear.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rick and AJ are The Market Guys. They are an active, lively pair with great trading backgrounds; read their bios below for more detail. In this session they will discuss some of the major mistakes investors make when trying to manage their portfolio in a volatile market along with solutions that will help increase return on investment. There is more to investing than just knowing about the Fundamentals of a company. Technical Analysis is the preferred risk management tool used by The Market Guys and they will share with you the all important 1% Rule for trading and investing. This entertaining yet informative discussion is something you will not want to miss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: The material covered in this meeting will be a sneak preview of what will be aired on National Pubic Television in June and is based off of their new book Take Charge of your Money Now! published by Random House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.themarketguys.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Here is The Market Guys website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Biography for AJ Monte&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a premier trading consultant, AJ is one of the most sought after in his field. He teaches professionals specialized techniques on how to accumulate and protect wealth through innovative market techniques. He has over 23 years in the business, ten of which were spent as a trader on the floor of the NY Commodity Exchange where he specialized in Gold &amp;amp; Silver Options.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During his time on the trading floor he served for two years as the Chairman of the Option Floor Trading Committee for Comex. He left the floor in 1992 to trade NASDAQ stocks for Mayer &amp;amp; Schwitzer &amp;amp; Nash Weiss, which is now part of Bank of America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several years later AJ pioneered the Trading Analytics Group for Charles Schwab &amp;amp; Co., which is a team of professionals who educate both clients and high profile brokers in the areas of Technical and Fundamental Analysis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For 2 years AJ was the co-host of the PBS weekly show, &amp;quot;Wealth &amp;amp; Wisdom.&amp;quot; He also co-hosts the top-rated on-demand radio show &amp;quot;The Market Guys Podcast&amp;quot;. His travels bring him to London, Switzerland and different parts of Asia teaching people how to manage risk by using technical analysis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AJ also appeared in the movie TRADING PLACES starring Dan Ackroyd and Eddie Murphy while consulting with Director John Landis and the stars to prepare them for their realistic roles in the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is a Chartered Market Technician and member of the Market Technicians Association who currently resides in Orlando, Florida. He is married, has two children and loves to coach Lacrosse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Biography for Rick Swope&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a veteran in the industry, Rick has presented in hundreds of seminars across the U.S. and around the world. Specializing in the areas of Technical Analysis and Risk Management, his topics have continually stayed in demand. His passion for teaching is obvious and his energy is contagious.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rick was the co-owner and managing partner of a trading firm in Cincinnati for several years, providing technical analysis, trading strategy and software training to the firm's traders. Rick also traded a partnership account during that time, executing up to 300 trades per day. Rick worked closely with some of the early pioneers of Small Order Execution System trading - the so-called SOES bandits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rick has presented with some of the top financial exchanges including the Chicago Board Options Exchange, the Chicago Mercantile Exchange and the International Securities Exchange. Rick created the first market technical analysis consulting team for a financial firm with $1 trillion in client assets. Many members of that team are now training and consulting leaders in other firms around the country. For 2 years Rick was the co-host of the PBS weekly show, &amp;quot;Wealth &amp;amp; Wisdom.&amp;quot; He also co-hosts the top-rated on-demand radio show &amp;quot;The Market Guys Podcast.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has extensive teaching experience from corporate training to six years as an adjunct Engineering instructor. He studied in the disciplines of Engineering, Mathematics, Operations Research and Statistics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rick is married with a 13 year old son and a 9 year old daughter. He is an avid runner and duathlete. Rick also holds a black belt and currently trains in both Tae Kwon Do and Brazilian Jiu Jitsu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map of MIT showing Building 6&lt;/b&gt; is &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?zoom=level2;selection=6;selectlayer=Buildings;selectfield=facility;centerx=711181;centery=495622" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Room 120 is just inside the big, main doors. This is one of our favorite rooms and we are grateful to MIT for the room.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235609131000</updated><rating><average>4.84999990463</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>64</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228862797000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guest Speakers: Take Charge of Your Money with The Market Guys</name><id>9310381</id><headcount>66</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234483200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9310381/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/8/global_7005128.jpeg</photo_url></item>