<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>327 Newbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 351-2500</phone><name>Sonsie</name><city>Boston</city><id>484983</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086174</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Would you like to get some new books for free? Do you have a book that you enjoyed and would like to pass on to someone else? Or maybe a book that's not your type, but someone else may enjoy? Then join us for dinner at Sonsie on Newbury Street. Sonsie is donating pizza for our group. The full menu is also available for you to order from. We will enjoy dinner, then swap books. Book swap is optional. you can still come and enjoy dinner and hanging out. This is always a popular event!  Please be sure that your books are in excellent condition, may be hardcover or paperback. Please no textbooks! You may bring two or three books if you would like. Please know that once you swap books, your original books will not be returned to you.  Everyone pays for their own food/drink. Hope to see you there!  Please note: Meet Up has removed the maybe option from the RSVP list. If you are not sure about attending, please write 'maybe' in the comment section. If your plans change, be sure to update your RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296676110000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295391155000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and Book Swap at Sonsie, Boston with Free Pizza</name><id>16098126</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296518400000</time><rsvp_limit>48</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/16098126/</event_url></item>