<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join the best Fashion Industry Meetup in the world. We have members who are experts in different aspects of the industry, &amp;amp; many who are beginners  looking for help from the more experienced members. We have fun, great networking time, and projects to get involved in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have come before you will note that we have a new meeting place.  Bay State College has volunteered one of their rooms for us to meet in.  The attendance at meetings has grown so that Positive Image studio is no longer large enough for our group.&lt;br /&gt;We need all types of fashion workers &amp;amp; entrepreneurs to join us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should attend if you are interested in fashion, design (clothing, jewelry, accessories), graphic design, modeling, photography, teaching, fabrics, sewing, etc.  The event is fun as well as very educational.   You will learn about  the Boston Fashion Industry, current conditions and how to navigate the maze to become successful here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you all there. Remember that starting in November we are meeting at Bay State College. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Fashion Industry Meetup organizers&lt;br /&gt;Shirley, Ron, Jamall, Jeffrey, Prithi, Evan.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will greet you. Make sure you RSVP Yes so that we know you are coming.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeffrey Engel</member_name><member_id>547287</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley Willett</member_name><member_id>1480973</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jamall Oluokun</member_name><member_id>6487580</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Prithi Pais</member_name><member_id>7208428</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229642013000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224198625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Fashion Industry November Meetup</name><id>8975854</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227222000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/8975854/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/9/global_5522201.jpeg</photo_url></item>