<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I’m pleased to announce the NHRuby January meeting, which will take place on Thursday, January 15th at RMC Research in Portsmouth. Jonathan Linowes of Parkerhill Technology Group will be coming down from the mountains of Lyman, NH to speak to us about a tantalizing trinity of interesting topics:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * A demo of his pet project, ReviewRamp, presently in Beta. ReviewRamp is a SAAS (software as a service) application for collecting and reviewing on-line submissions such as business plans, conference paper proposals, and grant applications. Users create projects in ReviewRamp which have their own custom submission forms, review scoresheets, and summary reports. Implemented in Ruby on Rails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * A review of how Jon is using Cucumber plain text stories for development and integration testing. Jon started using rSpec Story Runner over a year ago and recently migrated to the newer Cucumber implementation. Real examples from the ReviewRamp project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * A presentation of DynamicRecord, a database engine Jon is developing for ReviewRamp. DynamicRecord extends the Ruby on Rails’ ActiveRecord (AR) object-relational mapping (ORM) module, enabling creation of dynamic attributes that look and behave like standard AR ones without the need to add tables or columns to the database.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the meeting date is actually the third Thursday of the month as opposed to the usual third Tuesday. We’re switching up the dates this year to prevent conflicts with certain regularly-scheduled Boston.rb events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I’m really looking forward to Jon’s talk; it should be a good one. I’m sure there will also be some interesting conversation about the recently announced Merb / Rails merger. Hope to see everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>nap</member_name><member_id>6144459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235090516000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhruby</urlname><id>885450</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The NH Ruby and Rails Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230171295000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Secoast RoR Monthy meet up w/guest speaker Jon Linowes on 'DynamicRecord'</name><id>9386015</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232064000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhruby/events/9386015/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/f/global_4005199.jpeg</photo_url></item>