<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Call for reservations at Crabapple Rafting Trips at 1 800 553 7238..&lt;br /&gt;This trip is under the REIGINS PARTY if you want to be in the same boat...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS ARE E MAILED FROM CRABAPPEL E TICKET AFTER YOU CALL THEM..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP yes on the right if you have already contacted Crabappel and are IN..&lt;br /&gt;(its more so we know who is going and can make plans for the trip..etc..)  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I didnt ask how many openings there were left for this trip..(I already am on the boat so im in) but since there are only about 12 boats going there isnt time to waite till the last minute unless someone cancells late sept..last year there were 4 or so that really wanted to go but CrabApple said thay had no openings left and that was a month before the event...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dont complaine its too expensive..most of you waste money on 8 dollar drinks..and 10 dollar hambuggers at some bar or restuarant..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;fuel..we are car pooling...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner is included in this trip and it usually fills ya up..soooo there..&lt;br /&gt;so there.. get the idea...LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND we can do a tie-in event too...IE camping/hotel Barbie-q dinner and fire pit evening..then maybe MT tom on the return trip or other place...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you think you are a whimp or whussie..well you probally are..but even whimps can handle this trip...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check out their website for other trips also if you cant make this one...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok im already on the Crabappel Reservation list..so im going if no one else is or isnt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a trip acceptable for beginners and for kids down to 12 years old..and for WUSSY and WIMPY adults..&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; West River Rafting Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We raft the West River on scheduled dam releases during run-off in Fall foliage on September 27. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The West River offers a unique trip combining eight miles of continuous Class III intermediate action with some bigger rapids such as &amp;quot;Mudslide Landslide&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Chicken Soupe Dumplings&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start and meet for our trip at Mount Snow Ski Resort and end the trip there with a DELICIOUS gut stuffing cookout and slide show of the day's raft trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We begin our trip actual rafting trip start by walking to the top of Ball Mountain Dam. Our drop off spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Views from atop the dam are breathtaking as we look down at the first rapid and back across the reservoir at Stratton Mountain Ski Area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING A WATERPROOF CAMERA for those extra shots...make sure its secure in the boat though later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We then descend down to the river and practice paddling for the upcoming ACTION.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first half of the trip runs through beautiful Jamaica State Park and includes a half-mile rapid called &amp;quot;Mudslide Landslide&amp;quot; and the feature rapid of the day, &amp;quot;The Soupe Chicken Dumplings&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Chicken Soupe Dumplings&amp;quot; is a tight S-turn where strong team paddling is necessary to avoid a few boulders and hit the biggest waves. &lt;br /&gt;EVEN CHICKENS CAN HANDLE THIS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a quick snack, ( MAYBE CHICKEN NUGGETS) the second half of the trip has several more rapids like&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt; &amp;quot;The Ledges&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  (NO NOT THE FAMOUS &amp;quot;other&amp;quot; LEDGES..THAT WOULD SCARE YOUR CLOTHES OFF..)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THERE THE TRIP works back toward our base camp at Mount Snow.&lt;br /&gt;THEN ITS LUNCH...BETTER BARBIE-Q THAN MY EVENTS...YUMMY BROWNIES AND ALL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe even a camping stay overnight in the area...we will see closer to the event day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The West River has an unbeatable combination of ACTION and &lt;b&gt;scenery&lt;/b&gt; which is universally loved by both veteran and new rafters. Check out the Photo Gallery&lt;br /&gt;THAT ON THE CRABAPPLE WHITE WATER SITE...&lt;br /&gt;YOU GO LOOK FOR IT..NOT DOING EVERYTHING FOR YOU..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Trip Overview:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miles: 8&lt;br /&gt;Trip time: Full day&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Minimum Age: 12&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;... IF ITS OK FOR SNOT FACED LITTLE KIDS..ITS SAFE FOR WIMP ADULTS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food: Cookout at base after trip&lt;br /&gt;No. of people per boat: 6 - 8&lt;br /&gt;Rapid Classification: Class II-IV&lt;br /&gt;Digital Slide Presentation from &amp;quot;Landslide&amp;quot; rapid&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;West River Prices and Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;Rafting Price:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September  Adults $100pp Children 12-15 $83pp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group Rates  for groups of 12 or more&lt;br /&gt;Schedule:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  September 27&lt;br /&gt;( For full season of April - October rafting see Deerfield River Adventures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Includes:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-trip safety instruction, professional guide, PFD and helmet,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;wetsuit (April only), transportation to and from river, cookout (chicken, fish or vegetarian option), photo presentation of your adventure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chickens get made into Chicken McNuggets...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://kayaking.meetup.com/119/calendar/8389086/"&gt;http://kayaking.meetu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Snow Sundance Base Lodge &lt;br /&gt;Pisgah Rd; West Dover VT 05356 &lt;br /&gt;om Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;Follow I-91 North to Exit #2 in Vermont. Take Route 9 West 20 miles to Wilmington, VT. Turn right at the stoplight on to Route 100 North. Nine miles to Mount Snow/Haystack. Turn into Mount Snow Resort.  Follow the signs to Sundance BaseLodge and Crab Apple Whitewater.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL COORDINATE BEFORE, or ASK STAFF AT VERMONT LOCATION FOR REIGINS PARTY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223229967000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216742272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VERMONT FALL SEASON RIVER RAFTING TRIP</name><id>8389086</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222520400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8389086/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/6/global_3541542.jpeg</photo_url></item>