<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>40 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.492.1557</phone><name>Algiers Coffee House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669147</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121338</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What was a nice Eton boy like Eric Blair doing in scummy slums instead of being upwardly mobile at Oxford or Cambridge? Living Down and Out in Paris and London, he turned his sharply observant eye to the lives of the poor, inventing a new type of fictional reportage and a new persona for himself, George Orwell. Thus, his 1933 debut book came to be.  Initially, it was rejected by most publishers, including T.S. Eliot. Was its close-up portrait of lowlife too pungent for comfort?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Paris, Orwell lived in verminous rooms and washed dishes at the overpriced &amp;quot;Hotel X,&amp;quot; in a remarkably filthy, 110-degree kitchen. He met &amp;quot;eccentric people--people who have fallen into solitary, half-mad grooves of life and given up trying to be normal or decent.&amp;quot; For all that, it's surprising how entertaining many of his adventures are: gnawing poverty only enlivens the imagination, and the wild characters he met often swindled each other and themselves. The wackiest tale involves a miser who ate cats, wore newspapers for underwear, invested 6,000 francs in cocaine, and hid it in a face-powder tin when the cops raided. You get the idea...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263419300000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248121415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Orwell: Down and Out in Paris and London</name><id>10917830</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249855200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/10917830/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/a/7/global_5819031.jpeg</photo_url></item>