<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Room 160</address_2><address_1>Building 66</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>372740</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today we will be running a study night over at MIT in room 66-160 (Building 66, Room 160).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are directions to Building 66 from the Kendall/MIT Red Line T Stop:&lt;br /&gt;1) Get off at the Kendall/MIT Red Line Stop&lt;br /&gt;2) Walk up Main Street towards the MIT Coop Bookstore, Legal Seafood, The Kendall Hotel, etc.&lt;br /&gt;3) Turn left onto Ames Street&lt;br /&gt;4) Walk down the street until you see a triangle-shaped building on your right &amp;#8211; this is Building 66.&lt;br /&gt;5) Either wait until a student opens the door for you, or give my phone a call so that I can let you in (I am sending out my phone number to all attendees in a separate e-mail).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map showing the walk from Kendall/MIT Station to Building 66:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/~rschuman/www/walking_map_building_66.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;Walking Map to Building 66 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, here is a link that shows an image of Building 66:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?zoom=level2&amp;amp;centerx=710929&amp;amp;centery=496159&amp;amp;oldzoom=level3&amp;amp;map.x=298&amp;amp;map.y=192" target="_blank"&gt; Building 66 Information &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like I already mentioned, MIT keeps most doors locked at night, so please keep my phone number with you in case you have any issues getting into the building.  Also due to the experimental nature of this first-ever study group, please come with an open mind and a desire to help each other with our studies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Japanese and English Language Study Night&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, Sept. 18th, 7 - 8:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be combining members of the MIT community and the Boston Japanese and English Language Club for combined efforts in studying our second languages.  Essentially the format will involve introductions, writing in our second languages, Q&amp;amp;A relating to grammar, vocabulary, etc, and time to discuss other issues we are experiencing with our studies.  Attendees should come prepared with questions, writing materials, and anything else that may aid them in their studies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: By all means, please e-mail me with any questions you might have before the study meetup.  We will do our best to address as many of these as possible during our time together.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190389412000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189788875000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Japanese and English Study Night</name><id>6359350</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190156400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/6359350/</event_url></item>