<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 St Marys St</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.349552</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>8 St Marys St</name><city>Boston</city><id>5765962</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106735</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Start: Wednesday October 24, 2012 6:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost: Free Admission &lt;br /&gt;

 Organizer: American Islamic Congress &lt;br /&gt;

 Venue: Boston University Photonics Center Colloquium Room &lt;br /&gt;

 Address: 8 Saint Mary’s Street, 9th Floor, Boston, MA 02215 &lt;br /&gt;

 Halal food will be served.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fascinating dialogue between science and Christianity has gone on for centuries. But we seldom hear a public debate on intersection of Islam and science. That is why American Islamic Congress and Project Nur have launched a groundbreaking series of public dialogues to illuminate the relationships Muslims have with the sciences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fall’s dialogue at Boston University will focus on one of the most contentious issues in the field - evolution. Top scholars from across the sciences will meet to explore how men and women of Muslim backgrounds reconcile evolutionary theory with scripture, theology, and personal belief - or whether they do so at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keynote: Salman Hameed, Associate Professor of Integrated Sciences and Humanites at Hampshire College and Director of the Center for the Study of Science in Muslim Societies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panelists: Ehab Abouheif, Research Chair in Evolutionary Developmental Biology and Principal Investigator, Abouheif Lab, McGill University;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rana Dajani, Assistant Professor of Molecular Biology &lt;br /&gt;

 and Director, Centre for Studies, Hashemite University;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Omar Sultan Haque, Postdoctoral Fellow, Psychology, Harvard University and Psychiatry and Law, Harvard Medical School, and Co-Director, UNESCO Chair in Bioethics, American Unit.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351190100000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Arabic Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonArabic</urlname><id>1143990</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Area Arabic Language Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350067461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science &amp; Islam: Is there a clash between Islam and the theory of evolution?</name><id>86713172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351116000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonArabic/events/86713172/</event_url></item>