<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>500 Wigwam Ln</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06614</zip><lat>41.226917</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>st. mark's</name><city>stratford</city><id>2295601</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.128940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;When Saturday, February 18, 2012 &amp;bull;Time 7:30pm until 11:30pm &amp;bull; Description Tickets are 15.00 and are ONLY available by calling (203)377-8813. There will be no tickets sold at the door. This special event is a fundraiser for our friend Steve Yachymczyk who has recently been diagnosed with stage 3 lung cancer so that we may help him offset the financial hardships this horrible disease has caused. The event is Cabaret Style, BYOB (set-ups will be provided). There will be 50/50 raffles, drawings and plenty of chances to win some incredible prizes, not to mention the AWESOME MUSIC provided by the" Pocket Full Of Soul" Can't make the event, you can still help with a contribution to this very special and worthy cause! Click on the "give" button below or simply click this link: &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/1lMgr" class="linkified"&gt;http://goo.gl/1lMgr&lt;/a&gt; Send this out to as many of your Facebook Friends as possible! Thank you all for your support. See you at the show! http:// www.reverbnation.com/ pocketfullofsoulbandSee More THEY PLAYED BEAR &amp;amp; GRILL A COUPLE WEEKS AGO AND I SAW A BUNCH OF MEMBERS FROM THIS MEETUP THERE HAVING A GOOD TIME SO THIS SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD CAUSE WITH A GREAT BAND AND THE BYOB SOUNDS LIKE A CHEAPER NIGHT OUT. I CAN CALL AND GET THE TICKETS FOR WHOEVER WANTS TO GO JUST SEND ME A MESSAGE. THANKS&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carlin Hill</member_name><member_id>5148164</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329826018000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328752982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FUN RAISER SPONSORED BY THE POCKET FULL OF SOUL BAND</name><id>51640232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329611400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/51640232/</event_url></item>