<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Reservation Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03037</zip><lat>43.104805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pawtuckaway State Park</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>632081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.205055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be an easier hike in the sense that most of the trail sections are the width of a dirt road that cars could drive on (and did during the last deer hunting season) The trails are gated and closed to cars now). &amp;nbsp;The route we will take does not go up and down any mountain sides but rather goes in between them. &amp;nbsp;As there aren't many places in NH that are naturally flat there will of course be elevation gains and loses as we go up and down mostly gentler slopes without any steep sections of trail. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless the distance of the hike itself is an issue for you this should be a very easy hike for most people. &amp;nbsp;Two younger kids had no real problems on the steeper hike on S. Mtn. at Pawtuckaway last weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to find us:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Once you turn onto Reservation Rd coming off of Route 107 in Deerfield proceed 2.5 miles. The road turns into a dirt Road. Look for a white Suzuki Grand Vitara with the license plate 308 0904.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a back entrance into the park. &amp;nbsp;Do not use the front entrance to the park that is in Nottingham off of Rt 156. &amp;nbsp;Although this park is technically closed to dogs we are going there in the off season before the park is officially open for the season so that should not be an issue. &amp;nbsp;You will continue on Reservation Rd till it turns into a private road at a T intersection. &amp;nbsp;If you click on the meetup location under the date and then click on get directions in the upper left hand corner and then type in your starting address it will give you directions on how to get to Reservation Rd in Deerfield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to a trail map of the park. &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.com/Maps/pawhiking.html"&gt;http://www.nhstateparks.com/Maps/pawhiking.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you click on the link note that Reservation Rd. (back entrance) is shown on the left side of the map and Mountain Rd (front entrance) is on the bottom of the map. &amp;nbsp;We will be parking where Tower Road intersects with Reservation Rd on the map near the number 5.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304871163000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>On a previous hike to Pawtuckaway a few people had to cancel as the steeper trail sections on S. Mtn. would have caused difficulties for them or their dog.  So although this hike will have inclines and declines they are gentler with more even ground.</why><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304477948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pawtuckaway State Park -  Flatlander 3.3 Mile Hike</name><id>17536449</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304866800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/17536449/</event_url></item>