<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Mt. Washington Observatory raises funds each year in an event called Seek the Peak.  The moneys raised help support the weather observatory at the top of the highest peak in the Northeast.  This event runs July 23-24 in North Conway, NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have registered to be a hiker this year and raise funds for the cause.  I would enjoy the support and/or company of those who would like to tackle this challenge.  As was said to me on a difficult New Hampshire hike, &amp;quot;Anyone can climb anything with enough time and we have all day&amp;quot;.  I have set this as a goal, again....a big one for myself.  You can make this your goal also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Understand that this is the tallest Mt. in New England.  We will starting at Pinkham Notch and traveling up Tuckerman's Ravine.  It is a 4.2 mile hike with a 4200' vertical gain-that is 7 to 8 hours of climbing!  Oh, yeah, then you have to come back down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will need to seriously self assess your experience and fitness level on this event.  You need equipment for all seasons.  It can go from sunny and warm in the valley to sleat and rain on the way up.  You need rain gear, fleece, dry socks, water/food, headlamp, emergency gear, waterproof hiking boots.  &lt;br /&gt;Ask yourself this, can I carry a heavy pack of all I need uphill for at least 7 hours?  If you cannot reach the top by 3:00p.m. you have to turn around.  You need the utmost respect for this event.  People die up there.  No doom and gloom, just the honest truth.  You need to understand what you are attempting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seekthepeak.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.seekthepea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; to read more about the event, register as a hiker, or make a pledge under my name JaniceMay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a reception Friday night to collect goodie bags in Conway and a dinner after the hike at the end of the auto road.  My crew will head up Friday. I am staying at Joe Dodge Lodge at Pinkham Notch-the trailhead.  If you go to the AMC web site, www.outdoors.org, you can see availability for the logde.  It is $63 per night (includes dinner and breakfast).  If you stay alone add $25-the rooms are double occupancy.&lt;br /&gt;You can stay at the Hostel in Conway.  It is cash payment and it runs about $25 for the night.  That is the price to stay in the single sex dorms.  Private rooms are $68 with a charge for more people.  It is about a 40 minute ride to the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Albert B. Lester Memorial Hostel&lt;br /&gt;36 Washington Street&lt;br /&gt;Conway, NH  03818&lt;br /&gt;603-447-1001&lt;br /&gt;conwayhostel@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some folks have talked about camping.  That link has been posted in the responses.  Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many places to stay in North Conway.  I would book soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to contact me with questions if you want to join in.  My plans and carpools are set so you will have to make your own arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hike with a Purpose!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281656792000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270423637000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt. Washington, NH, Seek the Peak</name><id>13085606</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279969200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13085606/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_16128057.jpeg</photo_url></item>