<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come join us in our continuing exploration of Advanced Energy Healing. We are currently focusing on a Keylontic Science modality called Ka-Tha-Ra which is the ancient Anuhazi translation for &amp;quot;light-sound-one&amp;quot;. The detailed technicals are FASCINATING!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is CORE level healing, from the inside out. All miasms can be cleared by drawing frequency from the 12th dimension, where our original DNA template for perpetual health has been preserved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please do NOT park in the driveway with the &amp;quot;ULCS Clinic&amp;quot; sign. Instead go up the first driveway which has the Meetup Sign at the end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional guests from a 6:00 Meeting may be joining in with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This time the healing power of certain types of Orbs will be discussed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many types of orbs, ranging from elemental orbs to those created by advanced beings who use pre-ancient Keylontic Science techniques to project their consciousness to other locations by &amp;quot;orbing&amp;quot; there.  Natural organic Krystic orbs can be very helpful, whereas those created by fallen beings who are running reversed Merkaba mechanics on artificial bi-veca light fields are to be avoided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is important to know the difference, as well as how to protect against some of the deceptive practices now being promoted by well-intentioned practitioners who are ill-informed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A specific technique will be given to call forth certain VERY beneficial orbs.  Orbs photos will also be shown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup sign at end of first driveway and on front door. No need to knock.  Meeting is in downstairs classroom.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349856570000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278735570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healing with Orbs</name><id>jdtqnynlbwb</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282690800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/14057566/</event_url></item>