<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Salsa Fans:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's better than live music &amp;amp; dancing?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get together for some social dancing and to watch a great performance by one of the best salsa bands around.  I will be there around 7:00 to catch some appetizers. See you there!!!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can spot me (Angel) with my grey fedora hat.  Shouldn't be hard to miss...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS IS FOR THE DOWNSTAIRS AREA!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday February 18 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music by Ritmo Masacote&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dining 5pm-11pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showtime:  8:30 pm!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fee: Only $10.00  All night&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ritmo Masacote is an irresistible, percussive-driven project full of Boston's best talent. Joel Massicot leads the group through a unique set of compositions and arrangements with focused directions in Timba, Salsa, Latin Jazz grounded in Cuban roots, all wrapped up for dancers and music aficionados alike.  Everyone can Relate.  Ritmo Masacote has a strong cast of well seasoned musicians, the majority of which are from Berklee College of Music, with Special Guest from New York, Christelle Durandy.   Join us on Thursday, Feb 18 at 8:30pm for this special party with Ritmo Masacote.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Creating the bridge between music and dance”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us for an intense night of Music and Dance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Listen to our new sound for 2010!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Show time: 8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only $10 cover charge...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Ryles Jazz Club, 312 Hampshire Street, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;(Read below for afterparty details)&lt;br /&gt;*****************************&lt;br /&gt;What they're saying about Ritmo Masacote:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Joel and friends deliver an irresistible, percussive-driven project, which is hypnotic to listeners and toe-tapping to the swinging dancers.&amp;quot; -- Rudy Mangual, Latin Beat Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Irresistible, toe-tapping, hip, and head-shakingly groovy. Everyon can relate.&amp;quot; -- Kevin Ball, Host/Producer of Jazz Gallery (WGBH 89.7)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pianist Joel Massicot leads his group Ritmo Masacote through a unique set of compositions and arrangements on Fantagious that mix a wide palette of musical spices into a fantastic dish. Several tracks draw upon a straight-ahead Cuban influence, interpreted with a modern edge.&amp;quot; -- Chip Boaz, The Latin Jazz Corner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There is an independent spirit at work here, a sense of playfulness and adventurousness... The Ritmo Masacote band are a fabulous bunch of players, and on this date their talent really shows. Massicot’s piano playing is fluid and inventive, easily switching from intense Latin figures to gentle, almost classical ruminations...Highly Recommended.&amp;quot; Pablo Yglesias, Editor's Pick, Descarga.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****************************&lt;br /&gt;Looking for more? Join us at the afterparty!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't worry! We won't let the party stop here! Ryles Temporada Latina will be open until 1:30am this evening, and cover charge will be only $3 for anyone coming from the Ritmo Masacote concert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or!  Hop on over to Club Caribe after the concert where they will be providing free admission to all concert attendees!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Grey Fedora Hat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angel Santiago</member_name><member_id>5161614</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266713893000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264963315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ritmo Masacote at Ryles Jazz Club</name><id>12474882</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266540300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/12474882/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/7/global_13068967.jpeg</photo_url></item>