<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Spirals of Creation are important to understand for accessing natural Organic Eternal Life Healing Energy Flows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is necessary for restoration of our DNA and other Energetic Templates, Merkaba Flows, and Krystic Ascension as taught by Jeshua-12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time will begin viewing and discussing a Keylontic Science DVD called "Spirals of Creation", as well as circulating a 58 page study guide with color illustrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both can be purchased from the Azurite Press by clicking on this link: &lt;a href="http://www.azuritepress.com/products_us/spoc.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.azuritepre&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spirals of Creation are directly related to the topics of DNA Template Regeneration and Merkaba Flows, which we started to explore during our October and November Meetups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members who have not attended those Meetups are requested to click under the "Meetups" tab above and then select "Past" to view details there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time a distinction is made between "Krystic Universes" which are eternal life systems (as were all originally created to be), and finite life fallen Metatronic black hole universes which are subject to ultimate space dust return to Source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Krystic flows are based upon the Krystal Spiral expansion mathematics, whereas those degrading into finite life matrices are based on the Golden Mean and Fibonacci expansion spirals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the details, we can begin to understand the technicals of what is happening in our own universe, and why it is necessary to use the Keylontic Science techniques to heal the resulting distortions within our own multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is also related to why it is necessary to work on regenerating our original organic DNA templates and Merkaba flows, and accessing the Krystal Spiral.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As extracted from the product description, these details will be presented...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Krystal Spiral is key to the expansion of structure in a Krystic universe. It regulates the cycles of expansion and back flow return to Source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It operates in conjunction with Krystic Merkaba to regulate the flow of Primal Life Force current down through cosmic structures into our bodies and everyday lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The structure and mode of operation of the Golden Mean and Fibonacci Spirals differ in significant ways from the Krystal Spiral.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has major implications for their associated Merkaba mechanics, leading to a severing of higher dimensional connections, cutting off flows to and from Source and trapping of energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will explore the origins of both spiral sets and compare their mode of operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The growth of the Krystal Spiral is from the original Kathara Grid. This is compared to the development of the Golden Mean spiral from the Golden Mean rectangle, the development of the Fibonacci spiral from this and their relationship to the &amp;lsquo;Tree of Artificial Life&amp;rsquo; in Metatronic science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These spirals lie at the foundation of sacred geometry. The numbers and proportions associated with them are important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They influence Merkaba spin speeds and arise in many fields, e.g. biology, architecture, art, etc. The spirals directly impact physics and how energy flows into and operates in our world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In particular the Metatronic deviations have impacted our &amp;lsquo;natural&amp;rsquo; world in a very significant way leading to a closed isolated local universe with a finite amount of energy that is degrading, as detailed in our conventional energy laws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also affect the way our electricity and magnetism operate, our planetary magnetic field, etc. They condition the world we live in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately the Krystal Spiral is also present and accessible. This brings the possibility for full higher dimensional connection, open energy flows with Source and direct Source connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the spirals and understanding their differences empowers both our stewardship in creation and our connection to Source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is both a sacred entrustment, putting the sacred back into science, and a fascinating vista on our journey home.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Click on the link below for more info:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.azuritepress.com/products_us/spoc.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.azuritepre&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the length of this DVD, we may not be able to view it all this time. If not, this will continue on to the next month.  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Meetup adjourns at 9:00 PM. Please bring your own refreshments. Do not park in 2nd driveway which has the "ULCS Clinic" sign at the end. Come up the first driveway (with Meetup Sign). This is across the street from mailbox #298. Enter through the front door, which has another Meetup sign. No need to knock. Just go on downstairs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup sign at end of first driveway and on front door. No need to knock.  Meeting is in downstairs classroom.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305856538000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290447026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spirals of Creation:  Krystal spiral vs Fibonacci spiral</name><id>jdtqnypdbtb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305669600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/15526871/</event_url></item>