<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Thanks to those (7) who showed up for our December meeting, we had a typically animated discussion about the nature of time, and whether there's a scientific consensus about the so called block universe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;January Topic: Are we better off with false beliefs?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's an interesting paper, Positive Illusions, Perceived Control, and the Free Will Debate, at &lt;a href="http://gfp.typepad.com/the_garden_of_forking_pat/files/positive_illusions.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://gfp.typepad.co...&lt;/a&gt; which raises the question of whether or not we're better off being deceived about free will (it's being discussed at &lt;a href="http://gfp.typepad.com/the_garden_of_forking_pat/2007/12/positive-illusi.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://gfp.typepad.co...&lt;/a&gt; ). Naturalists understand and accept that we don't have libertarian (contra-causal) free will or ultimate responsibility, but are we wise to make this widely known? Perhaps all hell would break loose. Just as some think we can't be good without god, some think, including Israeli philosopher Saul Smilanksy (critiqued at &lt;a href="http://www.naturalism.org/fiction.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.naturalism...&lt;/a&gt; ) that we can't lead meaningful and moral lives without the illusion of free will. How would we decide that question, and if we need to be deceived about free will, how should we proceed? More generally, is it possible to live in the harsh (some would say) light of science, or must people suppose there's something beyond the natural world in order to stay psychologically healthy? Lastly, might it be that accepting a naturalistic view of ourselves would increase, not diminish, our psychological well-being?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;best,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org&lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200528285000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197335453000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Are we better off with false beliefs?</name><id>6891465</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200355200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/6891465/</event_url></item>