<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Join us for some Spanish and mingling around as we celebrate the launch of our Boston Spanish Fanaticos group! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are looking forward to meeting you all &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;. All levels are welcome. Take advantage of the opportunity to meet cool new people, and put your Spanish into practice! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come ready to rotate and talk to as many people as you can. We are all friendly and eager to get to know you. This is a very informal gathering. It will provide all of us with the opportunity to practice speaking Spanish in a real setting and get somewhat more acquainted to the Latino culture. Please bring your cameras and feel free to take and post as many pictures as you would like. Help us grow our community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will end at 9:00pm but you are free to stay and hang out with people you meet afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your questions about grammar or about Hispanic culture. I will be glad to answer any questions you may have !!! Si eres Hispano sientente por favor en confianza de hablar sobre tu pais y tu cultura. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an event sponsored by SpanishBlackBelt. No Meetup fee will be charged. Please support this meeting venue by ordering some appetizers and/or drinks so that we can continue meeting here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP if you are planning on coming. Nos vemos Pronto !!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If instead, or in addition, you want to attend one of our &lt;b&gt;regular Spanish classes&lt;/b&gt;, please &lt;a href="http://adults.spanishblackbelt.com/spanishtraining/checkout/searchcolor.asp?area=Boston%20MA" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to access all Small Group sessions currently being offered by Spanish Black Belt.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup badge and a big smile!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nico</member_name><member_id>8345418</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256512197000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Fanáticos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Spanish-Boston</urlname><id>1542675</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston's Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255935698000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Spanish Fanaticos Launch Event (Happy Hour)</name><id>11658791</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256338800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Spanish-Boston/events/11658791/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/global_11304205.jpeg</photo_url></item>