<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.370975</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University Institute of Politics</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>4449572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Demonstration at Newt Gingrich's Boston Event WARNING: NO RON PAUL PARAPHERNALIA ALLOWED! Whether we'd like to admit it or not, the mainstream media is telling us that Newt Gingrinch has surged to top-tier candidate status. We need to show up and inform his conservative supporters that he is a big-government Republican. I propose we wave anti-Net signs outside his Boston event this Friday, and then try to ask him difficult questions at his Q&amp;amp;A. PLEASE, DO NOT BRING RON PAUL STUFF; this will be a Newt protest. I suggest we wave signs from 4-6ish and then try to get into his forum. Please make/bring your own signs. If you need sign ideas or don't think that Newt is a legitimate threat I suggest you visit this site: &lt;a href="http://www.ronpaulforums.com/showthread.php?329010-Comprehensive-list-of-Newt-Gingrich-positions" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ronpaulfor...&lt;/a&gt; (member of CFR, voted for dept of education, voted for NAFTA, super interventionist, flip-flopped on torture, pushed school prayer amendment, supported Romneycare, said he'd bypass supreme court, want more foreign aid for Egypt, made climate change commercial with pelosi) I think I'll try to make a handout summarizing his these positions Here are some specific details about his visit: Newt and Callista screen A City Upon a Hill at Harvard University's Institute of Politics Friday, November 18, 2011 5:00 pm - Screening 6:00 pm - Forum and Q&amp;amp;A Session 7:15 pm - Book Signing Harvard Institute of Politics 79 John F. Kennedy Street Cambridge, MA 02138 &lt;a href="http://www.newt.org/events" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newt.org/e...&lt;/a&gt; REMEMBER, NO RON PAUL STUFF!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321654282000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321378606000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Demonstration at Newt Gingrich's Boston Event</name><id>41257352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321650000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/41257352/</event_url></item>