<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311540</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919685</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;   Our spiritual center, The Center of Light, is hosting national speaker, author, mystic, and priest Father Peter Bowes for a weekend of seminars on spiritually relevant topics. This Friday he will be speaking about how to find your real power and center by stilling your mind. Father Peter is a Master Teacher with decades of experience in practicing and teaching meditation for the purpose of deepening one's spiritual experience. If you have any interest in meditation, the law of attraction, or the inner spiritual path, you won't want to miss this one. There will also be an opportunity to meet Father Peter after the seminar. &lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna and Rev. David&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All it takes is one experience of true stillness in your being to provide a contrast to the usual busy-ness of your mind. After that point, living on mental autopilot won?t be appealing to you. Your thoughts are seeds which bear the fruits of tomorrow. Considering this, you can learn how to master your thinking, so you can choose the fruits that you want. Mastering the mind and knowing its true function is the key to empowerment and self-mastery. Learn how you can begin to master your destiny in this seminar designed to help you change your reality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A $25 donation is suggested.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347479000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208837451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Changing Your Life by Stilling the Mind</name><id>7787139</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209166200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/7787139/</event_url></item>