<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Madbury Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.137726</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sae Nhbe</name><city>Durham</city><id>1551116</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.925995</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been to a Murder Mystery Party?&amp;nbsp; Well it's one party&amp;nbsp;you don't want to miss out on. This Murder Mystery game is &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt; a board game; everyone will be participating at the same time.&amp;nbsp; Some requirements are that you&amp;nbsp;must&amp;nbsp;not be afraid of the dark and, second, you&amp;nbsp;must dress all in black clothing!&amp;nbsp; This is not a show that you just stand back and watch--you will be actively participating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have received permission to have this party in an historic and active Fraternity House on the UNH campus in Durham, NH.&amp;nbsp; If you ever wanted to party in a Fraternity House now is your chance!&amp;nbsp; The Fraternity name is Sigma Alpha Epsilon (SAE).&amp;nbsp; They have two huge rooms and some other interconnecting rooms that we can use. &amp;nbsp;If you're lucky you might even see a Fraternity brother there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be having a potluck before the game so bring something special to eat. &amp;nbsp;We will meet at 6 pm to socialize at which time I will explain the game and give a brief tour of the house.&amp;nbsp; Then at 7pm the mystery will start. &amp;nbsp;This is not a children's event so please do not bring your children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please park behind the house or in front of the building. The building is an all-brick building with two concrete lions guarding the house.&amp;nbsp; The driveway is between the SAE Fraternity and another brick Fraternity building to the right of it on Madbury Road.&amp;nbsp; Do not go up the one-way street on the left of SAE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I anticipate we will have a fairly large amount of people coming so I will be limiting the number of people for this event to a total of 40.&amp;nbsp; I will be combining this event with&amp;nbsp;other meetup groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please&amp;nbsp;RSVP&amp;nbsp;"Yes" only&amp;nbsp;if you are willing to actively participate.&amp;nbsp; This is not a spectator event.&amp;nbsp; Also, be aware that this event is played in nearly dark rooms. &amp;nbsp;Please dress in&amp;nbsp;comfortable (and&amp;nbsp;BLACK) clothing as you might be dying on the floor!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details will follow as we get closer to the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$10 at the door the night of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions call me at 603-312-6735 or 603-868-1346.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there for a memorable night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy in the black cape.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300747115000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>It's a blast and it's a great way to meet others!</why><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299509353000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Murder Mystery Party</name><id>16828854</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300572000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/16828854/</event_url></item>