<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>To be posted a few days before</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06408</zip><lat>41.498900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ralphs Place</name><city>Cheshire</city><id>1319244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.901100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey All,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time to wind down the year and get into the Holiday spirit with great friends, new people that will be great friends and chase away the blues.  Whatever holiday you celebrate bring it with you to share with whomever is here.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's celebrate the season and reflect on good things that have come our way in 2010 and get ready for (&lt;i&gt;gulp&lt;/i&gt;) 2011.  I am inviting all to share this holiday at my house.  The situation is the same as past wine tasting events...   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wine night at my house... on a Sat December 4, 2010! in Cheshire CT 6 pm - 10 pm +   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine (no boxed wine please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food, hors d'oeuvre or dessert.  Please indicate what food item you want to bring when you sign up.  Bring your wine glass also.  I have a few but not enough for all in case you forget to bring one.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is $15 or more.  Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $30 or more depending on the quantity of people in the group, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste testing...  Reds Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir, whites - sav blanc, chards, reisling, pinot grigio, etc   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be courteous to the group and ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a persons spot if you do not show up.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event if you don't have it already to all the &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVPs, due to this being a private residence.  It should go without saying to &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;Drink Responsibly.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  I will have water and coffee too.  Do not RSVP on more than one site to get an accurate count of people.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ralph&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve C</member_name><member_id>6197158</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph</member_name><member_id>8774347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291669046000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289869086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Holiday Wine Party "At Ralphs House"</name><id>15459372</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291503600000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/15459372/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/a/e/global_16726014.jpeg</photo_url></item>