<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The one day full presidential traverse is a goal of many and deserving of its reputation as a premier hike in the Whites. Unfortunately for many folks the full traverse is quite daunting with the elevation and distance far longer than they have typically ever hiked. For many this discourages them from even trying. The "presi lite" is intended for folks who arent out ot check off a list yet still want to get 95% of the views and the experience for less overall effort and time. This still is a 12 hour plus day going over some very rocky terrain so its definitely an advanced event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike starts at Appalachia at 5:00 Am and ends at Crawford Notch many hours later. The route is Valley Way to Madison Hut, then Gulfside to the West side connector to the Crawford Path. The "Lite" aspect is that there is no plan to hit any of the summits along the way .Even though we may skip the summits, this is one of the greatest hikes in the Northeast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone wanting to check off the boxes for the presidentials should find another hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is about 16 miles long with 6800 feet of total ascent. For reference a conventional traverse with all the summits is 20 miles and 8500 feet of ascent. Although the distance may be less than Isolation, the Owl or the Bonds in a day, the majority of the route is on rock with most of the hike above treeline with considerably more elevation gain. This is spectacular on a good day but for those unprepared or in less than reasonable condition, it is lot more effort than any of the 4000 footer hikes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In interest of keeping the group together, there will not be the option of bagging summits and then rejoining the group. If the group as a whole decides they want to add a summit it will be group decision that will take into account all the hikers and the schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is weather dependent, a forecast on THURSDAY night for rain or high winds will cancel the event &lt;br /&gt;

 This is still a very long day and is definitely an "advanced" hike. Water and electrolyte management are a must. I plan to carry minimal water up to madison hut, refill at the hut, then at the spring at the base of Clay and finally at Lake of the Clouds hut. I recommend powdered or tablet electrolyte supplements rather than lugging electrolyte liquids up the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pace will be intentionally slow and steady especially in the morning as it is quite easy to get burnt out early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will begin and could end in the dark, Bring a reliable headlamp with fresh batteries. Most folks will want to plan local accommodations Thursday evening and Friday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will only be done with a reasoanble forecast. It unfortunately can not be postponed to the weekend due to participants availlabilty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those interested in participating will have to plan to participate in a mandatory car spotting session the night before Thursday 8/23 at 7 PM. If you cant make it up for the car spotting session dont sign up. It is not practical to drive up the morning of the event.  The intent is to leave at least one car at the Cog and one at Crawford. Due to the car spotting, plan on having to drive back up to Appalachia after the hike although attempts will be made to minimize driving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All participants must be equipped with the 10 essentials in their packs and have recent significant hiking experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am setting this up as a wait list event. Once you have answered the questions and I have had a chance to review your answers I will add you to the list if you appear qualified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group size will be 8 maximum and I have already preapproved a few qualified hikers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345976842000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343662605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presidential Traverse Lite  - Friday hike</name><id>75527552</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345798800000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/75527552/</event_url></item>