<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>582 West St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02333</zip><lat>42.019890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 378-9335</phone><name>Johnny Macaroni's</name><city>East Bridgewater</city><id>1043647</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.980775</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Members and Guests of the SSDOMG for a rare Saturday Night Dinner!&amp;nbsp; Johnny Macaroni's in East Bridgewater is located on Route 106 just a couple miles from Route 24 and a few miles from Route 18.&amp;nbsp; They are what we can consider an "inexpensive" restaurant where just about everything on the menu is under $20, with more than half of their menu items under $15 (including entrees).&amp;nbsp; This is great for the budget-conscious who want to dine out affordably.&amp;nbsp; Please feel free to&amp;nbsp;bring a friend and join us for a Saturday Night Dinner in the heart of the South Shore!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday Night Dinner!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, September 10th @ 6pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;582 West Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;East Bridgewater, MA 02333&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;508-378-9335&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnymacaronis.com"&gt;www.johnnymacaronis.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet outside the front door. We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.&amp;nbsp; Meet us at our table after we are seated.&amp;nbsp; The reservation is under "Angela."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. We may be separated into two tables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. They can accomodate a party in excess of 10 people but we need to be there by 6pm to avoid a wait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. If anyone wants to carpool from Braintree please post in the Talk About it Section.&amp;nbsp; If there is enough interest by&amp;nbsp;Mon 9/5&amp;nbsp;I will post a carpool.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: [Current] Annual Members &amp;amp; 1 Guest&amp;nbsp;- FREE, Members - $2 each; Guests - $2 each; $6 to become a 2011 Annual Member&amp;nbsp; (One of your last chances&amp;nbsp;to do so as 9/30 is the last date you can&amp;nbsp;become a 2011 AM.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: No minimum as Angela and her Guests will dine just themselves if no one else joins us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Up to 2 per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: NOON&amp;nbsp;on Saturday, September 10th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;: Courtesy of one of Angela's Guests, Ann.&amp;nbsp; To be updated Labor Day weekend as there is a typo that I have to find.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overview: Located on Route 106 near Routes 18 and 24.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 24:&lt;/em&gt; Take the exit&amp;nbsp;for Route&amp;nbsp;106 East. Stay straight and follow Rt 106 through several sets of lights. At one point the road will come to a set of lights with a left and right turn and a fork&amp;nbsp; if you go straight with a strip mall with AT&amp;amp;T directly in front of you. go straight and bear left, keeping AT&amp;amp;T to your right&amp;nbsp;(stay in left lane for this, there will be a green arrow).&amp;nbsp; You will pass Trucchi's grocery store on your left. Continue straight for another few minutes, passing a small plaza w/Sandy Rose Cafe, antiques store and convenience store on your right. Johnny Macaroni's less than a mile after this on your right. As you cross the railroad tracks you will see a black silouhette sign with a figure pointing to parking (in back) for the restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 18 Southbound:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; Take Rt 18 through &lt;span&gt;Abington and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Whitman into &lt;span&gt;East Bridgewater&lt;/span&gt;. After passing Joppa Dance Studio and Viking Bowling,&amp;nbsp;bear right at set of lights&amp;nbsp;onto Rt 106 West. Follow for about 1 mile until you reach Johnny Macaroni's on your left (you will see a small car dealership on your right). &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 18 Northbound:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; Take Rt 18 through &lt;span&gt;Middleboro&lt;/span&gt;, and &lt;span&gt;Bridgewater&lt;/span&gt; until you reach East Bridgewater. At the set of lights at &lt;span&gt;Elmwood&lt;/span&gt; Antiques (aka Diana's Whatnot Shop) take a left onto Rt 106 West.&amp;nbsp; Follow for about 1 mile until you reach Johnny Macaroni's on your left (you will see a small car dealership on your right).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the front door or at our table after we are seated.  Reservation is under "Angela."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316646965000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314749540000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Night Dinner!</name><id>31631662</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315692000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/31631662/</event_url></item>