<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://i225.photobucket.com/albums/dd27/lorenzo66_photos/my_brother_is_an_only_child.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ciao Tutti - If you haven't had a chance to see this film you still have one more opportunity. Tonight @ 7:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's an Italian film that has received praises and has won 9 Donatello Awards (Italy's equivalent to our Oscar Awards).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any is interested please click on the links below for showtimes &amp;amp; a link to the film's official website. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Showtimes:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.cinestudio.org/index2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cinestudio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.cinestudio.org/index2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cinestudio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film's Official website:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mybrotherfilm.co.uk/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mybrotherf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission is $8.00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thing I recall about Cinestudio is that cash is the only form of payment they accept.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MY BROTHER IS AN ONLY CHILD&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Italy, 2007)&lt;br /&gt;108 min&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director: Daniele Luchetti. Screenplay by Sandro Patraglia and Stefano Rulli, based on the novel Il Fasciocomunista by Antonio Pennacchi. Cast: Elio Germano, Riccardo Scamarcio, Diane Fleri.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Best of Youth singlehandedly revived our love of Italian cinema, instantly becoming a favorite of Cinestudio audiences. This summer, The Best of Youth?s screenwriters have reunited to tell a new story of two brothers whose love/hate rivalry plays out in the bumpy politics of 1960s Italy. Older brother Manrico (Riccardo Scanarcio) is a handsome and charismatic Communist. Younger brother Accio (Elio Germano) valiantly fights to outdo him, first by joining a seminary, then by taking up with a group of young skinheads, Italian-style. The exhilarating swings between laughter, fighting, love (both fall for the same woman), and politics become a poignant tribute to that wellspring of many dramas - the family. Winner of 9 Donatello Awards (the Italian Oscars) including Best Actor (Elio Germano), Best Screenplay, and Best Cinematography.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lorenzo</member_name><member_id>4408109</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215731047000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Amici Italiani</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-452</urlname><id>535327</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>Connecticut's Viva Italia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215519123000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cinestudio - Italian Film - l'ultima sera</name><id>8298074</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215558000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-452/events/8298074/</event_url></item>