<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Guest Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Triple and Quadruple Digit Returns on your money with absolutely ZERO Risk regardless of market conditions&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SECRETS CAN MAKE YOU RICH!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oprah, Nightline, 48 Hours, 20/20  have all interviewed this legendary entrepreneur.  Learn how to Identify Foreclosures Months before ANYONE ELSE!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;300-3000% RETURNS On Your Money, and the United States Courts do half the work for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Legendary Investigator tells all...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * How to locate owners of abandoned property within minutes!&lt;br /&gt;    * How to use judgments to reduce a property?s cost!&lt;br /&gt;    * How to screen potential tenants!&lt;br /&gt;    * How to background potential business partners!&lt;br /&gt;    * How to use judgments to make a 1000% plus on your money!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:15 :: Networking&lt;br /&gt;6:45 :: Bring your deals&lt;br /&gt;6:55 :: Announcements&lt;br /&gt;7:00 :: Guest Speaker - Al Schweitzer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Al Schweitzer, with his more than 2 ½ decades of investigative experience, created a legendary reputation for success and made millions of dollars.  Schweitzer has appeared on more then 40 TV shows including Oprah, Nightline, 20/20, and 48 Hours as well as written about in books, magazines and newspapers as far away as France and Hong Kong. He is a graduate of numerous Federal and State Intelligence and Law Enforcement training programs, including the I.R.S.? Financial Investigative School. Schweitzer has been a consultant to the F.B.I., Department of Treasury, United States Customs Internal Affairs, United States Attorney?s Office, Federal Trade Commission, numerous State Attorney Generals, and has been an Expert for the United States Congress on the subject of Asset Investigations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For many years Schweitzer was the lead investigator for the major media, ABC News &amp;amp; CBS News, as well as a number of the magazine television shows, EXTRA, 20/20, 48 Hours, even the National Enquirer (tabloid) etc. Some of the more recognizable cases Schweitzer led included O.J. Simpson, Monica Lewinsky, Columbine, Jon Benet Ramsey, Iran-Contra, O.K. City Bombings, among others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximately 17 years ago, Schweitzer single handedly created the Judgment Recovery business, teaching people how they can make triple and quadruple digit returns on their money using his highly sought after investigative techniques, sources and resources combined with the power of the United States Court system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make a fortune processing judicial judgments!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Using Judgments to reduce the price of property&lt;br /&gt;    * Learn to use investigative techniques to give you an absolute edge in business, regardless of what industry you are in;&lt;br /&gt;    * Screen your tenants better&lt;br /&gt;    * Background potential business partners&lt;br /&gt;    * Conduct Competitor Intelligence&lt;br /&gt;    * Locate Owners of Abandoned Property&lt;br /&gt;    * Conduct Market Research to make you a better trader&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bottom Line: Information is POWER, and those that know how to obtain information will always be Steps a head of their competition!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us for the March Monthly Meeting!  Visit &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to register!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We usually have around 300-400 people at our monthly meetings, so finding where you need to be is never a problem.  When you arrive, please visit the check-in table and one of our volunteers will get you checked in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205966423000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>If you're serious about investing in real estate, the Connecticut Real Estate Investors Association is the group for you!</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203377749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting with Al Schweitzer</name><id>7357836</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205789400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/7357836/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/1/f/global_3388383.jpeg</photo_url></item>