<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360795</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1037495</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boston / Cambridge SEO Internet Marketing Networking Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite local Boston seo, affiliate marketing and search engine marketing professionals in New England area to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Microsoft NERD Center (Sampson Room, 1st Floor Conference Center)&lt;br /&gt;One Memorial Drive, Cambridge MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm to 7pm: Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Card Buffet: drop you card on the networking buffet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm to 7:30: 2 Min Elevator Pitch:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Tell us about you and your business or website interest &lt;br /&gt;* Any networking goal your trying to achieve out of this meeting?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - 7:45&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our food sponsor will be sending a product manager from N.Y to give us a brief live demo of Conductor's new &lt;a href="http://www.conductor.com/searchlight" target="_blank"&gt;Search Light SEO Tool &lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; related SEO Tips &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Conductor &amp;amp; Search Light SEO Tool: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conductor is the most widely-used SEO technology company empowering enterprise marketers to manage and improve their SEO efforts. More than 250 of the Fortune 500 and Internet Retailer 500 rely on the company’s technology solutions and expert team to continually measure, improve and manage their natural search efforts in order to increase site traffic and revenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conductor Searchlight is the go-to solution for enterprise marketers who need to take control of their brand’s search rankings and gain insight into search engine optimization (SEO) programs. Searchlight analyzes endless amounts of data so marketers can easily identify challenges in their strategy and improve their search ranking across thousands of individual keyword terms. Searchlight helps marketers manage natural search like any other marketing program, understand how they rank against their competitors and continually improve their SEO program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:45 - 8:15 Guest Speaker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Philip Nikolayev, PhD&lt;br /&gt;President &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.searchbenefit.com" target="_blank"&gt;Search Benefit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp; SEO Chat Forum Moderator&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See his detailed post on &lt;a href="http://forums.seochat.com/link-popularity-43/seo-link-building-302665.html" target="_blank"&gt;link building &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIO: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Search Benefit's founder and president, Dr. Philip Nikolayev, holds three degrees:a BA (magna cum laude) and an MA, both from Harvard University, and a PhD in Editing from Boston University's Editorial Institute. He was an award-winning instructor at Harvard in 1995-2000. An internationally known writer and marketing guru, Dr. Nikolayev has worked in the high-tech industry since the year 2000 in the varied capacities of software engineer, project manager, marketer and SEO consultant. He has provided corporate taxonomy training to large corporations, including Deloite Touche and Dun &amp;amp; Bradstreet (D&amp;amp;B). Dr. Nikolayev possesses an extensive background in computer science, linguistics and mathematical logic, as well as in several languages, SEO-based content production, and complex editorial projects. He is currently co-authoring a comprehensive textbook on SEO standards, techniques and strategies, which will serve as a basis for professional training and certification in SEO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:45pm The End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all at this informal Boston search engine round table discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge SEO MeetUp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Mark Your Calendar&lt;/i&gt; for Nov 1st &amp;amp; RSVP for the next event on October 4rth with Guest Speaker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.MurrayNewlands.com" target="_blank"&gt;Murray Newlands&lt;/a&gt; an Affiliate Marketer &amp;amp; Social Media Pro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Murray will be hosting an event on &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.monitoringsocialmedia.co.uk/boston/" target="_blank"&gt;Monitoring Social Media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; with a great line up of speakers on October 5th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special BostonSEO meetup discount with coupon code &amp;quot;BrianHawkins&amp;quot; to get 10% off&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker's Wanted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been working hard to find industry experts and to develop a formal agenda to keep it interesting for all those that attend at this new big meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food Event Sponsors:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEO Pro's, will work for food! Contact us about sponsoring the event with goodies and drinks in exchange for publicity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Matson</member_name><member_id>1490252</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Hawkins</member_name><member_id>2319452</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter T. Davis</member_name><member_id>2771541</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>24</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286838838000</updated><rating><average>4.61000013351</average><count>18</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in SEO/SEM</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSEO</urlname><id>219718</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276287583000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge / Boston SEO Meetup</name><id>13773461</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284417000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSEO/events/13773461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/9/d/global_10187021.jpeg</photo_url></item>