<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.129517</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-473-6611</phone><name>PINZ Bowling</name><city>Milford</city><id>734836</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.518942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;With 20 lanes to choose from, there’s always fun to be found. Open bowling is &lt;br /&gt;offered so we can meet on Sunday (Nov 16th) at 10 am. Each futuristic glow-in-the-dark bowling lane features the latest technology, while the seating at the lanes creates a perfect place to relax and enjoy the experience. This is for fun, doesn't matter your expertise level of bowling.  &lt;br /&gt;Pricing is an hourly rate (up to six people) or individual rate.   We can decide that morning what we would like to choose to split the payment.  Shoe rental is available at the front desk.&lt;br /&gt;     Sunday's &lt;br /&gt;Open: 10am – 5pm&lt;br /&gt;$21.95 for an hour (up to 6 people) or $4.50 per game per person.  Large group might want to consider per game pricing.  Depending on the number of YES replies will determine how many lanes we will need.  &lt;a href="http://www.pinzbowl.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pinzbowl.c...&lt;/a&gt;  Website has location directions, easy to find PINZ!&lt;br /&gt;After bowling, perhaps we can go out for Brunch somewhere local.  This will be a Fun Time!  So come on down!  Sign up by clicking the YES and submit!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the front desk what lanes for the Meetup Group</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227465253000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226231354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PINZ Bowling</name><id>9124732</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226847600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/9124732/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/1/global_4946673.jpeg</photo_url></item>