<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We usually provide handouts and have appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************************* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Friday, 4/17, we had a movie night featuring Dr. Wayne Dyer’s new movie “Ambition to Meaning”.  We all thoroughly enjoyed it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also a &lt;b&gt;BONUS Material DVD&lt;/b&gt; that many of us would like to watch, especially the part where Dr. Dyer was interviewed.  He &lt;b&gt;discussed further in depth&lt;/b&gt; about the spiritual journey from ambition to meaning. The powerful shift from the ego constructs we are taught early in life by parents and society—which promote an emphasis on achievement and accumulation—are shown in contrast to a life of meaning, focused on serving and giving back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Rickie Banning (who owns the DVDs), we get to watch this 1 hr interview.  If you haven’t seen the movie, no worries… the interview in itself is very rewarding to watch.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, Rickie facilitates a discussion where we have an opportunity to share our impressions, questions and “personal shifts” that Dr. Dyer talked about. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How The DVD was &amp;quot;manifested&amp;quot; as a Gift:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rickie Banning, BostonLOA member&lt;/b&gt;, received this wonderful gift from Dr. Wayne Dyer.&lt;br /&gt;Go to Message Board to read her story. &lt;i&gt;(Not included here because not enough space on Calendar)&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/messages/boards/thread/6796378"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rickie, once again, THANK YOU, for sharing your gift with us!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Wayne W. Dyer, Ph.D.:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;www.DrWayneDyer.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wayne Dyer is an internationally renowned author and speaker in the field of self-development. He’s the author of 30 books, has created many audio programs and videos, and has appeared on thousands of television and radio shows. His books Manifest Your Destiny, Wisdom of the Ages, There’s a Spiritual Solution to Every Problem, and The New York Times bestsellers 10 Secrets for Success and Inner Peace, The Power of Intention, Inspiration, and Change Your Thoughts—Change Your Life have all been featured as National Public Television specials.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wayne holds a doctorate in educational counseling from Wayne State University and was an associate professor at St. John’s University in New York.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243381493000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239191859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watch Interview with Dr Wayne Dyer &amp; Discussion</name><id>10142636</id><headcount>36</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241564400000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/10142636/</event_url></item>