<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>651 Willard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.235326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rattlesnake Rocks (Shea Memorial Rink)</name><city>Quincy</city><id>1303769</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.028552</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am intending to hike the entire Skyline Trail (9 miles) at the Blue Hills Reservation in Quincy and Milton this Sunday with some friends, and have decided to turn it into a meetup event, or 2 for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire trail can be seen as the blue dashed line trail on the map at this address: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/blue.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/blue.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first part of this trail, going from its starting point at the Shea Memorial Rink in Quincy all the way to the Reservation Headquarters at 695 Hillside Street in Milton, is about 5 miles long one way, and will be what is covered in this part of the meetup. As the name of the trail suggests, there will be many good views from the various hill peaks we will be passing through. The path we will be taking is highlighted below in pink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/6/a/event_135643882.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We estimate that it should take much less than 4 hours to complete this part of the hike, and we should be in time to continue on to Part II of the hike, covered in the next event, starting at 2 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With respect to arrivals and transportation to the start area, we will only be waiting for latecomers till 10:15 am before we set off. Please notify us if you need transportation from the Quincy Center T-station, and arrangements will be made if possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please wear boots or sneakers, and other proper hiking attire. As the weather is expected to be very hot, please bring lots of water, and snacks as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do note, this is meant to be a relaxing hike, so we will try to match the pace of the slowest, although there is a need to complete this part within 4 hours. Also, there will be a need to place cars at both ends of this part of the trail to facilitate transportation. If we finish the trail much earlier than 2 pm, we might be able to have some lunch nearby before coming back to continue the next part of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When RSVPing, please include a comment as to whether you will be doing part II of the hike as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wen</member_name><member_id>28888902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341884278000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341378841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Skyline Trail at the Blue Hills Part I</name><id>71899552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341756000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/71899552/</event_url></item>