<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;I'm scaling down the scope&amp;nbsp;of this workshop to one day and a few basics:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Getting in &amp;amp; out of your boat on land &amp;amp; on water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;Basic safety&amp;nbsp;info about&amp;nbsp;hypothermia and gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Paddling strokes and techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've long wanted to improve the kayaking skills of our group.&amp;nbsp; And since I'm fresh back from co-leading an AMC skills weekend in Maine, I think the time is right.&amp;nbsp; This workshop will be&amp;nbsp;geared toward&amp;nbsp;paddlers from raw beginner to intermediate.&amp;nbsp; And we'll keep the group small to facilitate one-on-one instruction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll paddle out to a sandy beach where we'll practice falling out of our boats (wet exits) and getting back into them; alone (self rescue) &amp;amp; with help from a partner (assisted rescue).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/2/d/event_48434381.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; If you absolutely do not want to go swimming,&amp;nbsp;you can participate by watching and helping others.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please let me know this ahead of time.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; And we'll see how the morning goes and probably want to have a leisurely paddle after lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You'll need&lt;/strong&gt;: kayak, paddle, PFD, towel, change of clothes, and your lunch.&amp;nbsp; If you have a paddle float, spray skirt,&amp;nbsp;and any other safety gear, please bring them but they are not required.&amp;nbsp; The water&amp;nbsp;is pretty warm&amp;nbsp;but if you have any kind of wetsuit or dry top, bring them with you as well.&amp;nbsp; Otherwise, a 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;synthetic shirt&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; and bathing suit or trunks should be fine.&amp;nbsp; Do Not Wear Cotton.&amp;nbsp; Contact me if you have any questions.&amp;nbsp; Leave all valuables in your car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: If your kayak does not have bulkheads separating the bow &amp;amp; stern compartments from your cockpit,&amp;nbsp;please contact me.&amp;nbsp; You may need to buy float bags or use a different boat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;I will have an extra kayak available for this workshop if anyone needs one.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Getting back into your boat&lt;/strong&gt; after a capsize could mean the difference between a minor inconvenience and a complete disaster.&amp;nbsp; You cannot just climb back into a kayak while you're floating in the water.&amp;nbsp; The boat will keep rolling over until you&amp;nbsp;exhaust yourself.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;But&amp;nbsp;there are a few simple techniques that make it possible to&amp;nbsp;get back in and continue safely on your way.&amp;nbsp; (None of them are very graceful, but we won't be&amp;nbsp;posting any embarrassing photos on the website!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing how to do this protects yourself, but it also protects your paddling partners who might otherwise&amp;nbsp;put themselves in danger trying to rescue you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will not be a comprehensive course, but it will go a long way toward helping you paddle more safely.&amp;nbsp; In the process, you'll also gain confidence with your boat and in yourself.&amp;nbsp; This will enable you to enjoy kayaking much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;NOTE: Time and location subject to change due to weather or other factors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Whether you sign up for this workshop or do one with a commercial outfitter, I highly recommend that EVERYONE who kayaks take at least one basic skills class.&amp;nbsp; Even if you've been paddling for years, if you have not practiced self and assisted rescues,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;you risk hypothermia and drowning if you cannot get back into your boat once you've fallen into the water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking poses inherent risks and dangers. Participation in this workshop is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>LOCATION MAY CHANGE Depending On Water/Air Temperature</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314708161000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314024973000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Skills Workshop: Captain of Your Own Ship</name><id>30421521</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314451800000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/30421521/</event_url></item>