<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Atlantic Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.353001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-930-5530 </phone><name>The Federal Reserve</name><city>Boston</city><id>818425</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Are you sick of the ruinous policies of the Federal Reserve System?  Have you seen various documentaries regarding the Federal Reserve and just get angry?  Would you like to participate in an organized national protest against the Fed?  &lt;u&gt;This&lt;/u&gt; is your chance:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;End the Fed! will announce the initiation of a&lt;br /&gt;grassroots, unfunded, transpartisan citizens movement&lt;br /&gt;for Sound Money with rallies at&lt;br /&gt;every Federal Reserve Bank and office.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will begin a campaign of support for the passage of&lt;br /&gt;H.R. 2755, Federal Reserve Board Abolition Act&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proposed Ideas for&lt;br /&gt;End the Fed! Action Program*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   1. November 22nd rallies for Sound Money; public awareness, media attention&lt;br /&gt;   2. Public educational campaign, petition drive and Congressional lobbying campaign for HR 2755&lt;br /&gt;   3. Campaign for a public, congressional audit of the Federal Reserve Bank&lt;br /&gt;   4. Campaign for a public, congressional audit of the gold held by the US Treasury Department&lt;br /&gt;   5. Legal challenges to the constitutional validity of the Federal Reserve Bank and FRN&lt;br /&gt;   6. Development of alternate, commodity backed currencies; local, community currencies&lt;br /&gt;   7. Development of free market barter and trade systems&lt;br /&gt;   8. Establishment of private banking institutions based on precious metals and commodities&lt;br /&gt;   9. Civil Disobediance&lt;br /&gt;  10. Exercise of 10th Amendment: States Rights, Powers Reserved to We the People&lt;br /&gt;  11. Election of representatives supportive of a Free Economy, Sound Money, Rule of Law and Constitutional Principles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      *Please note that this is only a partial list of proposed ideas for development.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please visit www.endthefed.us for more details or more information&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It won't be hard... Just show up!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4883658</member_name><member_id>4883658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227539367000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227194844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>End The Fed! Boston Rally!</name><id>9200190</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227366000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9200190/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/e/global_6377678.jpeg</photo_url></item>