<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi- &lt;b&gt;Screening time is 2:05 pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;Last Train Home&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a highly-anticipated documentary and it may sell out. You can purchase advance tickets on-line at : &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/ticketing.aspx?theatreid=231" target="_blank"&gt;https://tickets.landm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the Amsterdam International Documentary Film Festival Best Feature Award and&lt;br /&gt;100% Rating on Rotten Tomatoes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every spring, China’s cities are plunged into chaos as 130 million migrant workers journey to their home villages for the New Year’s holiday. This mass exodus is the world’s largest human migration—an epic spectacle that reveals a country tragically caught between its rural past and industrial future. Working over several years in classic verité style Chinese-Canadian filmmaker Lixin Fan (with the producers of the award-winning hit documentary Up the Yangtze) travels with one couple who have embarked on this annual trek for almost two decades. Like so many of China’s rural poor, Zhang Changhua and Chen Suqin left behind their two infant children for grueling factory jobs. Their daughter Qin—now a restless and rebellious teenager—both bitterly resents their absence and longs for her own freedom away from school, much to the utter devastation of her parents. Emotionally engaging and starkly beautiful, Last Train Home’s intimate observation of one fractured family sheds light on the human cost of China’s ascendance as an economic superpower. (Zeitgeist Films) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tells the story of a family caught, and possibly crushed, between the past and the future--a story that, on its own, is moving, even heartbreaking. Multiplied by 130 million, it becomes a terrifying and sobering panorama of the present.  NY Times&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;An expert, unobtrusive observer, (the director) disappears inside his own film and allows us to get completely inside his subjects' lives. LA Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll be going to a local restaurant for our group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Tom with a bright red Meetup Sign near the front row at the film's conclusion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284759881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>From China: Last Train Home</name><id>14807525</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286128800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14807525/</event_url></item>