<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.241085</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.571730</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Plan to arrive in time to be in your kayak and ready to paddle at 7:45 PM and we'll stay out until around 10:00 PM.  We'll head out across the lake to the big island and then meander through coves and boggy areas to look for wildlife. Bring a headlamp or flashlight since we will be out past sunset.  We will only use our lights as needed and will not be paddling with them on. This is not a trip for beginners who have no experience paddling and staying with a group.  Moon rise is at 8:15, but it will take a while before we see it above the trees.  Once we do, it should be beautiful.  We may just sit in the middle of the lake for a while admiring the view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking and launch is on Route 135 between Hopkinton and Westborough centers, approx 42.24166 North and -71.57316 West.  Do not program "Whitehall State Park" into your GPS. That will not take you to the launch site.  The nearest side road is Dale Road in Hopkinton, just west of the parking lot entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1341675650000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340718236000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Paddle at Whitehall</name><id>70793382</id><headcount>16</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341359100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/70793382/</event_url></item>