<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>501 Boston Post Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06477</zip><lat>41.279999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 891-0777</phone><name>The Corner Pocket Cafe</name><city>Orange</city><id>262473</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.029999</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>***Time and date change!!****&lt;br /&gt;The bar had something going on that night, so I moved this event to Thursday the 3rd. More drink specials to follow, so be sure to check back for future updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/b/2/event_941650.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, it's been a while, but I've found this great pool place and I figured I'd share it with you all. It's called &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/thecornerpocketcafe" target="_blank"&gt;The Corner Pocket Cafe&lt;/a&gt; and it's located on the Post Road in Orange, actually a little ways down from Blue Cube which is where we had our first Pool Night way back when.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've met and talked with the owner who is extending to us a great table discount. Essentially, it'll be $10 per table per hour and if we get enough people, the price will go down from there. So a table will end up splitting that either 2-4 ways, obviously depending on how many people are playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a great, no fuss, pool hall that serves excellent food along with well made drinks (with nicely priced double's as well). They also have a great selection of Scotch's and have some awesome bartender's that live in the area as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drink specials will be forthcoming, I'll be contacting the owner again closer to the date and again, if we get enough people I'm sure we will be rewarded with even more specials. I will update this with further specials details soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to be a stickler for the rules, you can take a look in &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/boards/view/viewthread?thread=2400496&amp;amp;pager.offset=20#5968726"&gt;this thread&lt;/a&gt;, however this is not a tournament, so the rules only apply for the game you are playing at that time. Obviously we'll be getting some variations to kind of loosen up the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, since this place is located on the Post Road in Orange I'm willing to give some rides to people and I'm sure others attending will as well, feel free to discuss that &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=2268079&amp;amp;pager.offset=0#5392918"&gt;in here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be your host for the night, Christine_H and you can contact me by email or by cellphone (203) 583-0932.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And as for a fee, I'm tentatively putting down only $5 for now, but that will probably change and is only necessary if you wish to play pool. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182222516000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176417640000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Return of Pool Night</name><id>5664431</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178233200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5664431/</event_url></item>