<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>800 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.348690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Prudential Center: Terrace Food Court</name><city>Boston</city><id>833924</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meetup Game Nite 8&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color: black"&gt; will be coming to Boston on January 14, 2011!  To see which groups are participating, and to learn more about this event, check out the &lt;b&gt;official Meetup Game Night Website&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://mgn.cardsconversation.org" target="_blank"&gt;mgn.cardsconversation.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey Boston -- it's time for another Meetup Game Nite!  Don't miss out on the event everyone is talking about.  Join us for our next &lt;a href="http://mgn.cardsconversation.org" target="_blank"&gt;Meetup Game Nite&lt;/a&gt; in Boston.  This is a great way to mix and mingle with old friends, meet new people, or perhaps learn something about other Meetup groups in the area! So grab your favorite board games, a deck of cards, and all of your friends for an early night on the town.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a joint meetup with a number of groups and organizations in the area (see the &lt;a href="http://mgn.cardsconversation.org" target="_blank"&gt;MGN website&lt;/a&gt; to see who's participating). Also, &lt;b&gt;MeetIn Boston&lt;/b&gt; and the &lt;b&gt;Yelp&lt;/b&gt; community will also be participating!  We may also get members of the public to join us, as the Prudential Center will be actively promoting the event on their website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Never been to a MGN?  Here's some pictures from previous Game Nites to give you a feel what to expect:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/8/a/highres_11336970.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/8/a/global_11336970.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/8/9/highres_11920073.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/8/9/global_11920073.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/8/3/highres_12551907.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/8/3/global_12551907.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/7/6/highres_13666710.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/7/6/global_13666710.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring?  Well, any card and board games are welcome. &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Apples to Apples&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Catch Phrase&lt;/span&gt; are always popular.  Up for some strategy games?  You'll see &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Settlers of Catan&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Ticket to Ride&lt;/span&gt;, and other board games being played.  For those of you who love cards, but don't quite remember how to play, don't despair! Members of &lt;a href="http://cardsconversation.org" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Cards and Conversation&lt;/a&gt; are always willing to teach old and new card games.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Mafia&lt;/span&gt; has been a hit at the past events and will surely be played again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So don't stay at home and watch TV, come out and have some FUN with us. And if you're going out on Friday night, the event is early enough that you can come socialize, play a few games, and then hit the town. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come for dinner, some warm drinks, or just games and socializing! Since this is an open event, come early, come late, stay for a bit, stay for the whole event, anything goes! Games last until 9:30pm or so, and many people go out for drinks and food at &lt;b&gt;Legal Sea Food&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cheesecake Factory&lt;/b&gt; after the event...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the rear of Food Court next to &lt;b&gt;Pizzeria Regina&lt;/b&gt;. Look for the Meetup sign.  &lt;a href="http://mgn.cardsconversation.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you game???&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO GET THERE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;By car:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; Here are some &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/gettinghere/directions.php" target="_blank"&gt; driving directions&lt;/a&gt; to the event.  Street parking on Bolyston Street and the surrounding streets are available, but it is very limited, especially on a Friday night. Your best best will be to park at the &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/parking/parking_map.php" target="_blank"&gt;Prudential Center garage&lt;/a&gt;, $12 with validation at any store or food vendor.  For more information about parking at Prudential Center, visit their &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/parking/rates.php&amp;quot;" target="_blank"&gt;parking rates&lt;/a&gt; page.  A map showing the parking garage entrances is &lt;a href="http://www.prudentialcenter.com/parking/parking_map.php&amp;quot;" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The cheapest and most convenient way to get here is to carpool with a couple of friends -- when you split the cost of parking, it can be cheaper than the parking and taking the subway...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;By subway:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;  If you are coming in via the subway, you have a number of great options: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Green Line:&lt;/b&gt; For 'E' trains only, please use &lt;b&gt;Prudential Station&lt;/b&gt; on Huntington Avenue.  For all other Green Line trains, please use &lt;b&gt;Copley&lt;/b&gt; on Boylston Street at Dartmouth Street (next to the Boston Public Library) or &lt;b&gt;Hynes Convention Center&lt;/b&gt; on Massachusetts Avenue at Newbury Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Orange Line or Commuter Rail:&lt;/b&gt; There's a direct underground connection between Copley Mall and &lt;b&gt;Back Bay Station&lt;/b&gt; on the Orange and Purple Lines. From Copley Center you can cross the Copley Bridge into Prudential Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the game players</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>8840173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295107337000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>174</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292281123000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup Game Night 8!</name><id>15724763</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295047800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/15724763/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/7/global_20245543.jpeg</photo_url></item>