<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;During the summer at our regular monthly meetings we change gears a bit and watch a movie together. We're showing Matthew Chapman's "The Ledge", a philosophical thriller about belief and its consequences. Chapman is an accomplished film maker, science advocate, writer, and the great-great grandson of Charles Darwin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is from Greater Boston Humanists showing: "Chapman started one of the largest science policy initiatives in American history, the effort to get the presidential candidates to have a debate on science in 2008. The organization of which he is still president, "Science Debate," has nearly 30 Nobel prizewinners as signatories, a hundred major science organizations, as well as the heads of almost every university in America.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has written and directed five independent movies and written several mainstream pictures. His latest film, The Ledge, (Official Selection at Sundance 2011) stars Charlie Hunnam, Liv Tyler, Patrick Wilson, Terrance Howard, and Christopher Gorham. The Ledge is a thriller in which a battle of philosophies between a fundamentalist Christian and an atheist escalates into a lethal battle of wills. Ultimately, as a test of faith, or lack of it, the believer forces the non-believer onto the ledge of a tall building. He then has one hour to make a choice between his own life and someone else&amp;sup1;s. Without faith in an afterlife, will he be capable of such a sacrifice?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The video trailer on the film from Sundance can be found here: 
&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hKvQcOK3ZeQ"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hKvQcOK3ZeQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the director's take on the movie can be found here: 
&lt;a href="http://friendlyatheist.com/2011/06/24/why-should-you-see-the-ledge-a-guest-post-by-matthew-chapman/"&gt;http://friendlyatheist.com/2011/06/24/why-should-you-see-the-ledge-a-guest-post-by-matthew-chapman/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're planning on starting the movie at 7pm, but feel free to show up at 6:30 if you'd like to chat or help set up (or claim a good seat). &amp;nbsp; All are welcome to hang out after the movie for a&amp;nbsp;discussion.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310667363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309549451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A film directed by and starring atheists? Yes! Come and see "The Ledge".</name><id>24257831</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310511600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/24257831/</event_url></item>