<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>811 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.350563</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-345-5432</phone><name>Rudi's Cafe&amp;Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>1220315</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110346</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a great night of productive business/social networking! We've left our room at the Watertown Library and found an awesome location - Rudi's Cafe &amp;amp; Bar at 811 Mass Ave in Boston!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event on April 6th at 6:00pm will be a collaboration between &lt;u&gt;3 Networking Groups&lt;/u&gt;- so you'll have a GREAT OPPORTUNITY to meet NEW professionals in the Boston area that you've never met. The event will be more social than previous 'Successful Anonymous' networking meet ups, but nonetheless will be focused on productive, efficient relationship building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 3 Networking Groups involved in April 6th's event are... &lt;br /&gt;1.) &lt;b&gt;'Successful Anonymous Networking'&lt;/b&gt; - Run by Dimitry Neyshtadt- focused on motivation and goal setting to drive your business by pooling resources with other business professionals! &lt;br /&gt;2.) &lt;b&gt;'Networlding Boston'&lt;/b&gt; - Run by Doreen Nicastro -  focused on the ever-evolving topic of Social Media, allowing all of us to collaborate for opportunity, success and fulfillment!&lt;br /&gt;3.) &lt;b&gt;'GBRN: The Greater Boston Referral Network'&lt;/b&gt; - Run by Ian Fletcher- a referral and lead group focused on growing your business through strengthening the partnerships of its members.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for the event itself, an agenda is still being finalized. However, we already know that appetizers will be provided, we will have a bartender available to us, and the space is reserved specifically for us to get our networking on! RSVP 'Yes' and tell your friends who may be interested in joining! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rudi's Cafe &amp;amp; Bar&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;811 Mass Ave. &lt;br /&gt;Boston MA 02118&lt;br /&gt;617-345-5432&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*VERY IMPORTANT*&lt;/b&gt; Parking is AVAILABLE in the garage on Northampton St, which is directly across from Rudi's. Be sure to bring your Parking Voucher to the event- The first 2 Hours are validated which means it's &lt;b&gt;FREE!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any Questions?&lt;br /&gt;Just give Dimitry a call - 617-680-7431&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dimitry</member_name><member_id>10566344</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276089842000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Success Addicts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>successfulanonymous</urlname><id>1551084</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Successful Anonymous</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268844286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Successful Anonymous- 'Collaboration Celebration'- Social Networking at "Rudi's"</name><id>12901542</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270591200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/events/12901542/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/3/global_13312019.jpeg</photo_url></item>