<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>250.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I have a backcountry permit for 6 people for 6 nights in Grand Canyon National Park October 8 thru 14, 2011. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Here is the itinerary. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Friday 10/7/11, fly to Phoenix AZ, I would like everyone on the ground by 12:30. My&amp;nbsp;flight from Manchester arrives at 10:12AM&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Rent a mini van (already reserved)and drive to Grand Canyon Village. &lt;br /&gt;

It is a 4.5 hour to Grand Canyon Village, need to find stove fuel along the way, maybe lunch/dinner too, and what ever else you may need. &lt;br /&gt;

Sunset is at 6:05 PM, sunrise at 6:25 AM, we will not get too much&amp;nbsp;daylight that night to look around the Canyon. &lt;br /&gt;

Currently I have two rooms reserved at the Yavapai Lodge East at $172.00 each for the night. &lt;br /&gt;

Each room sleeps 4. I will be trying to get some cheaper rooms as cancellations come in. I am told that Maswik is the most economical. see www. grandcanyonlodges.com if interested. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday 10/8, after a good breakfast get an early start at Hermits Rest Trail head &lt;br /&gt;

Hike 8.2 miles to Hermit Creek, BM7. Atfer setting up camp we may hike 1.5 miles each way without full packs down to the Colorado river. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Sunday 10/9, hike 4.6 miles to Granite Rapids BL8, this is right on the river, no out house. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Monday 10/10, hike 5.0 miles to Salt Creek, BL6, my permit warns of radiation in the water supply exceeding EPA daily drinking water standards but also warns that dehydration from not drinking poses a more immediate health risk. Who knows, we may save on headlamp batteries that night! &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Tuesday 10/11,&amp;nbsp; hike 7.3 miles to Indian Garden, CIG. After setting up camp we may make a 2.6 mile side trip out to Plateau Point to enjoy the evenings libations. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday, 10/12, hike 4.7 miles to Bright Angel Campground, CBG, here we stay for two nights. For those interested Phantom Ranch Canteen&amp;nbsp;is close by. Meals are served but are not cheap. &lt;a href="http://www.grandcanyonlodges.com/phantom-ranch-canteen-712.html"&gt;http://www.grandcanyonlodges.com/phantom-ranch-canteen-712.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Thursday, 10/13, we day hike toward the north rim, at least to see Ribbon Falls, an 11.6 mile round trip. Eat, drink, or give away everything that is left in your pack so you don't need to haul it out . &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Friday, 10/14, we hike up nearly 4800 feet over 6.9 miles out of the canyon on the South Kaibab trail ending near Yaki Point where we take a shuttle back to our rental or to town. We shower, we enjoy cold beer, real food, and a soft bed at Yavapai Lodge West where I have two rooms reserved for &lt;br /&gt;

$123.00 each, again, room for four in each room. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday, 10/15, pack up and head back to Phoenix. I suggest not scheduling a flight that leaves before noon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assuming that 6 of us go and we can divide costs, this is what I&amp;nbsp;estimate&amp;nbsp;for cost for myself, I hope to reduce where possible. &lt;br /&gt;

$300 air fare, I leave Manchester at 5:20AM and land at 10:12 AM on&amp;nbsp;10/7 and leave Phoenix at 1:22P on 10/15 &lt;br /&gt;

$100 airport parking &lt;br /&gt;

$150 mini van rental and gas, $900/6 &lt;br /&gt;

$60 hotels at current rates, (172+123)/6, I hope to cut this down a little &lt;br /&gt;

$32 back country permit $190/6 &lt;br /&gt;

$6 park entrance fee &lt;br /&gt;

$200 meals, things I missed, stove fuel, spending money, oh yeah, rum and beer! &lt;br /&gt;

$848 total, not too bad for over a week, did I miss anything?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

I am interested in people with at least a fair amount of backpacking experience.&amp;nbsp;If I do not know&amp;nbsp;you please tell me a little about your&amp;nbsp;recent hiking experiences. I would like to get in at least one local backpack with you before the trip. I will require a $250 deposit to cover van rental and gas, hotels, back country permit, and park entrance fee. Keep in mind my cost estimate is an estimate, if I can lower costs I will refund the difference, if higher I will ask for the difference. I will refund&amp;nbsp;your deposit only if someone takes your place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am cross posting this on MOAC and New England Hiking Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Tim&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim Gregory</member_name><member_id>10228942</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318816366000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313551969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grand Canyon Backpack October 2011!</name><id>29798971</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318005000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/29798971/</event_url></item>