<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 113</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.762356</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Morgan Trail parking lot</name><city>Holderness</city><id>9710332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.559120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;All hikers must have cold weather gear (including foot traction such as microspikes) and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. Total hiking distance is 5.4 miles starting at Mount Morgan Trailhead Back to here hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+47 ft on the Mount Morgan Trail From the parking area, the trail follows a logging road, turning left off it almost immediately. It soon reaches the Morse Trail (Morgan-Percival Connector) diverging right, leading to the Mt. Percival Trail. to the junction of Morse Trail hike 0.50 mi/16 min/-12 ft on the Morse Trail The Morse Trail descends easily to cross a small brook. It passes through a stone wall and ascends gradually, crosses a brook on a footbridge at 0.4 mi., passes through another stone wall, and bears right to meet the Mt. Percival Trail, 0.2 mi. from NH 113. to the junction of Mount Percival Trail hike 1.80 mi/1 hr 37 min/+1359 ft on the Mount Percival Trail The Mt. Percival Trail passes through a clearing, and it turns left onto a relocated section, then loops back to rejoin the original route. After a slight descent, it crosses a brook and climbs moderately. Then it turns right (northeast) and traverses the south slope of Mt. Percival. The trail then swings left and climbs steeply to a fork (From this fork an alternate route diverges left and ascends a difficult and very strenuous route through a boulder cave (not recommended in wet weather), then continues up ledges to the summit.) Here the main trail turns right, struggles up a steep, rough ledgy section, crosses a cliff top with a fine view of Squam Lake, and continues over ledges to join the Crawford-Ridgepole Trail at the summit. to Mt Percival Totals Distance 2.40 mi Time 1 hr 57 min Elev Gain +1501 ft Elev Loss -108 ft Elev Change +1393 ft Back to here hike 0.80 mi/30 min/-34 ft on the Crawford-Ridgepole Trail Continuing along the ridge with minor ups and downs and occasional views, it passes just west of the actual high point of the range (sometimes called the Sawtooth, it can be reached by a short but thick bushwhack and has a restricted view), and continues to a junction with the Mt. Morgan Trail. Here the Mt. Morgan Trail leads to the right 90 yd. to a fork; the left branch (almost straight ahead) leads another 50 yd. to a fine cliff-top viewpoint, whereas the right branch climbs 50 yd. to the true summit of Mt. Morgan, where there is a restricted view north. to the junction of Mount Morgan Trail hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+38 ft on the Mount Morgan Trail Here the Mt. Morgan Trail leads right to the cliff-top viewpoint; partway along, a short spur leaves it on the right and runs to the true summit. to Mt Morgan Totals Distance 3.30 mi Time 2 hr 31 min Elev Gain +1729 ft Elev Loss -331 ft Elev Change +1398 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.10 mi/3 min/-38 ft on the Mount Morgan Trail The Mt. Morgan Trail leads from the summit to the junction with the Crawford-Ridgepole Trail. The two trails coincide, descending a set of steps. to the junction of Crawford-Ridgepole Trail hike 0.30 mi/9 min/-308 ft on the Mount Morgan Trail The two trails continue, descending to a junction where the Mt. Morgan Trail diverges left and descends off the ridge. to the junction of Crawford-Ridgepole Trail hike 1.60 mi/49 min/-1005 ft on the Mount Morgan Trail The Mt. Morgan Trail descends the southeast slope of the mountain then traverses to the south and descends east at a moderate grade. The Morse Trail (Morgan-Percival Connector) diverges left, leading to the Mt. Percival Trail. to the junction of Morse Trail hike 0.10 mi/3 min/-47 ft on the Mount Morgan Trail The main trail follows a logging road to the parking area on Rt 113. to Mount Morgan Trailhead Totals Distance 5.40 mi Time 3 hr 35 min Elev Gain +1751 ft Elev Loss -1751 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357349940000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353939408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MTS MORGAN &amp; PERCIVAL</name><id>92843392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354374000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/92843392/</event_url></item>