<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet in the parking lot at 10:30.  Lunch afterwards at the Dogwood Cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This urban sanctuary, located on the grounds of the former Boston State Hospital, offers public programs year-round. Through its Boston Schools Initiative, the Boston Nature Center provides environmental education programs to Boston elementary schools weekly. Two miles of wheelchair accessible trails and boardwalks traverse meadows and wetlands where wildlife abounds, including coyotes, pheasants, and many species of migratory birds. The sanctuary?s George Robert White Environmental Conservation Center is one of the ?greenest? buildings in Boston, teaching environmentally sustainable design by example. The site also includes the Clark-Cooper Community Gardens, Boston?s oldest and largest, providing food and a green oasis for 260 local families. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Boston/index.php&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Donation: $2 for nonmembers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Boston Nature Center is located on the grounds of the old Boston State Hospital, bounded by Morton Street (Route 203), American Legion Highway, Walk Hill Street, and Harvard Street. Many road maps and bus route maps still identify it as &amp;quot;Boston State Hospital&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;State Hospital.&amp;quot; There is ongoing construction around our borders. Please drive or walk carefully. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Mass Pike: &lt;br /&gt;Take I-90 towards Boston/NH/Maine. Follow I-90 East until the I-95/Route 128 Exit, Exit 14. Merge onto I-95 South. Take the Route 9 East exit towards Boston/Brookline, Exit 20A. Follow the directions immediately below &amp;quot;From the West.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West: &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 East to Route 1 South, the Jamaica Way. Follow the Jamaica Way (past Jamaica Pond) then follow Route 203 past Arnold Arboretum, keep to the left over an overpass, straight through a rotary (Route 203 becomes Morton Street). Continue to follow Morton Street/Route 203 past Shattuck Hospital on your left and past Forest Hills cemetery on your right. Continue under an underpass (American Legion Hwy), and turn right at the second light onto Harvard Street. Follow Harvard Street to the light and turn right onto Walk Hill Street. Take the next right at the sign for the Massachusetts Biologic Labs (460 Walk Hill Street). Follow a short distance and turn left at the Mass Audubon sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: &lt;br /&gt;Route 93 South (across Boston) until you see the South Bay Mall on your right. Look for &amp;quot;Columbia Road/JFK&amp;quot; exit, Exit 15. Take right at bottom of ramp onto Columbia Road. Columbia Road will bear to the left at the intersection of Mass Ave. and Boston Street. Follow Columbia Road until it intersects with Blue Hill Avenue. (Franklin Park Zoo will be across the street.) Make left turn on Blue Hill Ave.; get into the right lane and follow to the intersection of American Legion Highway (at Mobil Station). Turn right onto American Legion Highway and follow to the light. Turn left onto Walk Hill Street. Take 2nd left at the sign for the Massachusetts Biologic Labs (460 Walk Hill Street). Follow a short distance and turn left at the Mass Audubon sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: &lt;br /&gt;Off Route 128, take Milton Exit (138 North). Follow through Mattapan Square, following Blue Hill Ave. until you come to Walk Hill Street (~5 miles). Turn left onto Walk Hill Street and follow through 2 sets of lights. Take your next right at the sign for the Massachusetts Biologic Labs (460 Walk Hill Street). Follow a short distance and turn left at the Mass Audubon sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Public Transportation&lt;br /&gt;By MBTA bus: (Suggested Routes below:) Route # Bus Stop Leaves from Service &lt;br /&gt;14 Am. Legion Hwy &amp;amp; Walk Hill Dudley Station/Roslindale Sq. Runs frequently; no Sunday service &lt;br /&gt;21 Harvard St. &amp;amp; Morton St. Forest Hills/Ashmont Station Runs frequently; hourly on Sundays &lt;br /&gt;28 Blue Hill Ave &amp;amp; Morton St. Ruggles/Mattapan Station Runs frequently; every 45 min. on Sundays &lt;br /&gt;29 Blue Hill Ave &amp;amp; Morton St. Jackson Sq./Mattapan Station Runs frequently; no Sunday service &lt;br /&gt;31 Harvard St. &amp;amp; Morton St. Forest Hills/Mattapan Station Runs frequently daily &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See the website above for additional directions for walking from the various t stops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogwood Cafe&lt;br /&gt;3712 Washington St. Jamaica Plain, MA 02130   Phone: 1-(617)-522-7997&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209393417000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208536806000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Nature Center walk</name><id>7764306</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209220200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7764306/</event_url></item>