<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>The Shoppes at Blackstone Valley Mall</address_2><address_1>70 Worcester Providence Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01527</zip><lat>42.192432</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-853-4000</phone><name>Blackstone Valley Cinema 14</name><city>Millbury</city><id>479940</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.770540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Resistance is Futile! A fully restored STAR TREK: The Next Generation - The Best of Both Worlds is being shown at 7:00pm, the evening of Thu, Apr. 25th at Blackstone Valley 14: Cinema de Lux, and I'm going. Want to tag along? &lt;strong&gt;You'll have to get your own ticket&lt;/strong&gt; at this link: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="https://www.movietickets.com/purchase/perf_id/701488937/movieid/157207" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.movietickets.com/purchase/perf_id/701488937/movieid/157207&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please only RSVP once you've bought a ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I may try to reserve a table at Pizzaria Uno or Feng based on the number of RSVPs. It would be an early dinner though, like 5:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&amp;amp;v=57TTj6Fg_Vw" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&amp;amp;v=57TTj6Fg_Vw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Synopsis: The Best of Both Worlds - the two-part storyline comprising the third season finale and the fourth season premiere of the beloved series Star Trek: The Next Generation(r)- will, for the first time ever, be seamlessly tied together as one continuous and uninterrupted story digitally restored with new CGI effects... on the big screen! Audiences will also see special clips from "Regeneration: Engaging the Borg", a behind-the-scenes look at the making of The Best of Both Worlds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Enterprise responds to a distress call from a Federation colony, but arrives to discover the colony gone, with only a crater remaining. Suspecting Borg activity, the Enterprise moves to intercept a Borg Cube, but the Borg flushes the Enterprise from the nebula with magnetometric-guided charges, boards the ship, abducts Picard and moves off at high warp speed towards Earth, with the Enterprise in pursuit. His Borg captors mutilate Picard into a half-Borg, half-human called Locutus, and begin manipulating him to gain insight into human behavior to aid their plan to conquer Earth and enslave humanity. They have also accessed Picard's extensive knowledge of the U.S.S. Enterprise, its crew, and their strategy to defend Earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning of their intentions to assimilate the culture and technology of the Enterprise through Picard/Locutus, Riker...now promoted to Captain... realizes he can use his former captain to foil the Borg. He searches for a way to use Picard/Locutus to access Borg information in the same way the Borg tapped the captain for U.S.S. Enterprise secrets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the Borg ship races toward Earth, Data attempts to use Picard/Locutus as a communications link to the enemy. With time running out, Riker must make an agonizing choice between Data's desperate attempt to end the Borg advance, or sending the U.S.S. Enterprise on a collision course with the enemy ship to stop them from reaching Earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Cast: Brent Spiner, Jonathan Frakes, Patrick Stewart&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367109737000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364171111000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner(?) &amp; a Movie: "STAR TREK: The Next Generation - The Best of Both Worlds"</name><id>110869152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366925400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/110869152/</event_url></item>