<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>93 I St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02127</zip><lat>42.334973</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-337-9531</phone><name>Rose Kennedy Greenway</name><city>Boston</city><id>747840</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.039960</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;ANOTHER UPDATE...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meetup originally was a "free flowing" event meaning you could come and go and there wasn't a specific group meeting.  It was posted to let everyone know about this festival (thanks Isabel!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that would like to meet as a group and then wander around the festival, let's meet at &lt;strong&gt;1pm at the Rings Fountain.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It might not be operating but it's a pretty noticeable landmark off of Atlantic Ave between Milk and Central Street.  I'll be at the fountain about 1pm and hopefully I'll remember to make a Meetup sign.  We can hang out for a few mins in case anyone may be late, then we can go check out the festival.  Feel free to hang out with the group as little or as long as you want, just come and have fun and make some new friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UPDATE:  Jack S. has volunteered to coordinate a specific time/location to MeetUp.  You are obvs more than welcome to enjoy the festival on your own or join the "meetup" group at the time/location announced.  Please see comments section below or updated info here!  Thanks! -Isabel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey guys! &lt;a href="http://bostonlocalfoodfestival.com/"&gt;The Boston Local Food Festival&lt;/a&gt; is going to be held on Sun, Oct 7th on the Rose Kennedy Greenway, near the Boston Harbor Hotel.  It's going on all day but I'll probably check it out about 1:00 or 2:00pm before heading over to the Patriots Viewing Party at The North Star. So, make an afternoon of it! Listen to some great music, sample some wares/food, and enjoy the day. Then you can come on over to The North Star and enjoy some football! ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is meant to be more of a "free-flowing" event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ENJOY! CHEERS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Isabel&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Free flowing event! This should be a great festival. Take some time to check it out!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jack S.</member_name><member_id>8756197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349793878000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348686795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Local Food Festival</name><id>84217592</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>18900000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349624700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/84217592/</event_url></item>