<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi NLPers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, a reminder: we will be starting the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, those who want a review, and those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we will get rolling with the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main event: Core Transformation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I was only allowed to use one NLP technique for the rest of my coaching/counseling career, it would be a tough choice between language patterns and Core Transformation.   Core Transformation is one of the most elegant, powerful, and general-purpose NLP techniques I have ever encountered.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will go over the Core Transformation process, then demonstrate it with one of our brave and resourceful meetup participants to transform one of their issues, and then we will practice it with each other.  Be prepared to be transformed!  If you want to do a little advanced reading, the book ? Core Transformation: Reaching the Wellspring Within, by Connirae Andreas and Tamara Andreas ? is the definitive source (Connirae is the creator of Core Transformation).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also stay for a while after the meetup, if anyone wants to work on specific issues they are having that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk straight ahead into the meeting room.  I'll probably be the one talking!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211063587000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208475225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Neuro Linguistic Programming May Meeting: Core Transformation</name><id>7760062</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210890600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/7760062/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/5/global_3984261.jpeg</photo_url></item>