<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>How can we as humanists take responsibility for and preserve our great and uncertain world unless we are conscious of and live in friendship with the self and the other? What does friendship mean to you? How does friendship affect you as a humanist and your responsibility to the world? These are some of the questions that Cliff Hakim will ask as he guides you through his seminar Life's Too Short to Drink Cheap Wine: A Salute to Friendship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cliff wrote the book by the same name which honors the life of Vin Calia and salutes Cliff’s 20-year friendship with him. Vin died from pancreatic cancer on Valentine's Day 2002, but before the Big Day Vin asked Cliff to write his eulogy, then read it to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this hour-long interactive seminar, Cliff will set context for aligning friendship with Humanism, share part of the eulogy that he read to Vin, explore your individual current values, and engage you in a thoughtful discussion that raises the bar for conscious friendship in your life and your Humanist responsibility to consider friendship as a means to create a more sustainable, promising world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cliff Hakim is a consultant, speaker and author.  He is the founder of Rethinking Work, a career consulting and executive coaching firm.  Cliff’s focus has been to guide and support people, inside and outside of organizations.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to show up at the church around 6:30pm if you would like to socialize.  The formal meeting will start at 7:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting is free and open to the public, but we always welcome donations at the door. If you are not already a paying member of GWH, we encourage you to become one.  It's only $30 for a one-year membership.  Dues help to pay the cost of speakers and other programming, and they allow us to do outreach and other activities.  Please show your support for Humanism and GWH.  You can pay dues at the GWH web site: www.worcesterhumanists.org or you can see our treasurer, Don Guyton, at the next meeting.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295374470000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292781136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clifford Hakim, “Life's Too Short to Drink Cheap Wine: A Salute to Friendship"</name><id>15772840</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294790400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/15772840/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/2/global_7423922.jpeg</photo_url></item>