<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>bpl.org</phone><name>Rabb Auditorium at Boston Public Library in Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>883985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the Boston Public Library site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/news/calendar.htm#/?i=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bpl.org/ne...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Flight from Monticello: Thomas Jefferson at War&lt;/b&gt; is a narrative of the invasion of Virginia by the traitor Benedict Arnold in 1781, when Jefferson was governor of Virginia. It was nearly five years after the Declaration of Independence was approved, and Jefferson and Virginia were unprepared for the invasion force of 1,600 men led by Arnold. Jefferson was forced to flee from Richmond and, ultimately, from mountain home of Monticello. Accused of cowardice for fleeing, Jefferson spent many years defending his actions, which both haunted him and shaped him. The book relies on many previously ignored or little-known diaries, journals and ship logs, which provide revealing details about one of the most tumultuous events in revolutionary American history. &lt;b&gt;Michael Kranish&lt;/b&gt; has been a reporter with The Boston Globe for 25 years. He has written many biographical articles about presidential candidates, including part of a series on John Kerry that was turned into a 2004 book, John F. Kerry: The Complete Biography. In 2008, he was a fellow at the International Center for Jefferson Studies at Monticello, where he did research for his new book, Flight from Monticello: Thomas Jefferson at War&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After entering the old section of the library facing out to Copley Plaza, go up the grand staircase past the stone lions. Reaching the top, take a right. That's the Abbey Room. T.J. Maher will be waiting near the stairs until 5:45 pm gathering whoever shows, then will be saving seats for people. Can't get there until just before six o' clock? Let him know so he can save you a seat. Can't get there until past 6:00 pm? It will probably be standing room only, judging from the last lecture. Grab a seat wherever. We can regroup after for dinner so the history buffs can talk about what the lecture left out. T.J. will be outside the lecture hall near the stairs, holding up a MEETUP sign after the talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Flight from Monticello: Thomas Jefferson at War (Kindle Edition)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Flight-Monticello-Thomas-Jefferson-ebook/dp/B00332FL3S/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;m=AG56TWVU5XWC2&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;qid=1265651010&amp;amp;sr=1-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;No great figures are now without multiple biographies, so why not slice up their lives into smaller subjects? Since that seems to be the current way, we're lucky to have a serious slice like this one. Kranish (a Boston Globe reporter and coauthor of John F. Kerry) focuses on Jefferson's much criticized yearlong governorship of Virginia during the last throes of the American Revolution. The British had invaded Virginia, the state militia was weak, and regular forces had not yet arrived. So Jefferson and the state legislature had to flee westward to avoid capture. By the time American forces, aided by the French, had forced a showdown at Yorktown in 1781, Jefferson's term in office had ended. Yet many held him responsible for Virginia's near disaster. That's allowed critics ever since to assail his behavior as cowardly and incompetent. Without making his book an open argument for the defense, Kranish relates the historical context and musters the facts that absolve Jefferson of the charges against him. It's hard to see how a stronger case could be made. Fluid prose makes the book readable&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Author&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonglobe.com/news/resources/bio.aspx?id=4082" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonglob...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kranish is a correspondent in The Boston Globe’s Washington bureau. He specializes in investigate reporting on national political affairs, presidential election politics and the Executive branch. Kranish has covered presidential campaigns for The Globe since 1984. In 2004, Kranish co-authored a book on Senator John Kerry during his presidential campaign entitled John F. Kerry: The Complete Biography by the Boston Globe Reporters who Knew Him Best. Kranish is a graduate of Syracuse University and has been with the Globe since 1984.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] &lt;u&gt;Topics on which writer/editor can comment&lt;/u&gt;: Executive branch, National political affairs, Presidential election politics, Washington politics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...]&lt;u&gt;Issues on which writer/editor can comment&lt;/u&gt;: Election Politics, Mitt Romney Presidential Campaign Bid, National Political Issues, Social Security&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Mural in the Abbey Room&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/central/abbey.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bpl.org/ce...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;The Quest and Achievement of the Holy Grail&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Wall paintings in the Boston Public Library installed in 1895 By Edwin Austin Abbey, R.A.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An Outline of this Version of the Legend By Henry James. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Holy Grail was fabled to be the sacred vessel from which our Lord had eaten at the Last Supper, and into which (having purchased it from Pontius Pilate), Joseph of Arimathea had gathered the divine blood of His wounds. Its existence, its preservation, its miraculous virtues and properties were a cherished popular belief in the early ages of European Christianity; and in the folk-lore from which the twelfth-century narrators, Walter Mapes in England, ChrÈtien de Troyes in France, and Wolfram von Eschenbach in Germany, drew their material, it was represented as guarded for ages in the Castle of the Grail by the descendants of the &amp;quot;rich man,&amp;quot; to whom the body of Jesus had been surrendered, where it awaited the coming of the perfect knight, who alone should be worthy to have knowledge of it. This perfect knight is introduced to us in the romances of the Arthurian cycle, so largely devoted to the adventures of the various candidates for this most exalted of rewards. Incomparable were the properties of the Grail, the enjoyment of a revelation of which conveyed, among many privileges, the ability to live, and to cause others to live, indefinitely without food, as well as the achievement of universal knowledge, and of invulnerability in battle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This revelation was the proof and recompense of the highest knightly purity, the perfection constituting its possessor the type of the knightly character; so that the highest conceivable emprise for the Companions of the Round Table was to attain to such a consecration - to cause the transcendent vessel to be made manifest to them. The incarnation of the ideal knighthood in the group here exhibited is that stainless Sir Galahad, with whom - on different lines - Tennyson has touched the imagination of all readers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;No 1. The child Galahad, the descendant, by his mother, of Joseph of Arimathea, is visited, among the nuns who bring him up, by a dove bearing a golden censer and an angel carrying the Grail, the presence of which operates as sustenance to the infant. From the hands of the holy women the predestined boy passes into those of the subtle Gurnemanz, who instructs him in the knowledge of the things of the world, and in the duties and functions of the ideal knight. But before leaving the nuns he has performed his nightly vigil has watched alone, till dawn, in the church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;No. 2. This ordeal of the vigil terminates in his departure. Clothed in red, he is girt for going forth, while the nuns bring to him Sir Lancelot, who fastens on one of his spurs, and Sir Bors, who attaches the other. [...]  [ &lt;b&gt;MORE&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/central/abbey.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bpl.org/ce...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267139289000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265651570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Michael Kranish, "Flight from Monticello: Thomas Jefferson at War" @ BPL</name><id>12551798</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266966000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12551798/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/e/global_13006622.jpeg</photo_url></item>