<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Soldiers Field Rd &amp; Everett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.364819</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artesani Park along Charles River</name><city>Brighton</city><id>723026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135521</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>There are still a few spots, so I'm going to leave this meetup open for another week for those who may change their mind. Currently we have 24 Ladies and 19 Men signed up. We can handle 8 teams of 8 on 4 nets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brettl Hupfers are hosting their summer volleyball league starting Wednesday June 2nd. If you think you are interested, RSVP and I'll send you more info. We'll be playing each Wednesday throughout the summer. It's a great way to stay in shape, and meet lots of people. The cost to join the league is 55.00$. Space is limited so sign up now! The league is competitive beginner and intermediate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Games will be at Artesani Park located off Soldiers Field Rd in Brighton, MA from 6:15 – 8:30 Wednesday nights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE PLAY / TEAM ASSIGNMENT &amp;amp; BASIC INSTRUCTION -June 2nd and June 9th. During the first 4 weeks we will have a professional volleyball instructor to do drills and work on team skills. Each group of 2 teams will work with the instructor for a 45 minute session. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGULAR SEASON -The regular season will last From June 16th to August 18th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Championship Weekend - All league players will receive free lodging at the Brettl-Hupfers Ski club in Bartlett, NH on the championship weekend. A party and cookout will be held after the games, and the winning team will receive prizes. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ken Simon</member_name><member_id>8614118</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276125718000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275574969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Outdoor Summer Volleyball League in Boston</name><id>13683880</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276121700000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/13683880/</event_url></item>