<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>on hwy 108, Long Trail parking lot on the west side</address_2><address_1>6443 Mountain Rd</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05672</zip><lat>44.520133</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt Mansfield/Stowe VT</name><city>Stowe</city><id>740157</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.771873</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is  Vermont’s  highest 4000 ft Mountain and with a long weekend, a good time to climb it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Print out a Trail map at &lt;a href="http://www.vtstateparks.com/htm/smugglers.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vermont State Parks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and find our hiking route. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will park in the Long Trail parking lot, just north of the Stowe Mountain Resort Gondola.&lt;/b&gt;   From here we will hike the Long trail (M rated) to the &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adam's Apple (4,060')&lt;b&gt;, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;hike south to the &lt;b&gt;Chin(4395 ft.)&lt;/b&gt; (Vermont's highest peak!), &lt;br /&gt;We are now on an exposed ridge walk (Let's see some views!). This Summit Ridge on the Long Trail is almost constantly above treeline, the only such long stretch of alpine zone in Vermont. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lower, and Upper Lip&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hike south to the &lt;b&gt; Nose (4,062')&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue to the &lt;b&gt;Forehead(3940 ft)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;and back to the &lt;b&gt;Nose (4,062')&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.summitpost.org/images/medium/73696.JPG" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this point  we will start our descend on the toll road to the&lt;b&gt;M rated Haselton Trail&lt;/b&gt; back to our trailhead and cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;about 10 miles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General trail information:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Mansfield has four major trails which one can hike to the summit. They range in difficulty from M (moderate) to DDD (very difficult). I don't plan on any DDD trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Long Trail, a famed route through VT, is rated as M&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Haselton Trail M&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Profanity Trail, which is rated as a DD (More Difficult)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cliff Trail, which is a very difficult trail rated DDD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These trails extend to the peaks named The Forehead, an elevation of 3940 ft., the Upper Lip and the Lower Lip, and The Chin (4395 ft.) . The Chin is Vermont's highest point. Each peak is generally named for the part of a face that Mount Mansfield resembles when viewed sideways.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Image:Mount_mansfield_20040926.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marking the trails are white and blue blazes. The Long Trail has 2&amp;quot;x6&amp;quot; white blazes. All other trails are marked with blue blazes. This is an extremely challenging .7 mile hike to the ridge, along which The Long Trail extends. To reach the Profanity Trail a long trek up The Long Trail must be done. Finally, the Haselton starts at the base of the gondolas, running up to The Toll Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;History&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mountain was called Moze-o-de-be-Wadso by the Abenaki, which meant &amp;quot;Mountain-With-A-Head-Like-A-Moose.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;adam's apple&lt;/b&gt; is on the north end of this ridge, and the &lt;b&gt;forehead&lt;/b&gt; to the south. From north of the mountain, looking south, this ridge appears as a triangular peak. At the northeastern portion of the mountain, there are spectacular cliffs. At the base of these cliffs (on the western side of the Notch Road/Rt 108), there is a large honeycomb network of talus caves. There are high cliffs on the eastern side of the Notch Road as well. These two sets of facing cliffs are separated by only a few yards at their base. The Pleasant Valley Road (from Cambridge to Underhill) follows closely to the western base of the mountain, and provides a gorgeous, intimate view of the entire ridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This facial profile is explained in a locally told story, involving an Indian legend: This mountain, as the legend goes, was taller and came to a distinct peak in ancient times. Indians of that time would seek a special, private place to 'await their maker', when they knew their time was near. One particular Native American (a chief, perhaps) chose to climb to the very top of this peak to await death even though he was crippled and could not walk without crutches. He supposely died before he reached the summit... and God carved his profile into the mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another oft-recited legend is that the two mountains, Mt. Mansfield and Camel's Hump, were formed when a man and his camel walked through the state. On becoming tired, they lay down to rest, but never awoke. They became the two mountains that we see.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diane's cell phone 603-477-5116   please post your phone # in the RSVP questions. I'll carry the list with me.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Long Trail parking lot, just north of the Stowe Mountain Resort Gondola and south of the picnic area   TRAILHEAD SOUTH</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247322946000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238011262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Face of Mt Mansfield, VT  </name><id>10034715</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246798800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10034715/</event_url></item>