<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03102</zip><lat>42.987201</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bear Brook State Park</name><city>Manchester</city><id>919334</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.474031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If your more of a three season hiker who is interested in trying out the winter hiking scene, this hike is for you!  I will not be traveling for the holiday and thought it would be great to hike.  Perhaps some other randomites out there have the 23rd off too and want to get outside.  Below are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear Brook State Park Hike: Smith Pond and Shelter Loop&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Drive to main  park entrance(in Allenstown NH) on Deerfield Rd.  Drive to the Campground entrance (on the right)) on Podunk Rd.  across from Bear Brook Horse Stables. The right turn onto Podunk Rd. is directly after a yellow &amp;quot;horse and rider&amp;quot; sign and a long group of mailboxes.  &lt;b&gt;Meet at  Hiker/Biker parking lot on the first right turn off of Podunk Rd.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   (For car GPS location: 157 Deerfield Rd. Allenstown NH .) Get more info and directions on &lt;b&gt;www.nhstateparks.org&lt;/b&gt; and Google Maps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. The park does charge a fee year round.  If you don't have a park pass sticker on your car it's $4.00/person for the day.&lt;br /&gt;    Envelopes are usually provided at three fee stations in the park.  (Cash or check to NH State Treasurer for $4.00 day pass)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. The hike is approx. 4 miles and approx. 3-4 hours depending on conditions of trails.  If there is snow, it will most likely take closer to the four hour mark, plan accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. The trail names to complete the loop are: Salt Lick Tr./Bobcat Tr./Broken Boulder Tr./Pitch Pine Tr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one of the official first days of winter so make sure to have warm clothes, bring layers.  Layers are key for winter hiking. NO COTTON!  Make sure to have snowshoes and microspikes - I'm planning on snow.  Bring snacks, and water.  We will hike as a group and stay as a group.  Always be environmentally aware and friendly!&lt;br /&gt; The trails are level and this hike is not strenuous since the highest peak  on the other side of the park Hall Mt, is 941'.  It will be a nice &amp;quot;half day hike&amp;quot; which will hopefully not be too far of a drive for anyone.  We will not be reaching a summit, but it will be nice to be in the woods.  This hike is dog friendly.  I will be bringing my two friendly golden labs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A special THANK YOU to my friend Lori (aka summitseeker) for helping me organize and lead this hike!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one with the two golden labs.  Moose and Tuckerman.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristen Curren</member_name><member_id>7131394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293141854000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291258403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tis the Season to HIKE!  Great beginners winter hiking experience.</name><id>15616247</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293122700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15616247/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/9/global_19980025.jpeg</photo_url></item>