<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Dyer Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.823509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dyer Street Dock (Gazebo on Dyer Street)</name><city>Providence</city><id>1296711</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the Second of the events I will be scheduling to offer the opportunity to assist with staging a Waterfire.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to do something different and have plenty of chance to chat with other newcomers, other Waterfire volunteers and make great contacts within the community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update this with the exact times of the effort, however, here's how it works;  I'll be coordinating with the Waterfire volunteer coordinator and let her know how many newcomers will be assisting.  She'll schedule us in and we'll show up and work a 5 hours shift, which will start somewhere around 6:30pm and run till the event ends at 11pm.  Please do not signup if you cannot commit to the full shift.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activities to be expected - Wear ALL BLACK - this is a requirement.  If we are assigned boat duty, all black, but practical.  Shore duty is business casual.&lt;br /&gt;  - Ambassador of light&lt;br /&gt;  - Starry Starry Night support&lt;br /&gt;  - Boat Crew (unlikely) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before the shift, I'd recommend that we get together for a meal at somewhere close to the event.  Perhaps the Red Fez, or McFaddens.  I'll schedule that separately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free parking for volunteers is available at the Park Rite lot at 198 Dyer Street.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Volunteer Checkin tables are here, I'll be here and be easily found.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283039199000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276347936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evening of Volunteering for  Waterfire w/ dinner beforehand</name><id>13778238</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283034600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/13778238/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>