<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's a long weekend so I'll have time to sleep later.&amp;nbsp; That's enough of a reason for a party for me.&amp;nbsp; Everybody can come - new people welcome, guests welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm  not setting a dinner time for this.  My main course will be kept hot  all day, just dig in when you want it.  Snacks and deserts will of  course be eaten all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring (select all that apply ;)  &lt;br /&gt;Games - We have plenty, but we don't have them all  &lt;br /&gt;Food  (non-snacks) - We can refrigerate or heat whatever you want to bring. I  am going to set out a make your own burrito bar. There will be plenty   for vegans, vegetarians, and omnivores.&amp;nbsp; I will also be making up a   large batch of pico di gallo. &lt;br /&gt;Food (snacks) - If you bring it, it will probably get eaten.  &lt;br /&gt;Drinks (non-alcoholic) - Sometimes everyone brings some; sometimes no one does. "You pay your dime you take your chances."  &lt;br /&gt;Drinks  (alcoholic) - I'm not driving and we'll have plenty of room for those  who want to crash, but we're not big drinkers ourselves.  &lt;br /&gt;Chairs - We  have a decent number of chairs, but if it's not too much trouble you  may want to bring one. You can even bring them and leave them if you  have any you want to get rid of.  &lt;br /&gt;Other - Bring anything you like as long as it doesn't get anyone in trouble with the law&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heat: I will be turning the heat up this time so it will be more comfortable for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donations: I have decided I want to put on even better events so I will be putting out a donations box this time.&amp;nbsp; Everything put in will go to paying for the heat and making the next event better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel/Parking:  &lt;br /&gt;Parking  - I live close to the beginning of the street, so at soon as you make  the turn start looking for parking. Most of the parking in the area is  resident only, but I will have parking permits by the front door for  everyone to park on the street. We have a driveway but no car so I'm not  shoveling it.  Enter at your own risk :) I will at least clear enough for people to pull in and drop things off and pickup parking passes. &lt;br /&gt;Train - we live 6-8 minute  walk from the back exit of Alewife (from the platform, go up the stairs in the direction the tains come). Just walk away from the main road  (the only one you can see from that exit) When you come to a fork in the  trail take the middle one. Clay street is a straight shot from there.  Turn left at Clay and we are on the left in a brown building.  &lt;br /&gt;Bus - nearby is the 350, 77, 79, 83, 87, 88, 89&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call me if you have any questions at all. Ben 617-997-3545&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;P.S.  I have a gas stove/oven, a smallish microwave, and a fondue  pot if you want to bring anything that needs heating up. Just give me a  call to make arrangements.&amp;nbsp; I will be using my crock-pot this time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Warmus</member_name><member_id>5401423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298391533000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297438933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Long weekend - let's have a party</name><id>16529300</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298138400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/16529300/</event_url></item>