<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Vegans and Animal Lovers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I am very excited to take over this group and I know it will be a great one! I am new to this &amp;quot;crazy vegan life&amp;quot;...have been since September. I love it! I would not change it for a thing.&lt;br /&gt;I should probably tell you a little about myself...I am 26, live in Hooksett, currently I have 2 roommates in addition to a dog and a cat. I am a special education teacher in north western NH and I love it!! I graduated from Southern NH University and am finishing my masters at Rivier College. I enjoy being outdoors! &lt;br /&gt;This meeting will be a potluck, so please bring your favorite dish and I would really appreciate if you dropped me a note to let me know what you may bring so I will make sure there is a variety of wondrous food. Think of this as a meet &amp;amp; greet...I am very open to ideas and suggestions you may have to make this group as awesome as it can be. Please email me with questions, comments, concerns...I may be new to this, but i have many resources at my fingertips and like you I have read and researched A LOT about being vegan. We don't even need to &amp;quot;meet&amp;quot; about that...lets just get together for some good food and i am sure a great time with great people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to meeting you all! Tell a friend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ruth.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Google directions or give me a call if you need directions.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365646527000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>conscientious diners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-204</urlname><id>160942</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Vegan/Animal Rights Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236789513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Meetup!!!</name><id>9931629</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237741200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-204/events/9931629/</event_url></item>