<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389534</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Center for the Arts at the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>6657372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106071</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This is an event that one of our members Phillip Berenz asked me to list and I thought it was a great idea. Phillip is the team leader and has cerebral palsy - he will be only the third person with cerebral palsy to successfully climb Mount Kilimanjaro unassisted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While you can RSVP here and coordinate with other randomites who might be going, you must purchase your ticket(s) using the link provided below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reel Rock Film Tour and Benefit For United Cerebral Palsy of MetroBoston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Join Climb for Cerebral Palsy as they host the Reel Rock Tour to raise money for United Cerebral Palsy of MetroBoston. Reel Rock is an exciting cinematic event where climbers and outdoors lovers come together to celebrate ultimate adventure filmmaking. The films this year include acclaimed climbers Chris Sharma, Conrad Anker, and Alex Honnold pushing their limits as they attempt to define the future of climbing. Brian Baldeck, Austin Whipple, Jared Villemaire, and Phillip Berenz -- the Climb for CP team -- will climb Mount Kilimanjaro in February 2012 to raise awareness and funds (with a goal of $30,000) for United Cerebral Palsy of MetroBoston. Phillip Berenz (the team leader) has cerebral palsy and will be only the third person with cerebral palsy to successfully climb Mount Kilimanjaro unassisted. Because this is a fundraising event, a majority of the proceeds will go directly to UCP of MetroBoston.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://youtu.be/VyUoVVDEa-E"&gt;Click here for the movie trailer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Doors open @ 6:30 PM so you can visit the sponsor's tables.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Film starts @ 7:30 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Price of ticket: $20.00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Location:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.artsatthearmory.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Center For The Arts At The Armory &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;191 Highland Avenue&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Somerville, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Amenities: A food and drink service area (beer, wine, and snacks) and restrooms will be open during the event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Handicap accessible: Yes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://reelrock7.brownpapertickets.com"&gt;Click here for tickets information.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REEL ROCK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;REEL ROCK shows are exciting events where climbers and outdoors lovers come together to celebrate the ultimate in adventure filmmaking. Prize giveaways, appearances by top climbers, and fundraising for non-profit organizations are just some of the ways that REEL ROCK events are more than just film screenings. For our seventh year, Sender Films and Big UP Productions are combining the biggest names in the sport with stories of pushing the limits like never before. From battling Himalayan peaks to a battle on Spanish limestone to establish the world’s first 5.15c. From the non-conformist world of offwidth climbing to the new found fame of the boundary-pushing sport of free soloing. This year’s films are nothing short of intrepid tales that will get your palms sweating from beginning to end.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HISTORY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;REEL ROCK founders Josh Lowell and Peter Mortimer have been producing and directing climbing and adventure films for over a decade, with devoted audiences around the world. Their work has been featured on NBC, NPR, and The New York Times, and has won a Sports Emmy Award, plus dozens of awards at international film festivals. After organizing small tours for their individual film releases, Lowell and Mortimer realized the huge demand for exciting live events in the outdoors community and combined forces to create The REEL ROCK Film Tour in 2006. In 2011, REEL ROCK screened in over 280 locations world-wide, drew over 65,000 audience members, raised over $15,000 for non-profits, partnered with more than 150 retailers, university outing clubs and climbing gyms, and won copious media coverage and critical praise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Phillip Berenz</member_name><member_id>13556962</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352515041000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350330642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reel Rock Film Tour in Somerville, MA (Movie Series)</name><id>87100852</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352503800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/87100852/</event_url></item>