<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Brugger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>317494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121030</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll discuss The Secret Life of Bees by Sue Monk Kidd. &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Secret-Life-Bees-Sue-Kidd/dp/0143036408/ref=pd_bbs_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1201623025&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon.com&lt;/a&gt; says: In Sue Monk Kidd's The Secret Life of Bees, 14-year-old Lily Owen, neglected by her father and isolated on their Georgia peach farm, spends hours imagining a blissful infancy when she was loved and nurtured by her mother, Deborah, whom she barely remembers. These consoling fantasies are her heart's answer to the family story that as a child, in unclear circumstances, Lily accidentally shot and killed her mother. All Lily has left of Deborah is a strange image of a Black Madonna, with the words &amp;quot;Tiburon, South Carolina&amp;quot; scrawled on the back. The search for a mother, and the need to mother oneself, are crucial elements in this well-written coming-of-age story set in the early 1960s against a background of racial violence and unrest. When Lily's beloved nanny, Rosaleen, manages to insult a group of angry white men on her way to register to vote and has to skip town, Lily takes the opportunity to go with her, fleeing to the only place she can think of--Tiburon, South Carolina--determined to find out more about her dead mother. Although the plot threads are too neatly trimmed, The Secret Life of Bees is a carefully crafted novel with an inspired depiction of character. The legend of the Black Madonna and the brave, kind, peculiar women who perpetuate Lily's story dominate the second half of the book, placing Kidd's debut novel squarely in the honored tradition of the Southern Gothic. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I learned after the fact that this book club read this novel back in December 2006, but it came in second in our recent poll. I hope that veterans of the meetup don't mind discussing this once again.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charis</member_name><member_id>3696786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264377239000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201623179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March book club</name><id>7220625</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206907200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/7220625/</event_url></item>