<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>40 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.492.1557</phone><name>Algiers Coffee House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669147</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121338</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Short stories, for all the dazzling diversity of the genre, are of two general types: those that yield their meanings subtly, quietly, and are as nuanced and delicate and without melodrama as the unfolding of miniature blossoms in Japanese chrysanthemum tea, and those that explode in the reader's face. Flannery O'Connor came of age in a time when subtlety and &amp;quot;atmosphere&amp;quot; in short stories were fashionable—as in the finely wrought, understated stories of such classic predecessors as Anton Chekhov, Henry James, and James Joyce, and such American contemporaries as Katherine Anne Porter, and Eudora Welty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But O'Connor's plainspoken, blunt, and flagrantly melodramatic short stories were anything but fashionable. The novelty of her acidly comic tales with moral and religious messages lay in their frontal assault upon the reader's sensibility: these were not refined New Yorker stories of the era in which nothing happens except inside characters' minds, but stories in which something happens of irreversible magnitude, often death by violent means.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Whenever I'm asked why Southern writers particularly have a penchant for writing about freaks, I say it is because we are still able to recognize one.”&lt;br /&gt;—Flannery O'Connor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several collections of O'Connor's short stories out there, of which I'd recommend &amp;quot;The Complete Stories&amp;quot; (FSG). And to focus our conversation, I'd suggest that you read and come prepared to discuss the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Good Man is Hard to Find&lt;br /&gt;The Life You Save May Be Your Own&lt;br /&gt;Greenleaf&lt;br /&gt;Good Country People&lt;br /&gt;Everything That Rises Must Converge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy reading! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arlinda&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263419405000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253037990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flannery O'Connor: Short Stories</name><id>11379287</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254693600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/11379287/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/a/7/global_5819031.jpeg</photo_url></item>