<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>198 Purgatory Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01590</zip><lat>42.129410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Purgatory Chasm State Reservation</name><city>Sutton</city><id>1513192</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.715233</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/4/a/event_23083594.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Purgatory Chasm is really easy to get to from Providence. Head north on 146 and it's exit 6. It is a really short, but fun hike that showcases some neat rock formations. Here is info from their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A unique natural landmark, Purgatory Chasm runs for a quarter of a mile between granite walls rising as high as 70 feet. Popular with picnickers and rock-climbers alike, the Chasm is believed to have its origin in the sudden release of dammed-up glacial meltwater near the end of the last Ice Age, approximately 14,000 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trails lead to a wide variety of rock formations, with such romantic names as The Corn Crib, The Coffin, The Pulpit, Lovers' Leap and Fat Man's Misery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/PurgatoryChasm.pdf"&gt;Trail Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's also supposed to be a hidden cave somewhere, which I've always been told about but never been able to find. So, if you're a spelunker, you might be able to go spelunking if you find the entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After wards, let's enjoy some ice cream right down the street at the lovely West End Creamery and Family Farm! We'll just stop for ice cream, but the farm also has mini golf, hayrides, and a corn maze which can be fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They serve as many as 65 different flavors of hard                  ice cream along                  with soft serve,                  sundaes,                  frappes, banana                  splits and so                  much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*If the weather is too rainy, then I will have to reschedule. I will send out an email for the rain date if that happens.*&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Visitors Center</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306449411000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Even if you didn't think much of the popular chasm, the ice cream is homemade and one of the best!</why><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304283581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Purgatory Chasm and then West End Creamery for Ice Cream!</name><id>17502059</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306083600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/17502059/</event_url></item>