<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Tonight, find sanctuary from winter's cold by focusing on warming detoxification practices. The moon reaches it's peak tonight at 4:38 pm. A perfect time to use this energy to rid your body of toxins and stress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the evening, choose from a variety of detox methods or take part in all of them  ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Food &amp;amp; Nutrition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - $1 wheatgrass shots, soothing herbal teas and cleansing juices. An introductory session for Spring Detox Week (a juice fasting program) will be held at 8 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Detox Yoga Workout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - To assist the body's natural healing and cleansing of the internal organs, &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://amymerli.com/yogabio.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Amy Merli&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; teaches yoga poses that increase blood flow to the organs and stimulate the digestive and lymphatic systems. By practicing in a warm environment, using deep yogic breathing, and working the large muscle groups, detox magic will happen! Bring a friend for only $10 each (2-for-1 special) or $20 requested donation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Infrared Sauna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - An infrared sauna session allows the skin's elimination of toxic chemicals and metals faster than other detox methods. Heat up and sweat it out! Sauna use is free for members or an additional $10 for non-members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Spa Therapies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - Hydrotherapy Foot Baths will soothe and gentlly massage the feet. Detox Back Scrubs use olive oil &amp;amp; myr or dead sea salt to improve circulation while easing tension and relaxing the body. Sample one or both therapies for an additional $10 each.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;All donations support the Growing Green Wellness Community &amp;amp; Healing Arts Space. All support is greatly appreciated!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the event, join Imani for the Spring Detox Week Introduction &amp;amp; Program Overview at 8 pm. This is an free &amp;amp; informal talk that explains the purpose of &lt;a href="http://www.growinggreenevents.com/nutrition-and-food.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spring Detox Week&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (March 1-5, 2010) and its ability to lay the foundation for a future of healthy eating and natural lifestyle practices. People interested in participating will receive an intro packet with more information and cleansing guidelines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Spring Detox Program uses a community style approach to put people in touch with mentors and like-minded others on the  same healing path for daily yoga practice, support groups, detox classes and shared meals. The Program will include includes juices for all five detox days, two fitness classes, two half-hour infrared sauna sessions, and two half-hour consultations with nutrition &amp;amp; living foods expert Eden Love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://livesuperfoods.com/mm5/graphics/00000001/smoothies.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eden Love</member_name><member_id>2826675</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267573375000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262043129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yoga Detox Full Moon Magic</name><id>12163218</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267399800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12163218/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/0/global_13078736.jpeg</photo_url></item>