<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Party it up at d Party in town. Join us on &lt;b&gt;Friday, June 19 from 6:00 to 9:00 pm&lt;/b&gt; at Thompson Design Group (35 Channel Center Street in Fort Point Channel). The d Party (&amp;quot;d&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;design&amp;quot;) is Common Boston's open-invite party, an opener to the weekend, celebrating good work by community advocates and local architects and lubricates good conversation between them. During the party, we’ll be debuting the work of the Neighborhood Photography Project, including images by photographers and community members in Ashmont, Jamaica Plain, Fort Point Channel, and Chinatown. Also on display during the event, Studio Soto will present an exhibition of photographs by Mobius Artists Group member Bob Raymond, who has been documenting Mobius’ activities for nearly thirty years, and an installation by Wenxiong Lin. Appetizers generously provided by Barlow’s Restaurant and Café, coming soon to A Street in Fort Point Channel.  It's free, it's a party, so what are you waiting for? Check out &lt;a href="http://www.commonboston.org/cb09" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.commonbost...&lt;/a&gt; for more free and fun Common Boston Weekend events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alyson</member_name><member_id>5616452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247611170000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244566677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>d Party</name><id>10612872</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245448800000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/10612872/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/4/global_9067316.jpeg</photo_url></item>