<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Conscious Movie Night:  You Can Heal Your Life&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Actor&lt;br /&gt;Louise L. Hay is a metaphysical lecturer and teacher and the bestselling author of numerous books. Her works have been translated into 29 different languages in 35 countries throughout the world. For more than 25 years, Louise has assisted millions of people in discovering and using the full potential of their own creative powers for personal growth and self-healing. Louise is the founder and chairman of Hay House, Inc., a publishing company that disseminates books, audios, and videos that contribute to the healing of the planet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Description&lt;br /&gt;This entertaining and inspirational movie based on the best-selling book of the same name is hosted by author and teacher Louise L. Hay. This film gives penetrating insights into Louises fascinating personal story; and shows how her views on self-esteem, abundance, and the metaphysical causes behind physical ailments were developed. It also reveals how she applied these concepts to her own emotional, spiritual, and professional life. A number of luminaries in the fields of self-help, philosophy, health, spirituality, and New Thought join Louise, giving their take on success, happiness, and the myriad ways in which people can heal their own lives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie will be followed by refreshments and lively discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Center of Light is on the Orange Line - Stonybrook T-stop.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220830300000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213643029000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night:  "You Can Heal Your Life"</name><id>8153394</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220657400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/8153394/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/e/global_4478430.jpeg</photo_url></item>