<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>306 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.348064</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-888-HARPOON</phone><name>Harpoon Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>669000</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On Sunday, November 14 from 3:00 - 6:00 PM Harpoon will host the 4th Annual Harpoon Helps Grateful Harvest Beer-B-Q, a fundraiser for The Greater Boston Food Bank. Harpoon's charitable giving program, Harpoon Helps, and the New England Barbecue Society (NEBS), have joined forces to put together a Thanksgiving meal, barbecue style, to raise money for the Great Boston Food Bank's annual Food Fund, which supplies Thanksgiving meals for families in and around Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The competitive barbecue masters will hitch up their huge smokers, park them in front of the brewery, and smoke more than 500 pounds of turkey along with all of the trimmings. In addition the NEBS Chefs will be on hand to offer attendees tips on how to make Thanksgiving meals a little more interesting this year. The dining tables will be set up family-style in a heated tent adjoining the Boston Brewery so that everyone can gather around, feast and be merry for a great cause. 100% of the $55.00 ticket price will go to the Greater Boston Food Bank.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to all-you-can-eat great food and pints of fresh beer, the Goodtime String Band will entertain guests with bluegrass and fiddle tunes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a Harpoon Beer Reception with passed appetizers from 3:00 PM to 4:00 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffet-style sit down dinner will be served from 4:00 to 6:00 PM  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the full menu on line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets must be purchased on line in advance at harpoon brewery.com&lt;a href="http://harpoonbrewery.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This will sell out.     &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will E Mail Yes RSVPs with Tickets</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289859951000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288668135000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Sox Natives Celebrate Thanksgiving at Harpoon Helps Grateful Harvest Beer-BQ</name><id>15306594</id><headcount>250</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289764800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/15306594/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/7/global_11511191.jpeg</photo_url></item>