<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1139 Randolph Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.229088</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newcomb Farms</name><city>Milton</city><id>10030302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071068</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join members of the SSDOMG as we discover another restaurant on the south shore!  Tonight we will be dining at Newcomb Farms which serves Breakfast all day as well as a limited Dinner menu, with most of the items under $15, depending on the Dinner Menu offerings.  Newcomb Farms is a cozy kitchy popular 2-room restaurant that warrants the wait in line if there is one when you arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I will be calling ahead and arriving my usual 10 minutes early, this restaurant does not accept reservations so we may have to wait a few minutes to be seated and they may not seat us if more than 2 people are not yet there.  If you are more than 15 minutes late and do not call me by 6pm you may lose your seat.  I will email my cell # to the Yes RSVPs around the RSVP Deadline for you to call only if you are running more than 10 minutes late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us as we have a fun night of conversation with new friends as we enjoy an Inexpensive Saturday Night Dinner - or Breakfast!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inexpensive Saturday Night Dinner - or Breakfast!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, November 17th @ 6pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newcomb Farms&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1139 Randolph Avenue&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Route 28 Southbound Side)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milton, MA 02186&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;617-698-9547&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet OUTSIDE the front door in the covered area. We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated as the restaurant does NOT take reservations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: [Current] Annual Members - FREE, Members - $2 each; Guests - $2 each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Minimum of 6 people 48 hours in advance.  Current maximum is 12 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note:&lt;/em&gt; The Wait List (WL) is set to "Automatic" which means as a spot opens up for the event it goes to the next person on the Wait List.  If there is a WL of more than 3 people more than 5 days before the event I will email everyone individually to let you know where you stand on the WL.  If you are on the WL and your plans change, please change your RSVP to No.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: This event has now been opened up to 1 adult guest per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Saturday, November 17th @ 12:30pm.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our Group's No-Show Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No-Show Policy on Membership Information Page:&lt;/em&gt; (Please click on the following link to be taken directly to the page.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/em&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.  This restaurant does NOT accept credit cards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Based on the weather forecast we should be OK.  There may be a passing shower but we will meet rain or shine.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather").&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages tab for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 93 to Exit 5B/Milton.  Go straight through the 1st set of lights.  Newcomb Farms is about 1/4 - 1/2 mile up on the left, approximately 2 miles from the highway.  Plenty of parking in the lot and possibly at the business across the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the front door or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353363014000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351381308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inexpensive Saturday Night Dinner - or Breakfast!</name><id>88843232</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353193200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/88843232/</event_url></item>