<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a winter hike in the White Mountains of New Hampshire of roughly 8.5 miles and 2,900 ft. altitude gain. We'll start from the Nancy Pond Trailhead on US-302 just south of Crawford Notch at roughly 1,000 ft. altitude and hike on the trail west to Norcross Pond. We then bushwhack roughly north to the peak of Mt. Nancy at 3,926 ft. altitude. If there is time, we'll bushwhack a little further northeast to the peak of Mt. Bemis at 3,725 ft. We'll then bushwhack down the stream valley between the two mountains to the established Nancy Pond Trail and back out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is still plenty of snow and ice on the ground so some experience with hiking/snowshoeing in deep snow as well as hiking in icy conditions is &lt;b&gt;required&lt;/b&gt;. The weather can change quickly in the White Mountains so be prepared for snow or even cold rain. This hike is not for beginners. If you have any questions as to your ability or equipment, contact Kevin S. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go MUST have:   &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing, equipment, trail food, and water   &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots  - There will likely be ice/snow or it could be wet/muddy!   &lt;br /&gt;* Gators - To keep snow out of your boots  &lt;br /&gt;* Crampons (or possibly MICROspikes) -MUST have! There WILL be ice!  &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet   &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too   &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves - MUST have and warm ones too!   &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - Warm outer layer &lt;br /&gt;* Hat - You loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too  &lt;br /&gt;* 2 - 3 quarts of water - MUST bring!   &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food/lunch - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.)  &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Plastic emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;* Emergency blanket - a metalized mylar &amp;quot;space blanket&amp;quot; to keep warm in emergencies &lt;br /&gt;* Rain poncho - We're in that weird time of year folks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Advised equipment:  &lt;br /&gt;* AMC map of the area to be hiked (#2 Franconia-Pemigewasset) &lt;br /&gt;Hiking poles - For better stability &lt;br /&gt;* Ice ax - May want to bring but don't expect to need  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM at the parking area at the trailhead (see location/directions below). We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 8 hrs. but it could be as little as 6 hrs. or as much as 9 hrs. depending on conditions. We'll stop for something to eat after probably in Bethlehem or Littleton, NH.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be advised, there is usually no cell reception in most areas of the White Mountains. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 but be advised we will leave either Sat. evening and stay over or leave 4 AM Sun. morning. We won't get back until about 11:30 PM Sun. night (could be earlier). Talk to Kevin S to arrange carpooling or if you have any questions (e-mail off profile, phone in RSVP). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to Nancy Pond Trail parking (off shoulder of US-302., just south of Notchland, NH and Crawford Notch):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/l=44.105;g=-71.3526" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(approx. Lat=44.105, Long=-71.3526)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239109752000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237898388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike/Bushwack to Mt. Nancy near Notchland NH</name><id>10023287</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238936400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10023287/</event_url></item>