<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cambridge, MA</address_2><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>MIT Building E-51</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>181966</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We repeat the discussion centered format that people praised last month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What's Hot and What's Not led by Tom Hill&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom leads a discussion on what trends, or themes, with their associated stock tickers are distinctly good for longs or shorts. The focus will be on ETFs and stocks for asset classes, sectors, industry groups and indexes. In particular, we will be looking to hear from you to find out what you have surmised and found a way to trade on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prospecting Using Investors.Com led by Jeff Orrik&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff will use Investors.com and the Premium package to prospect for stocks. The goal is to find stocks and ETFs at buy points while experimenting with the tools available on Investors.Com and using the various talents of everybody in the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harlan's Market Update led by Harlan Rieur&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harlan gives us his live market analysis on market trends. Using StockCharts.com and his own combination of indicators - Bollinger Bands, stochastic RSI, MACD, Williams%, OBV plus his panoply of moving averages. Always a pleasure for everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;StockPicks led by Chris Jones&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric announces which stocks performed best. Then we solicit all the picks from everyone and run through all them, with Jeff putting up the charts as we have done in the past. Afterwards we will focus on 5 of the stocks to be analyzed further and dissected by the group at large.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Premeeting Period is the Daytraders Meeting led by Eric Eklof&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Premeeting starts at 5:30 and runs until 6:50. Everyone is welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building on the enthusiasm created by his Daytrading Talk, plus his effusive personality during the meetings, Eric Eklof hosts a Daytraders Group. Everyone is welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;5:30-6:50 Premeeting Period&lt;br /&gt;- Daytraders Group led by Eric&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Meeting Begins:&lt;br /&gt;- Announcements and Polls, led by Doug&lt;br /&gt;- Harlan's Market Update led by Harlan&lt;br /&gt;- Prospecting Using Investors.com led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;- What's Hot and What's Not led by Tom&lt;br /&gt;- StockPicks led by Chris&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members value discussion highly. We try to pack as much discussion as possible. Expressing ideas and sharing knowledge is paramount to our members.&lt;br /&gt;All levels of expertise are welcome. No question is too simple - as a matter of fact the simplest question often evokes the best discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newcomers gather at the podium during the 8:00 break to learn about the group. Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you talk stocks with someone then bring them with you!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Virtual Trading game is up and running!&lt;/b&gt; Directions are at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c/7dab7a5592adbc28?lnk=gst&amp;amp;q=simulator#7dab7a5592adbc28" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Please be sure to choose a name that we can identify with you! Otherwise it is anonymous!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205449847000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203017270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Business Daily Tuesday Meetup</name><id>7331623</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205276400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/7331623/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/e/global_938062.jpeg</photo_url></item>