<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I've finally settled on the 2-day AT hike for June 26 - 27. We are going to skip about 6.3 miles from the last place we ended in VT northbound on the AT to allow a better 2-day hike. We'll go back another time to fill in that  missing part.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The AT hike will be in VT and going over Killington Peak. This is the 2nd highest mountain in VT and the highest AT elevation in VT. The section we will do will be from Route 103 to Route 4, northbound , about 17.5 total miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the first day, we have an altitude gain of about 3,000 feet over about 11.1 miles. We will stay in a stone/wood shelter (Cooper Lodge) near the peak (alt. 3,850 ft.) that sleeps 12 and also has tenting platforms that can take up to 10 additional. I believe this is the highest shelter anywhere in VT to boot! We will need to bring tents as there is a very good chance the shelter could be full. GMC (Green Mountain Club) runs the shelter and this one does not take a fee per the GMC website (&lt;a href="https://www.greenmountainclub.org/page.php?id=54" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.greenmoun...&lt;/a&gt; ). There is a privy there. No fires allowed due to sensitivity of area at altitude.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The second day we'll take the short side trail and ascend about 300 feet to the peak of Killington Peak. Then it is mostly down with roughly a 2,600 ft altitude loss over about 6.4 miles to the end on Route 4.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I think I'll limit the party size to 7 people to fit in one van for transport back. But I could extend to 10 people max. if enough people want to go and we arrange a second shuttle from end to beginning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we should come in earlier than I estimated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Full pack&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in&lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of cloathing -Avoid cotton as it stays wet (this includes underwear). Plus second day's clothing.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket or rain poncho -just in case&lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag -3 season or summer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Headlamp or flashlight -LED version best -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking tent -or share with someone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* 3 quarts water&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 4 meals for on the trail -DAY-1: lunch, supper; DAY-2: breakfast, lunch (all trash to be packed out!). High energy meals should be planned. Only supper may be cooked but if getting up early (6:00 AM) then breakfast can be cooked too.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Insect repellant -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;* Bear bag and 15' min. strong light weight cord -to hang food at night&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Toiletries &amp;amp; Toiletpaper -essential! Please no scented items as attracts bears.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Water filter -to restock water, strongly suggested&lt;br /&gt;* Camera and extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit -for blisters and such&lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping pad&lt;br /&gt;* Pocket knife&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof matches -for cooking, campfire, emergency fire (warm up, signal)&lt;br /&gt;* Mess kit -if needed&lt;br /&gt;* Camping utensils -if needed&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking stove and fuel -if cooking&lt;br /&gt;* Game(s) to play in camp -cards, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate directions to the meetup location at AT parking area and hike start (On Rte. 103 very near intersection with Gaynor Rd., Cuttingsville, VT) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Cuttingsville&amp;amp;state=VT&amp;amp;address=1599+Gaynor+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=05738&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=43.52015&amp;amp;longitude=-72.922289&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;MAPS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(To be posted later)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;INFORMATION&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;(To be posted later)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277729287000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276741290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT over Killington Peak, Killington VT</name><id>13826159</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277555400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13826159/</event_url></item>