<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hilldale Lane</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03070</zip><lat>42.982890</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Hillsborough County 4-H Youth Center (Fairgrounds)</name><city>New Boston</city><id>1339916</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.681620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/1/c/event_160540732.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/b/c/event_160540892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It is now hunting season for deer with regular firearms so you would be smart to have some sort of blaze orange on both you and your dog(s).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you have a GPS 105 River Road, New Boston could be used as an address to find the entrance to the fairgrounds (Hilldale Lane) as the house is on the same side of the road within sight of Hilldale Lane as are the 2 signs in picture one.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will do a easy line hike 3 miles one way (6 miles round trip). The actual name of the rail trail is the New Boston Rail Trail but most of the trail borders or is rather near the Piscataquog River for the dogs that like water.  Any one wanting more exercise could extend the hike to 8 miles round trip by simply following the rail trail to where it ends just before NH-114 in Goffstown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any adult guest you want to bring should sign up on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will gather at the back of the fairgrounds where the rail trail starts. Once you enter the fairgrounds at any intersection stay to the right and follow the road straight back to the end.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355072772000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353989117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Piscataquog River Rail Trail - 6 Mile Easy Line Hike</name><id>92968002</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354374000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/92968002/</event_url></item>