<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1900 Dorchester Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02124</zip><lat>42.286033</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peabody Square Clock</name><city>Boston</city><id>704183</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064212</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>($5 for BBF card holders)</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You may have heard other Boston By Foot tours billed as &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Charles_River_Basin" target="_blank"&gt;the best tour ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; but &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Ashmont_Hill" target="_blank"&gt;Ashmont Hill&lt;/a&gt; is definitely the best BBF tour to pass through three watersheds. Intrigued? Come along as we explore this amazing district of Dorchester.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start at the clock in Peabody Square. First we will explore the square area and the public buildings located there that support the neighborhood. Included is All Saints' Church, widely recognized as a masterpiece of the architect Ralph Adams Cram and a superb example of his Gothic Revival/Modern Gothic style.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we will head up the hill to visit what is one of the best preserved collection of Victorian homes in the City. All 8 Victorian architectural styles are represented (9 if you count the three-decker) as we wind our way around this garden suburb.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But wait, it isn't just architecture that is featured as we move through the sylvan surroundings.  The tour covers the wonderful people who lived here too.  We will discuss the notorious politician &amp;quot;Honey Fitz&amp;quot;, an early female photographer and her inventing twin brothers, some of the artists who created an art colony on Ashmont Hill during the nineteenth century and a former Dorchester Historical Society President who had a profound impact on the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will end back up in Peabody Square to talk about the renaissance that the Ashmont area is undergoing.  We'll see the new development that has taken place recently and then be in a perfect position to adjourn to the Ashmont Grill for after-tour refreshments.  Really, how can you stand to miss it??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tour is $15 (but only $5 for card-carrying &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot members&lt;/a&gt;, to join visit our &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join" target="_blank"&gt;membership page&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255214029000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250787324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walking Tour of Ashmont Hill, Dorchester</name><id>11157788</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254074400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/11157788/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/e/global_10295310.jpeg</photo_url></item>