<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;DESCRIPTION: Skip the stores and make your holiday gifts instead! Come by the studio to avoid the crazy shoppers and join us for a relaxing day of art. You can work on gifts, make holiday cards, or work on any projects you have in progress!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHAT TO BRING: Yourself, your basic art kit, and whatever you'd like to work on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COST: $10 per person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AMENITIES: Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.) and some supplies including acrylic paints, old magazines and books for collaging. Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom. Dinner in or out, if people are interested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND: Any member of the NE ATC+ or Altered Art/Assemblage Meetups and their guests (12+ only, please).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP: These smaller sessions are often full with a waiting list. Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CANCELLATIONS: In the unlikely event that we need to cancel---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jen H</member_name><member_id>10331591</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322487973000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319544501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Studio</name><id>38628222</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322330400000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/38628222/</event_url></item>