<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;To much of the world, Christmas means gift-giving, family gatherings, and holiday parties. In the midst of all the material noise, many of us have felt that there is something deeper about Christmas. In fact, there is much, much more to Christmas than what you see on the outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this seminar, the inner mystical teachings of Christmas will be revealed. Mystics interpret all the events in the life of Jesus and Mary as not only being literal events but also symbolizing each step along the spiritual path for those who desire transformation. In the Christmas story, not only do Jesus and Mary represent specific aspects of us, so do Joseph, the wise men, the shepherds, the star, the animals in the stable, and even the stable itself. Learn how to tune into these different energies inside of you and practically apply them in your spiritual practice to have a deeper, more radiant Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will get from this seminar:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An ability to deal with the outer holiday frenzy with more peace and love&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of how to create space for the Light inside of you by applying specific tools in your life during the Christmas season&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to avoid riding the up-and-down emotional roller coaster of the season, but instead remain peaceful in knowing what Christmas is really about&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop will also include a guided meditation. Join us for a warm, enlightening experience with others who are wanting to understand the inner meaning of Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Michael Knight</member_name><member_id>8983786</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Timothy Lin</member_name><member_id>11335175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355454749000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354494080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inner Meaning of Christmas: Mystical Interpretation of the Christmas Story</name><id>93791702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355443200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/93791702/</event_url></item>