<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Rye Ln</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03870</zip><lat>43.048695</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Ordione State Park Boat Launch</name><city>Rye</city><id>804289</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.727430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Due to high demand for Steve's trip, I will organize an additional small group to launch from Ordione State Park Boat Ramp. We'll launch at 9:30 am sharp and paddle across the Piscataqua River to Kittery and meetup with the main group. We'll paddle with them to Braveboat Harbor, have lunch and then continue on around Gerrish Island. At the end of Gerrish, conditions permitting, we'll head out to Whaleback light and then head back to Ordione. Approx distance for this paddle is 14 miles (plus any play/surfing we do along the way) Minimum Requirements: sea kayak 16ft or longer with bulkheads or airbags, PFD, sprayskirt, Paddle, paddle float, pump, water, lunch, great attitude Recommended: helmet, tow rope, extra paddle, camera Note: if you are already signed up for Steve's group and desire to launch from Ordione, MAKE SURE you cancel your RSVP so that a wait list person can be added to his group. You should have previous ocean paddling experience and the ability to paddle 14+ miles to join this group We are launching at 9:30! Be ready to paddle by that time, as we won't wait for stragglers. Weneed an hour to get over Kittery and meet the main group.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Cars and kayaks in the launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy Foley</member_name><member_id>7753713</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346619831000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345647565000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Circumnavigate Gerrish Island - Ordione Boat Ramp Launch</name><id>78856302</id><headcount>9</headcount><duration>23400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346506200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/78856302/</event_url></item>