<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>211 Sea St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.261285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-770-2835</phone><name>Grumpy White's</name><city>Quincy</city><id>728074</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.992116</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;It's a beautiful day in this neighborhood, &lt;br /&gt;A beautiful day for a neighbor, &lt;br /&gt;Would you be mine? &lt;br /&gt;Could you be mine?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh! Er, hi, fellow Meetup members! You'll have to excuse Mike - He tries not to sing where he can be overheard!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He just happened to be thinking about this month's &amp;quot;letter&amp;quot; restaurant, though...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You see, one phrase that keeps coming up when you mention Grumpy White's in Quincy is &amp;quot;neighborhood place&amp;quot;. By all accounts, Grumpy White's is a quintessential, no pretensions, no goat cheese, big portions, reasonable prices, yes-by-God-we-use-real-grease, neighborhood restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's also apparently that rare kind of neighborhood place where the buffalo wings, char-broiled burgers, foot long hotdogs and crumb covered baked haddock somehow manage to taste better than they do at the other place down the street or across town. Mike, who has yet to eat there himself, was left shaking his head at the way a burger joint inspired amateur reviewers to nearly poetical heights of expression. Consider the following examples:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christian D. on &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/grumpy-whites-quincy" target="_blank"&gt;Yelp&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;Go for the burgers... The buns appear buttered and tossed on the griddle and the fries are golden crusted. Add a Lime Rickeys (sic) to cap it off. Don't bother with an appetizer unless you want to lug home half a burger.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rachele K M on Yelp: &amp;quot;Get the buffalo chicken sub. Thank me later.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan N on Yelp: &amp;quot;Seriously, I could come here and drink coke with vanilla all day and night and be the happiest person on earth.  In recent years, I have heard of this myth of places adding vanilla to coke but have never experienced it for myself because I've never seen it.  Grumpy White's is the only place I've ever seen that has it!    And it's fantastic.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And finally, a serious entry in the Amateur Restaurant Review Quote of the Year Contest (if only there were one)... HiddenBoston on &lt;a href="http://chowhound.chow.com/topics/473824" target="_blank"&gt;Chowhound&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;The (Grumpy Double Burgers) were fantastic, as they use meat that is obviously not 93% lean (not even close!). It was a fatty, juicy, greasy dish of heavenly delight, and even my arteries seemed to smile as they slowly closed up.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Grumpy White's&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;211 Sea Street, Quincy&lt;br /&gt;617-770-2835&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, August 17 @ 5:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer: Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Ten members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Sorry, no Guests for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: S2.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, August 15 @ 5:00 PM. (Please note this is 48 hours prior to the event rather than our usual 24).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions: Please note:&lt;/b&gt; We are providing directions from &lt;b&gt;Route 3&lt;/b&gt;, but the route we are describing crosses several of the main local roads, including &lt;b&gt;Quincy Avenue&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Route 53&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Route 3A&lt;/b&gt;. Members coming from the local area should have little trouble finding a point from which they can pick up the route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3&lt;/b&gt;, take Exit 17 (Union St). This is the Union Street Rotary. Exit the rotary by turning onto Union Street, East Braintree exit, passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the next two lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just before the next light at Weymouth Landing, take a hard left onto Shaw St (directly across from the Union Congregational Church and Totland College).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Shaw St, passing the Windjammer Cove apartment complex on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the next light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the second light, Shaw Street ends, running into Howard St. Go straight onto Howard St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next light, just after a railroad crossing, is the intersection with Quincy Avenue. Turn left onto Quincy Ave/ Route 53 North.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the next light, Route 53 turns right, becoming the Southern Artery (You will see signs for WalMart and The Falls condominiums on your left). Turn right onto the Southern Artery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the next three lights (the third light is the intersection with 5th Ave).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next light is the intersection with Washington St/Route 3A (You will see Baxter Pharmacy on the far-left corner). Go straight across Washington St, remaining on the Southern Artery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the next five lights, remaining on the Southern Artery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The sixth light is Sea St (note Mount Wollaston Cemetary on far-right corner). Turn right onto Sea St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through the next light at Quincy Shore Drive (prominent sign indicates a left turn for Wollaston Beach).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through one more light (Samoset Ave, note Ginger Betty's Bakery on near-left corner), then look for Grumpy White's &lt;b&gt;IMMEDIATELY&lt;/b&gt; on your right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Seating is limited here. We'll probably be in a corner booth with a table added.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219384038000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217825975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grumpy White's!</name><id>8471627</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219006800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8471627/</event_url></item>