<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>North End</address_2><address_1>364 Hanover St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02113</zip><lat>42.365281</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-367-1123</phone><name>Maurizio's</name><city>Boston</city><id>1442198</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053207</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Maurizio's (&lt;a href="http://www.mauriziosboston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mauriziosb...&lt;/a&gt;) specializes in a unique cuisine in Boston's North End. It is from the island of Sardinia, off the Italian coast, from which chef/owner Maurizio Loddo hails. He has made up a holiday menu just for NEEM members. The 4-course dinner includes calamari or eggplant to start, then a salad, 4 entrees to choose from- ravioli filled with prosciutto &amp;amp; figs, a Sardinian pasta dish with meat sauce, frutti di mare (shrimp, scallops, clams, mussels, calamari in a tomato sauce, tossed with linguine), and filet of soul Sardinian style. The dessert course will be tiramisu or connoli and coffee. The prix fixe price is $30. Tax, tip and other drinks are extra. Cash will be the easiest way for us to settle the bill. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant is located on the left-hand side of Hanover Street as you walk from the Greenway, just before the Paul Revere Mall. (statue of Paul Revere) Haymarket (Green &amp;amp; Orange lines)is the nearest T-station and the Parcel 7 Garage, 136 Blackstone St. (entrance on Sudbury) the best place to park. If you get there between 6:00 and 7:00, join us for wine, beer or soft drinks, as we celebrate the season. It should be a delicious meal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of this busy season, RVSP's will be accepted immediately. But please note, if you're a 'Yes' (there are no 'Maybes') as of Friday, December 15th at 5:00 PM, the I will be obligated to pay for you whether you attend or not. Please try to join us.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for NEEM or Jim.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim S.</member_name><member_id>4216983</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296867210000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM</urlname><id>1397251</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>North End Eating Meetup (NEEM)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291326436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maurizio's-Holiday Dinner</name><id>15624204</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292457600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM/events/15624204/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/7/a/global_7834474.jpeg</photo_url></item>