<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Corner of Highland and Russell</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.270439</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Elm Park</name><city>Worcester</city><id>905026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.814621</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Personal Friend who also happens to be a visual artist or has somehow contracted the habit of hanging out around one or more of them a lot:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About a year ago, when Mihoko and I started the process of getting permission to do the SAORI Bridges of Elm Park (Wed. Aug.25- Sat. Aug.29), we asked our friend Nancy Smith (whose daughter Lillian was a longtime SAORI weaver) to do an imaginative rendering of what we had in mind for this project so people who didn't have the stomach for my 1,000 words didn't have to read them. She imagined this just out of her head:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now the real deal goes up next Wednesday morning; suddenly, it occurred to us that our color-oriented friends might enjoy painting or drawing their impressions of one or both of the bridges, either at the Park or later from photographs they took. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is no contest; no cash prizes. We just think this unique, transient spectacle  - up for only 5 days - might appeal to you &amp;amp; those you know. SO...I'd love your help getting the word out to them about this opportunity! I don't have the email network of visual artists that you have - so please forward this to anyone you can think of! (A lady in Missouri did this and 3 weeks later received 8,347 postcards from Jimmy Hoffa, all from different parts of the world.) I also mean to encourage photographers; just know that Erb Photography is under contract with us for this project, so all photos we use for promotional or commercial purposes will be theirs. We realize there are impressionistic (&amp;amp; all other types of -istic) photographers out there who will see the bridges through a personal lens, so to speak. We're primarily interested in how you transform this unusual display through your unique style and way of seeing things. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, if we do happen to reap a crop of wonderful renderings from this incitement to artistic riot, I will produce (with any helpers) a show at which you could all sell your renderings to the public and keep 100% of the sale price. The publicity for  SAORI Worcester would be worth the expense (hey, maybe I could make a deal with some establishment to cash in on liquor sales in return for springing for hors d'oeuvres - oy, such a businessman!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't need an RSVP. If you do create something, let me know when you do. If there are enough renderings, we'll throw the party and sell your stuff! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Merci beaucoup,&lt;br /&gt;Nat Needle &lt;br /&gt;Saori Worcester Freestyle Weaving Studio&lt;br /&gt;Mihoko Wakabayashi &amp;amp; Nathaniel Needle&lt;br /&gt;18 Winslow Street, Worcester, MA 01609&lt;br /&gt;508-757-4646&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://saoriworcester.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://saoriworcester...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. NOTES ON THE INSTALLATION:&lt;br /&gt;The red bridge will have more of an end-to-end effect, although the City insists that we leave some sort of gap to avoid strangling passing waterfowl - I am not making this up - and to deter would-be social deviants (or even wholesome outdoorsy lovers) from taking some kind of advantage of a the sort of total fiber screen pictured above.  [By the way, artists may boast of their imagination, but they have nothing on the officials of our Parks, Police, and Fire Departments. I have to hand it to these guys - they have lurid down.] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The iron bridge will have more of a striped effect (banner-grillwork-banner-grillworki etc.) because the Parks Dept. was concerned that someone might want to get their wedding pictures on that bridge on that weekend, so we needed to be ready to quickly take down and re-install the banners if someone in the wedding party just wanted plain grillwork in the photo. Again, I am not making this up. As it turned out, this plan made the number of banners involved more realistic, and I think the contrast between the two bridges will be sweet. That peeling red paint needs as much of a cover-up as possible, whereas that lovely black heart-shaped grillwork on the iron bridge should complement the weavings nicely.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283192688000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282314564000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SAORI Bridges of Elm Park Photo Op</name><id>14484419</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282770000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/14484419/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/2/global_17321202.jpeg</photo_url></item>