<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>770 Boston Post Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06437</zip><lat>41.288795</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comfort Keepers</name><city>Guilford</city><id>1845621</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.675476</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/d/2/event_178145842.jpeg" width="95" height="124" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This time of year, when we express gratitude for our blessings and share special time with our families and friends, is the perfect time to explore creative ways to express thanks to our clients and lead-generation contacts. Selling and Marketing specialist, Sally Tucker, has built 3 different sales careers spanning 30 years and has achieved award-winning success largely because of her focus on “gratitude marketing”. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sally, who for the past 4 years has worked as a top producer in residential Real Estate with Coldwell Banker, has many ideas to share about her rapid and stable business growth. You will learn simple ways and affordable resources for staying in touch with clients, and the significance of a scheduled structure that organizes follow-up efforts and strategies. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 “Thank Yous” come in different shapes and sizes…come explore how you can incorporate these concepts, ideas and strategies into the day-to-day business activity to build a stronger business for your company in 2013. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sally Tucker has worked with sales and marking training for local and National companies such as: Home Depot, Decorating Den, Macy’s, ASID (American Society of Interior Designers), Sears and IDS (Interior Design Society), to name a few. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne Garland</member_name><member_id>11311382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353153573000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Association-of-Women-Business-leaders</urlname><id>1543671</id><group_lat>41.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>AWBL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345297250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Giving Thanks, Growing Business - Speaker: Sally Tucker, REALTOR®</name><id>78281072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353072600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Association-of-Women-Business-leaders/events/78281072/</event_url></item>