<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>946 Ferry Boulevard</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06614</zip><lat>41.200240</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>2033753037</phone><name>Harborside B &amp; G</name><city>Stratford</city><id>373932</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.114350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet at Harbor Side at 1:00.&lt;br /&gt;Harborside Bar &amp;amp; Grille&lt;br /&gt;946 Ferry Blvd&lt;br /&gt;Stratford, CT.  06614&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;203-375-3037&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harborsidebargrill.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harborside...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.harborsidebargrill.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandsite.com/ct-stratfordharborside.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newengland...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.newenglandsite.com/ct-stratfordharborside.shtml&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leave for Stratford Day Activities after a cup of coffee or a&lt;br /&gt;Quick Brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.stratfordday.com/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.stratfordd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.stratfordday.com/index.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This annual town-wide event will be held on Main Street from &lt;br /&gt;Church St. to Stratford Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Main Street and Broad Street between Main and I-95 &lt;br /&gt;will be closed to thru traffic from approximately 7:00 am to 8:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Free, convenient parking is at Deluca Field, on Main Street,&lt;br /&gt; just south of Stratford Day.&lt;br /&gt;A free shuttle bus runs from Deluca Field to Main Street and&lt;br /&gt; Stratford Avenue, the southern border of Stratford Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Do?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stratford Day is an event where you can have fun, meet &lt;br /&gt;your friends, enjoy free entertainment, &lt;br /&gt;get some great food, check out some cool cars and motorcycles, &lt;br /&gt;play some games, people watch and just stroll around.&lt;br /&gt;We strive to have something of interest and value for every age.&lt;br /&gt;Stratford Day is an opportunity to bring together our townspeople&lt;br /&gt;and visitors from other towns for fun, entertainment and information. &lt;br /&gt;It's a way for our town organizations to publicize their missions. &lt;br /&gt;Some offer food and games to the public as fundraisers. &lt;br /&gt;We have a variety of crafters with unique items for sale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A free shuttle bus runs from Deluca Field to Main Street &amp;amp; Stratford &lt;br /&gt;Avenue, the southern border of Stratford Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-95 Northbound &lt;br /&gt;North to Exit 31 - bottom of ramp, STRAIGHT through light. &lt;br /&gt;Follow along interstate through two stop signs, &lt;br /&gt;one right after the other. Turn RIGHT onto SOUTH AVE. &lt;br /&gt;(at Camelot Motel and ramp back onto I-95). &lt;br /&gt;Next light turn RIGHT onto MAIN ST. Follow through two more lights, &lt;br /&gt;DELUCA FIELD is on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-95 Southbound &lt;br /&gt;South to Exit 31 - bottom of ramp, LEFT onto SOUTH AVE. &lt;br /&gt;Next light turn RIGHT onto MAIN ST. Follow through two more lights, &lt;br /&gt;DELUCA FIELD is on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 8/25 Southbound &lt;br /&gt;Take the Route 8/25 connector South to I-95. &lt;br /&gt;Follow directions for I-95 Northbound.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Merritt Parkway Northbound &lt;br /&gt;Exit 49 for Route 25 Southbound. Follow South to I-95. &lt;br /&gt;Follow directions for I-95 Northbound.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Merritt Parkway Southbound &lt;br /&gt;Easy Directions. A simple route to follow but a few miles out of &lt;br /&gt;your way. Take Merritt south all the way to Exit 49 for &lt;br /&gt;ROUTE 25 South. Follow directions for Merritt Parkway &lt;br /&gt;Northbound.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harder Directions. Exit 53 for ROUTE 110 SOUTH. &lt;br /&gt;Bottom of ramp at light turn LEFT. Follow RT. 110 SOUTH, MAIN ST. &lt;br /&gt;through two quick lights and turn LEFT at third light &lt;br /&gt;(1.9 miles, Mill River Country Club) to FOLLOW RT. 110 SOUTH. &lt;br /&gt;Straight through next two lights, under RR bridge and bear right &lt;br /&gt;at third light. Immediately get into the left lane. &lt;br /&gt;Follow straight through next light. Just past this light do &lt;br /&gt;NOT merge onto I-95 ramp. Instead bear left under the expressway, &lt;br /&gt;but then immediate right. STRAIGHT through light onto &lt;br /&gt;FERRY BLVD. Two more lights, LEFT onto ELM ST. &lt;br /&gt;Follow Elm St. to end, at light, LEFT onto MAIN ST. DELUCA FIELD &lt;br /&gt;is a short ways down on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deluca Field is right next to the Old Textron/&lt;br /&gt;Lycoming Factory.  Most who live in Stratford know where&lt;br /&gt;That location is on the far end of Main Street.&lt;br /&gt;Remember that most of Main Street will be closed off&lt;br /&gt;Due to Stratford Day.  I am planning on taking I 95, using&lt;br /&gt;The above directions to get to Deluca Field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Wait outside the restaurant door for around 15 minutes for members.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213031331000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Stratford Day has activities for all ages all day.</why><group><who>Coffee Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>coffee-397</urlname><id>570343</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Coffee Talk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206296926000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee Talk Sips Coffee the Day in Stratford</name><id>7587483</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212858000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/coffee-397/events/7587483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/e/global_2654830.jpeg</photo_url></item>