<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A loop hike on part of the Tully Trail - up to Spirit Falls and Jacob's Hill (with a detour to The Ledges!) and then around Long Lake.  Total distance about 5 miles (my best guess!)  Some hill as we climb to Spirit Falls, but nothing too steep!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;One of a series of hikes for those of us who want to start getting (back) into hiking and need to build up some stamina and endurance before attempting the rockier terrains and steeper inclines! Hikes will be taken at a slower pace, with gains of 1000 feet or less and most will be 3 - 4 miles and take about half a day.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tully Trail is a 22-mile loop trail that encircles the largely undeveloped Tully Valley in the North Quabbin Region of Central Massachusetts. From the summit of Tully Mountain to the cascading waters of Doane’s Falls, the trail connects some of the region’s most scenic properties and views. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you go here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/places-to-stay/tully-lake-campground/tully-trail.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;you can download a map of the Tully Trail and see our intended route!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Even though this hike is for those of us just starting out (or starting again) please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: We will meet in the parking lot of the Tully Lake Campground&lt;br /&gt;25 Doane Hill Road&lt;br /&gt;Royalston, MA 01368&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 2, take Exit 18 and turn left onto Rt. 2A West toward Athol. From the intersection of Rts. 2A and 32 North in Athol, cross the Millers River Bridge and bear left following the signs on Rt. 32 North. Proceed about 4 mi., passing the Tully Dam, and take a right onto Doane Hill Rd. Proceed for 1 mi. Tully Lake Campground is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am CAMPING at Tully Lake for the weekend!  I already have someone sharing my site, but if you are interested in camping, it might be worth a call - they also have 3 sites they keep back for &amp;quot;walk-ins&amp;quot; on the weekends.  Tully Lake is a beautiful campground - all sites are tent only, hike in (they give you these garden carts to lug your gear) and they have showers!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/places-to-stay/tully-lake-campground/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the parking lot by 9:45am.  I have a bright orange backpack and a big smile.  My cell phone is 774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286724325000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284991320000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It loop hike on the Tully Trail!</name><id>14830865</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286719200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14830865/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/a/global_18112554.jpeg</photo_url></item>