<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Water Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.955486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Water Street Cafe</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>11987302</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.661613</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will hike from the 1820 Court House on Court St. Plymouth.   The hike is approximately 5 miles and will take between two and three hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the first half of the long discussed but never really completed northern half of the Plymouth Wishbone Walking Trail-- a set of two trails envisaged about a decade ago that would connect Myles Standish state forest with downtown Plymouth and Ellisville Harbor State Park.  (The southern section running into Ellisville Harbor was mapped and trail signs were posted by local Scouts in 2007.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to meet for breakfast, please join us at the &lt;a href="http://waterstreetcafeplymouth.com/Home.html"&gt;Water St. Cafe&lt;/a&gt; at 7:45 am. (25 Water St., Plymouth) You can consult &lt;a href="http://www.parkplymouth.com/wheretoparkandrates.html"&gt;Park Plymouth&lt;/a&gt; for the locations of nearby free parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you prefer, you can meet us at the Water St. Cafe at 8:45 am. where we will organize a car shuttle. (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will need to leave cars at both ends of this hike as this is a one-way hike.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The second half of the northern section of trail will be done at a later date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recent weather has been variable but it always makes sense to wear layers of clothing that can be added or removed as necessary to adjust to changing conditions and exertion levels, to wear good shoes and to have a couple of bottles of water with you on a hike of this length. (2 hours plus) We are not speed demons and welcome you to join us but ask that you come prepared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more info on the group, visit our &lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com"&gt;Friends of Myles Standish State Forest website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bescherer</member_name><member_id>650729</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Malcolm MacGregor</member_name><member_id>29176842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370890041000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1370617857000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike half the northern half of Wishbone Trail</name><id>123448432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370868300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/123448432/</event_url></item>