<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hiker's Parking Lot</address_2><address_1>US 3</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03580</zip><lat>44.188220</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Liberty Spring Trailhead</name><city>Franconia</city><id>1343050</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.682055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is one of a handful of unfinished hikes on my to-do list for this summer!  Since I cannot hike during the weekend of the 20th, I'm scheduling a couple of mid-week treks to try and stay in shape.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, I am looking to do the &amp;quot;road less travelled by,&amp;quot; partly due to the fact that I do not think the dogs will be able to manage the Flume Slide trail.  &lt;i&gt;I will always welcome dogs on a hike - it is up to you to decide whether or not they can handle the terrain.&lt;/i&gt;  Please read the trail descriptions carefully.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the trailhead for the Liberty Spring Trail (US 3 hiker's parking lot, just north of the Flume Visitor Center by the Whitehouse Trail) and then carpool over to the Kanc and park at the trail head for the Lincoln Woods Trail.  If someone has better directions to the parking lot, please share!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will take the Lincoln Woods (Wilderness) Trail to the Osseo Trail, up the back side of Mt. Flume.  We will then follow the Franconia Ridge Trail over from Mt. Flume to Mt. Liberty and descend via the Liberty Spring Trail. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Book Time is: 7hr 30min - 8.4 Miles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plagerized from my White Mountain Guide for your benefit&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lincoln Woods Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;1.4 mi&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leaving the parking lot, the Lincoln Woods Trail runs across the porch of the information center (REALLY?)  and descends a wooden stairway, crosses the East Branch on a suspension bridge then turns right and follows the railroad bed, climbing almost imperceptibly.  At 1.4 mi the Osseo trail diverges left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Osseo Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(To Mt. Flume Summit via Lincoln Woods Trail, Osseo trail and Franconia Ridge Trail)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;4.1 miles&lt;br /&gt;2900 ft&lt;br /&gt;3 hr 30 minutes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail connects the lower end of the Wilderness (Lincoln Woods) trail with the south end of the Franconia Ridge, near the summit of Mt. Flume.  It begins on the west side of the Wilderness Trail, 1.4 mi north of the parking area on the Kancamagus Highway.  It heads west, following a brook in a flat area then climbs the bank to the right and soon enters a section of an old incline logging railroad grade at one of its switchbacks.  It continues up the valley on this grade and then on old logging roads not far above the brook.  At 2.1 miles, it turns right and climbs by switchbacks to the top of the ridge above the valley to the north, then ascends the ridge - winding about at first then climbing by zigzags as the ridge steepends.  at the top of this section are several wooden staircases and at 3.2 miles a side path leads to a downlook with a very fine view of Mt. Bond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon the trail reaches the top of the ridge and its grade becomes easy until it reaches the crest of the Franconia Ridge in an unusually flat area at 3.7 mi.  The trail turns sharp right here and ascends near the crest of a narrow ridge to ajunction with the Flume Slide Trail on the left and the Franconia Ridge Trail straight ahead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Franconia Ridge Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;From summit of Flume to summit of Liberty&lt;br /&gt;1.1 miles&lt;br /&gt;50 minute&lt;/i&gt;s&lt;br /&gt;The trail begins .1 mi south of the summit of Mt. Flume in a little col, at the junction with the Osseo Trail and the Flume Slide Trail.  It climbs out of the scrub and ascends along the edge of the west-facing cliff.  From Mt. Flum it descends across a lesser knob, crosses two small sags and climbs at a progressively steepening grade to the open summit of Mt. Liberty at 1.2 miles, reaching the summit from the east, then makes a hairpin turn and descends to the east, just a few yards north of its ascent route.  It then continues to descend across ledges into the woods and passes a junction with the Liberty Spring Trail on the left at 1.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Liberty Spring Trail (We will be doing this section &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;IN REVERSE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;From the base to the Summit of Mt. Liberty via Franconia Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;(Since we are &lt;b&gt;descending&lt;/b&gt; this way, figure it will take a little less time)&lt;br /&gt;3.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;3 hr 10 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail climbs past Liberty Spring Campsite to the Franconia Ridge trail .3mi north of Mt. Liberty.  It begins on the Franconia Notch Bike Path, just north of the bridge over the Pemigewasset River, near the site of the former Whitehouse Bridge parking area;  the Cascade Brook trail begins just south of this bridge.  This trailhead is reached from the hiker's parking lot on US 2 just north of the Flume Visitor Center by the Whitehouse Trail or from the Basin parking areas by the paved bike path.  The trail ascends steadily and rather steeply at times, but the footing, while not smooth is always reasonably good.  This trail is part of the AT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the bike path, the trail climbs moderately northeast through hardwood growth.  At .4 mi it truns sharp right, joining the old main logging road from the former Whitehouse mill and soon levels off.  At 6 mi the Flume Slide Trail leaves right (south).  The LIberty Spring Trail bears left, ascending gradually and crosses a fairly large brook at 1.1 mi.  It then climbs moderately, truns sharp left off the logging road at 1.4 mi, then turns sharp right at 2.2 mi and climbs more steeply by switchbacks.  In places the footing is rough.  At 2.6 mi the trail reaches LIebery Spring Campsite on the left and the spring (last sure water) on the right.  The path then ascends fairly steeply through conifers and ends in .3 mi at the Franconia Ridge trail.  Turn right (south) for Mt. Liberty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282275110000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281290975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mid-Week:  Liberty and Flume</name><id>14357521</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282132800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14357521/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/c/global_16741820.jpeg</photo_url></item>