<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>550 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.762928</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hartford City Hall </name><city>Hartford</city><id>11397372</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674225</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join us for the Annual Trashion Fashion event featuring recycled fashion. Fun for all ages!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUGGESTED DONATION: $15 to go towards Sustainable Farm School&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;In collaboration with City Hall’s Green Action Team, Evergreen Design Co. and founder and organizer Amy Merli. All proceeds go to a scholarship fund for local children to attend The Sustainable Farm School.&lt;/span&gt; This year we have over 60 different designs that will make you rethink the way you view trash. Food trucks Lucky Taco and Urban Chef that will be parked outside City Hall starting at 5pm. String Theorie will be playing at 6:30pm. Emcee Debbie Allen Wright of Project Closet will announce the show. There will be a “stomp” inspired tap piece lead by Mike Barker and Will Jackson and a live drumming will accompany the runway show starting at 8pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The event will feature over 20 different local artists, students and designers including students from The Greater Hartford Academy of the Arts and students from Hall High in West Hartford. The models are made up of dancers, students, professional models and area celebrities including the mayor of Hartford, Pedor Segarra who will be wearing a "Trashion" tie down the runway. City hall will also be transformed into a recycled forest that is being created by students and artists from the area. After the runway there will be a Q&amp;amp;A with designers. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 There will be over 20 different eco friendly vendors and presenters. We will also be giving away seedlings out of egg shells that students from the Sustainable Farm School planted. Be sure to come early. There is a collaborated after party called Welcome to Bohemia 9pm at Hartford Bicycle that will have wine, poetry, music, food and a place to get more intimate with the artists from the Trashion show. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This is so much more than simply an Earth Day event, the Trashion Fashion Show is intended to be a community-driven effort to promote environmental awareness and the local Hartford arts scene.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366520468000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365953743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Trashion Fashion Show</name><id>114283342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366495200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/114283342/</event_url></item>