<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The exact length and path covered on this hike will depend on the weather and trail conditions. We generally plan to hike up to the ridge and follow it from a north-east to south-west direction. If there is something like 8 inches or more of snow we will likely snowshoe our way (please bring snowshoes as there may be enough snow, especially on the ridge). We'll hike no more than approximatly 7.5 miles with less being the case if conditions require more effort given a 6 hour window for hiking. More than likely we will do around 6 miles. Most of the hike is estimated to be moderate in difficulty with some opportunity for high-moderate to high exertion. Streams, forest, and quiet solitude will dominate the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Tom State Reservation is a little Northwest of Springfield with 2,082 acres with 20 miles of hiking and walking trails; cross country skiing and ice skating on Lake Bray. Mt. Tom boasts an unparalleled view of the Connecticut Valley north and south, the Berkshire mountains to the west and the Pelham hills to the east. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Those who wish to go need to have:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots only!&lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too. &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves - MUST have &amp;amp; warm ones too! &lt;br /&gt;* Gators (or snowpants) - Strongly suggested, to keep snow out of your boots and to keep dry! &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - BRIGHT color best (white isn't too good)&lt;br /&gt;* Hat - You loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too. &lt;br /&gt;* 1 - 2 quart of water - MUST bring! &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;MicroSpikes&lt;/span&gt; (or Crampons or other traction device) - strongly urged to get through icy areas!&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food/lunch - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.) &lt;br /&gt;* Bright clothing -(I don't mean white!) for visability.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advised/optional equipment depending on conditions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Hiking poles (or snowshoe poles) - For better stability&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Snowshoes&lt;/span&gt; - Strongly advised if there is 8 inches or more of snow.&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp - Just in case&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added. Please note it tends to be windy on the ridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM at the parking area at the main entrance by Lake Bray (see the park map). Directions are below. We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 6 hr. and get back to the vehicles at about 3 PM. Then the plan is to head out to eat an early dinner together at a location to be determined. We would finish up eating at about 4:30 PM and head home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor ***leaving*** at a 8 AM for those interested. There will be a dark green Dodge Caravan. Please chip in for gas and the drive is an hour. Return at about 5:30 PM. It is advised to call Kevin (number in RSVP) so he knows you plan to carpool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to meet at park parking area:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Holyoke&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=50+Reservation+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/directions for the carpool meet-up can be found at:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?searchtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;searchtab=home&amp;amp;formtype=address&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=69+Prospect+Hill+rd.&amp;amp;city=East+Windsor&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;General park information:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/mtom.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Park map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/Mt.Tom.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Can meet me in E. Windsor to join in a carpool or to follow up to hike location. Can also meet at hike location at Visitor's Center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263305281000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262714156000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Mt. Tom State Reservation in Holyoke MA</name><id>12229587</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263132000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12229587/</event_url></item>