<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What would ethics in the context of an integral and evolutionary worldview look like? Do we embody these ethics, and do our leaders embody these ethics?  In this evening's talk, we will explore where ethics have come from and where they ought to go.  Ken Rosenstein and Ted Saad will consider the idea of integral meta-ethics in a complex changing world, and whether or not there is Integrity to Integral.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ken Rosenstein&lt;/b&gt; has been a student of Integral theory and Practice for many years. He has recently been invited by Dustin DiPerna to write articles on Integral Judaism and Integral Ethics for different editions of a forthcoming volume on Integral titled &amp;quot;What is Integral?&amp;quot; to be published by Integral Publishing House. Ken is a rabbinic student and has taught Integral Torah Study. He is an active participant in the Boston Integral Commons group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ted Saad&lt;/b&gt; has 20+ years of experience in environmental engineering &amp;amp; policy, information technology, and project management. He has also studied and published work on systems thinking and ecology. He has been a student of Integral theory for nearly 10 years, and currently organizes the Boston Integral Commons group.  Ted is also a practitioner of Vajrayana Buddhism and Evolutionary Enlightenment.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291944605000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289492732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Does the Integral Emperor Have No Clothes?: The Edge of Ethics</name><id>15415660</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291940100000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/15415660/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>