<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01570</zip><lat>42.049465</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edwards Emporium</name><city>Webster</city><id>690322</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.883395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Shamballa Multi-Dimensional Healing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Witches have always had the ability to do hands-on healing,&lt;br /&gt;Now you can too! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Level One Class- Hands on Healing&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 19, 2008&lt;br /&gt;From 4:00- 6:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Included in the class each student receives a Shamballa booklet, class notes, and practice with hands-on energy healing, and a certificate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Students are also eligible to become certified with the Shamballa Foundation.&lt;br /&gt;The FIRST class will be offered to Meet-up members for a special introductory price of $35.00 per person. Classes are usually $50.00 for private classes, and $60.00 for store classes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are (4) levels to the Master Degree, with is equivalent to a Reiki Master Degree.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;]Level l - Heal Yourself &amp;amp; Others Hands On - July 19th&lt;br /&gt;Level ll- Long Distance Healing- August 9th&lt;br /&gt;Level lll- Attune To Level l Only - August 30th&lt;br /&gt;Level lV- Master Teacher- Attune &amp;amp; teach all Levels- September 6th&lt;br /&gt;______________________________________&lt;br /&gt;You may take just one level, or all four to Master&lt;br /&gt;If the student wishes to continue, levels 2 through 4 will be $60.00 for each class&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each level builds upon the other, and you must take each level before continuing on.&lt;br /&gt;I must have at least (4) students to be able to do the classes, with a limit of seven. Fee is due upon beginning of class&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;What is Shamballa?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHAMBALLA IS THE ENERGY BEYOND REIKI.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have finally reached a collective consiousness&lt;br /&gt;to be able to bring in this more powerful healing energy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shamballa is an extension of Reiki and means&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Unconditional Love&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And unconditional love, is meant to be spread around the planet.&lt;br /&gt;Shamballa is not just meant for so called,&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Healers&amp;quot;, it is meant for EVERYONE.&lt;br /&gt;Shamballa is for anyone who wants to become&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;whole&amp;quot; and who wants to heal themselves at&lt;br /&gt;all levels: Physically, Mentally, Emotionally,&lt;br /&gt;and Spiritually.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shamballa can break addictions, releases negative karma, and helps people to &amp;quot;awaken&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;remember&amp;quot; why they have come here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It helps to raise your vibration, gives you spiritual &amp;quot;gifts&amp;quot; and helps one to spiritually evolve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And I believe, that when each one of us,&lt;br /&gt;spiritually evolves, we then therefore help to raise the whole&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Collective Consciousness&amp;quot;, and we ALL to evolve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Shamballa check out my website at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shamballaa.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.shamballaa...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO EDWARDS EMPORIUM:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATED DIRECTIONS! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rte. 290 South to Rte. 395 South to Webster. Take Exit 2 off 395. At the end of the ramp, take a right onto Rte. 12 (also the same as Rte. 16). Continue on that main road through four sets of lights (make sure at the 3rd light @Webster Credit Union to stay on Rte. 12/16 which goes toward the left). Once you've passed all the fast food places (from BK to KFC to McD's) and finally gone thru the 4th light (only a bit more than a mile in total from the exit), you will pass town hall on your left and the post office on your right, which is the beginning of downtown. Start looking at street numbers and you may see #211 (Commerce Insurance) prominently marked up high on a building on the right--the class is held next door to that building at: Edwards' Emporium which is #201, and also right next door to the Party Planner. (If you get to Dunkin Donuts or the railroad tracks, you've gone too far.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk in the front door! :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216670886000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pagans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pagan-1307</urlname><id>1221723</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pagan Learning Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215977140000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shamballa Healing Level One Class</name><id>8333399</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216497600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pagan-1307/events/8333399/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/c/global_4771708.jpeg</photo_url></item>