<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I urge you to attend Rochester's Tea Party and unite as citizens to send a message to Washington DC...although symbolic, the tea party is a chance for you to join with other people in your community to express your outrage over the burden that our government is placing on us, our kids and future generations of Americans...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I realize that something like this is an uncommon act for most people, but it's a great way to send a message to politicians that seem to no longer listen to the people...I hope you join us and please pass this along and encourage your family, friends and neighbors to come to!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: April 15, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Time: 4PM - 7PM&lt;br /&gt;Place: Rochester Commons&lt;br /&gt;      Rochester, NH 03867&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional information and updates on this event, please email Michele at mpara3786@metrocast.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred Leonard (for the organizers of this event)&lt;br /&gt;603-509-3327&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click Here for &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=43.2981374+-70.9703406" target="_blank"&gt;map&lt;/a&gt; to Rochester Commons.  The Rochester Commons is the park/baseball field that is located between South Main Street (Route 108) and Arthur's Market.  If you know where Walgreen's and Frisbee Memorial Hospital are, Rochester Commons is about halfway in between those two locations.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239999296000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239021465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rochester Tea Party</name><id>10125376</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239825600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/10125376/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/6/global_2979206.jpeg</photo_url></item>