<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;An easy way to become the recognized authority in your field is to share your expertise. Whether writing a blog, newsletter, or an article, there are many ways to set you apart and take your business to the next level. Creating that on-line presence can be a hurdle for many who like the idea but lack the time or writing skills. Claudia will help make it easier to create written content that demonstrates your expertise, establishes you as an authority, and creates trust. She&amp;rsquo;ll give you templates, formulas, and how-to&amp;rsquo;s for generating attention-grabbing info give-aways.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Claudia Gere (www.ClaudiaGereCo.com) helps business leaders, entrepreneurs, and consultants develop their best writing strategy for an online presence and to realize their dreams of becoming an author. Through her webinars, workshops, and individual coaching, she has launched many first-time authors on the path to writing and publishing success. Some recent author successes include: More Time for You: A Powerful System to Organize Your Work and Get Things Done, published by AMACOM, Creating Demand: Generate Cool, Custom Marketing Ideas, published by Prometheus Books and for release next year by McGraw-Hill, Conversation Transformation. She has helped many other authors publish and promote their books and is the author of Name Your Book: 94 Nonfiction Title Tips. Claudia holds a bachelor's in English and a master's in management. She is a board member of the grassroots organization Hidden-Tech.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suzanne Larocque</member_name><member_id>9376325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306195749000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303772780000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Breakfast Meeting- Create an On-Line Presence with Authority</name><id>17430585</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305805500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/17430585/</event_url></item>