<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/d/6/event_211212502.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March Breakfast Meeting: Passion Sells: 3 Keys to Connecting Powerfully With Your Audience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; $20 in advance (members receive $5 cash back at check in)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How effective are you at engaging your audience? If you’re struggling to convert your prospects into customers, this session is for you! Kim George will share how she utilizes the passion of her nonprofit mission to engage volunteers, donors, and sponsors to make a difference in Springfield. People buy emotion. Learn how to maximize your authenticity, communicate with passion, and channel positivity to build your business or grow your career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim’s nonprofit, Kane’s Krusade™, provides C.A.R.E. Kits to help families take care of their dogs in difficult economic times. This keeps loved dogs out of shelters and saves the tax payer money. To support the dog of a family in need, please consider bringing a can or two of dog food to the WBOA meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kim is a professional coach, trainer, speaker, and the best-selling author of “Coaching Into Greatness: 4 Steps to Success in Business and Life” (Wiley &amp;amp; Sons). Kim’s professional experience includes founding The Abundance Intelligence Institute®, a coaching, consulting, and training company based on her revolutionary methodology, Abundance Intelligence®. Kim also founded Leverage Dynamics, a business strategy firm; was VP of Strategic Alliances for the CoachVille School of Coaching; and acted as Dean of The Referral Institute® Directive Coaching School.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kim is co-author of the NY Times bestseller “Masters of Success” with Dr. Ivan Misner. Called a "brilliant maverick" by "Guerrilla Marketing" author Jay Conrad Levinson, Kim is a recognized expert in the areas of social capital and strategic alliances.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In 2012, Kim founded Kane’s Krusade™. The Springfield non-profit improves the quality of life of dogs by providing C.A.R.E. Kits to families in need. C.A.R.E. Kits include food, treats, toys, vaccinations, spay/neuter, insulated dog houses, and behavioral training.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kim has a B.S. in Paralegal Studies from Rivier College.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Parizo</member_name><member_id>5035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363895357000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362460546000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Breakfast Meeting: 3 Keys to Connecting Powerfully With Your Audience</name><id>107673392</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>6300000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363866300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/107673392/</event_url></item>