<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;RESCHEDULED!!!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan Sackett will be joining us for our monthly meeting to give a presentation on &amp;quot;Humanism/Freethought in Star Trek -- Did It Boldly Go?&amp;quot; with special emphasis on the Philosophy of Gene Roddenberry and how it changed throughout the original series and Next Gen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[Ms. Sackett] began an association with Gene Roddenberry, creator of the television legend Star Trek, serving as his personal executive assistant for over 17 years until his death in October 1991. She also served as his production assistant on the first Star Trek film and worked closely with him on the next five Star Trek movies.  In addition, she served as Production Associate during the first five seasons of the television series, Star Trek: The Next Generation.  She is the author of 10 books about the film and television industry. In 1994, Susan left California and relocated to Arizona, where she got involved with the Humanist Society of Greater Phoenix, for which she has been president since 2000. Since 2005, she has been on the Board of Directors of the American Humanist Association, and currently serves on the Executive Committee as Secretary.&amp;quot; - Point of Inquiry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a great presentation. Right now it is scheduled to start at 7 at the UU Church of Worcester, with doors opening at 6:30 for socializing and conversation. Please watch this page for changes of venue or time since this Meetup is a ways off.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276717956000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265399203000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Susan Sackett - "Humanism/Freethought in Star Trek -- Did It Boldly Go?"</name><id>12529582</id><headcount>63</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276641000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/12529582/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/3/e/global_12953694.jpeg</photo_url></item>