<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We all know what's said about April. (Thanks, T.S. Eliot.) But what about May, that fuzzy month of sprimmer...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"May is a pious fraud of the almanac."-- James R. Lowell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"What potent blood hath modest May." --Ralph W. Emerson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it's knocking at our doors, as I write this, and we can finally take to the great outdoors. (See note about the meetup location at the bottom.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A number of you know and like well our tradition-in-the-making...our poetry readings, or as I call them, our literary gift-giving. Let's do one again! Let us each bring a poem or two that we love and would like to share with the group. In the past people have brought poems long and short, or excerpts from epics or novels in verse (Homer and Pushkin qualify!), often from the usual suspects, but sometimes not. If you could introduce us to something new or get us to experience a poem we already know in a new way, you'll have accomplished what we're after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll have up to five minutes of our attention. So, choose wisely. You may decide to participate or to simply listen. If possible, let us know in advance your selection, and if you can, bring copies of the piece to share with the group (it makes it easier to follow).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I leave you with yet another poem that makes mention of May, though we don't have to stick to nature and passing seasons. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The trees are coming into leaf &lt;br /&gt;

Like something almost being said; &lt;br /&gt;

The recent buds relax and spread, &lt;br /&gt;

Their greenness is a kind of grief. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Is it that they are born again &lt;br /&gt;

And we grow old? No, they die too, &lt;br /&gt;

Their yearly trick of looking new &lt;br /&gt;

Is written down in rings of grain. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Yet still the unresting castles thresh &lt;br /&gt;

In fullgrown thickness every May. &lt;br /&gt;

Last year is dead, they seem to say, &lt;br /&gt;

Begin afresh, afresh, afresh." &lt;br /&gt;

- Philip Larkin, &lt;em&gt;The Trees&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: Weather permitting, let's meet right outside Crema Cafe a few minutes prior to the meeting. We'll then head over to the Radcliffe garden for the reading.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337047336000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335831773000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poetry Reading Evening</name><id>62844242</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336945500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/62844242/</event_url></item>