<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Exact Address TBA</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.283432</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>George's House</name><city>Needham</city><id>4409152</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.232834</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/2/0/event_122432032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;50 Shades of Grey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by E. L. James&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"When literature student Anastasia Steele goes to interview young entrepreneur Christian Grey, she encounters a man who is beautiful, brilliant, and intimidating.  The unworldly, innocent Ana is startled to realize she wants this man and, despite his enigmatic reserve, finds she is desperate to get close to him.  Unable to resist Ana’s quiet beauty, wit, and independent spirit, Grey admits he wants her, too—but on his own terms. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Shocked yet thrilled by Grey’s singular erotic tastes, Ana hesitates. For all the trappings of success—his multinational businesses, his vast wealth, his loving family—Grey is a man tormented by demons and consumed by the need to control.  When the couple embarks on a daring, passionately physical affair, Ana discovers Christian Grey’s secrets and explores her own dark desires. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Erotic, amusing, and deeply moving, the Fifty Shades Trilogy is a tale that will obsess you, possess you, and stay with you forever."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, at least, that's what the editors at Amazon seem to think.  But whether you enjoy the book or not, it would be hard to deny that 50 Shades of Grey has fast become something of a cultural phenomenon, and is poised to become the guilty secret of this year's summer reading.  I expect I am not the only one intrigued and a bit curious . . .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides, what better choice to introduce the new "after dark" meetup series, featuring books with decidedly adult themes?  Please note that, given the subject matter of books in the "after dark" series, these events will generally be held at more private locations and participants should be prepared for adult oriented discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With respect to this event, for those who have not yet attended an event in my home, I live in Needham, and the exact address will be sent via email to all yes RSVPs the day of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
Also, I have a greyhound in residence, so if you are highly allergic or scared of large dogs, this may not be a good meetup event for you. Finally, please note that the number of attendees is limited due to size constraints.  Therefore, please only RSVP if  you plan on attending, and please also keep your RSVP up to date.  Thanks!</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341071333000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337803796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"After Dark Series" - 50 Shades of Grey</name><id>66046812</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341012600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/66046812/</event_url></item>