<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Central Square)</address_2><address_1>780 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366772</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-868-8800</phone><name>Tavern in the Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1001184</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If there's enough interest, I'll host a last minute happy hour at Tavern in the Square, (That's in Central Square, Cambridge).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out Tavern in the Square's website:  &lt;a href="http://www.taverninthesquare.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.taverninth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I going to see the Chicken Slacks at the Cantab at 9pm with a few other Meetup groups, so feel free to join me for that as well.  Originally, I had planned to go to the gym, then go see the Chicken Slacks, but um, I really don't feel like going to the gym that night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out The Cantab's website:  &lt;a href="http://www.cantab-lounge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cantab-lou...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will reluctantly give out my cell phone # to the people who respond yes or maybe around 2pm July, 2nd.  Please only call me if you can't find us in the restaurant.  Call the restaurant if you need directions.  The best way to get there is to take the red line to Central Square.  If you want to drive, you can usually find parking in the area.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please maintain your own tab because there will be no group tab.  People come and go as they please, so a group tab doesn't work out well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, join me for a last minute happy hour at the Tavern in the Square at 6pm and then to see the Chicken Slacks at the Cantab at 9pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cantab is just a hop, skip and a jump away from Tavern in the Square.  Since you'll be with me at the Happy Hour, you can just take my hand and we'll hop, skip and jump there together.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll email my cell phone # at 2pm on July 2nd.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>2969721</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247177622000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246465296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tavern in the Square in Cambridge - Last Minute Happy Hour</name><id>10779390</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246572000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/10779390/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/d/global_9267149.jpeg</photo_url></item>