<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364744</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-1580</phone><name>Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1019999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Composed of four compelling portraits of Jewish emigres whose lives have  been scarred by exile, dislocation and persecution, this unusual work  of fiction is pervaded by a sensibility and a degree of circumstantial  detail so authentic that it could pass for historical documentation. Ultimately, it is a meditation on memory and loss.&amp;nbsp; Sebald re-creates the lives of   four   exiles--five if you include his oblique self-portrait--through their    own  accounts, others' recollections, and pictures and found objects.  But he  brings these men before our eyes only to make them fade away,    "longing for  extinction."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sebald's own longing is for communion. En route to Ithaca (the real   upstate   New York location but also the symbolic one), he comes to feel   "like a   travelling companion of my neighbor in the next lane." After the   car  speeds  away--"the children pulling clownish faces out of the rear    window--I felt  deserted and desolate for a time." Sebald's narrative is  purposely  moth-holed (butterfly-ridden, actually--there's a recurring   Nabokov-with-a-net type), an escape from the prison-house of realism. And he seems to have inherited his family's&amp;nbsp; special way of coping with trauma, or as he calls it "an illness which causes lost memories to be    replaced by  fantastic inventions."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299608833000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297875629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sebald: The Emigrants</name><id>16587821</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299452400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/16587821/</event_url></item>