<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A vision is a mental picture of something that you want. An individual can have a vision of their ideal job; an organization can have a vision of the future they want to create. A compelling vision is one that is clear, exciting, and inspiring. For an individual, it is strong enough to pull us out of our comfort zones and get us into action. For an organization, a compelling vision is one that inspires the staff to fully commit themselves to the organization’s mission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A compelling vision tells you where you want to get to. When you set goals and act without a compelling vision, you may be in motion but you can’t be sure where you are going to end up. It gives you the energy and inspiration to move past whatever blocks arise in the process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our February meetup, coaches Monique Morimoto Flaherty and Ted Behr will talk with us about just what does make a vision compelling and will lead us in a process of discovering our own compelling vision, whether it is for our organization or for ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Introductions: (15 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Roundtable Discussion: (60 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Announcements, opportunities, connections (10 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.. Exchange business cards/social networking. (15 mins)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the room 15 minutes early.  You'll recognize me from my photo!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jari Poulin</member_name><member_id>4665005</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248823151000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233751068000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creating a Compelling Vision for Yourself or Your Organization!</name><id>9670629</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237417200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/9670629/</event_url></item>