<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Another late post, but I think there are some of people like me who make plans at the last minute.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I never heard of this film until I was exploring the Kendall's website, but the plot and subject matter look intriguing. Hope you can make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About &lt;em&gt;Even the Rain&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Spanish film crew arrives in Bolivia to make a film about Columbus in the New World. Idealistic director Sebastian (Gael Garc&amp;iacute;a Bernal, &lt;em&gt;The Motorcycle Diaries&lt;/em&gt;) wants to denounce the injustices of the past, focusing on exploitation of the indigenous people. Practical producer Costa (Luis Tosar, &lt;em&gt;Cell 211&lt;/em&gt;), working on a tight budget, has chosen Bolivia, one of Latin America&amp;rsquo;s poorest countries, to stand in for Santo Domingo because extras will work for only $2 a day. After an open casting call almost degenerates into a riot, Sebastian hires outspoken Daniel (Juan Carlos Aduviri) to play the rebel Indian leader. But when the locals begin demonstrations against a multinational's plans to privatize water&amp;mdash;even the rain&amp;mdash;Daniel is in the thick of them, endangering the film&amp;rsquo;s shooting schedule. The thought-provoking screenplay by Paul Laverty &lt;em&gt;(The Wind That Shakes the Barley)&lt;/em&gt; cunningly parallels the Spanish conquest of the Americas with the modern spread of capitalism. This fascinating mixture of past and present, fiction and fact, features spectacular scenes of the period film within a film. Directed by Ic&amp;iacute;ar Bolla&amp;iacute;n &lt;em&gt;(Take My Eyes)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The movie-within-a-movie being filmed about Columbus is as vivid as a Werner Herzog period adventure." - Gerald Peary, &lt;em&gt;Boston Phoenix&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Making a film about making a film is a landmine, one that's both tripped up and rewarded directors for decades. Bolla&amp;iacute;n manages it wonderfully, almost too well." - Justin Strout, &lt;em&gt;Orlando Weekly&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Scenes of Columbus's arrival and of his imperialist and religious sloganeering, and of the carnage he wreaks, have a grandeur and a force reminiscent of Terrence Malick films. The segments about the chaotic water riots have a documentary immediacy." - Stephen Holden, &lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film, I'll be near the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300631971000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300296517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Even the Rain</name><id>16944414</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300564800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16944414/</event_url></item>