<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Priyatam Mudivarti of &lt;a href="http://www.crameronline.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crameronline.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crameronli...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will lead a discussion of Seam at the April meetup. He says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tired of Java MVC Frameworks? Jealous of RoR stack?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to Seam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Written and led by Gavin King (the creator of Hibernate), Seam is a powerful open source development platform for building rich Internet applications in Java. Seam integrates technologies such as AJAX, JSF, Java Persistence (JPA), Hibernate, Enterprise Java Beans (EJB 3.0), Business Process Management (BPM), first class support for Security and Identity Management and dependency Injection among others into a unified full-stack solution, complete with &lt;a href="http://jboss.org/tools" target="_blank"&gt;sophisticated tooling&lt;/a&gt;. Seam has been designed from the ground up to eliminate complexity at both architecture and API levels. It enables developers to assemble complex web applications using simple annotated Java classes, a rich set of UI components, very little XML with rich support for integration testing and code scaffolding out of the box. Seam's unique support for conversations and declarative state management can introduce a more sophisticated user experience while at the same time eliminating common bugs found in traditional web applications. Seam also works with other view technologies like GWT (using web remoting), Wicket, Adobe Flex and works well for pojo development (not just EJB3).&lt;br /&gt;More about Seam Framework &lt;a href="http://docs.jboss.com/seam/latest/reference/en-US/html/Book-Preface.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Environment Setup&lt;br /&gt;    * Overview of Seam&lt;br /&gt;    * Top 10 Reasons to use Seam&lt;br /&gt;    * Demo Application with Pojos/JPA/Tomcat (with Security features)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker  bio:&lt;br /&gt;Priyatam has over seven years of experience in Java/J2EE Technologies in several consulting roles. Interests: Spring Suite, JBoss Suite (Seam, Hibernate, Envers, Hibernate Search, Drools, JBpm etc), EJB3, Groovy&lt;br /&gt;He's currently a Senior Engineer at &lt;a href="http://www.crameronline.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Cramer&lt;/a&gt;, a digital marketing firm. More about him, on his tech blog -- &lt;a href="http://www.reverttoconsole.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.reverttoconsole.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.reverttoco...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/pub/dir/?last=mudivarti&amp;amp;first=priyatam" target="_blank"&gt;linkedin profile&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presentations/discussions are held at MIT's EHS Office, 265 Massachusetts Ave, upstairs from the MIT Museum; the office is on the 4th floor of the building; please use the door that is noted in the following picture:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/johnarch/2341265278/sizes/m/" target="_blank"&gt;presentation location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation we will head over to The Asgard, a restaurant/bar at the corner of Mass Ave and Sidney Street (350 Mass Ave):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=350+massachusetts+avenue,+cambridge,+ma&amp;amp;sll=42.366487,-71.098816&amp;amp;sspn=0.008815,0.022745&amp;amp;g=Massachusetts+Ave+%26+Sidney+St,+Cambridge,+Middlesex,+Massachusetts+02139,+United+States&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.366963,-71.097186&amp;amp;spn=0.008815,0.022745&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;cbll=42.362981,-71.099593&amp;amp;panoid=VqQEj12CG6gv-yL4iXehHQ&amp;amp;cbp=1,178.60443018981482,,0,-0.8543880653277005" target="_blank"&gt;asgard location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the past, some of you may have parked your car in the lot adjacent to my building, but unfortunately the lot has since become a 24-hour tow zone for non-MIT vehicles. There is usually parking on Windsor street alongside my building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are personal, engaging and everybody is sharing in the topic at hand. Come and share your experience with your peers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.: Thank you to the many members that RSVP (one way or another). This helps your humble organizer to manage the crowd at the venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>take eleveator to 4th floor &amp;&amp; look for meetup signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Archambault</member_name><member_id>2399674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245107905000</updated><rating><average>4.11999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237246956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Java April Meetup: Seam</name><id>9968789</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240871400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/9968789/</event_url></item>