<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>989 Ellington Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06074</zip><lat>41.822426</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 289-7929</phone><name>Mill on the River</name><city>South Windsor</city><id>517746</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.588196</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Come join us for Happy Hour at Mill On The River ( www.themillontheriver.com). It's been several months since we've had a Happy Hour at this picturesque restaurant (directions are below).  &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;The  restaurant, at one time was occupied by a grist mill and has history dating back 200 years.  It's original damn, built by Colonists and Podunk Indians, is the oldest in Connecticut.  As you walk to the restaurant from the parking area, you walk through a covered bridge (walkway) which is over the damn and river.  The nearby pond is adjacent to the bar area where we'll be gathering.  &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;Happy Hour specials are from 3:00 to 6:00 in the bar only. The specials are: $5 wines by the glass, $5 martinis, $3 pints on tap and 1/2 price small plates (see below).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Small Plates:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Maryland Crab Cake&lt;br /&gt;accompanied by chive cream and lemon Remoulade sauces $10&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Eggplant Timbale&lt;br /&gt;roasted eggplant layered with spinach, sun-dried tomatoes, and herb Alouette cheese; topped with smoked buffalo Mozzarella cheese, and house-made sweet marinara $7&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Berkshire Pork Tenderloin Medallions&lt;br /&gt;wrapped in applewood-smoked bacon and served atop a bed of mashed turnips with an herb-infused demi-glace $8&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Harvest Quesadillas&lt;br /&gt;stuffed with smoked native corn, black beans, harvest squashes, and herb jack cheese; topped with a native tomato and grilled corn poblano salsa $8&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Coconut Shrimp&lt;br /&gt;with an apple curry dipping sauce and hand-gathered baby field greens $9&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Grilled Beef Brochettes&lt;br /&gt;tender, marinated Angus beef brochettes with ginger soy and apple curry dipping sauces $9&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Classic Calamari Fritti&lt;br /&gt;with zesty caper marinara and lemon Remoulade sauces $8&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Assorted House-Made Bruschettas&lt;br /&gt;with tomato and sweet basil, herb goat cheese and roasted red bell peppers, hummus and olive tapenade, adn white bean with truffle oil and parsley $6&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Grilled Swiss Bratwurst&lt;br /&gt;traditional veal sausage, pan-seared and served in a pan gravy with sauerkraut and sweet grain mustard $7&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Free-Range Buffalo Chicken Tenders&lt;br /&gt;with spicy ancho pepper marinade, matchstick vegetables, and Great Hill Bleu cheese dipping sauce $7&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.E.I. Mussels&lt;br /&gt;sauteed and served with your choice of marinara sauce, spicy tomato Fra Diavolo sauce, or with a garlic, herb, and white wine Poulette sauce with a touch of cream $9&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Butternut Squash Bisque&lt;br /&gt;topped with nutmeg-infused creme fraiche and spice pine nuts $6&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Pan-Seared New Bedford Scallops&lt;br /&gt;with a cinnamon and nutmeg glaze, grilled native apples, and port wine reduction $10&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Garlic &amp;amp; Gorgonzola Bread&lt;br /&gt;rustic-style bread topped with melted Gorgonzola cheese and roasted red bell peppers $5&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Roasted Vegetable Antipasto Sampler&lt;br /&gt;roasted eggplant, zucchini, yellow squash, caramelized onions, assorted olives, caperberries, oven-roasted tomatoes, Parmesan and Provolone cheeses, diced hard salamis, Prosciutto di Parma, basil pesto, and aged balsamic $15&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Artisinal Cheese Plate&lt;br /&gt;Aosta Valley Fontina, smoked Farmstead Gouda, Vermont Buttermilk Bleu, Swiss Gruyere, Wisconsin Brie, champagne grapes, caramelized walnuts, toast points, and a fig jam $14&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FROM HARTFORD: 91 North to exit 35A (Rt. 291) take exit 4 off Rt. 291. Stay to the left and go straight through the light to Rt. 30 (you will be facing granite signs that say &amp;quot;Welcome to South Windsor&amp;quot;) Follow Rt. 30 approximately 2 miles and we will be on the right-hand side. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;FROM SPRINGFIELD: 91 South to exit 35A (Rt. 291) take exit 4 off Rt. 291.Stay to the left and go straight through the light to Rt. 30 (you will be facing granite signs that say &amp;quot;Welcome to South Windsor&amp;quot;) Follow Rt. 30 approximately 2 miles and we will be on the right-hand side. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;FROM BRADLEY AIRPORT: 91 South to exit 35A (Rt. 291) take exit 4 off Rt. 291. Stay to the left and go straight through the light to Rt. 30 (you will be facing granite signs that say &amp;quot;Welcome to South Windsor&amp;quot;) Follow Rt. 30 approximately 2 miles and we will be on the right-hand side. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;FROM WEST HARTFORD: 84 East to exit 62 (Buckland Street). At the end of the ramp make a left onto Buckland St. and follow for 2 miles until you come to a four way intersection with Rt. 30. (White church will be directly in front of you) Make a left onto Rt. 30 and we will be 1.5 miles down on the left hand side. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FROM BOSTON OR STURBRIDGE: 84 West to exit 63. At the end of exit ramp make a left onto Rt. 30. Follow Rt. 30 for 5 miles and we will be on the left hand side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1261260776000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260494310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour, Mill On The River, South Windsor, Thurs., December 17 @ 5:00 PM</name><id>12062684</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261087200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12062684/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/f/global_12178127.jpeg</photo_url></item>