<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dogtown Commons represents one of the few deserted villages in New England. Settled in the early eighteenth century as primarily a farming community, its population declined sharply after the American Revolution.  Many local men didn't return from the war and those who did moved on to the coastal regions of Cape Ann.  Left behind were the widows, the poor and the abandoned family dogs.  By 1830, only dogs roamed the area. Today, it is comprised of 3,000 acres of undeveloped land, which is mostly owned by the City of Gloucester and is used as a watershed for Babson and Goose Cove reservoirs. Three walks are available, each offering their own unique sites. The walk we'll be taking in the Dogtown area begins on Dogtown Road and proceeds to Wharf Road, Commons Road and through Adams Pines. The distance is approximately three miles, taking about one to two hours. Birds, animals, geological formations, and cellar holes and wells of the early settlers can be seen.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs are allowed off leash.  Hunting is allowed in Dogtown from October 19th through April 1st.  No hunting is allowed on Sunday (hence heading out Sunday morning).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: From Route 128 in Gloucester, drive to the Grant Circle Rotary. (There are two rotaries on Route 128. One is Blackburn Circle, which leads you to Blackburn Industrial Park and a school, which is not what you want. The Grant Circle has a view of the marsh and businesses (Friendly's Restaurant) adjacent to it and the large Welcome to Gloucester sign).  At the Grant Circle rotary watch the signs and take the third exit toward Lanesville, Route 127/Washington Street, then take an immediate right onto Poplar Street. Drive a short distance, then turn left onto Cherry Street, up a steep winding hill to a flat area, then continue about 1 mile and watch for signs on the right, and turn right up a hill to the Dogtown Road parking area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253214723000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>trail seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NE-Trail-Dogs</urlname><id>1347727</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>New England Trail Dogs</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231213924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dogtown Commons (Gloucester)  *Dogs permitted off leash.</name><id>9455774</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232892000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-Trail-Dogs/events/9455774/</event_url></item>