<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our October pick is The Great Gatsby by F. Scott Fitzgerald.  Here is the synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is not only about the American Dream, but it is also a love story, of sorts, the narrative of Gatsby's quixotic passion for Daisy Buchanan. The pair meet five years before the novel begins, when Daisy is a legendary young Louisville beauty and Gatsby an impoverished officer. They fall in love, but while Gatsby serves overseas, Daisy marries the brutal, bullying, but extremely rich Tom Buchanan. After the war, Gatsby devotes himself blindly to the pursuit of wealth by whatever means--and to the pursuit of Daisy, which amounts to the same thing. &amp;quot;Her voice is full of money,&amp;quot; Gatsby says admiringly, in one of the novel's more famous descriptions. His millions made, Gatsby buys a mansion across Long Island Sound from Daisy's patrician East Egg address, throws lavish parties, and waits for her to appear. When she does, events unfold with all the tragic inevitability of a Greek drama, with detached, cynical neighbor Nick Carraway acting as chorus throughout. Spare, elegantly plotted, and written in crystalline prose, The Great Gatsby is as perfectly satisfying as the best kind of poem. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in November and I hope you enjoy the book!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228866719000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224029301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club November Meetup - The Great Gatsby</name><id>8963071</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226448000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/8963071/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/8/global_5881352.jpeg</photo_url></item>