<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
          &lt;strong&gt;The Greater Hartford Festival of Jazz was originally conceived by Paul Brown, noted Hartford jazz bassist and music educator who produced the Monday Night Jazz Concerts in Bushnell Park for&amp;nbsp;25 years.&lt;/strong&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
        
          
            
              
                &lt;p&gt;
                &lt;strong&gt;The Greater Hartford Festival of Jazz's mission is to expose, &amp;nbsp;educate their ever-growing audiences while celebrating America's only true art form, JAZZ, by presenting over twenty-five hours of music performed by internationally acclaimed, world-class jazz musicians and ar&lt;/strong&gt;tists.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
              
            
            
              
                 &lt;br /&gt;
              
            
            
              &amp;nbsp;
            
          
        
        &lt;p&gt;
          &lt;strong&gt;Currently,&amp;nbsp;The Greater Hartford Festival of Jazz has grown to be the largest FREE jazz event in New England, featuring great jazz artists from around the world, the USA, as well as young and up-and-coming performers from the local region,&amp;nbsp;averaging an attendance of over 45,000, and attracting more than 55,000 fans during the three day Festival in 2010.&lt;/strong&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          &lt;strong&gt;Now in its twentieth year, The Greater Hartford Festival of Jazz Stage has been graced with the presence of many outstanding and notable jazz bands and vocalists.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          &lt;strong&gt;With Connecticut's State Capitol Building and Hartford's skyline providing a beautiful, dramatic backdrop as the sun sets and the stars rise in the night sky and on stage, audiences are sure to enjoy a wonderful summer evening of jazz. &amp;nbsp;Best of all its all FREE!!!!&lt;/strong&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;Friday&lt;/strong&gt;
         &lt;br /&gt; 
        &lt;strong&gt;6:30 pm - Opening Ceremony&lt;/strong&gt;
         &lt;br /&gt; 
        &lt;strong&gt;7:00 pm -&amp;nbsp; 
        &lt;a href="http://www.goyapiano.com/band" target="_blank"&gt;David Gonzalez &amp;amp; The Latin Jazz Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
         &lt;br /&gt; 
        &lt;strong&gt;8:30 pm -&amp;nbsp; 
        &lt;a href="http://www.curtisbrothersmusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Zaccai Curtis Latin Jazz Quintet feat. Ray Vega, Dafnis Prieto, Andy Gonzalez &amp;amp; Reinaldo de Jes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
        &lt;strong&gt;
        &lt;a href="http://www.curtisbrothersmusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;us&lt;/a&gt;
         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;
          &lt;strong&gt;MEETING TIME 6:30 PM. I WILL PROVIDE MY # TO YES RSVP'S THURSDAY NIGHT. &amp;nbsp;I WAS THINKING THAT A GOOD MEETING AREA WILL BE BY THE BIG SHADED TREE ON THE LEFT SIDE OF THE STAGE. &amp;nbsp;BRING BLANKETS AND CHAIRS AND SNACKS TO SHARE. HOPE TO SEE YOU THERE!! JOLETA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          &lt;img src="http://www.hartfordjazz.com/images/festival_pic02.jpg" width="200" height="260" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
           &lt;br /&gt;
           &lt;br /&gt;
           &lt;br /&gt;
           &lt;br /&gt;
           &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will provide my tel# to YES RSVP's to locate where the group will be. There is a nice shaded tree area close to the left side of the stage, I was thinking meeting in that area.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310853412000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310522436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Night 1: Greater Hartford Festival of Jazz</name><id>25545791</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310769000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/25545791/</event_url></item>