<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Providence River Sunset &amp;amp; Full Moon Paddle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 7:30 PM, Launch by 8:00. Sunset is 8:25 PM.&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancellation will be made by email before 5:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip organizer: Mark Roberts 401-533-1883 Cell email: hrmmark@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lights for your boat are required for night paddles. So are PFDs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Providence is absolutely beautiful at night. The lights from the city make the paddle spectacular and enjoyable. It is a very easy paddle, suitable for all style and length boats. We will be paddling into the sunset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We launch on South Water Street, just beyond Hemenway's Restaurant. After passing under the first bridge you are in and under the city. Waterfire braziers line the center of the river. The Providence court house and RI School of Design (RISD) are on your right. Passing under more bridges you come to the confluence of the Woonasqatucket and Moshassuck Rivers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bearing to the left you come into Water Place Park. The Providence Mall is in front of you. Paddle under the mall and the train tracks and continue up river until you run out of water. This section can only be done at high tides, which it will be tonight at 8:03 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the South Water Street boat ramp across from the parking lot after Hemenway's.&lt;br /&gt;Auto GPS: Use address 280 South Water Street, Providence&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the South Water Street Boat Ramp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 1 from Rt. 195 (Downtown Providence)&lt;br /&gt;At end of Exit Ramp, merge onto Dyer Street&lt;br /&gt;Follow Dyer Street for about .25 mile, then turn right onto the Crawford Street Bridge. At end of Crawford Street Bridge, turn right onto South Water Street Boat Ramp, ahead on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS Coordinates: N 41 49 341 W071 24 351&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our leaders provide directions as a courtesy to paddlers however, you are responsible to refer to a map and familiarize yourself with the trip location.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277663730000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276538060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence River Sunset &amp; Full Moon Paddle</name><id>13797451</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277508600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/13797451/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/0/global_6975552.jpeg</photo_url></item>