<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>M1</address_2><address_1>300 Summer St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.349928</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>FPAC Gallery</name><city>Boston</city><id>765821</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.049334</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join Us in Exploring One of the First Artists' Communities to Hold Open Studios in Boston! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1978, Fort Point artists have opened their studios to the public during the third weekend in October. Open Studios events attract about 10,000 visitors to our neighborhood, offering the public a rare glimpse into the living and working spaces of artists, while providing a valuable opportunity for artists to sell their work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Fort Point is a neighborhood of South Boston located next to Downtown, a short walk from South Station. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will meet at 300 Summer Street, Fort Point Channel Gallery at 1:00 pm. At 1:30 we will begin our stroll around to the various studios. I should be easy to identify/find - I will be wearing a red jacket - and my posted photo is recent and looks just like me...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check out the map link below.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/visual-art-appreciators-boston/pages/http%3A//www.fortpointarts.org/images/open_studios/2009/FPAC_visit.pdf"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fortpointarts.org/images/open_studios/2009/FPAC_visit.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fortpointa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By public transit: Take the T's Red Line to the South Station stop. Look for the Summer Street or Federal Reserve exit. Once above ground, orient yourself so that the clustered buildings of downtown are at your back; the steel-gray Federal Reserve building should be to your left and South Station to your right. This is Summer Street. Walk for one block and cross the Fort Point Channel. Turn right on Melcher Street and follow it 2 blocks where it ends at A Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By car:Please use a free online map service, such as Mapquest, Google Maps or Yahoo Maps. If visiting us for Open Studios, Art Walk or our Holiday Sale, enter 249 A Street as your destination to be directed to free event parking. &lt;br /&gt;Free Parking for Open Studios events will be located:&lt;br /&gt;in the Central Parking Lot across from 249 A street, enter the lot from Binford Street, off of A Street&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen S.</member_name><member_id>8159655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>20</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248739000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253376025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fort Point Channel Open Studios</name><id>11412995</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255885200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/11412995/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/5/6/global_10775718.jpeg</photo_url></item>