<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/7/6/event_151819062.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;September's meeting will be big a WINGs program. It should be very interesting. We have a knowledgeable pair of aviation lawyers coming to speak with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this meeting, please RSVP both on the meetup site AND the FAA site at &lt;a href="http://faasafety.gov/SPANS/event_details.aspx?eid=45869&amp;amp;caller=/SPANS/events/EventList.aspx"&gt;http://faasafety.gov/SPANS/event_details.aspx?eid=45869&amp;amp;caller=/SPANS/events/EventList.aspx&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is an excerpt from the FAA website about the program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So You Think You're Legal and Safe?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Hi, I'm from the FAA and have a few questions for you&lt;/span&gt;". How would you respond to that? Or, how do you respond to a call or letter from the FAA concerning your aviation activities? Attend this exclusive briefing and learn how to stay safe and legal.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This exciting program features three speakers: FAASTeam Program Manager Jim Adams, aviation industry attorney Kevin C. Cain and FAA New England Region Counsel Chris Poreda.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FAASTeam Program Manager Jim Adams will begin the program with a review of recent accident trends and several hot safety topics, then, featured speakers Kevin Cain and Chris Poreda will address the safety and legal issues of owning, operating and maintaining an aircraft in today's complex world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chris Poreda is a pilot, CFI, attended the US Air Force Academy and has experience in the F-4D/E and T-37 aircraft. Chris has served as the New England Region Counsel from 2002 to present and an FAA Attorney from 1990 to 2002. Prior to this he was with the practice of Bingham, Dana and Gould, (now Bingham McCutchin).  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kevin C. Cain&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is an aviation attorney and Partner at the Law Practice of Peabody and Arnold LLP, Boston, MA. Kevin has represented major domestic airlines, aircraft owners, aircraft renters, flight instructors, flying schools, fixed-base operators and pilots. He has served as panel counsel to the Aircraft Owners &amp;amp; Pilots Association for the defense of pilots in FAA enforcement actions. In addition, he has handled a variety of aviation coverage matters; including coverage issues in general aviation accidents such as litigation over excluded uses, breach of warranty clauses, renter-pilot exclusion, pilot qualification clauses and open pilot warranty clauses.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $30bucks a year?&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Scales</member_name><member_id>6873008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347505866000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344690655000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 Monthly Meetup</name><id>lrkdnyqmbpb</id><headcount>90</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347400800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/77292322/</event_url></item>