<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Fred didn't get a chance to schedule this movie, and I offered to step in if it turned out I have the time. And I do. And did you hear how hot it's going to be outside the air-conditioned theater on &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Thursday?!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Safety Not Guaranteed&lt;/em&gt; stars Mark Duplass, who is fast becoming one of my favorite actors/directors. I first saw him in &lt;em&gt;Humpday&lt;/em&gt;, which also played in Boston in 2009. He and his brother directed &lt;em&gt;Jeff, Who Lives at Home&lt;/em&gt;, a recent Boston-area release. And Aubrey Plaza is hilarious. This movie is getting rave reviews for its originality. I want to see if I am surprised by the ending.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;*****From the theater website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;In the romantic comedy &lt;em&gt;Safety Not Guaranteed&lt;/em&gt;, an unusual classified ad inspires three cynical Seattle magazine employees (Aubrey Plaza, Jake Johnson, and Karan Soni) to look for the story behind it. They discover a mysterious eccentric named Kenneth (Mark Duplass, &lt;em&gt;Your Sister's Sister&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Humpday&lt;/em&gt;), a likable but paranoid supermarket clerk, who believes he's solved the riddle of time travel and intends to depart again soon. Together, they embark on a hilarious, smart, and unexpectedly heartfelt journey that reveals how far believing can take you. Written by Derek Connolly and directed by Colin Trevorrow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;*****&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;I will purchase my ticket by 6:30 p.m., then wait at the foot of the stairs in the theater lobby. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for me carrying a red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; At about 6:45, I will move into the theater auditorium (can’t miss the previews). You can find me there, if you are late. &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The movie starts at 7:05 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;After the movie, I will wait in the theater lobby to gather everyone. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for the red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If we decide to go out after the movie, be prepared to add 25% to the cost of your order for both the tax and the tip. Restaurants in the area add the gratuity to the check automatically. Bring cash to make division of the check easier.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend this event so I know who to look for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Marianne&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the red backpack. You'll be able to find me at three different points. See the event description for details.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340335517000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339991211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Safety Not Guaranteed</name><id>69617942</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340317800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/69617942/</event_url></item>