<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>399 Newtonville Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02460</zip><lat>42.350968</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Volga Bo Olam</name><city>Newton</city><id>912252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.203889</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>11.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The new moon in Sagittarius is a special time.  Sagittarius' approach to life is enthusiastic and positive.  Sagittarius does not shy away from mental or physical exploration.  It is genuinely curious about how things work and why they work the way they do.  If it's broke, Sagittarius won't stop until it is fixed. Sagittarius loves adventure.  This sign, ruled by Jupiter, thinks BIG!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In life, embodying the enthusiasm of Sagittarius requires us to set our sights on new horizons, take on new challenge, and being honest enough to realize when something is not working as well as we would like.  Does it seem like you've been traveling the &amp;quot;long, winding road to nowhere&amp;quot;? Maybe it's time for you to change direction. Pick a new fork in the road. Go right instead of left. Take a class. Learn a new language, reinvent yourself.  Plan a trip somewhere you don't speak the language (but grab a phrasebook) - take a fresh, new approach towards an all-too-familiar problem.  Where in your life could you use some fiery, optimistic and fear-less energy?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come attend this special New Moon Circle as one of our members celebrates an important milestone in her life, while in turn, you get choose what milestone(s) to celebrate in your own life...and set an intention for new ones this coming new year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested donation: $11&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please consult Hopstop.com for public transportation routes that are best for you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292015111000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289784416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Moon Women's Circle</name><id>15447557</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291680000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/15447557/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/d/global_19640557.jpeg</photo_url></item>