<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:10, so let's meet at 6:40 outside the theater tomorrow (Tuesday) and then head in to buy our tickets and goodies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP up-to-date. And call me with any last-minute RSVPs, for directions, or to tell me you're running late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow for Funny People!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://funnypeoplemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Funny People&lt;/a&gt;'s marketing team is going overboard with this (even radio ads -- who does those anymore?!), but I do think it'll be a great movie. Adam Sandler is best when he's heartfelt and this looks like a great story. Also starring Seth Rogan (Zach and Miri Make a Porno, Knocked Up), Leslie Mann (The Cable Guy, 40-Year-Old Virgin) and Eric Bana (Hulk, Star Trek). Directed by Judd Apatow (The 40-Year-Old Virgin, Knocked Up). Okay, so I'm seeing a pattern here with Apatow hiring his favorite actors again and again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;George is a very successful stand up comedian who learns that he has an untreatable blood disorder and is given less than a year to live. Ira is a struggling up-and-coming stand up comedian who works at a deli and has yet to figure out his onstage persona. One night, these two perform at the same club and George takes notice of Ira. George hires Ira to be his semi-personal assistant as well as his friend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the theater doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup with a specific time a few days before, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Funny People!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251157119000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248919877000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Funny People</name><id>10990413</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250634600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10990413/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>