<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is not a formal Oxford Astronomy Meetup event but I thought it would be nice to open up the Aldrich talk scheduled for this Saturday evening to the members of this meetup group. We will have Kevin Boucher, an Aldrich member, speak about the NASA Kepler Mission which is a search for extrasolar planets that are more like Earth in size. There are over 450 extrasolar planets around nearby stars but most are at least 5 times the Earth in Mass so this will be the first serious attempt by scientists to look for Earth sized planets around nearby stars. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be plenty of munchies, beverages and handouts as well as outdoor observing of Saturn and other available night sky objects through Aldrich member telescopes.  The meeting takes place on the campus of Anna Maria College in Paxton, Massachusetts in the Science Building and there is plenty of free parking in the Trinity parking lot which is a short walk to the Science Building. Paxton offers nice dark sky views but it will be a waxing gibbous Moon this weekend with Saturn as the highpoint view of the night sky!  The weather looks ideal for this weekend too! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also want to say I like some of the ideas proposed for meteor watching - one date is very close to the annual Starfest 2010 which will be held on the campus of Anna Maria College on Saturday, July 31st 2010 from 6PM to 11PM.  That is pretty close to the meteor watch night that was mentioned plus we will have plenty of telescopes available and a possible appearance by a NASA astronaut who also is an astronomer! The August meetup suggestion is another good idea - I will check my calendar for that one too. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone is interested in attending the Aldrich meeting this weekend, please respond and I will e-mail a campus map with locations for parking and where the Science building is located.  Families are encouraged to attend too! Drive very slowly on campus - telescopes will be behind the Science Building which will be found at the very end of the drive onto the campus - it is a large white building with the word Science over the door plus it will also have the Aldrich welcome sign on the front stairs! Parking will be to the immediate right of the building - I can send a map to those interested in attending!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---Jim J. Zebrowski &lt;br /&gt;   President Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. &lt;br /&gt;   Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group Organizer &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Science Building is way at the back of the campus with a large foldout sign at the front door. Parking directions will be e-mailed to those interested in attending!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274631118000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274357732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Aldrich Spring Family Science Night</name><id>13541231</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274571000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/13541231/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/global_7975572.jpeg</photo_url></item>