<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Photonics/Optics - Understanding the Latest Applications of Light-based Technologies in Medical, Consumer, Industrial, and Defense Sectors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether for treating disease, advancing solar energy cells or enhancing semiconductor performance, recent advances in photonics and optics have created myriad opportunities for entrepreneurs to break new ground across a tremendously wide spectrum of commercial activity. As ever, the Greater Boston area’s potent mix of university resources and entrepreneurial culture have made our region a leader in a new and constantly evolving technological field. The May 19th EntreTech Forum will bring together some of the regions educators, researchers and entrepreneurs to focus on this academic/commercial nexus of innovation, and to answer key questions around (i) understanding the local resource base for photonics-based innovation (ii) distilling the key drivers that define success or failure for early-stage research-driven photonics entrepreneurs and (iii) defining for the audience what the next great ideas in photonics/optics technology will look like. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fairbairn, Managing Principal, Fairbairn Ventures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Rosen, Executive Director, Institute for Technology Entrepreneurship and Commercialization, BU School of Management&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Saylor, President &amp;amp; CEO, SiOnyx&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George Tegos, Instructor at MGH, Wellman Center for Photonics&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245189526000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225199017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photonics/Optics -Understanding  Latest Applications of Light-based Technologies</name><id>9046442</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242772200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/9046442/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_4560057.jpeg</photo_url></item>