<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Mt Hale has traditionally been one of the less awe inspring 4000 footers in the whites, Its not its fault, but barring a major natural event, its just been one to click off the list. The views in other than the winter are non existent and the traditional route up is a tad bit commonplace. Although I cant do much about the views from the top, but I can make getting there half the fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The proposed meetup is to retrace the route of the long abandoned fire wardens trail. Without spoiling the details, this is a minimal off trail adventure, with a very good grade, some unexpected views and at least one unusual forest type. This is not a strenuous hike relative to most 4000 footers but would not be a good entry level hike and would tend to appeal to those who have already climbed many of the 4000 footers. It also may be of interest to those who are contemplating the 100 highest list and its untrailed peaks as a slight taste of off trail hiking. The trip duration is probably in the six hour range and 8 miles round trip (thats a guess). The pace can be slower than on trail hiking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who are interested in attending, should be ready for the occasional climb over a blowdown, possibly a muddy stretch of trail, an occasion branch or bush intruding into the trail and possibly an occasional peek at a map. If there is interest we could do a traverse across the mountain but that would require a car spot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The actual meetup location will be emailed to those who are signed up and have filled in the questions. The general location is Twin Mountain NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conditions of particpating is that you and anyone of your guests, agree in advance to leave their GPS, or other electronic devices with capability of storing a detailed track of the trip, either in the car or powered down for the duration of the trip. You and your guest will further agree not to publish in any electronic or written format a detailed description of how to locate the start or end of the trail. These conditions are intended to keep a valuable resource (an abandoned trail) from becoming overun by those who are not willing to put in the extra effort. Altimeters, maps and compasses are welcome. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an abandoned trail can be brushy, a 30% chance or rain will cancel the event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The standard qualifiers apply, as a condition of signing up, you understand and agree that the host or the New England Hiking Meetup is not and can not be held responsible for any injuries, any muddy shoes that may occur as a consequence of participating in the meetup.      &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284981638000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283203094000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Hale via the Abandoned Fire Wardens Trail</name><id>14595556</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284901200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14595556/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/6/global_17449414.jpeg</photo_url></item>