<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Science and Democracy: Arundhati Roy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can We Leave the Bauxite in the Mountain?&lt;br /&gt;Field Notes on Democracy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arundhati Roy is the author of&lt;br /&gt;The God of Small Things&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Booker Prize, 1997)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This lecture and discussion is free and open to the public.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Commentator&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Homi Bhabha, Anne F. Rothenberg Professor of the Humanities and Director, Humanities Center at Harvard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moderated by&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sheila Jasanoff, Pforzheimer Professor of Science and Technology Studies, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Abstract&lt;/b&gt;: What happens once democracy has been used up? When it has been hollowed out and emptied of meaning? What happens when each of its institutions has metastasized into something dangerous? What happens now that democracy and the free market have fused into a single predatory organism with a thin, constricted imagination that revolves almost entirely around the idea of maximizing profit? Is it possible to reverse this process? Can something that has mutated go back to being what it used to be?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What we need today, for the sake of the survival of this planet, is long-term vision. Can governments whose very survival depends on immediate, extractive, short-term gain provide this? Could it be that democracy, the sacred answer to our short-term hopes and prayers, the protector of our individual freedoms and nurturer of our avaricious dreams, will turn out to be the endgame for the human race?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is organized by the Program on Science, Technology, and Society, at the Harvard Kennedy School and co-sponsored by the School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, the Graduate School of Design, the South Asia Initiative at Harvard, and the Harvard University Center for the Environment.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Science and Democracy, is a lecture series aimed at exploring both the promised benefits or our era's most salient scientific and technological breakthroughs and the potentially harmful consequences of developments that are inadequately understood, debated, or managed by politicians, lay publics, and policy institutions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information on Science, Technology, and Society events at Harvard University, please visit: www.ksg.harvard.edu/sts/.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;April 1, 2010 - 5:00pm - 7:00pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ksg.harvard.edu/sts/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ksg.harvar...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Contact Name: Lisa Matthews &lt;br /&gt;lisa_matthews@harvard.edu &lt;br /&gt;617-495-8883 &lt;br /&gt;Piper Auditorium, Gund Hall 48 Quincy St. Cambridge, MA&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270328837000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268781712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science and Democracy</name><id>12895399</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270155600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12895399/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/7/global_6176535.jpeg</photo_url></item>