<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Juniper Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.401520</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-489-5050</phone><name>Habitat</name><city>Belmont</city><id>622696</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184450</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Habitat Education Center and Wildlife Sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Belmont Hill, just 6 miles northwest of downtown Boston, lies Habitat, an 87-acre urban oasis that has been devoted to environmental education since 1970. Over 2.5 miles of gentle trails wind through deciduous and evergreen forests, across meadows, around 2 ponds, and along a wetland containing a vernal pool. The visitor center is a brick Georgian-style mansion where monthly art exhibits can be viewed. Outside, there?s a pleasing and calming formal garden. The building and gardens can be reserved on weekends for weddings and other events. This sanctuary has the following universally accessible facilities: Nature Center, Restrooms, Garden Terrace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;10 Juniper Road&lt;br /&gt;Belmont, MA 02478&lt;br /&gt;617-489-5050&lt;br /&gt;habitat@massaudubon.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center/Trail Hours:&lt;br /&gt;Visitor Center: Monday through Friday, 8 a.m. to 4 p.m., Saturday 10 a.m. to 4 p.m. Trails: Open every day, dawn to dusk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LUNCH AFTER THE WALK AT A LOCAL RESTAURANT FOR THOSE INTERESTED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Your Safety &lt;br /&gt;Do not feed any animals &lt;br /&gt;Stay on trails to avoid ticks and poison ivy &lt;br /&gt;Do not smoke anywhere on the sanctuary &lt;br /&gt;Do not pick or collect plants or crops without permission &lt;br /&gt;Avoid Conflicts with Wildlife &lt;br /&gt;Picnic only in designated areas &lt;br /&gt;Do not bring motorized vehicles or bicycles onto the site &lt;br /&gt;Hunting, fishing, or trapping are not permitted&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;$4 for nonmember adults;&lt;br /&gt;$3 for nonmember children (3-12) and seniors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the west: Take Rt. 2 (eastbound) to exit 58, Park Avenue. At the first traffic light (Park Ave.) turn right. Proceed a short distance to a small traffic circle. Take the second right onto Prospect Street (The Belmont Hill School will be on your right). Take the next right onto Tyler Rd. Take the next right onto Juniper Rd. The sanctuary entrance is 0.2 miles ahead on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the east: Take Rt. 2 westbound, to exit 59 (Rt. 60/Belmont Ctr.) At end of ramp turn left onto Rt. 60 west/Pleasant Street. Follow Pleasant Street for 0.6 miles and take a right at the third traffic light onto Clifton Street. Take the first left onto Fletcher Rd. Bear left at the fork and take the next left onto Juniper Rd. The sanctuary entrance is 0.2 miles ahead on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By public transportation: Habitat is a one-mile walk from Belmont Center, which is accessible by the MBTA Commuter Rail or MBTA Bus #74/75 from Harvard Square, Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acres:&lt;br /&gt;8&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203444494000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202755678000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HABITAT - BELMONT - CHESTNUT HILL WALKING MEETUP</name><id>7310545</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203271200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/7310545/</event_url></item>