<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I will be paddling at the East Brimfield Resivour / Lake  on Wednesday.  I'll  be launching out of the Boat Ramp on the North side of Rte 20. In Brimfield/Sturbridge  The boat ramp sign is on the right  just past the entrance to the Brimfield Damn (if your driving west).  There is another ramp on the south side of Rte 20 also so if no ones there your at the wrong one :-).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The season is comming to a close and the water cooling.  But its not to late to enjoy a pleasant fall day on this great Lake and River.  Weather is calling for a chance of showers, but then Kayaking is a wet sport  so a paddle jacket is helpful.  The water is cooling so make sure you have spare fleece in a drybag just in case.   We will as a group (if any show) decide just where to wander but its a beatuful spot this time of year Lake or River. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll  bring a backpack stove so we can make hot water for soup or tea at break to warm the bones up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be there around 11:30 and plan to launch around 12 and paddle for about 3 hours.  It will be a moderate paddle as i like to goof off roll and play along the way.  All are invited and welcome.  But be sure to have spare clothes in a  drybag.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Paddling &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ken C&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Yellow /White Anas Acuta with a Greenland (skinny) paddle.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ken C</member_name><member_id>7777174</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240683059000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225804290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Weekday  Paddle- Nov 5th-E. Brimfield Lake 12:00</name><id>9091312</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225904400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/9091312/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/global_2046284.jpeg</photo_url></item>