<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Wayland Ave.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.828461</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>McBride's Pub</name><city>Providence</city><id>3875592</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.388420</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: McBride's Pub in Wayland Square!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The opening of McBride's Pub was a much anticipated event for the Wayland Square P-Collective folks early last summer. It instantly became a natural gathering place for the neighborhood - sitting outside on the patio for a pint or enjoying the cozy warmth of the large bar and bistro tables on a rainy night - its great! Did I mention that its also a funeral home?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So for those that know (and there are A LOT of you), and those that don't - yet. We're heading to McBride's - again! Come over to the East Side and bring your good cheer.&amp;nbsp; Its a great one to know about - you'll be back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...Nothing cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ali is hosting this one! Please look at her picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ali</member_name><member_id>4513002</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330053204000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327445842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - McBrides in Wayland Square!</name><id>49483222</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329778800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/49483222/</event_url></item>