<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>15 Newton Street</address_2><address_1>Great Lawn</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.330002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Larz Anderson Park Auto Museum</name><city>Brookline</city><id>328698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There is yet another movie left in the Cars and Stars at Larz series brought to you by the Coolidge Corner theater. Basically, you watch car-themed movies outside. Last night, they showed Back to the Future and brought out five De Laureans for people to sit in. You also can go into the auto museum for free and see the schoolhouse there as well. There's food and fun for all! This time they are showing the Great Race. The movie starts at 8:15, so if we meet at 7:30, it should give us enough time for to mingle and walk around beforehand. Directions and info on the movie is below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crank your engines! With a roar, sputter and pop, drivers wheel westward in wacky turn-of-the-century autos for a New York-Paris race. Ahead lie 20,000 miles, a barroom brawl, a sinking iceberg, 2,357 pies in the face and incalculable laughs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1965) dir. Blake Edwards, w/ Tony Curtis, Jack Lemmon, Peter Falk, and Natalie Wood, 2h40m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be hosted by Nicole, who will yet again set up an army blanket surrounded by red balloons. Bring a chair/blanket and a snack/drink to share with everyone else. Please note that per Brookline Township, this is an alcohol free event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Boston/North Shore&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 93 South to Storrow Drive. Take the Fenway exit. Follow Outbound /Riverway signs to Boylston Street (taking a right off the ramp). Boylston St. will merge onto Brookline Ave. Follow Brookline Ave. to the Riverway/Jamaica Way intersection. Turn left onto the Riverway (this will turn into the Jamaica Way). You will go through the intersection with Perkins Street (Max Warburg Sq.) and Jamaica Pond will appear on your right. Go 1/2 way around the rotary (Kelley Circle) and at the lights turn right onto Pond Street. Pond Street will turn into Newton Street. The museum is located in Larz Anderson Park on the right about a 1/2 mile from the rotary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from West (Rte. 128/ I-95)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Rte. 128/ I-95 to Rte. 9 towards Boston. You will eventually pass the Chestnut Hill Mall on your left. Six lights after the Mall, you come to a major intersection (approx. 5 miles from Rte 128/ Rte. 9 intersection). Take a right onto Lee St. (If you pass the reservoir on Rte. 9 you?ve gone to far). Follow Lee to it?s end. This is Newton St. Turn left onto Newton St. Stay to the right around the bend. The museum is in Larz Anderson Park which is 1/4 mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Boston/South Shore&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Rte. 3/ I-93 to exit 11. Granite Ave/Ashmont. Follow Granite Ave north to second traffic light, then turn left onto Rte. 203. Follow Rte. 203 (also called Gallivan and later Morton Blvd.) to the rotary where the Arborway and Rte. 203 meet. Follow the Arborway for 1/2 mile, merging left with traffic. You will come to a third rotary (Kelley Circle). Follow the rotary 3/4 of the way around to the light, effectively reversing your direction. Turn right onto Pond Street which becomes Newton Street. The museum is located in the park on the right 1/2 mile from the rotary. You have gone too far if Jamaica Pond is on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions using Public Transportation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the Green Line D to Reservoir or Green Line C to Cleveland Circle. From either Forest or Reservoir/Cleveland Circle take bus # 51. (The #51 Bus begins and ends at the Forest Hills station, the terminus of the Orange Line) Ask the driver to stop at Newton Street near the Brookline Country Club. Take a left onto Newton Street. Newton will bear right. (Goddard bears left) The Museum is 1/4 of a mile up on left. (The #51 bus does not operate on Sundays.) For more detailed schedule and route information, please use the trip planner on the MBTA website.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188689911000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187982902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Car-themed Movies Under the Stars: The Great Race</name><id>6237268</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188516600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6237268/</event_url></item>