<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Zakim Bridge is indeed a beautiful structure, but there are few vantage points from which to photograph it. At night, it lights up in cool blue and there's lots of other colorful lights to make the scene interesting. Add a high Moon and reflections and you've got yourself a postcard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This little known area where we will meet was only recently open to the public, and is full of colorfully lit scenes with which to experiment creatively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll also have an opportunity to try out "Rear Curtain" flash sync for objects with lights in motion at night. (yes it's in your camera, and I'll explain how to use it).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The date is August 31st - we have a Friday night with a full Moon. &lt;br /&gt;

 I will email all RSVP's with location and directions.  &lt;br /&gt;

 Weather permitting, this should be a fun and interesting activity for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your camera, tripod, flash and (optional) guest(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will want a lens with wide angle capability. Depending on your camera that's a focal length of 28mm with a full frame sensor and 18mm with a crop factor 1.5 (Nikon DX) or 1.6 (Cannon) sensor, or wider, i.e., shorter focal length.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NON PHOTOGRAPHERS ALSO WELCOME&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have a talent for creative direction? &lt;br /&gt;

 Do you want to model for our photographers? &lt;br /&gt;

 Do you want to engage in an interesting activity with other creative people?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/9/a/event_142421882.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em style="color : #8797fa"&gt;Yes, the Moon is Photoshopped from another photo since even with HDR, there is no dynamic range broad enough (about 12 EV's) to accommodate seeing the Moon's face in a nighttime scene except with the naked eye.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will contact all RSVP's with details</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Domenico</member_name><member_id>9296355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>16</waitlist_count><updated>1346478575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers, Models &amp; MUA</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonportraitphotographers</urlname><id>830833</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Portrait Photographers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343116907000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zakim Bridge Night Time Shoot (For Photographers/Models/Artists)</name><id>74657882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346454000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/events/74657882/</event_url></item>