<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Birchmeadow Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.857342</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sons of the Wind Farm, School of Equestrian Arts</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>7122672</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.980919</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This event is part of the Boston Portuguese Festival, &lt;a href="http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org/"&gt;http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Portuguese Festival and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonsofthewindfarm.com/"&gt;Sons of the Wind Farm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are proud to welcome you for a Demonstration of The Lusitano horse. This will be a great opportunity to understand the role of the wonderful Lusitano horse in Portugal’s history and culture. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Sons of the Wind Farm located in Merrimac, MA, is home to the national horse of Portugal. This horse, also referred to as the “Royal Horse of Europe”, is known for his extraordinary beauty, bravery, athletic, talent and intelligence.     &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The day’s events will feature Portuguese freestyle dressage clinics, contest for the Portuguese Community Schools of this consular area with the support of the Coordination of Portuguese Language Programs and Education Affairs in the US, also “airs above grounds” demonstrations, soccer and other activities, such as tasting Portuguese gastronomy and Portuguese winery. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please bring family and friends to enjoy a day of fine entertainment at Sons of the Wind Farm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This event is open to the public, free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a joint Meetup with the Boston Culture Club&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/events/64126372/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/events/64126372/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a member of both groups, please only reserve your attendance in one group so I can have an accurate attendance count.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>To be announced</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338665994000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336596340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CANCELLED! Portuguese Lusitano Horse Show - in Merrimack- Free!</name><id>64126732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338654600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/64126732/</event_url></item>