<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>96 Russell Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01035</zip><lat>42.341641</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413.584.8000</phone><name>Carmelina's</name><city>Hadley</city><id>1123967</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.597150</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>WBOA has put together yet another great evening social event.  This less structured format allows you to connect with other members on a more personal level, as well as enjoy a great meal prepared by Carmelina's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$26 includes your salad, entree, dessert, coffee, tea, or soft drink, as well as tax and tip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 Cash Bar&lt;br /&gt;6:30 Sit Down Dinner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by December 7 with your meal selection.  Carmelina's is happy to work with people with special dietary needs.  Please send us a note if you have any food sensitivities that we can help to accommodate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;House Salad - Organic Mesclun greens, carrots, olives, red onion, cherry tomatoes and fresh Feta cheese, with your choice of our house-made Balsamic Vinaigrette or Gorgonzola dressing &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Entrée Choices&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer Risotto - A satisfying medley of Arborio risotto tossed with fresh Hadley asparagus, pancetta (optional), and wild mushrooms, topped with grated fresh Parmigiano&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicken Piccata – Sautéed Chicken Breasts finished with a delicious preparation combining white wine, lemon, butter and capers served with Angel Hair Pasta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spaghetti Carbonara - Made the old-fashioned way. A simple preparation of spaghetti, pancetta, Parmigiano, egg and cracked pepper, served in the traditional style without cream&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicken Marsala –Sautéed Chicken Breasts finished with a wonderful preparation of sautéed oyster mushrooms in a sweet Marsala wine sauce served with Angel Hair Pasta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Original Crazy Alfredo - on the menu since 1985, chicken, sausage, roasted red peppers and fettuccine in a spicy Alfredo sauce &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fettuccini Alfredo - A traditional preparation of cream, butter, Parmigiano and nutmeg tossed with fettuccini&lt;br /&gt;Fettuccini Alfredo with Broccoli – Above preparation and broccoli&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shrimp Scampi - Shrimp sautéed with garlic, capers, white wine, lemon, artichokes, and sweet butter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angel Hair Puttanesca - A spicy tomato sauce with anchovies (or not), capers, olives, white wine and basil tossed with angel hair pasta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;La Palermitana - Sicilian soul food. Rapi greens, sun-dried tomatoes, garlic, pine nuts, golden raisins, and angel hair pasta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linguine Clams or Mussels - Choice of fresh littleneck clams or fresh mussels, served with your choice of red sauce, or white wine and garlic sauce with linguini&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brasato - A slowly braised short rib with aromatics, red wine and sweet tomato, served with Pasta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicken Parmigiano - Simply prepared boneless chicken breast baked with our tasty marinara sauce and Parmigiano, served with Penne Pomodoro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Choice of Desserts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tiramisu - Espresso and brandy soaked ladyfingers, layered with whipped mascarpone, and chocolate&lt;br /&gt;Or&lt;br /&gt;Cannoli - Crunchy pastry shell filled with sweet ricotta and chocolate chips&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Beverages Included&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Choice of Coffee, Tea or Soft Drinks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Beverages Available&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beer, Wine and Cocktails available for purchase&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292079633000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290020228000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Evening Social Event- Carmelina's on the Common</name><id>15479011</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291933800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/15479011/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/global_10758349.jpeg</photo_url></item>