<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>472 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363752</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Middle East (Upstairs)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>237774</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101252</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/5/5/event_7275445.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Please attend the Art opening of a local artist who has focused his efforts on creating both visual images and text, intended to help awaken the public out of their CNN slumber. Many topics are covered, many voices are needed, to help support the truth and awakening, on subjects ranging from the police state, false flags, dangers of GMO, BPA, water privatization, the Fed, Constitutional upheaval, governmant intrusion, deadly vaccines, illegal wars, chemtrails, flouride, resisting the NWO et al. Together we can create an environment, where "Conspiracy" is shown to be reality, they might own the news, but they don't own us, yet? WAC video to be shot of event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the press release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;ART FROM THE UNDERGROUND,&amp;rdquo; showing through September, at the Middle East, 472 Mass Ave. Cambridge, highlights a series of images from local artist, Eric Cross, that bridges fine art aesthetics with social activism. Artist&amp;rsquo;s reception Sunday the 11th, 3-8pm Contacts, theericcross@yahoo.com, darkgrape.media@yahoo.com 617-388-3415&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cross, a MassArt grad in painting and video has once again re-invented himself, having traversed through classicism, modernism, and post-modernism, Cross now challenges the pixel for social dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Scratch Tickets,&amp;rdquo; a large collage, of found object scratch tickets, become the pixels, to create both, and artistic collusion between the artist and the mark making of the ticket scratchers, as well as draw commentary on the amount of &amp;ldquo;money&amp;rdquo; found in the trash. Over $10,000 &amp;ldquo;worth&amp;rdquo; of denominated tickets were found, over a two week period, in three separate Jamaica Plain stores. Raising questions about our ideas on, wealth, happiness, and &amp;ldquo;legal&amp;rdquo; gambling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In parallel, another collage &amp;ldquo;One Hundred Dollars,&amp;rdquo; uses actual one dollar bills as the pixels in a mathematical design. With their denominations, printed on paper, the bills bare a stark resemblance to the scratch tickets, as well as challenging the idea of inflation, fiat currency, and the private &amp;ldquo;Federal Reserve.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The graphic art tryptic entitled &amp;ldquo;Three Generations,&amp;rdquo; alludes to Van Gogh&amp;rsquo;s final painting &amp;ldquo;Crows over a Wheatfield.&amp;rdquo; However, in this piece, DNA strands are woven through the fields, as the crows manifest through the tryptic. A series of framed texts accompany the Art, raising concerns about GMO foods, terminator seeds, Monsanto, and research studies on the effects of GMO consumption and major infertility in test animals after, &amp;ldquo;three generations.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Drought #1&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Drought #2&amp;rdquo; are two graphic images portraying the dangers of water privatization. The first image shows outstretched hands holding seeds over a parched earth, as the water in the distance is blocked by s&amp;ldquo;security&amp;rdquo; forces. The second shows the skeletal remains of a fish and a boat on a shrinking waterfront. Ac-company-ing text highlights the misuse of public water contracts, corporate water acquisitions, and predatory pricing by major corporations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Alien False Flag,&amp;rdquo; a large print on canvas, is a montage of alien invasion images and recent anomalies, such as the &amp;ldquo;Norway Spiral,&amp;rdquo; and the &amp;ldquo;Moscow Independence Day Cloud.&amp;rdquo; Recent economists and global strategists, remarks and discussions on mainstream news (CNN, RT), about the economic and unifying benefit of an &amp;ldquo;alien invasion,&amp;rdquo; and as, the United Nations looks to appoint an &amp;ldquo;extra-terrestrial&amp;rdquo; ambassador, the Vatican announces to welcome &amp;ldquo;aliens,&amp;rdquo; as well, as the constant and intensifying &amp;ldquo;sightings,&amp;rdquo; movies, and news from around the world, beg the question. Are you ready for the Alien False Flag?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several other works for view and discussion, WTC7, chemtrails, occult symbolism, riot police, etc
 &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best Regards, Eric Cross&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>eric cross</member_name><member_id>11298242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316485946000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314741068000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bring your voice to "Art from the Underground"</name><id>31615282</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315767600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/31615282/</event_url></item>