<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>217 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.107596</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413•788•4929</phone><name>Pintu's Indian Palace</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>862543</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.623421</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>27.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mark your calendars now for the next WBOA Evening Gathering, Wednesday Februray 8th at Pintu's Indian Restaurant in West Springfield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're changing things up this time and plan a family-style meal and a little round-robin between courses. We'll all share a fabulous array of dishes, loved by fans of Indian food and newbies alike. Between courses, we'll all get a chance to change seats and network with a fresh set of dining partners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These dinners are always a fun way to get to know WBOA members outside our regular breakfast meetings. Please feel free to bring a guest or colleague.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our three-course dinner will include appetizers, several entrees and dessert. Total price including tax and tip will be $27. Cash bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Informal networking begins at 5:30, dinner at 6:30. Please RSVP by Monday, February 6 on our MeetUp site. If you have any questions, please contact Amy Woolf at amysrq@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Appetizers: Assorted Pakoras - Florets of cauliflower, potatoes, onion, &amp;amp; paneer deep-fried in chickpea flour batter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entrees: Chicken Tikka Masala - bar-b-que chicken cooked in a special fresh creamy tomato sauce with a variety of herbs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mixed Vegetable Jhalfraze - a variety of vegetables sauteed &amp;amp; simmered gently in a makhani butter sauce&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beef Boti Kebab - skewered beef marinated in herbs and spices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saag Paneer - cubes of homemade cheese cooked in a fresh creamed spinach gravy Naan bread Dessert&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328831192000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326765610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Evening Social Event- Pintu's Indian Palace</name><id>48393042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328740200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/48393042/</event_url></item>