<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;On the message boards, about 5 people recommended this title, so I am posting it as our April Book Club Book.  I am looking into David Sedaris visiting our area (looks like he will be at the UMASS Fine Arts Center on April 5).  It would be really cool if we could have an April Social Meetup to go to his lecture, and then meet two weeks later to discuss his book. That's the plan. I will look into times/prices and then post an April Social Meetup ASAP.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;In the mean time, I will sell you on why you should read this book:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Amazon.com Review:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With essay collections such as Naked (1997) and Me Talk Pretty One Day (2000), Sedaris kicked the door down for the “quirky memoir” genre and left it open for writers like Augusten Burroughs and Jeannette Walls to mosey on through. Sometimes the originators of a certain trend in literature are surpassed by their own disciples—but, this is Sedaris we’re talking about. When it comes to fashioning the sardonic wisecrack, the humiliating circumstance, and the absurdist fantasy, there’s nobody better. Unfortunately, being in a league of your own often means competing with yourself. This latest collection of 22 essays proves that not only does Sedaris still have it, but he’s also getting better. True, the terrain is familiar. The essays “Old Faithful” and “That’s Amore” again feature Sedaris’ overly competent boyfriend, Hugh. And nutty sister Amy can be found leafing through bestial pornography in “Town and Country.” Present also are Sedaris’ favored topics: death, compulsion, unwanted sexual advances, corporal decay, and more death. Nevertheless, Sedaris’ best stuff will still—after all this time—move, surprise, and entertain. --Jerry Eberle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;See you at Red Rose on the 28th.  All are welcome at our table.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the table in the front with the book!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meagan</member_name><member_id>6521348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242775284000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238410129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Meet Up - When You are Engulfed in Flames by David Sedaris</name><id>10068365</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240957800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/10068365/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/2/global_7905282.jpeg</photo_url></item>