<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Harvard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.339744</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 232-8787</phone><name>The Corrib Pub</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1481034</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120833</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Have you always wanted to run a little stronger, a little faster, and have some motivated people around to help push you along? Well now you can have all of those things at the best &lt;i&gt;Hill workout&lt;/i&gt;  ever. &lt;br /&gt;Interest peaked? Read on for more details including the weekly workout.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the &lt;a href="http://www.corribpub.com/brookline/" target="_blank"&gt;Corrib Pub&lt;/a&gt; as usual, 6:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Corrib is here:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=201+Harvard+Street,+Brookline,+MA+02446-5013&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hnear=Cambridge,+MA&amp;amp;cid=0,0,12002921145954879027&amp;amp;ll=42.33953,-71.119716&amp;amp;spn=0.01272,0.027874&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;iwloc=A" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workout is a repeating hill workout designed to add some variety to our otherwise boring lives ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rest of this details the workout and highlights a few things I think are important to remember.  Skip it if you would rather just wing it and meet us at the pub.  We'll fill you in there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have never run repeating hills before, don't worry if none of this makes sense right now.  As much as I will try to prep you, it usually just takes a few laps around the track for all of this to sink in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Hills (not the TV show) Workout&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workouts vary on a weekly basis and are usually based on runner suggestions. We sometimes do workouts that are fun and different. Come see what this weeks workout is!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Things to remember&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hill running (in my opinion) is supposed to be FUN and challenging!  Don't be intimidated or dread a hill workout.  This is supposed to be a fun supplement to your other &amp;quot;normal&amp;quot; runs.  With all of us out there encouraging each other it should be a blast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a running stopwatch/wristwatch if you have one!  Using the start/lap/stop function will help you pace yourself on the hills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't push it!  If something hurts or starts to feel tight, don't risk an injury because you ran too hard on your first hill workout of the season.  We have plenty of time to ease in...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Stick around and have some friendly libations, food and water with the crew afterwards~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;All are welcome with a laurel and hardy handshake.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;amp;hosted_button_id=GLVQPYGG7BBE6" target="_blank"&gt;DONATE to TMIRCE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my running shoes.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy - ti.mer.see - Marx </member_name><member_id>6766032</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296079261000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288716717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TMIRCE Tuesday's: Hill Extravaganza</name><id>vldjqypcbhc</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295998200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/16126676/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/5/8/global_9613624.jpeg</photo_url></item>