<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The film starts at 7:20, so lets meet up at 6:45 or so.   It is showing in one of the big theaters downstairs which tends to be on the crazy side.  I would like to go into the theater by 7 to get good seats.   I will be inside the ropes near the concession stand and I am wearing a badge so those new to the group can recognize me.

See you there.

The name of the movie is The Eye

Starring: Jessica Alba, Parker Posey, Alessandro Nivola, Tamlyn Tomita, Chloe Moretz

Plot Summary: Sydney Wells (Jessica Alba) is an accomplished, independent, Los Angeles-based concert violinist. She is also blind, and has been so since a childhood tragedy. As our story opens, Sydney undergoes a double corneal transplant, a surgery she has waited her whole life to have, and her sight is restored. After the surgery, neural ophthalmologist Dr. Paul Faulkner (Alessandro Nivola) helps Sydney with the difficult adjustment, and with the support of her older sister Helen (Parker Posey), Sydney learns to see again. 

But Sydney's happiness is short-lived as unexplainable shadowy and frightening images start to haunt her. Are they a passing aftermath of her surgery, Sydney's mind adjusting to sight, a product of her imagination, or something horrifyingly real? As Sydney's family and friends begin to doubt her sanity, Sydney is soon convinced that her anonymous eye donor has somehow opened the door to a terrifying world only she can now see.

"The Eye" is a bone-chilling supernatural thriller that tests the boundaries of perception and reality. Directed by David Moreau and Xavier Palud, the team who directed the suspenseful international hit "Them," "The Eye" stars Jessica Alba, Alessandro Nivola and Parker Posey. Produced by Tom Cruise and Paula Wagner with Mike Elliott, Don Granger and Michelle Manning serving as executive producers.


I will update this with exact movie times when I can get them closer to the event.

I will be wearing a badge so those who don't know me can find me.  If the movie is upstairs I will grab a table near the coffee vendor at the top of the escalator.  If it is down stairs then I will be beyond the rope in front of the concession stand.

See you there.

Trailer:
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/No1jc7RvgCI&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a badge.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206381679000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>This is a great group of movie crazed fans and it's always more fun to see movies with other people.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198767065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Eye</name><id>6975820</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201995900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6975820/</event_url></item>