<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Who knows if we’ll always have Paris, but hopefully we’ll always have this marvelous film to watch. CASABLANCA has a reputation of being swooningly romantic, and it certainly is, but it’s also wryly funny, somewhat cynical, and remarkably thrilling. It’s the French Morocco during WWII and ex-pat bar owner Rick Blaine (Bogart) finds himself once again tangled in the web of his lost love, Ilsa (Bergman), when she arrives in Casablanca with her current beau, a French freedom fighter looking to get passage to America and escape the Nazis. Often imitated but never matched, CASABLANCA has a special recipe for success that includes a top-notch script, fantastic supporting players, and iconic star turns by two Hollywood legends. Not to be missed particularly on this most romantic of weekends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: These screenings will likely sell out in advance. Secure your letters of transit and keep in mind that the theatre will be at capacity, so there will be minimal room for coats, bags, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Although it was made in 1942, &amp;quot;Casablanca&amp;quot; is still the greatest romantic drama ever made. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As time goes by, the appeal of Casablanca shows no sign of diminishing. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of those rare films where every shot and every quotable line of dialogue counts&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&amp;quot;This is it. The best movie ever made.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Casablanca at the Brattle on Valentine's Day.  I think this could be the start of a beautiful friendship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John will be sipping Morrocan Tea at Crima as early as 3:15 for those that wish to Meetup before the film and wait, and wait, and wait.  As time goes by, we'll go to a lovely place (Finales?) and play it again, and again, and again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263949917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Casablanca</name><id>12367701</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266182100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12367701/</event_url></item>