<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>341 Milford St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06013</zip><lat>41.733648</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 675-8130 </phone><name>Sessions Woods Wildlife Management Area</name><city>Burlington</city><id>693310</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.954677</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/wildlife/images/outreach/wildlife_management_areas/Sessions_Woods/sessions.jpg" alt="Conservation Education Center at Sessions Woods WMA" width="377" height="168" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Sessions Woods is a great area in Burlington.&amp;nbsp; As I continue my Achilles tendon recovery, I am offering a hike around the Beaver Pond&amp;nbsp;loop that runs 2.6 miles.&amp;nbsp; This area includes scenic nature views throughout the area.&amp;nbsp; I am offering this event with a photographic element.&amp;nbsp; If you are interested in bringing your camera and enjoying the scenery, please come.&amp;nbsp; There are beautiful views and we are going to take a pace that allows us to photograph the park.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a professional but am willing to offer suggestions.&amp;nbsp; I would love to see folks who have camera ability come and share their knowledge.&amp;nbsp; I was hoping we could gather after the hike to share the images we took but the nature center will not be open that day.&amp;nbsp; Maybe we can solve that when we meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail is groomed and easy to walk on.&amp;nbsp; Sneakers are appropriate as we are not going to encounter any great challenges.&amp;nbsp; I would bring a small pack with water and snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know this is a holiday weekend but some of&amp;nbsp;us will have no events.&amp;nbsp; If you like this idea but cannot attend, let me know so I can plan future trips.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As with me, NO DOGS NO KIDS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the link to the park information with the trail map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2723&amp;amp;Q=326220"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2723&amp;amp;Q=326220&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;By clicking on "I'm Going" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304296201000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><why>This will be a pace that all can enjoy taking photos.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303479250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike with a photography element at Sessions Woods, Burlington CT</name><id>17396075</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304172000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/17396075/</event_url></item>