<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Conference on Behavioral Epigenetics&lt;br /&gt;When:         October 29 - 30, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Where:        University Massachusetts Boston Campus Center - Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;                   100 Morrissey Blvd (UMB &amp;amp; JFK Exit 15, South East Expressway)&lt;br /&gt;                   Boston, MA  02125&lt;br /&gt;Website:      www.nyas.org/behavioralepi&lt;br /&gt;Behavioral epigenetics has made exciting advances in understanding basic biologic mechanism underlying normal and abnormal behavior, mind and brain. This 2-day CME-accredited conference will explore epigenetic mechanisms related to fetal programming and neural plasticity, learning, memory, mental illness, and developmental psychopathology.  It will consider prenatal as well as postnatal factors that may produce epigenetic changes in behavior, and the intergenerational transfer and reversibility of these effects when assessing behavioral outcomes.  Topics will include issues of vulnerability and resilience and the development of new targeted therapies for alterations in behavior (e.g. depression, addiction, schizophrenia, and neuro-developmental disorders).  This conference brings together the leading researchers in the field and will be among the first meetings specifically focused on one frontier of the epigenetics field: Behavioral Epigenetics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Edward Tronick (University Massachusetts Boston, and Children's Hospital Boston, Harvard Medical School), Barry Lester (Warren Alpert Medical School of Brown University), and Eric Nestler (Mount Sinai School of Medicine) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speakers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ted Abel, PhD, University of Pennsylvania&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barry Kosofsky, MD, PhD, Weill Cornell Medical College&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christopher W. Kuzawa, PhD, MsPH, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carmen Marsit, PhD, Warren Alpert Medical School of Brown University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ian Maze, PhD, Mount Sinai School of Medicine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Meaney, PhD, McGill University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa Monteggia, PhD, University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hans M .H. M. Reul, PhD, University of Bristol&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David H. Skuse, MD, PhD, University College London&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J. David Sweatt, PhD, University of Alabama at Birmingham&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marcelo Wood, PhD, University of California, Irvine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by:  University of Massachusetts, NYAS, and Warren Alpert Medical School of Brown University. The Massachusetts Life Sciences Center is an organizational supporter of this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288355002000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284993890000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conference on Behavioral Epigenetics</name><id>14831257</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288350000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/14831257/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>