<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Coolidge is showing a newly restored print of this classic so that film lovers like us can luxuriate in this exquisite film on the Big Screen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30&amp;nbsp;Panera Bread for light supper, snack, coffee, and talk.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 Coolidge Corner Theater for best seating.&amp;nbsp; Everyone is welcome, but I won't know to look for you if you RSVP late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchase tickets in advance.&amp;nbsp; This time of year it's hard to&amp;nbsp;gauge whether or not it will sell out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Coolidge Corner website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Federico Fellini, a key figure of the Italian neo-realist movement, already had seven films to his credit though he was not yet 40 when he charted entirely new territory with this 1960 masterpiece. &amp;nbsp;A large-scale and fascinating satire on the decadent &amp;ldquo;sweet life&amp;rdquo; of Rome at the moment of profound social transformation, it portrays the city as the epicenter of jet-setting indulgence, moral emptiness, and frenzied media madness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With &lt;em&gt;La Dolce Vita&lt;/em&gt;, Fellini boldly insisted on breaking the bones of traditional narrative only to reset them in an astounding new way. To say that this film is innovative and influential is an understatement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It caused a sensation even before it was released and was a massive box office hit. &amp;nbsp;It divided audiences (Fellini was both spat on and cheered at the premiere), critics (it won top prize at the Cannes Film Festival), and religious leaders (it was condemned by the Vatican). It shocked viewers with its frank treatment of sex, including homosexuality, by its blasphemy, and above all, by the scope of its vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcello Mastroianni became an international star with this film, playing a journalist who is both witness to and participant in the decadence, debauchery, and desolation of the glittering city. The term &amp;lsquo;paparazzi&amp;rsquo;&amp;nbsp; originated in &lt;em&gt;La Dolce Vita&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a statement about the film&amp;rsquo;s recent restoration,&amp;nbsp; Martin Scorsese, as Founder and Chair of the Film Foundation, writes: &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;La Dolce Vita&lt;/em&gt; was shot by the great cinematographer Otello Martelli in dazzling black and white [Cinema]Scope, in a rich array of tones that seemed to glow and sparkle. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to convey exactly how special the look of this picture was at the time. And now, it is again&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Restored by Cineteca di Bologna at L&amp;rsquo;Immagine Ritrovata laboratory, in association with the Film Foundation, Centro Sperimentale di Cinematografia-Cineteca Nazionale, Path&amp;eacute;, Fondation J&amp;eacute;r&amp;ocirc;me Seydoux-Path&amp;eacute;, Medusa, Paramount Pictures and Cinecitt&amp;agrave; Luce.&amp;nbsp; Restoration funding provided by The Film Foundation and Gucci.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Betsey will be at 5:30 Panera Bread for Supper Snack Coffee Tea - 6:30 Coolidge for best seats  Red Meetup Sign Visible.  Ask around if you can't find us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309536745000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308844715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>La Dolce Vita - Restored Print -June 27 6:30 Coolidge- Film begins at 7:00</name><id>23253691</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309213800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/23253691/</event_url></item>