<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>518 E HARTFORD AVE</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01569</zip><lat>42.101979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>West Hill Dam</name><city>Uxbridge</city><id>962850</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.608343</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a continuation of the meetup that Sarah setup. She did such a great job let's do the same this month! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's the middle of the week, you are tired, your pup is hyperactive, and its SO LONG until the weekend and the NEBBC rail trail walks! What are you going to do?! Join us on a tour of the lovely state parks that the Blackstone Valley has to offer. Every Wednesday Kyra &amp;amp; I will be journeying out to a different state park in the Blackstone Valley area (and maybe some slightly outside of the area) and would love some company! Please meet us for some on-leash (and maybe off-leash) fun. Will be weather-dependent, though Ky and I will generally go in most weather excepting blazingly hot or torrential downpours :) &lt;br /&gt;

The current plan is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April 4: West Hill Dam, 518 E Hartford Ave, Uxbridge, MA [note: there is a Dam and a Park entrance...we are meeting at the Dam] &lt;br /&gt;

April 11: Riverbend Farm/Blackstone Heritage Park, 287 Oak St, Uxbridge, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April 18: Purgatory Chasm, 198 Purgatory Rd, Sutton, MA [note: current plans are to go through the chasm - somewhat difficult hike!]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April 25: Upton State Park, Westborough Rd, Upton, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If these walks are successful I will definitely add more in the area!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336146891000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335459945000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Afternoon Walks!</name><id>62249852</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335990600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/62249852/</event_url></item>