<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 Pine St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02901</zip><lat>41.822945</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 861-1782</phone><name>McFaddens</name><city>Providence</city><id>814016</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Tom and I have already participated in last weeks event and want to start a newcomers team.  You don't have to come to every Monday's event.&lt;br /&gt;McFaddens is offering Half Price appetizers during the event, I don't recall the drink special.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if you don't feel like pedaling, its fun to watch some poor sucker pedal their guts out for 30 seconds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to come late, races run until everyone is too tired to continue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter blues got you snowed under?  Just think: this is only the begining!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a cure for those winter blues.  Announcing, the RI VeloSprints Winter Series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RI VeloSprints is Rhode Island's winter series for cyclists, spinners, commuters and hipsters frustrated by Mother Nature's cold shoulder!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RI VeloSprints is 500 metres of full out sprinting on rollers. We fix the forks to help keep you vertical as you challenge friends, enemies, other co-workers or folks you may have just met!   There are multiple categories to address the needs of all of your mid-winter personas.  The bravest are forming teams to share the therapeutic benefits of the series!  Speaking of prizes, there will be nightly winners AND series Champions, crowned in March.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of your blood,sweat and tears, your registration fees and a portion of beer sales supports the U.S. Open Cycling Foundation's mission to empower a healthier, cleaner America through cyling AND also to support the work of the Providence Bike Coalition and the East Coast Greenway Alliance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration for the 10 night series is $25 per individual or $75 for a team of up to five.  There is a $5/night ride fee.  For those who are commitment averse, there is a $10 one-nighter fee.  At the end of the series you will receive a receipt for the total of your donation.    McFadden's (52 Pine St, Providence) has graciously agreed to host the entire series.   Bring your friends, leave your lycra at home!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dates for the series (participation at all events not required for series score):  January 4,11,25 February 1,8,22 March 1,8,15,29&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the private room</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263424213000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262789505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RI VeloSprints Winter Series, Night 2</name><id>12239526</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263250800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/12239526/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>