<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wander among crop fields and livestock pastures, wetlands and forest, at America’s oldest, continuously operating farm.  A gift of Colonel Francis R. Appleton, Jr., and his wife Joan, Appleton Farms is one of the oldest continuously operating farms in the country, established and maintained by nine generations of the Appleton family. Six miles of footpaths, bridle paths, farm roads and wooded trails, some of which are part of the Bay Circuit Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facilities&lt;br /&gt;Public restrooms are available in the Carriage Barn in the Farmstead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a 2 hour brisk walk through the wooded trails, with turn back points for those who want a shorter walk. We will meet in the parking lot by Joan's Honda Fit and hit the trail at 10:00 AM (cell 978-269-4232). I am sorry that dogs are not allowed here.  After the walk, if you wish, join us at Stone Soup Cafe, 141 High Street, Ipswich for lunch/coffee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions are below:&lt;/b&gt;  But you should probably Google or MapQuest  yourself also to get a better sense of it. Use the above address &amp;amp; name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the South:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 North to Rte 128 North to Rte 1A North (exit 20A). Travel about 7 mi. north on Rt. 1A and turn left onto Waldingfield Rd. Parking area immediately on Left (20 cars).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the North:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 South to exit 54 for MA-133 toward Georgetown/Rowley  Follow Rte 133 to Rte 1A South.  After about 2.2 miles start to look for the VERY SMALL Appleton Farms sign on your Right  Turn Right onto Waldingfield Rd.  Immediately on Left is parking lot (20 cars).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Joan's Silver Honda Fit</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joan C</member_name><member_id>5518283</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>17</waitlist_count><updated>1258218506000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255306651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Appleton Farms Hike - Ipswich, MA</name><id>11604051</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256479200000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/11604051/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/a/global_11174170.jpeg</photo_url></item>