<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Room 117</address_2><address_1>167 Thayer Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02912</zip><lat>41.826104</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MacMillan Hall - Brown University</name><city>Providence</city><id>1101120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.400096</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Thanks to Ted, for guest-hosting this event!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Vowell, from the radio show &lt;i&gt;This American Life&lt;/i&gt;, will be discussing and reading from her book &lt;i&gt;The Wordy Shipmates&lt;/i&gt; at Brown University. The event is free and open to the public. The book covers, among other things, Roger Williams and the founding of Rhode Island in funny detail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ted will meet people in front of the Sciences Library (aka the tall ugly building that can be seen for miles) at the corner of Thayer and Waterman. He will meet people outside starting at 6:30, then head inside at 6:45 for seats, the event is scheduled to start at 7. This event is likely to draw a crowd so the earlier we can go inside the better. Afterward we can walk to one of the many bars/restaurants on Thayer St for drinks/coffee/etc if we want to hang out more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Vowell is the &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt;’ bestselling author of five nonfiction books on American history and culture.  By examining the connections between the American past and present, she offers personal, often humorous accounts of everything from presidents and their assassins to colonial religious fanatics, as well as thoughts on American Indians, utopian dreamers, pop music and the odd cranky cartographer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She’s been a guest numerous times on &lt;i&gt;The Daily Show&lt;/i&gt;,&lt;i&gt; Conan O’Brien&lt;/i&gt;, and &lt;i&gt;David Letterman&lt;/i&gt;. She also provided the voice of Violet in the Pixar movie &lt;i&gt;The Incredibles&lt;/i&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info on her can be found here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.barclayagency.com/vowell.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.barclayage...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ted will meet at Sciences Library @ Thayer &amp; Waterman between 6:30 and 6:45pm</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257028902000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256301193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Author Sarah Vowell @ Brown - FREE EVENT</name><id>11693171</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256855400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/11693171/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>