<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Temple Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304665</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-498-2500</phone><name>Criterion Cinema</name><city>New Haven</city><id>827452</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928467</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The group that made fun of zombies in &amp;quot;Shaun of the Dead&amp;quot; (which I found hysterical) is back with a new movie: Hot Fuzz &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show starts at Criterion Cinemas at 7 pm and I'll be in the lobby by 6:45. &lt;br /&gt;Contact is Andrea 203-641-8083.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason &amp;amp; Alexis are doing fuzzy dinner around 5pm (time flexible) in downtown New Haven. If interested, call or text Jason, 203-901-4957&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed by: Edgar Wright &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Simon Pegg , Martin Freeman, Bill Nighy  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Angel is the finest cop London has to offer, with an arrest record 400% higher than any other officer on the force. He's so good, he makes everyone else look bad. As a result, Angel's superiors send him to a place where his talents won't be quite so embarrassing - the sleepy and seemingly crime-free village of Sandford. Once there, he is partnered with the well-meaning but overeager police officer Danny Butterman. The son of amiable Police Chief Frank Butterman, Danny is a huge action movie fan and believes his new big-city partner might just be a real-life &amp;quot;bad boy,&amp;quot; and his chance to experience the life of gunfights and car chases he so longs for. Angel is quick to dismiss this as childish fantasy and Danny's puppy-like enthusiasm only adds to Angel's growing frustration. However, as a series of grisly accidents rocks the village, Angel is convinced that Sandford is not what it seems and as the intrigue deepens, Danny's dreams of explosive, high-octane, car-chasing, gunfighting, all-out action seem more and more like a reality. It's time for these small-town cops to break out some big-city justice.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177529466000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177080625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sun. 4/22--Hot Fuzz. Fuzzy dinner too</name><id>5690696</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177281900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5690696/</event_url></item>