<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Monica Trust (978)877-1119&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVPs for this event will close two days before it is scheduled to occur.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What we're doing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this trip we will hike to East Osceolas&lt;/span&gt; (4,156' #34) and Mt Osceola (4340' #24) using the Greeley Pond&lt;/span&gt; trail off the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kancamagus Highway.&lt;/span&gt; Mount Osceola is among one the most climbed mountains in the Southern White Mountains. Though Mt. Osceola never reaches timberline, the two views from the summit are spectacular. On any given clear, high visibility day you can see forty one of the of the other 4000's in New Hampshire and even faintly see Mt. Mansfield towards the west. We will be coming from the east and this climb can be very tough. At time the trail here can become Class 2 especially on part of the way up East Osceola and a section of the trail called the chimney between East Osceola and Mount Osceola. This is a &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace trip&lt;/strong&gt; we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 7.6 miles round trip with an elevation gain of 3232 ft. Book time is 5 hours 25 minutes not including breaks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It could be cold and windy, it could snow, or it could be warm with blue skies. Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need warm layers, wind protection, and traction among other things. I will update everyone if weather conditions more than what is described below. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike provided they are experienced "hikers", well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination. Be sure to indicate in your RSVP if you will be bringing a dog.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com/"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;It is winter in the mountains - expect cold and windy conditions. Temperatures drop 3-5 degrees for every 1,000 feet of elevation gained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel this hike - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will begin this hike by meeting at Greeley Pond Trailhead at 10 AM. According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 141 miles from Boston and it should take about&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span&gt;2 hours 28 mins&lt;/span&gt; minutes to drive there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.031458,-71.516428(Greeley+Ponds+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.031458,-71.516428&amp;amp;sspn=0.007621,0.01929&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFeLdnwId9L68-w&amp;amp;oq=boston,+ma&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; the link below for driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355807222000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353986110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Two 4K Footers--Mt Osceola and East Osceola (Intermediate Level)</name><id>92962952</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355668200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/92962952/</event_url></item>