<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>please contact revchristine@centersoflight.org to get the full address</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Cambridge - Close to Alewife</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10409462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"Satsang" is a Sanskrit word (sat = true, sang = company) meaning "the company of the highest truth". Mother Clare will hold this satsang, discussing the spiritual path and the role that a Teacher or Master plays in helping you discover your true nature. A Grace Blessing is an opportunity to receive a blessing from a Master Teacher and experience the movement of the healing divine energy within your being. Be ready to experience Light, Love and Life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking will be available to everyone. When you arrive to the seminar, you will be given a parking permit that will allow you to park on the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Suggested donation for one seminar is $20 to $35, more or less depending on your resources. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare Watts is an ordained Master Teacher and Priest and has been teaching the mystic way for more than 10 years. She's the director of the Order of Christ/Sophia and Centers of Light. She holds a Master’s Degree in Counseling Psychology with post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, and is a Certified Professional Midwife. She is also the author of Giving Birth to God: A Woman's Path to Enlightenment and Mystical Roses of Peace. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 About Centers of Light &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We welcome people of all races, faiths, ages, genders and sexual orientations. Large or small, young or weathered by time, strong or broken, we welcome you into a life of healing through relationship with God and the teachings of the great Masters of all times. We welcome you into real Christian community founded in love and acceptance, in respect and compassion for all the struggles and losses people are challenged by. We will do all in our power to call out your strengths, your wholeness and your Divine Self, while healing your past, your weaknesses and your wounds. We know the way, for we walk it. We know the pain, for we have lived it. We know the love, for it heals us too.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366425737000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365529978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Satsang and Grace Blessings</name><id>113496682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366414200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/113496682/</event_url></item>