<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Westminster st</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822720</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-421-3300</phone><name>Tazza Caffe</name><city>Providence</city><id>700461</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.412926</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Providence Collective Monday Meetup series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar and restaurant scenes in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Tazza - on Westminster St. in downtown Providence&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tazza is a perennial favorite of P-Collective members and was requested for this Monday Night - so here we go. Its been awhile and hey, why not!? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tazza has everything and is a super versatile place with lunch, dinner and breakfast as well as different events, live music, etc. almost every night of the week. Its trendy yet cozy, and always a good time. If we're lucky they also might be playing some great movie on the big screen, aka the wall next to the bar. So if you haven't been, this one is worth knowing about - you'll be back. So let's check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tazza is also a great place to go before, during or even after the outdoor summer movie series in Downcity - which just happens to be across the street!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.&lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure what scarf I'll be wearing - but we're hard to miss! I'll be inside, and depending on the weather may move outside to the sidewalk if there is space. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280360020000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279990531000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup  - Tazza!</name><id>14199978</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280181600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/14199978/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>