<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.763718</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>5321232</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.673576</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;January's theme for First Thursday at the Wadsworth Atheneum is INDIAN SPICE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is "English Vinglish", beginning at 8:00 pm. I set the meetup at the time I will try to be in the lobby of the Aetna Theater, but feel free to get there earlier to participate in the First Thursday activities. From the museum's website, they include: "Experience the culture of India with traditional music from Wesleyan University musicians and a dance performance by Rachna Agrawal. Participate in a Bollywood dancing lesson with heartthrob Deepak Arora or find your center during a yoga demonstration by Downtown Yoga. Enjoy Indian food, shop Indian clothing and create your own miniature painting inspired by an Indian illustrated manuscript in our collection!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They summarize the movie as follows: "In this comedic Bollywood drama, an insecure Indian housewife enrolls in an English class and her self-esteem begins to soar." Directed by Gauri Shinde and recently released, the movie will have subtitles. A longer summary and review of the movie can be found here: &lt;a href="http://tribune.com.pk/story/449613/movie-review-english-vinglish-mushy-but-marvelous/" class="linkified"&gt;http://tribune.com.pk/story/449613/movie-review-english-vinglish-mushy-but-marvelous/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Thursday, January 3 at 8 p.m. (Free with First Thursday admission of $5)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you cannot come on Thursday but want to see the movie, they have two other showings:  Saturday, January 5 at 7 p.m. and Sunday, January 6 at 2 p.m.  My eyes are still healing from surgery, so if they don't feel up to a 134-minute movie at the end of a work day, I may go on Saturday evening instead.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I am a short brunette with glasses and a black-and-green purse with an "M" on it.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358312697000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356918702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"English Vinglish" at First Thursday</name><id>97140242</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357260300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/97140242/</event_url></item>