<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Elizabeth Circle</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.284267</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-872-4770</phone><name>Nancy Zare Home</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1199656</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415802</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FRAMINGHAM RAW FOOD POTLUCK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She will be showing the film, &amp;quot;Breakthrough&amp;quot; by Storm Talifero.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breakthrough is a documentary about a raw vegan family! This is a beautiful film with a peaceful pace bringing you into the Talifero home. You'll meet the children and see their daily activities, playing music together, creating animations, and making and eating raw vegan food. You'll see a doctor's visit for a regular checkup for the kids and an interesting talk with the doctor. You'll see Storm's nephew shed 75 excess lbs. over a four month span on raw foods. You'll see Storm's 29 year old son Snow climbing a seven story cliff face with no ropes, showing the raw lifestyle as an ideal diet for the extreme athlete. Storm tells wonderful stories about his family and in his narration of this film he brings a unique clarity and conviction to this way of living. I believe that people who see this film will walk away with a renewed passion for the raw vegan lifestyle!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Storm has been eating a raw vegan diet of fruits, nuts, seeds, and vegetables in their unheated state for over 30 years, and has become known among raw vegans for his body builder's physique. At 57 he is still youthful. Jinjee first started eating a raw vegan diet when she met Storm 12 years ago. Her before and after pictures show her transformation. The whole family is 100% raw vegan with no supplements or dehydrated foods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This documentary was assembled from footage that Storm and Jinjee collected over the years. They have four raw vegan children; the oldest is eight. In the film they share the challenges that they've faced, both personally and with friends and families, and the differences that cooked vegan and raw vegan have made in their lives. They share nutrition information and information about the growth and development of their children, with taped visits to the doctor, and comparisons to CDC height and weight charts. There is a good section on raw vegans and exercise requirements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is impressive footage of Jinjee during a raw vegan pregnancy, exercising, and walking 5 miles a day, even as she came to term. There is footage of her taken ten days after her child was born, with Jinjee healthy, radiant, active and thin... There is an interview with Jinjee discussing her four pregnancies, both cooked vegan and raw vegan, and how the raw vegan deliveries went much smoother and faster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anybody raising raw vegan children, or considering doing so, I heartily recommend this film. There are enough beautiful women and hunky men in the movie to keep even the most non-raw spouse interested in the film. (Yep, weightlifters and Swedish blondes.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.breakthroughthedocumentary.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.breakthroughthedocumentary.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thegardendiet.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.thegardendiet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.breakthroughthedocumentary.com/images/dvdgraphic.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(It's off Route 126, about 6 blocks walk from downtown Framingham, which has a commuter train stop.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take Route 9 East and exit at Framingham State College, Main Street, Edgell. At the light turn right and follow Main Street (becomes Union at a slight rotary). Turn left on Lincoln Street, where MetroWest Hospital is located (follow Blue H Hospital sign). Go to end of street and at light (Concord Street, Route 126), turn left. Elizabeth Circle is the second left, one street past Dunkin Donuts. Park along circle, inner and outer as well as driveway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East: Take Route 9 West and turn right at the second of the Route 126 exits. Take the cloverleaf over Route 9. Pass 5 traffic lights, including one for the fire station. Look for Elizabeth Circle on the right just before Dunkin Donuts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Office: 508-872-4770&lt;br /&gt;Cell: 508-981-2315&lt;br /&gt;nancy.zare@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(posted by &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.essenic.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy Zare</member_name><member_id>8751033</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274499007000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270234085000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck: Framingham</name><id>rbmjnynhbqb</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273701600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/13070001/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/7/global_13610903.jpeg</photo_url></item>