<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>393 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06062</zip><lat>41.690453</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>793-8809</phone><name>Confetti's Restaurant</name><city>Plainville</city><id>450781</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.850190</lon></venue><fee><label>a fee of</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>24.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt; &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Making the most of the changes in our industry&amp;quot;:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Marketing guru and NY agency veteran, &lt;b&gt;John Follis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.follisinc.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, offers ideas on how to embrace new technologies as part of your creative process. Whether you're a writer, photographer or designer, learn how the changes in our industry provide alternative and exciting opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Follis spent 25-years on Madison Avenue as an award-winning creative, and then, as co-founder of an award-winning ad agency. More recently, John has become a respected national authority on Social Media and Web 2.0 marketing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A featured speaker at &lt;i&gt;Chicago's Social Media 2007&lt;/i&gt; John also writes on the topic for &lt;i&gt;ADWEEK&lt;/i&gt;. And, for the past two years, John has hosted a podcast: &lt;b&gt;The Marketing Show with John Follis and blog: The Follis Marketing Report.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you're a business owner seeking a cost-effective strategy for maximum sales results, ask John about his &amp;quot;Marketing Therapy&amp;quot; program, or look it up online at &lt;a href="http://www.follisinc.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.follisinc.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;- RSVP &amp;amp; pay for your meal via PayPal by Wednesday, March 19th.&lt;/b&gt;   Click on the PayPay tab above (www.paypal.com) and select the &amp;quot;Send Money&amp;quot; tab.  Insert &amp;quot;[address removed]&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Recipient's Email&amp;quot;. - Type in the amount you wish to send. ($24 per person) - Select &amp;quot;Service&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;Type&amp;quot; (of money sent). - Put ICC meeting-March 25 in the &amp;quot;Subject&amp;quot; box. - Note: Use the PayPal message box to type in your meal preference. Meal choices are &lt;br /&gt;? Basa Sole with Course Breadcrumbs and Feta Cheese&lt;br /&gt;? Stuffed Eggplant&lt;br /&gt;? Chicken Cacciatore&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do not indicate a choice, you will be assigned a vegetarian entree. All meal choices include bread, salad, dessert &amp;amp; coffee or tea. Cash bar available. Don't forget to select &amp;quot;send money&amp;quot; to complete your order. Your completed PayPal transaction will confirm your reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;OUR RESERVATION DEADLINE is Wednesday, March 19th.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; You must be paid in accordance with the instructions above before your reservation is considered accepted. Because we have to plan ahead, we need to collect money in advance. If you need to cancel, we will be able to refund your money only if you PHONE Laura Kolk at 860.646.0542 by the end of the day on March 21, so that we can cancel your reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Confetti's is a small venue. Ask for the "ICC" party</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda Bedard</member_name><member_id>5621944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette Mayer</member_name><member_id>5934991</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Kolk</member_name><member_id>6023842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206655794000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>This is a very casual group of folks. I suggest you come at 6:00 to enjoy the networking.</why><group><who>Network Marketers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>networkmarket-792</urlname><id>818489</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4400024414</group_lon><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203092091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford March Meetup</name><id>7336536</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206482400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/networkmarket-792/events/7336536/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/a/global_3272538.jpeg</photo_url></item>