<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Achieving World Peace by Finding Inner Peace&lt;br /&gt;   a workshop with Mother Clare Watts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, June 12 at 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are already active in the effort of bringing peace to the world or you now wish to begin participating in this endeavor, this seminar will introduce you to new and powerful ways of working toward this all-important goal. The mystics of all times and cultures have long stated that the most effective methods of bringing change to the world lie in the inner practices of its many individuals. Join us for this seminar, as we explore and experience the powerful inner practices of the mystics that will be paramount in bringing the Earth into ever-deepening peace and harmony.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** refreshments will be served **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare Watts is a mystic, ordained priest, Master Teacher of Christian mysticism, and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 13 Centers of Light in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she directs the effort to build the Sophia Peace Center.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Center of Light in Jamaica Plain is located just around the corner from the Stony Brook T stop on the Orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213486713000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206767586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Achieving World Peace by Finding Inner Peace</name><id>7625785</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213313400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/7625785/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/8/global_1017208.jpeg</photo_url></item>