<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.828388</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>XO Cafe</name><city>Providence</city><id>5846732</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: XO Cafe (formerly Cafe Noir, which WAS XO Steakhouse before that - lol!) It's across from Olives and next to Mills Tavern on N. Main St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So they switched the name two years ago to Cafe Noir from XO Steakhouse, now they've&amp;nbsp; combined the name to XO Cafe. Cafe Noir was a French inspired restaurant with a distinctively cozy and comfortable European feel, and the decor is pretty much the same. The bar is large and the creative drinks and food are tasty. This is a good one to know about and they offer a Ladies Night (sorry, guys...) on Wednesdays that includes a three-course tasting menu with purchase of a drink. Its really THAT good and well worth it! We haven't been back since the summer, so, whether you've been there before, or you'd like to give it a try, or just go again to see what the changes are, its always a good time and let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jon chose this location because he is a self-professed wine snob and knows many of you enjoy some good vino, too. On Monday nites at XO all bottles of wine and champagne are 1/2 price! So go in on a bottle with your fellow Collective Members and have a great time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jon has graciously offered to host this one, please look at his picture!!!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>33219162</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331393429000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>55</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330053084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - XO Cafe!!!!</name><id>53586632</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330988400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/53586632/</event_url></item>