<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The film starts at 7:05 PM.  &lt;b&gt;Herb and Dorothy&lt;/b&gt; is only scheduled for one week and since it's subject matter is so wonderful, I suggest ordering tickets in advance (see below). Please Note: Neither Herb nor Dorothy will  be present at the screening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, well, who are Herb and Dorothy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Herb and Dorothy&lt;/b&gt; tells the extraordinary story of Herbert Vogel, a postal clerk, and Dorothy Vogel, a librarian, who managed to build one of the most important contemporary art collections in history with very modest means. In the early 1960s, when very little attention was paid to minimalist and conceptual art, Herb and Dorothy quietly began purchasing the works of unknown artists. Devoting all of Herb's salary to purchase art they liked, and living on Dorothy's paycheck alone, they continued collecting artworks guided by two rules: the piece had to be affordable, and it had to be small enough to fit in their one-bedroom Manhattan apartment. Within these limitations, they collected over 4,000 pieces and proved themselves curatorial visionaries; most of those they supported and befriended went on to become world-renowned artists. Kendall Description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The story of how this collection — a large portion of which now resides at the National Gallery of Art in Washington — came to be is the subject of Megumi Sasaki’s modest, touching documentary, &lt;b&gt;“Herb &amp;amp; Dorothy.”&lt;/b&gt; NY Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As they share their views of modern art, director Megumi Sasaki's film feels like a cozy visit with neighbors whose insights are priceless.  New York Daily News &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As much as it is a tribute to the Vogels' devotion to the arts, &lt;b&gt;Herb &amp;amp; Dorothy&lt;/b&gt; also fascinates in how it explores the art of seeing. We want to see through their eyes, to learn to appreciate as they do. By conventional standards, minimalist and conceptualist art is not the most accessible, nor the most beautiful; Herb even calls it &amp;quot;tough art&amp;quot; for its hard, unforgiving shapes and colors. The Vogels have no explanation for why they're drawn to the works they are drawn to; they respond to what they feel is beautiful is as far an explanation as they give. And that speaks to the overriding theme of &lt;b&gt;Herb &amp;amp; Dorothy&lt;/b&gt;: that how we see beauty is as mysterious and mystifying a phenomenon as how we create it. Slant Magazine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion. &lt;br /&gt;Tickets can be purchased at &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" target="_blank"&gt;https://tickets.landm...&lt;/a&gt; after the actual screening time is announced. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246491318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Herb and Dorothy at Kendall</name><id>10783149</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247353200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10783149/</event_url></item>