<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As a duo Mike + Ruthy have refined their sound down to the very core of acoustic American music, demonstrating an uncommon ability to create songs as lyrically sophisticated as Bob Dylan or Leonard Cohen and as harmonically beautiful as Gillian Welch &amp;amp; David Rawlings or Simon &amp;amp; Garfunkel. With their arsenal of fiddle, banjo, guitar, ukulele and their hallmark harmony singing, a Mike + Ruthy concert is overstuffed with soulful songs and stories and a timeless sound that is spellbinding and pure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over a decade of touring has taken them worldwide where they've performed well over a thousand concerts in listening rooms, living rooms and festivals as well as performances at NYC's Carnegie Hall accompanying Arlo Guthrie in 2005 (with their former band The Mammals) and Madison Square Garden as part of Pete Seeger's 90th birthday celebration in 2009.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2012 will see Mike + Ruthy's 4th release entitled The NYC EP featuring the premiere recording of "My New York City" a beautifully revived Woody Guthrie lyric from the Woody Guthrie Archives. The song will also be included on "My Name is New York," a 4-CD compilation being issued by Woody Guthrie Publications including new recordings by Pete Seeger, Arlo Guthrie, and Bob Dylan and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike + Ruthy are on tour in 2012; with a springtime CD release tour and another national swing in the fall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The essence of American music . . . this summer's must-hear acoustic album." - Performer Magazine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Quite a few folks have done this 'set-Woody's-lyrics-to-music thing' over the past couple decades. I'm not sure anyone's ever done it better than this." - Peter Blackstock (co-founder of No Depression)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Extraordinary . . . some of the most exquisitely expressive vocals you will hear in the roots music field" -AmericanRootsUK.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike + Ruthy are carrying the torch for simple, heartfelt acoustic music . . . the rustic kind without any smoothing out of the edges with a direct line back to the Carter Family via Woody Guthrie, Hank Williams, Bob Dylan and even the Byrds" - Maverick Magazine, UK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mike + Ruthy have become a force to be reckoned with in the acoustic music world, and [The NYC EP] proves their mettle . . . Bold banjos rule, fiery fiddles run wild, and an expansive sound that threatens to raise the rafters prevails.” – The Daily Freeman”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There's perhaps no better way to summarize the lasting impact of Woody Guthrie's music than to note the quality of the very newest music being made with his words. Husband-wife Mike and Ruthy Merenda got the lyrics to "My New York City" from the Guthrie archives and set it to one of the most gorgeous melodies ever to accompany one of Woody's songs. It came out in April 2012: Brand new right now, it's destined to become a classic.” - eMusic’s 20 Best Woody Guthrie Songs (Sung By Other People)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Mike + Ruthy channel Woody Guthrie." - Journal &amp;amp; Courier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The first couple of folk rock." - Radio Free Americana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Everything else starts from music like this." - AmieStreet.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Infectious new folk rock" - Boston Globe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Seemingly descended not just from one famous folkie, but the entire folk tradition itself." - Willamette Week&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Some of the best songwriting of their generation - literate, political, melodic, alternately angry and satirical and sensual." - Michael Simmons&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;======================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested donation $19 + $1 preservation fee &lt;br /&gt;

Reservations strongly recommended: &lt;br /&gt;

notlobreservations at gmail dot com &lt;br /&gt;

More info at the notloB website: &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee from JP Licks &lt;br /&gt;

Pastries from Fiores&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=======================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please sign up for our concert announcements - &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352434283000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347411734000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mike + Ruthy (formerly of the Mammals)</name><id>81979432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352422800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/81979432/</event_url></item>