<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join Valley 9/11 Truth for a meeting beginning 6:00 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the first meetup of Valley 9/11 Truth in 2010! The theme of this gathering is about our group, and celebrating film and art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What campaigns do we as a group want to support this spring?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Mark will update on a campaign regarding this 911blogger page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://911blogger.com/node/22805" target="_blank"&gt; 9/11 Crime - Misprision - Citizens Action&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click following for most recent PDF file copy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/300645/Truth%20Over%20Treason.pdf"&gt;A Call for Truth Over Treason Stop War by exposing the 9/11 Cover-up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/300645/Valley%20911%20truth%20FN%202%20films%2014%20April%202010.doc"&gt;Download a one-page flyer on films and meeting!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel welcome to bring your dinner to our meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;At 7:00 - The Revolution Will Not Be Televised&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;At 9:00 - A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Moon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Revolution Will Not Be Televised&lt;/b&gt; - the film&lt;br /&gt;Directed and Photographed by Kim Bartley and Donnacha O'Briain&lt;br /&gt;Running time: 74 minutes, English narration, some Spanish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE REVOLUTION WILL NOT BE TELEVISED&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film concerns events around the short-lived coup d'etat of President Hugo Chavez of Venezuela on April 12th 2002. &amp;quot;What had in fact taken place was the first Latin American coup of the 21st century, and the world's first media coup.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Revolution Will Not Be Televised&amp;quot; was first broadcast in Europe in February 2003 and since then has been aired on a variety of national TV stations including the BBC, ZDF (Germany), Arte (France), and NPS (Holland) as well as at numerous international film festivals. In Venezuela the film had its first airing on national TV in April 2003.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Revolution Will Not Be Televised details the story of the Coup in 2002 against President Hugo Chavez from INSIDE the palace. This is the single biggest tool to disprove the lies of the opposition and demonstrates peoples resistance to fascism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Moon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;by Bart Sibrel - film running time - 47 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flyby News has provided screenings and discussions of a controversial film alleging a moon-landing hoax. The moon is 240,000 miles away from Earth. The space shuttle has never gone more than 400 miles from our atmosphere. Except for Apollo astronauts;, no humans even claim to have gone beyond low-earth orbit. When the space shuttle astronauts did get to an altitude of 400 miles, the radiation of the Van Allen belts forced them to a lower altitude. CNN reported: &amp;quot;The radiation belts surrounding Earth may be more dangerous for astronauts than previously believed (like when they supposedly went through them thirty years ago to reach the Moon.) The phenomenon known as the 'Van Allen Belts' can spawn (newly discovered) 'Killer Electrons' that can dramatically affect the astronauts' health.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a recent (2008) article in the Guardian (UK), a science correspondent wrote: &amp;quot;The question of how to fend off the solar wind has been given some urgency by an international plan - the Global Exploration Strategy, signed by 14 space agencies including those of Britain, China, France and the US - to return to the moon and send astronauts further into space. George Bush has committed the US to a return trip to the moon by 2020..&amp;quot; So why after the supposed multiple successful lunar landing and take-offs has humans remained in low orbit, since the 1972 and Apollo missions ended; is it coincidence that these missions ended when Russia and other countries had the technology in place to confirm a human moon landing and take-off. According to Bart Jordan, at that time NASA did not have the technology to lift off the moon even if they landed on it, and survived the intense Van Allen Earth-Sun magnetic radiation belt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is unique about Bart Sibrel’s film, besides its artistic blending of images demonstrating the hubris of humankind throughout the ages, and the current events of the arms race, Vietnam War, race riots, but he also presented some mislabeled, unedited, behind-the-scenes footage from NASA showing the crew of Apollo 11 'staging a shot of being half-way to the moon.' The quote used in his film from George Orwell’s book, 1984, is very apropos: &amp;quot;Those who control the future control the past.&amp;quot; It may be time for another look back to what many of us believed once was true. Did man really land on the moon?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More on these and other films, see&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FlybyNews.com &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1053728158,12232,"&gt;Films that Make a Difference!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donations of $2 to $5 per person would be appreciated to cover expenses for renting room, and promoting the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271455934000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268327009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>6pm Meeting - 7pm Chavez film - 9pm moon movie</name><id>12849421</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271282400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/12849421/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/global_576113.jpeg</photo_url></item>