<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hunt Room</address_2><address_1>405 Pine St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>42.992096</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-624-6550</phone><name>Manchester City Library</name><city>Manchester</city><id>884929</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.459190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What we accomplish in life is often a reflection of what kind of power we use.  Information, money and big titles are all highly prized sources of power.  But none of these can compare with the beauty and elegance of the results we get through using our inner powers:  The power to be generous towards someone who insults me, to keep quiet when others gossip, to make the right decision when I’m up against the wall.  The elegance of inner power is that it can help in any situation.  Its beauty lies in the happiness that it creates all around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inner power is very subtle.  It is a resourceful nature, a kind of resiliency.  In times of need, it turns my attention inward rather than outward.   Inner power frees me from following the crowd.  It gives me unlimited options.  I listen to my own voice; I make my own decisions; I tap into my own strengths.  With inner power I have the flexibility to respond creatively to any situation.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please go to Winchell room to find us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>10101462</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zvika</member_name><member_id>11183871</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272914216000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Great Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight</urlname><id>1499616</id><group_lat>43.0</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Owning Greatness Through Raja Yoga  Manchester Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266189529000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RECLAIMING OUR INNER POWER</name><id>12604549</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272740400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight/events/12604549/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/4/global_13107284.jpeg</photo_url></item>