<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>557 acres with hiking trails on Talcott Mt. Thie hike will be for about 2.5 miles. Beautiful views from the mountain of 1,200 square miles. A 165 foot tower sits at the top. The state website says the park is in Bloomfield but the bulk of the park with entrance road and tower are in Simsbury.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the parking area near the Yellow tailhead (Tower trail) on the park road off of Rte. 185 at 8 AM. The hike is anticipated to take about 1.75 hours and should be done by about 9:45 AM. A trail map can be found at the park link provided. A beautiful way to start the day and our hiking group meeting/brunch is at 11 AM with another hike planned at 3 PM. All in one day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions can be found in the notes area of this event. Kevin S will lead and is the contact for this one. I know it's early but I hope you can join in on the hike!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 North or South: take Exit 35B, which is the Bloomfield Route 218 exit. This road is also known as Cottage Grove Road. Follow Cottage Grove Road heading west until you hit Route 185. Follow Route 185 heading for Simsbury. At the top of the hill, the entrance to Talcott Mountain State Park/Heublein Tower will be on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-84 East or West: take the Route 44 Exit. Follow Route 44 heading west until you hit the junction of Routes 10 and 202 in the town of Avon. Follow Route 10 north until you hit Route 185 in Simsbury. Follow Route 185 heading for Bloomfield. At the top of the hill, Talcott Mountain State Park/Heublein Tower is on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PETS: &lt;br /&gt;Pets on a leash are permitted in picnic areas and on hiking trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/talcott.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/talcott.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1142576431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Talcott Mountain SP in Simsbury CT</name><id>4878432</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1143378000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4878432/</event_url></item>