<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Very long hike! (probably 21.5 miles, a few steep hills)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quabbin Reservoir: my favorite place!&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/f/a/event_73253242.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin is the most beautiful place in Massachusetts! You can see some pictures at my website: &lt;a href="http://www.custom-pro.com/portfolio/quabbin" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.custom-pro.com/portfolio/quabbin&lt;/a&gt;. At 18 miles long, it's the second-largest (in surface area) man-made body of water in the world! Quabbin Park is at the southern end, with paved roads, long dams, and beautiful viewing spots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploratory Hike Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've wanted to do this hike for some time, but it's very long, and in the summer it's too hot and muggy. Goodnough Dike is one of my favorite spots at Quabbin Reservoir. You can no longer drive over the dams. Park at the beginning of the Goodnough Dike loop (on your right, almost a mile down the park road from the East Entrance).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll walk over the dam (paved) and take Gate 50 at the end. This is a dirt fire road along the east shore. It diverges uphill a while to meet an old logging road, then back down near the shore. The old road continues past an island called "Mount Lizzie" before detouring through the woods around a big hill. Along the way, we'll pass several marshes and cross a stream. (I &lt;strong&gt;assume&lt;/strong&gt; we can cross the stream...&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;hence "exploratory hike."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; I haven't been there, but this is an actual old road.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we'll come out on Greenwich Road (paved) and turn left. Where South Baffle Dam meets the east shore, we are close to as many islands at once as possible on the entire reservoir! Oh, yeah, and being 2/5 of the way up, we'll be able to see almost all up and down the entire Quabbin Reservoir!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is possible to carve 2 or 3 smaller hikes out of this, but I don't know which are worth it by themselves, hence this "exploratory" hike. It's probably 10.5 or 11 miles one way, so 21 or 22 miles altogether. (No, I am not crazy, I have walked this far before, several times... just not here.) If you're a long-distance trooper, you are welcome to join me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Bring lunch, extra snacks, plenty to drink, flashlight or headlamp (just in case), rain gear, emergency toiletries (there may or may not be any outhouses on this route) including plastic/ziplock bag, and your camera!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will be sunny and 44 degrees! It will rain at night (later?); bring at least a rain coat or poncho and extra layer in case of emergency (like sprained ankle). We should finish about 3 or 4 pm, but be prepared with flashlight or headlamp just in case. No leaky shoes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you, in an extra pocket or plastic bag.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I will start the hike promptly at 8am! I leave my house by 7, so I won't see last-minute comments and messages. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. (From the North, use I-290 to get to Route 9.) Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware and some steep hills, there's not much except scattered houses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The East Entrance is on the right, around the curve after a pulloff where fishermen park. (The pulloff has a wood barrier at the start of a trail.) Turn right and continue straight roughly one mile. You can park in the small dirt lot on the right, or at the entrance to the loop road itself. (There will be a small, brown sign that says "Goodnough Dike.")&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you pass marsh on both sides of Route 9, you've gone too far. That's okay, just take the next entrance (the Middle Entrance) on the right. After more than a mile, continue straight through the rotary. (Don't go uphill to the tower.) The Goodnough Dike loop will be a few miles further on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live closer to Route 31 or 122 than to I-290, just take the appropriate route South to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above. Or, as an alternative, take 122 North (it heads kind of West), and take Route 32A South to Route 9. See the directions from Worcester...pick it up from downtown Ware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points North and West:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the North, take Route 202 South. (From east or west, use Route 2 to get there.) Turn left and go East on Route 9. The East Entrance is the 3rd entrance on your left, and it will take you at least 5 more minutes to get there. Before you get there, you will pass a marsh on both sides of the road. Also, there's a sign for the wildlife sanctuary on the right, shortly before you see the park entrance on the left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326379959000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325885171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Reservoir Exploratory Super-Hike: Goodnough Dike, Gate 50, S. Baffle Dam</name><id>46993082</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326286800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/46993082/</event_url></item>