<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's start the season off with an easy terrain playground. &lt;a href="http://video.google.com/videoplay?docid=-2451206667623766986" target="_blank"&gt;Tower Hill Pond &lt;/a&gt; offers a gorgeous scenery this time of year, complete with phonics produced by the ice/snow melting streams gurgling peaceful sounds on their way into the pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail to the pond and around the pond is about 3 miles, easy going and a great way to start off the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At a leasurely pace, complete with throwing sticks and talking, it can be completed in about 2 hours without breaking a sweat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The area is only accessible by foot or bicycle - gifting visitors with a near serene nature experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;Route 101 East&lt;br /&gt;Exit 2 &lt;br /&gt;Right on Hooksett Road&lt;br /&gt;1/4 mile up take a Left onto Old Candia Road --- drive by Smiley Veterinarian on Left hand side&lt;br /&gt;1/4 mile another left under Route 101 OVERPASS ---- there's a house on the corner of this DIRT road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 3 places to park, drive to the 3rd one; about 1/2 mile up the road &lt;br /&gt;Look for my car: Light Green Volvo Station Wagon; License plate eprint&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://activedogs.meetup.com/254/calendar/7696059/"&gt;Human Soles &amp;amp; Doggie Paws April Meeting at Tower Hill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll put a Meetup Sign where you have to take a left off of Old Candia Road&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WANTED: Meetup Assistants&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; - please let me know if you'd like to help me ensure the success of the group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Name Tags&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; - I will bring some labels we can put on our clothes so we can learn each other's names better. I, for one am terrible with names and need all the help I can get!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Things you may consider bringing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comfortable Walking/Hiking Shoes - waterproofed if you have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bug Spray&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Water for you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rain Coat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The more CAMERAS the better - I'd like to post Pix of our Meeting (with your permission, of course)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Things to bear in mind in general&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Horses, bicycles, other walkers frequent the trail - we must share the space&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tower Hill feeds into Massabessic &amp;amp; therefore there is no swimming or wading signs posted everywhere. Fines can be issued if those rules are broken.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are certain DISCREET areas where my poor clumsy Puppy always seems to fall into the water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;I'm hoping the rain they are predicting is for later on during the day. I don't mind walking in a little misty rain, but not anything too heavy. Should Mother Nature not cooperate we'll have to reschedule. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The rule of thumb will be that if it's pouring at 1:30 pm then the meeting at Tower Hill will be rescheduled to May 25th.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting everyone this weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My super friendly, will roll over so you can see how friendly he is, Golden Retriever HUGO will find you first... most likely! Otherwise look for the puppy mobile with a NH license plate of "eprint". Directions under the windshield wipers, if late.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4894798</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209492525000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>With Mother Nature's good blessing wouldn't it be great to fill a Lazy Sunday Afternoon with a relaxing walk with your four legged companion(s)?
Since this is such a "Small World" don't be surprised to find someone you already know.</why><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207620210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws April Meeting</name><id>7696059</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209319200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/7696059/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/global_3732006.jpeg</photo_url></item>