<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you sometimes wish that people would find you more interesting?  More appealing?  More attractive?  The truth is... you already are interesting, but perhaps you don't know how to put your best qualities on display so they can effortlessly attract the attention (and desire) of other people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll cover all that and more in this upcoming class.  You'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The single most important ability you must develop in order to be interesting and attractive to other people.  Once you master this, you'll have a never ending supply of quality people wanting to spend more time with you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My proven method for instantly make people feel closer you.  You can use this for dating, friendship, and even business, and people will find themselves making excuses to spend more time with you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &amp;quot;secret question&amp;quot; that everyone's subconscious mind is asking when you first meet them.  Once you know this, you'll be able to put people at ease and make them feel comfortable around you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simple steps you can take right away to make yourself more physically attractive.  I tried these myself as an experiment, and now I'm getting a lot more compliments (and more dates).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;And that's only the first half of the meeting.  During the second half, you'll have an opportunity to practice everything you learned in the lesson.  We'll do fun, interactive exercises and drills to ensure that these concepts and techniques become automatic.  That way they will be there for you in the real world when you really need them.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The meeting is limited to 25 due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings almost always sell out within a day or two, and we end up with a waiting list, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Monday, December 8th available.  The meeting runs from 8pm to 10pm and is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 3 minutes walk from the red line.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that night free, go ahead and RSVP for this meeting right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  These meetings always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $10, which helps pay the cost of running this group, classroom rental, and printed materials.  Please bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$10 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems.  My cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk in the bldg, down the hall, 2nd door on right.  It's called the music room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231288683000</updated><rating><average>4.17999982834</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228350818000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Skills Meeting - How To Make Yourself More Interesting To Others</name><id>9275895</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228784400000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/9275895/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/b/global_4864315.jpeg</photo_url></item>