<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>471 Shetucket Tpke</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06351</zip><lat>41.553127</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-376-4081</phone><name>Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream</name><city>Griswold</city><id>690077</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.883911</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sorry for making this last minute folks, but I wanted to be more sure of the weather, and this looks like it's going to be the best day for this meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the second-to-last of the Sunflowers for Wishes event at the Buttonwoods farm. This year they have grown 14 acres of sunflowers to sell for the Make a Wish Foundation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This would be a great meetup for anyone who loves photography. I was going to schedule this last weekend, but apparantly the sunflowers were late this year due to all the rain we've had. I've picked a late meetup time so that we hopefully get the best possible light. Fingers crossed that it's still sunny at that time of day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buttonwoods farm is also well known for their great home-made icecream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we've finished having a tour of the sunflowers and stuffing ourselves with icecream, there's always the option of deciding to retire to a local restaurant for a late supper if we wish to keep on chatting. The farm itself is open until nine thirty, so if we just want to hang out and get to know each other that might work as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CARPOOLING:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm coming from Mansfield Center, and have two spaces in my car if anyone wants to carpool. The only thing is - I have my disabled client with me, and if she wants to leave early, we do have to go. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston (89 miles) Rt. 90 (Mass. Pike): West to exit 10 (Auburn), I-395 South to exit 85. Cross over Rt. 138. Left on Rt. 164 South, 5 miles to left on Rt. 165. East 5 miles to Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Providence (34 miles): I-95 South to Rhode Island exit 5A. 1 mile south on Rt. 102. Right on Rt. 3 South for 1 mile. Right on Rt. 165 West. 13 miles on Rt. 165. West to Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hartford (49 miles): Rt. 2 East to exit 28N. I 395 North to exit 85. Right on Rt. 164 South. 5 miles to left on Rt. 165. East 5 miles to Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New York (130 miles)/New Haven (60 miles): I-95 North to exit 76 (left exit). I-395 North to exit 85. Rt. 164 South. 5 miles to left on Rt. 165 East. 5 miles on Rt. 165 East to Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New London (Orient Point Ferry/Transportation Center) (23 miles): Rt. 32 North to I-395 North to exit 85. Right on Rt. 164 South. 5 miles to left on Rt. 165 East. 5 miles to Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mystic (17 miles): From exit 90 (Seaport exit) off I-95 – Rt. 27 North. Bear right at General Store. Continue to Rt. 184 – Cross over Rt. 184 Lantern Hill Rd. 5½ miles to left on Rt. 2 West. 2 miles to right on Rt. 164 North. 3 miles to right on 165 east. 5 miles on Rt. 165 east to Buttonwood Farm Ice Cream.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a camera hanging around my neck, and I'll have my developmentally disabled client with me. I'll be wearing a pink shirt, but that might not help if it gets cool.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251057180000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NorthEast-Connecticut-Friends-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1330452</id><group_lat>41.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.2099990845</group_lon><name>The NorthEast Connecticut Friends Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248529428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last minute meetup!!!! - Buttonwoods Sunflower Farm and homemade icecream!</name><id>10954321</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248557400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NorthEast-Connecticut-Friends-Meetup-Group/events/10954321/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/c/global_6487468.jpeg</photo_url></item>