<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5450 Fitch Ave</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04011</zip><lat>43.899780</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207.406.2081</phone><name>Brunswick Executive Airport   (KBXM)</name><city>Brunswick</city><id>1597235</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.923973</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This was a Naval Airbase. 11 nm NE of Wiscasset Me. About 120 nm from FIT or an hour or so flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They are having an International Fly In. The NEPG will also be attending and we thought this would be a good one for us as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Brunswick Executive Airport (BXM) &lt;br /&gt;As of Saturday, April 2, 2011 at 1:00pm (EST) the Brunswick Executive Airport at Brunswick Landing is open for business! With an 8,000 foot runway open, even a low wing can land long here :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This looks like a good days event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/a/8/event_22672392.jpeg" width="262" height="137" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/5/6/event_22672310.jpeg" width="385" height="99" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mrra.us/bxmairport.html"&gt;http://www.mrra.us/bxmairport.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Brunswick International Fly-In will feature a pancake breakfast, keynote addresses by Alan Klapmeier of Kestrel Aircraft Company, and Craig Fuller, the president of the Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association (AOPA).&lt;/strong&gt;  A pilot town hall forum will follow the keynote addresses.   The afternoon will feature safety seminars for pilots interested in continuing education credits.&lt;strong&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;In addition, the Experimental Aircraft Association (EAA) will conduct a contest judging homebuilt aircraft,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;as well as workshops on building your own airplane.&lt;strong&gt;  The day concludes with music and a New England Barbeque and Maine Lobster Bake.  The Fly-In will also serve as an open house to non-aviation enthusiasts interested in seeing and learning about this new general aviation airport in their community.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;“Pilots will enjoy flying into Brunswick Executive Airport” said Marty McMahon, MRRA’s Aviation Services Manager.  &lt;strong&gt;“This airport has 8000 ft parallel runways&lt;/strong&gt;, instrument approach capabilities, and state of the art building designed for aviation use.  The 1.8 million square feet of ramp space and thousands of tie-downs make the airport a great venue for a Fly-In.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Please go to the airport website and look over all the information provided. Important airport information is posted such as closed runways. To get to the website click on the airport name next to the map picture. Once you click the airport name you will see the email adress. Once on the airport website click on BXM Airport on the far right to see Pilot Information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307197741000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>We like to fly, eat and learn with other aviators. Not to mention the beautiful scenic coastal flight to
 Maine :-)

Not sure BXM is in your gps data base yet.   N43-53'-32.0  W 69-56'-19.01    Rwy 1R &amp; 19L is open.  Unicom is 122.725</why><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302726100000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunswick Executive Airport Open House KBXM</name><id>17294655</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307192400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/17294655/</event_url></item>