<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday, May 17. Meet by 6:45 p.m., AMC Cinema, 22 Flutie Pass, Framingham, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a meet-up to see "The Great Gatsby" at the AMC Cinema in Framingham. Movie starts at 7:00 p.m. We will be seeing the Non-3D version. We'll start to gather around 6:30 p.m. and at 6:45 I'll see who is there and will get in line to get tickets. You'll have time to visit the concession stand before we get our seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet in the first (interior) lobby, to the right of the ticket counter. I will be wearing a small "Meet Up" badge. I will have discount passes that will cost $8 per person (regularly $11.25). Exact change is helpful. After the movie, anyone who wishes to can go out to a local restaurant together to talk or to discuss the movie. Please remember to update your RSVP if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Great Gatsby &lt;br /&gt;

 The Great Gatsby follows Fitzgerald-like, would-be writer Nick Carraway as he leaves the Midwest and comes to New York City in the spring of 1922, an era of loosening morals, glittering jazz and bootleg kings. Chasing his own American Dream, Nick lands next door to a mysterious, party-giving millionaire, Jay Gatsby, and across the bay from his cousin, Daisy, and her philandering, blue-blooded husband, Tom Buchanan. It is thus that Nick is drawn into the captivating world of the super-rich, their illusions, loves and deceits. As Nick bears witness, within and without the world he inhabits, he pens a tale of impossible love, incorruptible dreams and high-octane tragedy, and holds a mirror to our own modern times and struggles. &lt;br /&gt;

 Running Time: 2 hr 22 min &lt;br /&gt;

 Genre: Drama &lt;br /&gt;

 Rated: PG-13 &lt;br /&gt;

 Director: Baz Luhrmann &lt;br /&gt;

 Cast: Leonardo Dicaprio, Tobey Maguire, Carey Mulligan&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the lobby, to the right of the ticket counter</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>6039490</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368921780000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368232726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framingham Movie Meetup: "The Great Gatsby," 5/17</name><id>118822862</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368830700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/118822862/</event_url></item>