<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Top Floor</address_2><address_1>5 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.284571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beyond Fitness</name><city>Natick</city><id>948748</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.347907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is Nia?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;Through Movement We Find Health&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Done barefoot to diverse and inspiring music, Nia is a transformational movement practice that teaches you to be more JOYFUL, EXPRESSIVE and ALIVE in your body, both inside and outside of the studio. Nia is holistic, engaging your body, mind, emotions and spirit. Nia draws from dance arts, martial arts, and healing arts to create purposeful movement that will help you grow and learn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why Practice Nia?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nia increases the pleasure of living in your body; Nia creates weight loss and proper weight maintenance; Nia strengthens muscles, improves muscle tone, and increases muscle definition; Nia calms the mind and relieves stress; Nia increases grace, flexibility and endurance; Nia builds reservoirs of energy and improves cognitive functioning. And so much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Practices Nia?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nia is practiced by people of all walks of life, ages and fitness levels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited!  RSVP early&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donna McGurk is a Natick resident who has been doing Nia since 1999. She has been teaching Nia in Metro West since 2003. In 2007 she completed the 3rd level of Nia Intensive training – the Brown Belt.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;As this is a &amp;quot;moms only&amp;quot; event, potential members are welcome to attend! To become a member of the Framingham Area chapter of Mothers &amp;amp; More, you must either mail in an official membership form with your dues, or fill out the enrollment form online and pay via credit card at &lt;a href="http://www.mothersandmore.org/AboutUs/join.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mothersand...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact Asst. Organizer, Kate to have memberships forms and more chapter information mailed to you. Thanks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many other events will be held in April-August (available to paid members only due to insurance liability policy requirements.) &lt;br /&gt;Mom and Kids Lunch at Bugaboo Creek &lt;br /&gt;See the Big Trucks at the Framingham DPW truck lot &lt;br /&gt;Southwick Zoo Trip &lt;br /&gt;Tour of Whole Foods &lt;br /&gt;Berry Picking &lt;br /&gt;Ice Cream at Gerards &lt;br /&gt;Family Baseball Night -watch the Lowell Spinners &lt;br /&gt;Davis Farmland and Splashpad Visit &lt;br /&gt;Ice Skating &lt;br /&gt;Family Cookout &lt;br /&gt;Hopkinton State Park Beach day &lt;br /&gt;Water Fun Sprinkler/Slide/Wading Pool party &lt;br /&gt;Playground Drop-ins at designated Parks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Other events that Mothers &amp;amp; More offers- Movie Mamas monthly movie night at the AMC Framingham, Book Group, Cooking Group, Unfinished Object Night (scrapbooking, knitting, general projects on your to-do list.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanya</member_name><member_id>7153030</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245882754000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241369002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to NIA</name><id>10325968</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245195000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/10325968/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/a/global_8459978.jpeg</photo_url></item>