<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>319 Todd Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06716</zip><lat>41.564697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-808-5829 </phone><name>Terri's House</name><city>Wolcott</city><id>1368806</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.972048</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Well, we're doing it again...the big bash at Terri's house...annual party/picnic! If you were there last year, you'll know of what I speak. If you were not, then ask someone who was. They will tell you that this was the event of the summer! You, and your friends, are all invited to do it again with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on for picnic info...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are winding down the summer season with a bash at Terri's house. Why let summer slip away without one more super party? Let's get together and celebrate summer!!! And yes there WILL BE A BAND again...the Troy Brown Band will again be playing for our entertainment pleasure. We will be dancing under the grapevine and stars!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a BYOB event...we are also asking you to bring a dish ...appetizer, entree or dessert. No grilling meats please. I will be coordinating the food again, so we will have a variety. You will be asked what you will contribute when you RSVP. Please DO NOT bring foods that require heating up in my ovens, as I will NOT be manning the kitchen this year...I will be socializing. So please be certain that what you bring is outdoor ready.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are asking guests to bring beach chairs, coolers, ICE, and any games you may want to play (badminton, horseshoes, bocce balls, cards, board games, etc.). I also have a firepit for chilling and marshmallow roasting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a large driveway, but please do not park in the middle...leave room for others. Also road parking is available. If you park at a nearby commuter parking lot ( there is one right off I 84) and car pool it would be best. However, we will make do...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come join us at Terri's place for good times...good food ...good company! There will be a $5.00 cover charge. If you need to contact me, my cell is 203-808-5829. I will be updating, so more to follow...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, save the date...8/20...and RSVP early to save your spot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Please note:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;covenant as follows:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant,&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;connected with Eat, Laugh and Be Merry in West Hartford for and related to the above listed event. I attest and&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;of this above listed event. I grant the "Group" permission to use any&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>white house with red brick front and look for red balloons..203-808-5829 terri  860-729-4504 chuck</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chuck</member_name><member_id>11483387</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314036226000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Smiling Happy Faces</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford</urlname><id>1498492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Eat, Laugh, and Be Merry in West Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>159</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306695632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>second annual summer picnic at Terri's</name><id>20162111</id><headcount>140</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313870400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford/events/20162111/</event_url></item>