<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi, All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2010 Coolidge Award recipient is Jonathan Demme which means, weather permitting and a great way to help us through this time of year, we will have a chance to view a lot of his films in retrospective during Tuesdays in February and March.  I've selected two films (a difficult decision) for the meetup schedule and beginning Monday tickets will be available at the box office and online by going through www.coolidge.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, February 16, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;6:45 Stop Making Sense &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, February 23, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;6:45 Silence of the Lambs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Wikipedia: &amp;quot;Stop Making Sense was very well-received by critics, maintaining a 97% &amp;quot;fresh&amp;quot; score at Rotten Tomatoes.[5] It won the National Society of Film Critics Award for best documentary in 1984.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pauline Kael wrote: &amp;quot; &amp;quot;Stop Making Sense&amp;quot; makes wonderful sense. A concert film by the New York new-wave rock band Talking Heads, it was shot during three performances at the Hollywood Pantages Theatre in December, 1983, and the footage has been put together without interviews and with very few cutaways. The director, Jonathan Demme, offers us a continuous rock experience that keeps building, becoming ever more intense and euphoric. This has not been a year when American movies overflowed with happiness; there was some in &amp;quot;Splash&amp;quot;, and there's quite a lot in &amp;quot;All of Me&amp;quot;—especially in its last, dancing minutes. &amp;quot;Stop Making Sense&amp;quot; is the only current movie that's a dose of happiness from beginning to end. The lead singer, David Byrne, designed the stage lighting and the elegantly plain performance-art environments (three screens used for backlit side projections); there's no glitter, no sleaze. The musicians aren't trying to show us how hot they are; the women in the group aren't there to show us some skin. Seeing the movie is like going to an austere orgy—which turns out to be just what you wanted.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>5:45 Meetup at Panera's  for light supper and chat. I'll have the IA logo on red card stock in plain view.  6:15/6:30 Gauge when we need to get in line for optimal seating.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264896252000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stop Making Sense</name><id>12470204</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266363900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12470204/</event_url></item>