<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Buffalo Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03266</zip><lat>43.814055</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rumney</name><city>Rumney</city><id>807315</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.858176</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Depending upon interest we will leave friday afternoon.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have reserved a camp ground at Baker river camp ground    &lt;br /&gt;Friday night and Saturday night. The cost is 10$ per person per night   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The site should be large enough to acomadate us and if more sites are needed we can deal with that later.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The sites have running water, electric, toilet and shower. Pet freindly with proof of rabies shot and on leash.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday morning we will hit the walls and enjoy an awesome day. It is suppose to be 70 and sunny all weekend!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camp saturday evening and repeat on sunday.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you that can not make it up friday night and want to join us early saturday please def do so!    &lt;br /&gt;Come saturday in the AM climb all day and just camp the one night and climb sunday!    &lt;br /&gt;Its only 2 and half hours from boston and the best sport climbing from 5.2 to 5.13 in the Northeast   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you arriving on friday evening to camp the first night we will meet at the Baker River Campground. For those of you in Boston and wishing to caravan please email.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bakerrivercamp.." target="_blank"&gt;http://bakerrivercamp...&lt;/a&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those arriving saturday morning to climb saturday and camp saturday night please contact me to meet either at the campground or the rumney parking lot   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email or call me for any questions and or details.    &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to meeting some new climbers and enjoying the weekend!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bobby    &lt;br /&gt;781-589-0385    &lt;br /&gt;bassk94@gmail.com   &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286029667000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285798842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rumney NH Hosted by Mountaineering, Backpacking, and Climbing Of New England</name><id>14943125</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286024400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/14943125/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/b/global_4328635.jpeg</photo_url></item>