<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Middletown Avenue, </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06473</zip><lat>41.358608</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Festival is held on the grounds of St. Therese Church </name><city>North Haven</city><id>8489452</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.840309</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The North Haven Sons &amp;amp; Daughters of Italy Lodge No. 2805 will sponsor their Eighth annual Italian festival of angels.  I will be working sometime during the festival and will not be hosting this event but please show up anytime on Friday between 4 PM and 10 PM and Saturday between 10 AM to 10 PM to enjoy the wonderful sights and sounds of Italy come to life in North Haven.  This is NOT in the center of North Haven for the second year.  It will be on the grounds of St. Therese Church, 555 Middletown Avenue, North Haven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be an Italian Heritage tent display, Italian items to purchase, many craft vendors Italian food vendors and local entertainment with an Italian Idol contest as well.  There is a small $2.00 entrance fee as a fundraiser event and sponsors support the rest paying for our festival operating expenses and allowing us to give back to the community with many charitable activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Festival is intended to embody the attributes of generosity and goodwill that define the Italian Spirit!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/b/8/event_144700632.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of the procession prior to the festivities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;"We feel that this Festival has become an important community service to North Haven and our surrounding communities, as well as sustain the social vitality and cultural vibrancy of the Italian American heritage by strengthening family life, uplifting human services, binding together the diverse historical traditions of Italians, and honoring the legacy of Italian immigration to the United States."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lenny Ricciardelli, Festival Director&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the day with food, soft drinks and song throughout the festival!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find out more about the festival and our lodge you can visit the web site at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northhavenlodge2805.org/index.htm"&gt;http://www.northhavenlodge2805.org/index.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ciao!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enjoy the day</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345425325000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343775136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Haven's Italian Festival of Angels August 17 &amp; 18, 2012</name><id>75749472</id><headcount>1500</headcount><duration>108000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345233600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/75749472/</event_url></item>