<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>163404</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.healthyworldaffiliates.com/educational-products-pharmawhores-the-showtime-sting-of-penn-teller-140-min-dvd-p-1005.html" target="_blank"&gt;PHARMAWHORES: The Showtime Sting of Penn &amp;amp; Teller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; is set to launch nationally on June 5th, and is bound to raise awareness about Big Pharma's ties to the Mainstream Media. The film includes compelling evidence that ties 'Big Pharma' to '9/11 Terrorism' and profiteering. &amp;#8232; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On June 6th, the PharmaWhores film will be screened at the nations oldest and largest gathering of conspiracy experts at the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ConspiracyCon.com" target="_blank"&gt;Conspiracy Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; in Santa Rosa, CA, and on June 12th will be held at the &lt;a href="http://www.baltheatre.com" target="_blank"&gt;Bal Theatre&lt;/a&gt; in San Leandro, CA,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;On July 1st, the East Coast premiere screening will be held at the Frances Crowe Community Meeting space in Northampton, MA.&lt;/b&gt; It is sponsored by &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Flyby News&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.valley911truth.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. There will be no admission charge at the Northampton screening, however, donations to cover costs will be appreciated. Dr. Leonard Horowitz and Sherri Kane, who both star in the film, will be attending to participate in Q &amp;amp; A. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This whimsical tongue-in-cheek documentary, produced by Dr. Leonard G. Horowitz exposes BigPharma's media connections. It is filled with ironic humor, centering around the Las Vegas comedy team of Penn &amp;amp; Teller and their SHOWTIME TV show called, &amp;quot;Bullshit!&amp;quot; Originally, the program planned on debunking Horowitz for his natural healing product endorsements. However, the doctor, a YouTube favorite, along with FOX News defector Sherri Kane, armed with documents, props, and a professional film crew, exposed SHOWTIME's network executives in partnerships with the most powerful drug industrialists. The &amp;quot;counter-sting&amp;quot; proves Penn &amp;amp; Teller are more than celebrity magicians. They serve BigPharma as media propagandists--PHARMAWHORES! Plus, the film provides compelling evidence that ties 'Big Pharma' to '9/11 Terrorism' and profiteering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Leonard G. Horowitz, the award-winning author and producer of &lt;a href="http://inlieswetrust.com" target="_blank"&gt;In Lies We Trust: The CIA, Hollywood &amp;amp; Bioterrorism&lt;/a&gt;, is an internationally known authority in the overlapping fields of public health, behavioral science, natural healing, and a Harvard trained expert on emerging diseases.   He has written 16 books, and three national bestsellers. His book &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.healthyworldstore.com/index.php?act=viewProd&amp;amp;productId=25" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;Emerging Viruses: AIDS &amp;amp; Ebola--Nature, Accident or Intentional?&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; was referenced by Obama’s pastor, Reverend Jeremiah Wright during the Obama 2008 Presidential campaign.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following their film screening, Dr. Horowitz and Ms. Kane will update us on their efforts to help people stay healthy in a deceptive world, as well as a way to finance grassroots organizations and campaigns. They are advancing &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.healthyworldaffiliates.com/2925" target="_blank"&gt;Healthy World Affiliates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; and as an alternative to the corrupt World Health Organization. There are no obligations, financial investments, or purchases necessary to participate, and company profits go to humanitarian projects. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please help promote this event by downloading this &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/300645/PHARMAWHORES%20Northampton%20SCREENING%20POSTER.pdf"&gt;PDF-FLYER&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;For more on the film, go to:&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;a href="http://pharmawhores.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PharmaWhores&lt;/b&gt;.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278083168000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274215562000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr. Len Horowitz, Sherri Kane + PharmaWhores screening </name><id>13523227</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278021600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/13523227/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/c/global_14707244.jpeg</photo_url></item>