<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>[&lt;b&gt;The Youth Movement: Digital Media's Leaders and their Ideas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, November 20, 2008&lt;br /&gt;THIS MEETING IS FREE, THERE WILL BE NO CHARGE to attend, however, pre-registration is preferred!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register Online at &lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.entretechf...&lt;/a&gt;, walk ins are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the location of this meeting is at:&lt;br /&gt;Northeastern University - &lt;br /&gt;Room 440&lt;br /&gt;Egan Research Center&lt;br /&gt;120 Forsyth Street, Boston MA  02115&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Overview&lt;br /&gt;A panel of the region's young, dynamic digital media company founders and CEOs will discuss a wide range of topics relating to their personal careers, their experiences running their companies, where they get their best ideas, and the future of the digital media industry in Boston.  The panelists are backed by some of the leading firms in the venture capital industry and are all on aggressive growth paths.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The panel will be moderated by Professor Terrence Masson, a member of the faculty at Northeastern.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;The panelists will discuss:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Their personal career path to their leadership position and their thoughts on preparing young people to follow in their footsteps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hot new digital media trends and business models and how they keep their companies innovative and competitive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How they convinced venture capitalists and angels to back their companies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The role universities do or should play as a source of talented employees and new ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to make Boston a world-class center for digital media companies.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terrance Masson, Director of Game Design:  NU Author of &amp;quot;CG101: A Computer Graphics Industry Reference&amp;quot; (2007 Second Edition) www.cg101.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;20 years of production experience, since 1994 running own consulting company &amp;quot;Digital Fauxtography&amp;quot; as a Creative Producer, Director and VFX Supervisor.  I've come up through the ranks on about 20 feature films as well as many commercials and video game projects including three Star Wars movies and getting SouthPark started.  Member of the Producers Guild of America, the Visual Effects Society and have been active in SIGGRAPH since 1988, most recently as the 2006 Computer Animation Festival Chair and currently as SIGGRAPH 2010 Conference Chair.  www.visualfx.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evan Schumacher, CEO, Going.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karen Ong, Founder, MyHappyPlanet.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Balfour, Founder/CEO, Viximo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Lauzon, Co-Founder and CEO, Paragon Lake&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Shin, Founder/CEO, Visible Measures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitor Directions and Parking, Main Campus :  &lt;a href="http://www.northeastern.edu/campusmap/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northeaste...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking at The Renaissance Parking Garage, 835 Columbus Ave. Boston, MA.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***From the parking garage you can get to the campus by walking through the orange line train station and go down the stairs out into the campus &amp;amp;  Forsyth St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Open to all</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Georgia</member_name><member_id>6917121</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 7170621</member_name><member_id>7170621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229473051000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224632378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DIGITAL MEDIA - (GLOBAL ENTREPRENEURSHIP WEEK)</name><id>9006086</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227223800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/9006086/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/3/global_4559507.jpeg</photo_url></item>