<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/b/c/event_66700892.jpeg" width="144" height="207" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;November Business Meeting:&amp;nbsp; News, Public Relations and Profitable Businesses &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Best PR practices for Winning Positive, Front Page News Coverage and Strategies to Grow Successful Businesses.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Speaker:&lt;/strong&gt; Janine Fondon, President and CEO of Unity First Direct, Inc. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt; Thursday, November 17, 2011 &amp;ndash; 7:45am &amp;ndash; 9:30am &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt; Yankee Pedlar Inn, 1866 Northampton Street, Holyoke, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; Members- $20 in advance (with $5 cash back at check-in), $18 at the door. Non-members- $20. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;RSVP by Sunday, November 13, 2011 at midnight&lt;/strong&gt; by registering on our Meetup site or by calling (413) 827-4182. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Janine Fondon specializes in marketing and media communications consulting as well as diversity outreach. Fondon, who will be joined by a distinguished media panel, will share best practices to help business owners create positive &amp;lsquo;front page&amp;rsquo; newsworthy stories that win business, increase visibility and get people buzzing. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;ldquo;We invite business owners, communications professionals and media to attend,&amp;rdquo; says Janine Fondon, who looks forward to inspiring a great holiday season for businesses and a new year --2012-- filled with success.&amp;nbsp; Fondon, who co-leads UnityFirst.com with her husband Tom Fondon, enjoys consulting with organizations and corporations that desire to create effective communication strategies to better engage both mainstream and emerging diverse markets.&amp;nbsp; With key skills in navigating multicultural social networks, diversity focused e-communities and positioning diversity-related initiatives, Janine and her husband have developed one of the most innovative online news networks sharing information locally across the Commonwealth as well as across the U.S. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Fondon is the current Public Relations chair for the Women Business Owners Alliance, a member of the Springfield Affiliated Chamber of Commerce Board of Directors, and Board Chair of the WTCC Radio Advisory Board (Springfield Technical Community College). She has received numerous awards, including recognition as &amp;ldquo;Western Massachusetts Magazine Women of the Year in Publishing&amp;rdquo; as well as one of&amp;nbsp; the &amp;ldquo;Top 25 Women in Business&amp;rdquo; as noted by New York&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Network Journal. Over the years, her work has been highlighted in many publications, including FORBES, Fortune, Black Enterprise, BusinessWEST, The Republican, The Boston Globe, and others.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321656493000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319491493000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Breakfast Meeting- News, Public Relations and Profitable Businesses</name><id>38559072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321533900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/38559072/</event_url></item>