<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>170 Water Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.963104</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue-Eyed Crab Grille and Raw Bar</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>7436182</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.669655</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Summertime, and the dining is easy! Or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually, "easy" is a pretty vague tag for a culinary experience. For our purposes, more relevant criteria might include things like; 1) Delicious 2) Outdoors and 3) Close to the water. Fortunately, we're happy to report that The Blue-eyed crab in downtown Plymouth records positive marks in all three categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in The Village Landing Mall, just across the street from the waterfront, The Blue-Eyed Crab is a fun, informal place. The decor is nautical and quirky, the staff are accommodating, and the food is at least a couple steps above the standard "pub grub" that you might expect from a small place located at ground zero for the annual tourist invasion of "America's Hometown".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As with our recent trip to The Dan'l Webster Inn in Sandwich, this is a joint event with the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group (SSDOMG) and we hope that members of both groups will be able to join us at 1:15 on Saturday, June 9th. If you come, please don't be in a hurry because lunchtime crowds at this time of year can be unpredictable (and we may just decide to hold out for outdoor seating if we can get it without waiting too long). We ourselves are planning to take our time over lunch, then walk it off either strolling along the waterfront or poking into some of the many shops in the downtown area, starting with the ones right in The Village Landing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that unless you're a current Annual Member of SSDOMG, the SSDOMG's standard event fee of $2.00 applies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Blue-Eyed Crab&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;70 Water Street, Plymouth, MA 02360&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;508-747-6776 &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:info@blue-eyedcrab.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://blue-eyedcrab.com/default.htm"&gt;The Blue-eyed Crab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/blue-eyed-crab-grille-and-raw-bar-plymouth"&gt;Yelp Reviews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer:&lt;/strong&gt; Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/strong&gt; None at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Range:&lt;/strong&gt; The Blue-eyed crab has a reputation for being on the pricey side, but it's much less so for lunch. An assortment of sandwiches range from $9.95 to $12.95. Have a look at the &lt;a href="http://blue-eyedcrab.com/menu.html"&gt;online menu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over five years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; No Event Fee for current Annual Members of SSDOMG. Other Meetup Members and Guests: $2.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Friday, June 8th at 7:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Points North of Plymouth:&lt;/strong&gt; From Route 3 South, take Exit 6A (Route 44 East). Head towards the waterfront, crossing Route 3A. At the small rotary, proceed 3/4 around and exit onto Water Street. Take your first left into the Village Landing Marketplace (This is also the driveway for the Radisson). Free parking is located in behind the shops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Cape Cod:&lt;/strong&gt; From Route 3 North, take Exit 6 (Route 44) and head East towards the waterfront, crossing Route 3A. At the small rotary, proceed 3/4 around and exit onto Water Street. Take your first left into the Village Landing Marketplace (This is also the driveway for the Radisson). Free parking is located in behind the shops.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339354645000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339020336000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don't it Make My Stalked Eyes Blue?</name><id>68058292</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339262100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/68058292/</event_url></item>