<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>KBED airport</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.469264</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Signature</name><city>Bedford </city><id>1425952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.289139</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I plan on going to this and have heard from several others as well. So, thought I'd put this on as a meet up. Please read the details to reserve a spot for both yourself and a plane if flying in..... We should leave early enough to get there, tie dow and get a seat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 "...Please join me for a pilot town hall gathering on Saturday, May 18, 2013 from &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30 am – 10:00 am at Signature Flight Support's Hangar 13 located on Hanscom Field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the national elections behind us, a new year ahead of us, and the economy just maybe starting to show some signs of growth, I am anxious to get out into the flying community and talk with those who are passionate about flying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout 2013, I'll visit major metropolitan areas and gather with fellow pilots and AOPA members to discuss the issues that most directly affect our freedom to fly. I will share my perspective on the current state of general aviation and AOPA's initiatives to grow the pilot population. I'll also bring you up to speed on AOPA's efforts in Washington, D.C., and key issues nationwide, on how we fight to protect airports, prevent tax hikes, and build the GA community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When aviators connect, great things happen. Together, we can generate new ways of thinking and make general aviation stronger. I'll be in your area soon, and I invite you to join me, and even bring a friend who's interested in aviation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Event Is Free, But Please Rsvp To Events@Aopa.Org So We Know To Expect You. Be Sure To Include Ma In The Subject Line If You Plan To Attend. If You Are Flying In, Aircraft Parking Is Available At Signature Flight Support. They Can Be Reached At 781-274-0010, Or Email Bed@Signatureflight.Com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, May 18, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30 am – 10:00 am &lt;br /&gt;

 Signature Flight Support &lt;br /&gt;

 Hangar 13 &lt;br /&gt;

 160 Hanscom Dr &lt;br /&gt;

 Hanscom Field &lt;br /&gt;

 Bedford, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can join me at Hanscom Field, I look forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Craig L. Fuller&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369079419000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365078110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Visit with AOPA President Craig Fuller at KBED</name><id>112630572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368876600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/112630572/</event_url></item>