<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please find some updates on this meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Knight and Day is at 6.30 PM and the Eclipse is playing at 7.10 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can meet at Fleming's bar area around 5.30 PM and people who would like to go for Knight and Day can go to the the theatre around 6.15 PM.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Eclipser's can hang out in Flemings further and go to the theatre around 7.00 PM. Feel free to meet us in the theatre around this time lines if you wish to come late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have also extended the RSVP time limit until tomorrow. Please do update your RSVP if you change your mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I liked Karen's idea of to have two different (really different) movies scheduled for the same time. So I am going to try something like that too. Here is some details about this meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update final details few days before the show: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can get together at Fleming's for a Happy Hour around 5.15 PM and head to the theater around 7.00 PM for either Eclipse or Knight &amp;amp; Day per our choice. We can also go out for dinner/drinks/deserts after the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please specify which movie you are interested in? You can also join only for the Happy Hour or the movie. Please specify your interest while RSVPying.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the detail for Flemings: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.flemingssteakhouse.com/locations/ct/west-hartford/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flemingsst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Hour Menu: &lt;a href="http://www.flemingssteakhouse.com/menu/FMG_menu_v18.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flemingsst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address: &lt;br /&gt;44 South Main Street&lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06107&lt;br /&gt;(860) 676-9463&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Knight &amp;amp; Day (Synopsis):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A fugitive couple (Tom Cruise and Cameron Diaz) wages a war between truth and trust while speeding across the globe in an attempt to avoid capture by a determined federal agent (Peter Sarsgaard). Paul Dano, Viola Davis, Olivier Martinez, Maggie Grace, and Marc Blucas co-star. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eclipse (Synopsis):&lt;br /&gt;In 'The Twilight Saga: Eclipse,' Bella once again finds herself surrounded by danger as Seattle is ravaged by a string of mysterious killings and a malicious vampire continues her quest for revenge. In the midst of it all, she is forced to choose between Edward and Jacob -- knowing that her decision has the potential to ignite the struggle between vampire and werewolf. With her graduation quickly approaching, Bella is confronted with the most important decision of her life.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will send details later.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287966152000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277660687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fleming's Happy Hour, Eclipse Or  Knight and Day</name><id>13926215</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278711000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/13926215/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/7/global_16007943.jpeg</photo_url></item>