<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Garden St &amp;  Mass Ave</address_2><address_1>Cambridge Common</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373318</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lincoln Monument</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1287574</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097603</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;A bi-weekly outdoors acoustic &amp;amp; low volume electric jam&lt;/b&gt;, with vocals, mini amps, woodwinds, light percussion welcome.  This meetup is at the Lincoln Monument in Cambridge Common.  The plan is to meet on the Cambridge Common Saturday mid afternoon, to faciltate both car and T riders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;All levels of musicians and all types of music are welcome&lt;/b&gt;, and we will generally rotate around the group for the next idea for a song, original or jam.   Interactive music and listening encouraged. Personal recorders could be a good thing to have if you come across inspiring stuff. Songwriting encouraged. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The Lincoln Monument is near the Center of the Cambridge Common basically straight across from the end of Appian Way.    We can sit on the stone benches and share guitar or other low volume instruments /voice styles.   After meeting &amp;amp; greeting, we can break into smaller groups of 3-4 people with similar instrumental interests, if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is not a performance, and is not in heavily traversed areas we believe no permit would be required.   This Meetup is common with other musician meetup groups.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If it rains we will move to Christ church next to Sharaton Commander across from the baseball field of the common.   On Mason street the left side of the church has an enclosed area under some arches.  We may move inside the church if possible.  There are also a number of other covered spaces in Harvard Sq. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My name is Bill.  Find Duncan or myself.  We are both 6'4".</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283093285000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279173364000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Common Outdoors Music Jam </name><id>fklbpynlblc</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283025600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/14521756/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/0/global_15459040.jpeg</photo_url></item>