<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Contra dancing is a wonderful way to make friends, enjoy great live music and just have fun - great fun! It requires no prior skills other than the ability to walk to music. You don't need to bring a partner - our custom is to change partners for each dance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The callers lead the dancers in a walk-through before the music starts, and continue to guide us as we begin dancing to the music. As a community, we range from young kids to active seniors, with a large group of energetic teens and twenties.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music we dance to has a similar heritage to the dances. Some tunes are traditional and others are contemporary, composed by the musicians that are playing that evening. We get a rich mix of artists playing live music, out of the French Canadian, Celtic (English, Scottish, Irish, etc.) and Scandinavian folk traditions, mixed through the blender of New England and other parts of the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who aren't familiar with contra dance, this introductory website will give you some idea about contra dance &lt;a href="http://www.sbcds.org/contradance/whatis/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sbcds.org/contradance/whatis/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sbcds.org/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;Scroll down to the bottom of the page, there is video clip about some basic elements of contra dance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, please join us for a Saturday night Contra Dance at Scout House in Concord MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: May 16th&lt;br /&gt;Time: 8PM to 11PM&lt;br /&gt;Price(cash only): $8, $5 teenagers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a pair of soft-soled shoes to protect the floor, no street shoes are allowed. But I have seen people danced in socks, barefoot, in tennis shoes or whatever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Casual dress is best. Loose, comfortable clothes that don't restrict movement will feel and look the best. Some women enjoy wearing skirts or dresses that twirl when they turn or spin. As for men, light slacks or shirts with t-shirts or lightweight dress shirts are popular choices. Some men like to dance in skirts, for the same reasons as women! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are plenty parking spaces available on Walden St., but don't use Church Parking lot or unmetered spaces on Walden St. There are also two public parking lots, one behind the bank of Boston across Walden St., one behind the post office and the stores on Walden St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Caller: Beth Parkes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The band: Full Tilt&lt;br /&gt;Carol Bittenson - fiddle&lt;br /&gt;Jim Guinness - flute/clarinet/saxophone&lt;br /&gt;Debby Knight - fiddle/piano&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a joint event with The Metro West 30's to 40's Singles Group and The Cambridge Single Parents group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will meet at the front entrance</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242955719000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241298262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Contra Dance</name><id>10321318</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242518400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10321318/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/d/8/global_8444776.jpeg</photo_url></item>