<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For those with Good Friday off, a 6.7 mile looping hike of moderate difficulty totally within the Paugusset State Forest. A portion of the hike will be along the Lake Zoar portion of the Housatonic River and then rise up onto the cliffs. You will be fortunate to see this section of trail as it will soon close on April 15th untill mid-August for the protection of nesting hawks. We'll also have an opportunity to check out Prydden Falls. We will be up to 550 feet above and overlooking the lake!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the parking area big enough for about 12 cars (carpooling is encouraged) at 9:30 AM. The hike would start from the trailhead off of the parking lot.  I estimate the hike taking about 4 - 6 hrs. depending on the group's speed. Please bring a trail lunch. We would finish at about 3:30 PM at the latest and head out to eat if people feel inclined.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions for parking area (12 cars) off Great Quarter Rd., Newtown, CT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/l=41.402412;g=-73.187653" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Lat=41.402412,Long=-73.187653)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map (rough, lower large blue loop. Parking area marked with &amp;quot;P&amp;quot; at lower-right): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.hikect.com/index.php?lat=41.409003&amp;amp;lng=-73.202076&amp;amp;zoom=14&amp;amp;type=p" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.hikect.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Trail information: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hikect.com/trails/Zoar_Trail" target="_blank"&gt;http://hikect.com/tra...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://sheltontrails.blogspot.com/2008/11/zoar-trail-newtown.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://sheltontrails....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one in Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1239633606000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237766289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Zoar Trail in Newtown CT</name><id>10011666</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239370200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10011666/</event_url></item>