<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2ND FLOOR</address_2><address_1>5 Pleasant Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.263517</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 736-0742</phone><name>EPOCA OFFICE</name><city>Worcester</city><id>669439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802325</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Prime [Lens] Sunday&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;9:00 am&lt;br /&gt;Sunday&lt;br /&gt;June 7, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Worcester Public Library Parking Lot&lt;br /&gt;Salem St, Worcester&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The idea of this meet-up is centered round users of cameras with interchangeable lenses. The idea is to spend some time shooting with one prime lens. That is, shoot with a single camera body with one fixed focal length lens for the morning.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is for that one body with that one prime lens mounted on it. I know the temptation will be great to pull out another lens or even (ack!) a zoom. It takes a bit of discipline to shoot with just one focal length and work with only that perspective. The return and reward for working with the restriction will be worth it. One learns to move the feet rather than the zoom. One figures out how to see with the lens rather then look around and bend the view with a zoom.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is not a zooms versus primes diatribe because both deserve their place &amp;quot;in the bag.&amp;quot; It's about technique and perspective. Learning to shoot with a prime definitely leads to a way to see photographically that many folks miss. And yes, at the beginning it can be frustrating, but I can assure you that if you stick with it the improvement of your photography is assured.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(Note we're not going to be strict here. If you don't own a prime lens we can bend the rules just a bit. You can always bring that zoom and gaffer tape it to a single position - just shoot without zooming. Also we do not care if its film or digital. And lastly for the crazies in the bunch, yes, you can use the 400mmm, Lensbaby or fisheye.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Let's see what you've got on warm late-Spring day!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245021902000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239737407000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot - Prime [Lens] Sunday</name><id>10184613</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244379600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10184613/</event_url></item>