<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Our Maltese Meet this month will take place on Sunday, November 6th.  We will meet again from 1pm to 4pm at Especially for Pets in Sudbury. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are presently contacting dog trainers to see if one of them would like to do a presentation about obedience/agility at our next Meet, possibly doing demos with our dogs.  If you know of a good candidate for this, please write me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you that have asked for a way to contact the Bardin family with condolences over the loss of their dog, Muffin, to a big-dog attack, you can email them at:  stbardin@msn.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And several people have asked where the attack took place.  It was near the Memorial Spalding School in Newton.  The dog in question was a German Shepherd who is not kept on a leash and who has mauled two other dogs and bitten numerous children.  For those of you that live in Newton,  we strongly suggest that you stay away from this location when walking your dog, until this matter gets resolved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regarding the Boston Maltese Meet that usually takes place in downtown Boston --- we are presently searching for a bigger space, and will announce another Meet when we locate one.  The staff at Doggie Day has been very helpful, going way out of their way to make us feel welcome there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on November 6.&lt;br /&gt;Maltese best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273539920000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1128276154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Maltese November Meetup</name><id>4775152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1131300000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/4775152/</event_url></item>