<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;he plan is to hike to Middle and South Carter as well as Carter Dome by following a loop that will take us up the Nineteen Mile Brook trail, and then up along the ridge following the Carter Moriah Trail and down by the North Carter and Imp trails. &amp;nbsp;We will shave about a mile off the route by taking an easy bushwhack and a short road walk at the end. &amp;nbsp;We will also have the option of extending our hike by heading for the .6 mile out and back to North Carter, thus completing a sweep of the Carters. &amp;nbsp;This will involve a steep ascent from the Carter Lakes to Carter Dome. &amp;nbsp;We will also visit Carter Notch Hut before ascending to Carter Dome, this gives us a chance to take a break and refill water bottles (thus allowing us to carry less at the start).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portions of the trip will be steep and and challenging. &amp;nbsp;There may be significant ice or snow left on the trail. &amp;nbsp;I recommend checking trail conditions prior to the trip to see if snowshoes or crampons may be needed. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elevation Gain: 4,700 feet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: &amp;nbsp;12.6 &amp;nbsp;miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book Time: 9:00 +/- b&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather forecast for middle Carter: &lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.302721485103355&amp;amp;lon=-71.1690902709961&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;smap=1&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text" class="linkified"&gt;http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.302721485103355&amp;amp;lon=-71.1690902709961&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;smap=1&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pace: Moderate. I start with the notion of doing the trip within an hour of book time (allowing for one long break and a number of smaller ones). I'm fine with going a faster, especially if late afternoon thundershowers are forecast or a little slower if that's the pace the group is comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you RSVP for this trip, you will be asked several questions. If you are RSVPing "no" please skip the questions. I will cancel the "yes" RSVPs of those who do not answer the questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description: This is challenging hike. We will be going above treeline, so you must come prepared for bad weather. Weather in the mountains is unpredictable. People have died from exposure hiking in the White Mountains in summer, so care and preparation are essential year round. Traction and snowshoes may be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Necessary equipment&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp;BE PREPARED FOR WINTER CONDITIONS]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Headlamp (or flashlight) with spare batteries, or a second headlamp/flashlight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Clothing: Layering will be important wool, synthetic or belnded shirt/pants - no jeans or cotton. Cotton does not insulate well when wet. Windy ridge conditions can compound this. Insulating layers will be essential&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Outerwear: Waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and something (even a fleece vest) to wear for extra insulation if needed. Rain or ski pants may be needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Food and Water: High-energy snacks and at least two quarts of water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Other Gear: Sunscreen (possibly insect repellent).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Trail hardy Footwear. See the winter hiking gear and preparation discussion on the message board for more informaiton and ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=the-10-essentials"&gt;http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=the-10-essentials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; &amp;nbsp;Any equipment or medication required to meet your medical needs in case of any foreseeable emergencies (e.g. an epi-pen if that is something you may need).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Anything else your experience, judgment or research tells you that you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more information&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;please look for the list of 10 essentials, other gear and the Hiker Responsibility Code at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Car Pooling&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; Lets save some gas money and shrink our carbon footprint! If you have a ride to offer or need a ride please post your needs or availability on your RSVP. Please note your interest in giving or getting a ride and contact hikers directly if their posts or profiles indicate it might be convenient to share rides with them. It looks like my car is close to full (I will be taking a dog and two other hikers), but could probably squeeze in another and I'll likely have more room for the return trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs&lt;/strong&gt;: Well behaved dogs are welcome, I'm bringing mine. Please mention your dog in your RSVP if you are bringing one. &amp;nbsp;I plan on limmiting dogs to three.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please allow plenty of time and let me know ASAP if you are running late as cell phone coverage is not reliable. Having been burned by no shows a few times, I will not keep people waiting unless I am sure you are coming.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MY DISCLAIMER: MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT. HOPEFULLY WE'LL ALL HAVE SOME FUN AND ENJOY A GREAT HIKE IN GOOD COMPANY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip is cross posted with the Boston Hiking Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be there with a shaggy black dog</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David (Ped Xing)</member_name><member_id>4566112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305720642000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304786594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Carters + Mt. Hight - Advanced</name><id>17579309</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305637200000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/17579309/</event_url></item>