<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At recent meetings, one feeling that's&amp;nbsp;been mentioned is&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Inertia&lt;/strong&gt;: not being able to break out from an accustomed pattern. Come learn how to cope with the doldrums associated with inertia and procrastination- to take control of life once more and head confidently in the direction that we ourselves choose, freed from as much unnecessary baggage as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Martin will join us again to share insights gleaned from neurolinguistic programming (NLP)- which I have been finding beneficial, along with many others in our Meetups this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin will share with us a fantastic new&amp;nbsp;strategy called&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;S.O.R.T.&lt;/strong&gt;, which&amp;nbsp;can be used to help&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;clean up the mental clutter&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;that is a source of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Inertia&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free also to come share your SUCCESSES in tackling Inertia - as well as to raise any other particular clutter-related challenges for which you seek solutions. Feel welcomed to post comments here, as well, about topics you would&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to see addressed in our upcoming meetings, along with information about subject-matter experts you know of who could perhaps shed light for us on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-And perhaps come away with a Decluttering Buddy to help you steer into the weeks ahead with a cleared living space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our new venue, Andala Coffee House,&amp;nbsp;is across Franklin Street from First Baptist Church at the intersection with River Street in the heart of Central Square, Cambridge ... here are photos, transit directions, and more information on Yelp:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/andala-coffee-house-cambridge"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/andala-coffee-house-cambridge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Andala, we will meet downstairs (if you have any questions about location, just ask Leo) in a quieter atmosphere than we've enjoyed before, with no background music piped in around us - much better suited to NLP demonstrations, it seems. &lt;em&gt;We'll find out for sure&lt;/em&gt;- and I am excited to do so!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to order refreshments, ALLOWING EXTRA TIME TO FIND PARKING, if needed, in or near Central Square. Parking in a lot is available ONLY&amp;nbsp;in City Lots 4, 5 , and 6 ("back of Central Sq.") off Norfolk Street &amp;amp; Bishop Allen Drive -- NOT in the private lot to the left of Harvest Co-op, i.e., off Essex Street, which is carefully monitored and ticketed ... meters in the city lots and on the streets around Central Square operate until 6 pm.&amp;nbsp;While no purchase minimum for refreshments is specified by our host venue, participants are encouraged to order something substantive to&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;support the business in appreciation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;of Management's permission to meet in their space. Please also be advised that commercial eating establishments generally cannot permit on-site consumption of refreshments brought from elsewhere, due to liability concerns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Approximate)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30 pm- Order dinner&amp;nbsp;or other&amp;nbsp;refreshment: ~$2 for coffee, tea, or soda (and upward) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:00 pm- Introduction to neurolinguistic programming (NLP)&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 pm- Roots of Inertia&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:30 pm&amp;ndash; NLP and possibly other therapeutic techniques described&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:45 pm - Demonstration(s) on volunteers, application to others' volunteered situations&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30 pm- Questions and Answers&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 8:45-9 pm- Wrap-up&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Notepad &amp;amp; pen or other note-taking device, calendar to schedule Action Items (next steps). Dress in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in case the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer) and comfortably, as Kevin sometimes has us do NLP/EFT physical exercises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OUR&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;VENUE WISH LIST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome suggestions for alternative Venues&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;especially quiet, preferably free-of-charge spaces under friendly, fairly flexible management, with ample free parking nearby and public transportation that runs on a frequent schedule until at least 9:30 pm (permitting participants to linger and converse after meetings). ...OR we could meet outside in a public park (with shelter nearby in case of rain) during warm weather, perhaps over a potluck dinner, since group members have said they especially like to be out in Nature- where we need not feel too responsible for how everything looks, and maintenance! (...I also read that a Travel Meetup group might meet in a restaurant at Logan Airport- interesting idea: such&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;relevance!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Might we do something similar?&amp;nbsp; I welcome ideas!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VIDEO PREVIEWS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Bandler: NLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S. Andreas: Compulsion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: EFT/procrastination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: Tapping&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hung by the Tongue: What You Say is What You Get&lt;/em&gt;, by Francis P. Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Biology of Belief: Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter, &amp;amp; Miracles&lt;/em&gt;, by Bruce H. Lipton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt;, by Richard Bandler&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;- &lt;strong&gt;EXCERPTS are provided&lt;/strong&gt; in previous Meetup descriptions, e.g., August 1, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLARIFICATION FROM KEVIN--&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Misconceptions&amp;nbsp;about hypnosis&amp;nbsp;abound- formed through TV, movies, and staged entertainment. The most prevalent misconception is that hypnosis is a form of mind control - that a hypnotist can make someone rob a bank or do terrible or absurd things. This is absolutely false! A hypnotist cannot make anyone do anything against their values. No one will do anything they would not normally do or that they have not wanted to do. Onstage, a hypnotist provides a 'safe' atmosphere for people to have fun and act on things they may not normally do socially; however, if they have never wanted to do some particular thing, they will not do so under hypnosis. In a clinical offfice session, people under hypnosis do only what they feel safe doing, and no more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hypnotist is only a guide; the person under hypnosis is actually doing the work by following suggestions. That is why we say that all hypnosis is self-hypnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another general misconception is that someone under hypnosis is sleeping. This is far from true: Most people are totally aware of what is happening around them, and can remember everything. Most&amp;nbsp;hypnosis&amp;nbsp;sessions are experienced as deep relaxation - approximating the state of awakening in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The $10-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal, preferably, or in cash to Judy Stitt at the event&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;before presentation begins&lt;/em&gt;, please) helps to compensate (1) the presenter for his time, training, and specialized knowledge so generously shared with us, and gasoline for travel into town, and (2) the organizer(s) for time spent planning, administering, and coordinating events, and interfacing with members as needed, e.g., answering questions and providing links with various people and resources - and to defray Meetup.com's monthly charge that is assessed organizers for this Web site and other resources to serve our group.) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will set a Meetup tent sign at our place (at least until the formal meeting begins at 7 pm)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316546912000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314706837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breaking Through Inertia</name><id>31531642</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316473200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/31531642/</event_url></item>