<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;As part of their annual Iranian Film Festival, the MFA is screening &lt;br /&gt;The Willow Tree by Majid Majidi (2005, 96 min.). In this existential drama by Academy Award--nominated director Majid Majidi (Children of Heaven, The Color of Paradise), a man is given the opportunity to regain his sight after forty years of blindness. Youssef (Parvis Parastui) is a renowned poetry scholar who enjoys a comfortable life and loving relationship with his wife and young daughter. A brush with illness brings him in touch with a Parisian doctor who is able to restore his sight. Returning to Iran, he becomes bitter at the life he now sees as having been stolen by blindness as he risks everything for experiences previously, and quite literally, unseen. Majidi creates extraordinary tableaux...elegant, spare, and at times, almost unbearable in its visual beauty and affective power. Director will receive the ninth annual ILEX Foundation Award for Excellence in Iranian Cinema. Tickets: $10, $12. MFA description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The filmmaker compels us to see in the dark, to recognize beauty in the absence of color and light.  Film Journal International&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A spiritual masterpiece on gratitude, transformation and surrender to God by the gifted Iranian filmmaker Majid Majidi. Rumi would love it!  Spirituality and Practice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.newsday.com/entertainment/movies/ny-etcaps5316601aug03,0,7765646.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newsday.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film and then its off to a local eatery to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195865321000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193095284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Willow Tree: The Iranian Film Festival at the MFA</name><id>6598126</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195260300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6598126/</event_url></item>