<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Union St.</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05255</zip><lat>43.162373</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Equinox Preserve</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1058463</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.079330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Eastern Mountain Sports (EMS) in Manchester, VT will be celebrating their 42nd anniversary by getting dirty outside! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are partnering with the Manchester office of the Vermont Institute of Natural Science (VINS) to help clean up the Equinox Preserve by removing invasive plant species.  Invasive plants such as shrubby honeysuckles, Japanese barberry and buck thorns have severely and negatively impacted the natural plant communities of the Equinox Preserve.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us as we help to “clean up” (remove) these  invaders and help restore the natural plant communities of the Preserve.  Our store in Manchester will be closed Tuesday, September 15th (till 2pm) while engaged in this important work. We are looking for volunteers to help give back to the outdoors. There will be giveaways, snacks and even some fun to be had!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Volunteers should bring work gloves, a shovel, water bottle, sturdy closed toed shoes, and most importantly a desire to make a beautiful area even better! Meet at the Red gate parking lot at the end of West Union St. Manchester, VT at 9:00 SHARP and expect to work ‘till 1pm. If you’d like to sign up, donate food or supplies, or have any questions please call EMS at 366-8082 or come in to the store. Come find out how much fun getting a little dirty can be!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Member Marge will be there.  Read the event for details</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253364867000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252331078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Get Dirty Outside!   Equinox Preserve</name><id>11308909</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253019600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11308909/</event_url></item>