<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374305</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-491-4340</phone><name>Burdick’s Chocolate Shop &amp; Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>724928</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122097</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Here's a special summer night adventure for #BIMM'ers into Mobile Marketing. 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/3250963246259337556533/img/smileys/cool.gif" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll have a series of teams check in at a few well known Harvard Square landmark locations, perform the necessary task and work our way to the final presentation spot at Tavern on the Square at 7:30 pm (Porter Square) where we'll Join authors Aaron Strout and Mike Schneider as they explore this most social of all media, and its effect on social groups, businesses, and messaging now and in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 'crawl' is an Invitation only event and is limited to the first 8 BIMM'ers who can ACTUALLY make it! Your team will be counting on you to come thru -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;*You must have a mobile friendly 'smart phone' that can handle Foursquare, etc.&amp;nbsp; Wear COMFORTABLE shoes as we'll be walking &amp;amp; you may need to hop on the T.&amp;nbsp; Make sure your mobile batteries are FULLY CHARGED too! (We all know how quick they lose power)&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a few $$ for food, drink, T fare, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a free event but be prepared to spend a $$ or 2 along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the password protected signup link:
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/1828335601" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.eventbrite.com/event/1828335601&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Password = checkin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The AMA Boston CheckInVitational is an invitation-only event. Join teams of marketers and digital professionals from around Boston as we compete in teams, completing mobile challenges. We will meet at Burdick's in Harvard Square at 6pm to start. Come join your friends for an evening of fun and learning--followed by a Q&amp;amp;A session with mobile and location-based marketing experts Aaron Strout and Mike Schneider.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;By registering for this event, you agree that neither AMA Boston, the Boston Internet Marketing Meetup nor any of the organizers or participants of this event are liable for any consequences arising out of your participation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;******************************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PRESENTATION DETAILS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Foursquare reaches its 10 millionth user, consumers, marketers and small business owners are still struggling to find the value in location-based services. The potential is great, but how to unlock this potential to reach consumers effectively at the point of purchase, event participation, or during everyday activities? Location-based services raise the potential of marketing to consumers in much less intrusive way than many other channels, including most other forms of social media. You can provide immediately relevant messages and offers to customers when they are near your venue, help museum and other cultural attraction visitors gain better insight into what they're seeing, and promote events in real time. For individuals, location-based services provide the opportunity to select the messages they receive from vendors, yes, but also socialize in entirely new ways that are both more intentional and more spontaneous. Join authors Aaron Strout and Mike Schneider as they explore this most social of all media, and its effect on social groups, businesses, and messaging now and in the future.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;This tweetup is also the endpoint of the CheckInVitational, an invitation-only scavenger hunt around Harvard Square from 6-7pm for teams made up of marketing departments, agencies, and independent marketers.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Where: Tavern on the Square, Porter Square, back room
 &lt;br /&gt;When: 7:30-9:30pm
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Hashtag: #amabtu, #BIMM&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at Burdicks in Harvard Square at 6pm to start (next to the perfume store)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lew</member_name><member_id>10673992</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310568718000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309960574000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Mobile Crawl of Harvard Square - The CheckInvitational</name><id>24739331</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310076000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/24739331/</event_url></item>