<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Mountain Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06032</zip><lat>41.721367</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.677.4787</phone><name>Hill-Stead Museum</name><city>Farmington</city><id>664278</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.827520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;SUNKEN GARDEN POETRY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Music by Brass City Brass begins 6:15&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;poet Donald Hall begins reading at 7:30 pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$5.00 admission per person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;come and picnic in the garden with us, there is also food and beverage,wine and beer available for purchase.....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;I will be there around 6:30&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Donald Hall&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;"Hall has long been placed in the Frostian tradition of the plainspoken rural poet. His poems... [are imbued] with a tone of sincere authority." — Billy Collins&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Poetry Prelude:&lt;/strong&gt; Talk on Donald Hall by Michael Cervas &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The fourteenth United States Poet Laureate from 2006–2007, &lt;strong&gt;Donald Hall&lt;/strong&gt;was born in New Haven, Connecticut, in 1928. He received his bachelor's degree from Harvard in 1951, and in 1953 his &lt;img src="http://www.hillstead.org/images/activities/poet_hall.jpg" alt="Donald Hall" width="100" height="120" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;bachelor's in literature from Oxford University. For the past thirty years he has lived on Eagle Pond Farm in rural New Hampshire, in the house where his grandmother and mother were born. He was married for twenty-three years to the poet Jane Kenyon, who died in 1995. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Hall has published sixteen books of poetry, beginning with &lt;em&gt;Exiles and Marriages&lt;/em&gt; in 1955. In 2008, his memoir &lt;em&gt;Unpacking the Boxes: The Life of a Poet&lt;/em&gt; was published. Among his books for children, &lt;em&gt;Ox-Cart Man&lt;/em&gt; won the Caldecott Medal. His twenty books of prose include &lt;em&gt;Willow Temple: New and Selected Stories&lt;/em&gt; (2003), &lt;em&gt;The Best Day the Worst Day: Life with Jane Kenyon&lt;/em&gt; (2005), and a collection of his essays about poetry, &lt;em&gt;Breakfast Served Any Time All Day&lt;/em&gt;. He has written extensively about life in New Hampshire in his memoirs &lt;em&gt;Seasons at Eagle Pond&lt;/em&gt; (1987), &lt;em&gt;Here at Eagle Pond&lt;/em&gt; (2000), and &lt;em&gt;Eagle Pond&lt;/em&gt; (2007). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For his poetry, Donald Hall received the Marshall/Nation Award in 1987 for &lt;em&gt;The Happy Man&lt;/em&gt;; both the National Book Critics Circle Award and the Los Angeles Times Book Award in 1988 for &lt;em&gt;The One Day&lt;/em&gt;; the Lily Prize for Poetry in 1994; two Guggenheim Fellowships; and a National Medal of Arts. He is a member of the American Academy of Arts and Letters. &lt;span&gt;Photo by Mark S. Simon.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.hillstead.org/images/activities/music_brass.jpg" alt="Brass City Brass" width="200" height="130" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Brass City Brass&lt;/strong&gt; is a quintet of great musical virtuosity and wide ranging knowledge. Their collective playing experience covers the entire spectrum of musical periods and genres and they bring to every performance those unique insights that make their concerts informed, exciting and completely engrossing. Members of Brass City Brass include Joel Winter on French horn and Wagner tuba; Harold Zinno on trumpet and flugelhorn; Ken Andresen on trombone and euphonium; Ernie Adams on bass trombone and euphonium; and Ryan Storms on trumpet and flugelhorn. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The &lt;strong&gt;gates open&lt;/strong&gt; at 4:30 pm. Pre-performance &lt;strong&gt;Preludes lecture series&lt;/strong&gt; takes place 5–5:45 in the Makeshift Theater. &lt;strong&gt;Music begins&lt;/strong&gt; at 6:15 pm; &lt;strong&gt;poetry begins&lt;/strong&gt; at 7:30 pm. Attendees may bring their own &lt;strong&gt;food&lt;/strong&gt; or purchase on site (sandwiches, wraps, salads and beverages), from &lt;strong&gt;The Epicurean Caterers&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.theepicureancaterers.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.theepicureancaterers.com&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;strong&gt;Attendance&lt;/strong&gt; to the Festival is $5 per person, free ages 12 and under. On-site &lt;strong&gt;parking&lt;/strong&gt; is FREE. Bring a blanket or lawn chair for &lt;strong&gt;seating&lt;/strong&gt; in and around the garden. In case of &lt;strong&gt;rain&lt;/strong&gt;, performances will be held indoors or under a tent. &lt;br /&gt;

Find more detail at &lt;a href="http://sunkengardenpoetry.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Sunken Garden Poetry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for the black and white balloons</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343445316000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339855087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SUNKEN GARDEN POETRY</name><id>69430512</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343255400000</time><rsvp_limit>36</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/69430512/</event_url></item>