<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/f/6/event_163823542.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Man in the Woods by Scott Spencer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most acclaimed modern American novelists, Scott Spencer captures the intensity of human passion—and its capacity to both destroy and redeem—with unparalleled precision and insight. Now, in his most stunning novel yet, this wry, witty, and deeply sensitive writer returns to the territory of his New York Times bestseller A Ship Made of Paper, in a gripping and provocative psychological thriller of morality and manhood, choice and fate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul has been on his own since he was a teenager, leading a life of freedom and independence, beholden to no one and nothing. Fearless, resolute, and guided by his own private moral code, he has hunted for food in Alaska, fought forest fires, and been deputized in a manhunt for a kidnapper in South Dakota. Once he thought his life would have no particular rhyme or reason, touched only by transient strangers. Then he meets the beautiful, intelligent, loving Kate Ellis and her daughter, Ruby, who offer order and constancy. But Paul is a man of deep convictions, and the compromises we all make to get along in the world elude him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On his way home after rejecting a job remodeling a luxurious Manhattan apartment, Paul stops to gather his thoughts at a state park just off the highway. Instead of peace, he finds a man savagely beating a dog, and in a few fateful moments Paul is plunged into a world of violence and onto a tumultuous journey of self-knowledge, guilt, and redemption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the psychological acuity and razor-sharp prose for which he has been celebrated, award-winning, bestselling novelist Scott Spencer once again takes us on an unforgettable journey of manhood lost and found.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Steve&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Night Circus by Erin Morgenstern&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The circus arrives without warning. No announcements precede it. It is simply there, when yesterday it was not. Within the black-and-white striped canvas tents is an utterly unique experience full of breathtaking amazements. It is called Le Cirque des Rêves, and it is only open at night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But behind the scenes, a fierce competition is underway—a duel between two young magicians, Celia and Marco, who have been trained since childhood expressly for this purpose by their mercurial instructors. Unbeknownst to them, this is a game in which only one can be left standing, and the circus is but the stage for a remarkable battle of imagination and will. Despite themselves, however, Celia and Marco tumble headfirst into love—a deep, magical love that makes the lights flicker and the room grow warm whenever they so much as brush hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True love or not, the game must play out, and the fates of everyone involved, from the cast of extraordinary circus performers to the patrons, hang in the balance, suspended as precariously as the daring acrobats overhead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Written in rich, seductive prose, this spell-casting novel is a feast for the senses and the heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Cathy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve</member_name><member_id>2742447</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sara</member_name><member_id>6494254</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy</member_name><member_id>25472152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352256338000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344301898000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October's Discussion: Man in the Woods &amp; The Night Circus</name><id>76643892</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352244600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/76643892/</event_url></item>