<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>179 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.375713</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charlestown Branch Library</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>12260862</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064407</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Friends of the Charlestown Branch Library&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Boston Organics&lt;/strong&gt; present &lt;strong&gt;“Forks Over Knives”&lt;/strong&gt; : film screening followed by a discussion moderated by &lt;strong&gt;Amy Levine&lt;/strong&gt; of Boston Organics and a reception&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Thursday&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;, March 14, 7:30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;pm. Charlestown Branch Library, 179 Main Street, Charlestown. Free and open to everyone. Wheelchair accessible. For more information: 617-242-1248, &lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/branches/charlestown.htm"&gt;www.bpl.org/branches/charlestown.htm&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Charlestown-based &lt;strong&gt;Boston Organics&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;Friends of the Charlestown Branch Library&lt;/strong&gt; join together in presenting the eye-opening film &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Forks Over Knives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; that could very well &lt;em&gt;“save your life,”&lt;/em&gt; according to renowned film critic Roger Ebert. The feature film examines the profound claim that most, if not all, of the degenerative diseases that afflict us can be controlled, or even reversed, by rejecting animal-based and processed foods. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 What has happened to us? Despite the most advanced medical technology in the world, we are sicker than ever by nearly every measure. Two out of every three of us are overweight. Cases of diabetes are exploding, especially amongst our younger population. About half of us are taking at least one prescription drug. Major medical operations have become routine, helping to drive health care costs to astronomical levels. Heart disease, cancer and stroke are the country’s three leading causes of death, even though billions are spent each year to “battle” these very conditions. Millions suffer from a host of other degenerative diseases. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Throughout the film, the idea of food as medicine is put to the test. The cameras follow patients who have chronic conditions from heart disease to diabetes. Doctors teach these patients how to adopt a whole-foods plant-based diet as the primary approach to treat their ailments — while the challenges and triumphs of their journeys are revealed. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Forks Over Knives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;, f&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;ilmed all over the US, Canada and China&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;and released in 2011,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; utilizes state of the art 3-D graphics and rare archival footage. The film features leading experts on health, examines the question &lt;em&gt;“why we don’t know,”&lt;/em&gt; and tackles the issue of diet and disease in a way that will have people talking for years. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Further background information on the presenters&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Boston Organics&lt;/strong&gt;, located in Charlestown, provides access to fresh, organic produce to promote and support healthy living in a mindful and sustainable way that respects the environment, supports local farms, local businesses, and fair-trade practices. In 2011, Boston Organics received the &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sustainable Food Leadership Award&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; from Mayor Menino and the City of Boston. &lt;a href="http://www.bostonorganics.com"&gt;www.bostonorganics.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The &lt;strong&gt;Friends of the Charlestown Branch Library&lt;/strong&gt; was formed in 1953, becoming the second Friends group to organize within the Boston Public Library system. The Friends schedule four to six evening programs a year, support the Reading is FUNdamental programs for children, and maintain the library’s landscaping. The mission of the Friends remains today what it was in 1953: to serve as an advocacy and support group for the needs of the Charlestown Branch Library, its staff and users. &lt;a href="http://www.charlestownonline.net/libraries.htm"&gt;www.charlestownonline.net/libraries.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0053ZHZI2/ref=as_li_tf_il?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0053ZHZI2&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=essway-20" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://ws.assoc-amazon.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;ASIN=B0053ZHZI2&amp;amp;Format=_SL110_&amp;amp;ID=AsinImage&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;WS=1&amp;amp;tag=essway-20" alt="FOKDVD" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1615190619/ref=as_li_tf_il?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=1615190619&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=essway-20" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://ws.assoc-amazon.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;ASIN=1615190619&amp;amp;Format=_SL110_&amp;amp;ID=AsinImage&amp;amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;amp;ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;amp;WS=1&amp;amp;tag=essway-20" alt="FOK Recipes" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</member_name><member_id>55605982</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363315497000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363273963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Forks Over Knives" FREE Film</name><id>109237202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363303800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/109237202/</event_url></item>