<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.407043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-1499</phone><name>Together in Motion</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.133880</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Noah Gross is coming from Israel and will do a free workshop on ACT.  He describes it as follows:&lt;br /&gt;This one for an in depth explanation of what ACT is and is about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.akban.org/wiki/index.php/ACT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.akban.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; and this one for more pictures of knife and bolo fighting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=9825212996" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the world of martial arts the concept of MMA ? mixed martial arts, has become accepted and widely practiced. The reasons for this are many. One of the central reasons is the wide exposure we have in this modern age to so many different martial arts and the quest for practicality in our endeavor as martial artists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Within the wide range of martial arts systems practiced world wide there are two distinct categories, styles which teach and practice fighting unarmed and those which teach and practice fighting with weapons. Within the realm of weapons based systems there is a growing trend born of desire to explore our skill with weapons in a practical manor. The application of developed skill with weapons in sparring is a clear growing trend. ACT is the result of ten years of exploration of combat with weapons in sparring.&lt;br /&gt;The main emphasis in ACT is full strength non sportive fighting with as few rules as possible. This makes the practice fighting and sparring very realistic. ACT practitioners use a wide range of accurate practice weapons that imitate the weight, feel and build of historical weapons. Both edged and staff weapons are taught. Unique weapon simulators are produced by ACT under advisement of collectors and historians). All drills are based on collective experience of system practitioners, derived from combat situations. Essentially ACT is bringing weapons to the world of MMA and MMA competition. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The system combat style is comprised both from studying the traditional martial arts and from the personal interpretation of ACT practitioners of the techniques learned. A modern approach of introspective debriefing is used to establish ?what works?. Every technique is combat tested and every technique that worked in combat is analyzed to understand why and how it worked and what the optimal conditions to recreate the success are. ACT - Armed Combat and Tactics is an open style of fighting, a martial art school and a platform for full contact weapon sparring open to all practitioners of any combat system dealing with weapons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ACT is an ongoing process of trials, mutual airing of perspectives and effective full strength sparring. The ACT system is the creation of Alex Zhelezniak, a Russian émigré that resides in Israel. The group that started in the 1990's attracted a large student base of adult veterans from many martial arts. Today we have many members who are practitioners of various martial arts many of them being instructors in their own respective styles. We enjoy cross training and cooperating with many styles and teachers in Israel and abroad.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erik K.</member_name><member_id>4200552</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210377715000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Martial Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>martial-221</urlname><id>502152</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>The Arlington Martial Arts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209429202000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ACT sportive fighting with weapons workshop</name><id>7831587</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210204800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/martial-221/events/7831587/</event_url></item>