<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Southbridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.261272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>877-571-7469</phone><name>Hanover Theatre</name><city>Worcester</city><id>840605</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.803322</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for somehting photo related to do on a Wed night? Check this opening out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Franklin Square Society Salon Gallery at the Hanover Theatre for Performing Arts (Worcester, MA) – Double Exposure, an exhibition by Peter Wise and Catherine Wilcox-Titus, opens March 20, 2013 and will run through June 24, 2013. Working in photography and photomontage, they have created images in dialog with each other that are inspired by the theatricality of early 20th century movies. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 In the photographs by Dr. Wilcox, “streets and storefronts are seen as theatrical sets. Mannequins and objects in wi&lt;/span&gt;ndow displays are filled with dramatic potential.” Peter Wise’s technique draws from film production, and “mimes the language of film with photo stills, jump cuts, and arrangements that suggest the editing process of film.” The results of both approaches are unexpectedly eerie and provocative. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An opening reception will take place at the Franklin Square Society Gallery at the Hanover Theatre on Wednesday March 20, from 6-8 PM. This event is free and open to the public. To see the exhibit after the opening, an appointment with the artist is required, for more information, contact ArtsWorcester at 508-755-5142 or info@artsworcester.org. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Images: &lt;br /&gt;

 Romance of the Telescope (detail) by Peter Wise &lt;br /&gt;

 Enigma of the Green Dress (detail) by Catherine Wilcox-Titus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363828813000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363709743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photography Opening reception at the Hanover Theater</name><id>110005922</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363816800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/110005922/</event_url></item>