<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So it's been too long since our last event!  Nightlife has not been forgotten, instead my father's ill and I've been in and out of town for the past several months.  Things are now settling down and this should be a great event, especially for those new to Meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biagio (with Social Fun) loved how many of us came out to and livened up the party last time, so he's reached out to us again.   We're hosting another Mix and Mingle party for 160+ Meetup members. This is not a Singles Party, so couples are welcome.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've got a max of 40 rsvp's, so only rsvp yes if you know you can come.  Be warned that spaces will fill up fast — last time, the event was 95% full in the first several hours of posting.  I cannot up the rsvp limit, so please be kind to other members who may want to go by only signing up if you are 100% positive you will use the spots you reserve.  I will not leave a maybe option and waitlisted people will move up automatically.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty OSheas is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100 Website:&lt;a href="http://www.kittyosheasboston.com/home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Kitty O'Sheas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2nd floor holds 160 people. There are 2 bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, DJ area and dance floor, plus bathrooms,  so we'll we separate from the rest of the bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Music will remain at medium levels in main room upstairs for dancing and  low in the back room for chatting.&lt;br /&gt;At 9PM  the dancing starts, and the main room will get loud. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 Bartenders upstairs: 2 at the front Bar and 1 in the back .&lt;br /&gt;Biagio has  ordered and paid for over $200 worth of appetizers (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) because their Kitchen is too small and we will never get enough food for 160 members. The bar will refill any appetizers platters once.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Important: After you get inside the Security post at the stairs, please tell them you are here for the Social Fun party.   If you say ANY other group they will not let you in.  We had a few issues with this last time and Security did not let some people in, because they could not remember to say they were with Social Fun.  Biagio is the one who has been dealing with the bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;When you get inside: Please introduce yourself to me, and I'll help you find Biagio and collect the money. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;The $5 covers the cost to rent  the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders +the DJ so its not all just to cover the food. Please find Biagio at the party and  give Biagio the $5. Avoid $1 bills.  Please have $5 in hand at the top of the stairs, so the lines will move quickly.  We cannot block the stairs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. After 9PM you will have to pay another $10 as cover for the Bar Entrance,  $15 total. $10 to bar and $5 to cover the cost to rent the 2nd floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. If you get in before 9PM you ONLY have to pay $5 to Biagio to cover the cost to rent. Hint Hint: Make sure you get there early!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. It will be have a couple hundred of people throughout the night.  Get there early, lines will form later in the night&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;4. If you come after 7:30PM you might not even get in right away and you will have to wait in line downstairs to go upstairs. So come at 7PM to get in. Last time late comers had to wait over half an hour to get in! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. They will not let you upstairs till 7PM so please wait downstairs till 7PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Tell Security you are with Social Fun to get in -even if you are with a different group. Again if you say ANY other group they will not let you in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;The 5 Meetup Groups that are invited to come:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Social Fun &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Biagio)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Happy Hour &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meet.."&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt;. (Yet to be Confirmed by Tonya)&lt;br /&gt;    * Girls just want to have FUN Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Sarah)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.co.."&gt;http://euro.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Noelle)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Night Life Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Rebecca)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had over 175 members at last Mix and Mingle party.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Nightlife Group members came out in force last time, let's do it again!  For those of you I know, I can't wait to see you again.  For those of you I haven't yet met, please make sure to introduce yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there :)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE, TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll most likely be in the front room.  My picture is posted.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6966003</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266192836000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>52</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263929652000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Mix and Mingle Mega Meetup Event (5 groups attending)</name><id>12364234</id><headcount>52</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266019200000</time><rsvp_limit>52</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/12364234/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/c/global_11309676.jpeg</photo_url></item>