<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;HI All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Lauren &amp;amp; Chris will be our discussion leaders this time!!! WOOT!!!!!!! WOOT!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;here are the specifics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Date: Sept 7, 2011 (Aug seems to be the month that everyone is moving)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: Life Alive (Unless otherwise noted)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book Selection:&amp;nbsp;Everything Beautiful Began After, by Simon Van Booy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A young girl walks in the woods alone. She knows the basic details of how she came to be, but longs to know more of who her father was before she existed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On the walk back home through the dusk, she&amp;rsquo;s going to ask her father for the story of how he met her mother.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;All she knows is that someone fell, and that everything beautiful began after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rebecca is an artist from France who is living in Athens. She meets George, an American, and while he&amp;rsquo;s in love with her, she can&amp;rsquo;t return his affection. Instead she falls in love with Henry, an archeologist working on a dig site outside of Athens. Through a coincidence, Henry runs into George &amp;ndash; literally &amp;ndash; and the three of them form an unlikely friendship. Rebecca, George and Henry are each fighting their own personal demons &amp;ndash; being abandoned by a mother, alcoholism, the guilt of causing the accidental death of a baby brother. Then tragedy strikes when an earthquake levels Athens and Henry must find a way to cope with losing the love of his life. He spends 2 years flying around the world, spending little time in one place, until he ends up back in Athens and must confront his past in order to move on with his life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0061661481/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=talannet&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=217145&amp;amp;creative=399373&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0061661481"&gt;Everything Beautiful Begins After&lt;/a&gt; is written in an unusual style and tone. Sentence fragments and staggered phrasing make the prose a challenge to follow at times, and may turn off some readers. While the first half of the book is told in the third person, mixed in with flashbacks, it switches to second person while Henry learns to deal with his loss. The final portion switches back to third person, signifying Henry having moved on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0061661481/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=talannet&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=217145&amp;amp;creative=399373&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0061661481"&gt;Everything Beautiful Begins After&lt;/a&gt; is haunting and beautiful, with surprises thrown in that make you question what you thought you knew. Simon Van Booy is an author that&amp;rsquo;s not to be missed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paras Hezar</member_name><member_id>12400154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315943811000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311973826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Book Club Meetup - Everything Beautiful Began After, by Simon Van Booy</name><id>27532981</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315436400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/27532981/</event_url></item>