<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.378188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.495.3045 </phone><name>Harvard Museum of Natural History, Geological Lecture Hall </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>845303</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116422</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Six Years on Mars&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/lectures_and_special_events/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lecture by Andrew Knoll &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price&lt;/b&gt;: FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thursday, December 10, 6:00 PM&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Harvard biologist Andrew Knoll hasn’t actually been to Mars, but he has spent a lot of time examining its rocks, including four-billion-year-old salt deposits investigated by the rovers Spirit and Opportunity. Knoll will reflect on six years of NASA Mars Rover exploration; what the evidence tells us about the history of water and its implication for life on the ancient surface of the Red Planet. Intended audience is teens and older. Free and open to the public in the Geological Lecture Hall, 24 Oxford Street&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be inside the lecture hall and will be saving seats for the group at around 5:40 pm. Feel free to sign up at the last second before 4:00 pm on December 10th, or drop out before then, but if you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;, please show up. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and he will place red MEETUP signs on chairs to save seats. T.J. needs to know beforehand how many people will truly be coming and how many seats he needs to save. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... we can wander around the Museum for a bit after the lecture, and then grab dinner in Harvard Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Harvard Museum of Natural History's Night at the Museum program&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/lectures_and_special_events/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Thursday, December 10, 5:00 - 8:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Free admission from 5:00 to 8:00 pm. Check out  the newly restored Great Mammal Hall and visit the Evolution and Language of Color exhibitions. Take 20% off your purchase at the Museum Shop (not to be combined with other discounts.)&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Andrew Knoll:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Andrew_H._Knoll" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Andrew H. Knoll (born 1951) is the Fisher Professor of Natural History and a Professor of Earth and Planetary Sciences at Harvard University. He is best known for his work on Precambrian microfossils and using stable isotopes for stratigraphic correlation, but has longstanding interests in geobiology, paleobotany, and the planetary evolution of Mars. He is a member of the Organismic and Evolutionary Biology and Earth and Planetary Sciences faculty at Harvard and the National Academy of Sciences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Knoll was born in West Reading, Pennsylvania in 1951 and graduated from Lehigh University with a bachelor of arts in 1973. He received his Ph.D. from Harvard University in 1977 for a dissertation entitled 'Studies in Archean and Early Proterozoic Paleontology.' Knoll taught at Oberlin College for five years before returning to Harvard as a professor in 1982&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... it appears he wrote a paper about Mars, according to Wikepedia: &amp;quot;Tosca, N.J., Knoll, A.H., McLennan, S.M. (2008) Water activity and the challenge for life on early Mars. Science 320: 1204-1207&amp;quot;. Darn. Seems like you need to pay to read this article. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Andrew Knoll's website&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.oeb.harvard.edu/faculty/knoll/knoll-oeb.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.oeb.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map from Harvard Square&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/images/stories/hmnh_map.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Waiting inside the lecture hall saving seats with red MEETUP table tents.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260659049000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257188344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Andrew Knoll, "Six Years on Mars" @ Harvard Museum of Natural History</name><id>11772314</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260486000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11772314/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/c/global_11608700.jpeg</photo_url></item>