<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>88 Sleeper Street</address_2><address_1>Fort Point Landing</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.326100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-426-CRAB</phone><name>The Barking Crab</name><city>Boston</city><id>757830</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Web site: barkingcrab.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer's officially over, but we can still squeeze out one last harborside feast before autumn hits! Join us at the Barking Crab, and enjoy a relaxed dining experience with friends among the rustic picnic-table-and-wooden-bench setup. Boston magazine gave it a &amp;quot;Best of Boston&amp;quot; award, deeming their fried clams &amp;quot;exceptional.&amp;quot; Ocean breezes abound, so bring a sweater or jacket if you're easily chilled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;, please be 100% certain you are able to attend: a credit card number was required to hold our reservation. &lt;u&gt;Avoid a NO-SHOW incident by keeping your RSVP accurate...update it as soon as you find you're not able to attend.&lt;/u&gt; Please read our &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Member Guidelines&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; below for more information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;~ ADDITIONAL INFO ~&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Neighborhood: Seaport/Fan Pier district. Landmarks: Moakley Courthouse, Northern Avenue bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Menu and Directions: Visit www.barkingcrab.com. Nearest MBTA stops are the Silver Line &amp;quot;Courthouse Station&amp;quot; stop; the Red Line at South Station; or the Blue Line &amp;quot;Aquarium&amp;quot; stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Parking: Meters on adjacent Seaport Blvd. are free on Sundays. There are also several $12 &amp;quot;All Day&amp;quot; parking lots surrounding the courthouse on Northern Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; If you're planning on ordering alcoholic beverages, please heed the restaurant's online recommendation to &amp;quot;Bring your ID: We're serious about carding.&amp;quot;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following &lt;b&gt;MEMBER GUIDELINES&lt;/b&gt; were developed so our events run smoothly:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while &lt;br /&gt;sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow foodies' time by arriving promptly so that we can be seated together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO &lt;br /&gt;with a comment to be placed on the wait list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES afterward and you have not attended, it will count as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours, without an explanation, it will count as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, to those on the wait list, to the organizer, as well as the restaurant, whose staffing and seating plan are based on the size of our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;If it is less than twenty-four hours from the event and you are not able to attend, you MUST call or text Tonya at (617) 445-7549.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO, is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're removed and have extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so rate the event by completing the survey afterward.&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet outside. If you're late, ask for the Brunch Meetup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222789026000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220916234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch at The Barking Crab</name><id>8717208</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222615800000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/8717208/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/0/global_5449568.jpeg</photo_url></item>