<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have been Excorsized...The Devil has left me...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i need to replace that &amp;quot;green stuff&amp;quot; with some real food...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes from Linda Karen (asst. organizer):  Devils Hopyard is a great place for hiking, and picnicking.  So let's get together for a picnic and to see the great &amp;quot;geological&amp;quot; features, as Al puts it.  A place to dip your hot toes and a place to rid yourself of past demons!  Many of us had already talked about casting our old woes into the fire here at the Devil's Oven. So if you want to bring old photos of your ex-boy/girl friends/spouses, other things (like old wedding dresses, pics of your ex in-laws) bring them.  This will be a fun event.  Please bring some food to share with the word &amp;quot;devil&amp;quot; in it: dogs, cake, etc.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To those who were freaked out by Al's last description, lighten up!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From CT Route 9: take Exit 7, (=rte 82) then a left at the end of the exit ramp onto CT Route 154 north. Take a right at the first traffic light and follow the signs. You keep a bit to the right of the intersection go up the hill. at the top. take a quick right and left onto rte 434 = Mount Prnassus rd.&lt;br /&gt;Follow 434 to the name change of Hopyard road..pass foxtown road go down hill to entrance on left?&lt;br /&gt;Look for car with cone on roof and cones by picknick table in view of the covered bridge..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 395: take Exit 80 west. Take a right onto CT Route 82 west. Take a right onto Hopyard Road and follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;From I-91S: take Exit 22. Take Route 9S, Exit 10. Take Route 9AS to Tylerville. Take Route 82E over CT River for about 3 miles. At the stop sign take a right, and then take immediate left. Follow that road for approximately 8 miles, then follow the signs.&lt;br /&gt;This is the more scenic route to the Oprah house?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Gps, mapquest, others, use 375 Hopyard Road, East Haddam, ct 06432 to get you close enough?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the normal case..The environmental police patrol the park so the burning has to be finely tuned..one thing at a time?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187113104000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186416551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Nice Little Picknick at Devils Hopyard</name><id>6133495</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186939800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6133495/</event_url></item>