<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Lexington Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.460152</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish In Concord</name><city>Concord</city><id>1591498</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333300 ; font-size : small"&gt;The Reverence for Life Program at First Parish Church in Concord presents "A Delicate Balance". &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333300 ; font-size : small"&gt;There will be a discussion following the film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Documentary will leave each person fully informed as to some of the causes these illnesses and offers ways of improving human health. This documentary predominantly explores the effects of animal protein on the human body and the environment. &lt;em&gt;Written by &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/search/title?plot_author=Aaron%20Scheibner&amp;amp;view=simple&amp;amp;sort=alpha"&gt;Aaron Scheibner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every person today has been touched or will be touched by the loss of a loved one to illness and premature death. In a time when modern medicine and science have made such enormous advancements, why is this so? The film identifies the effects of animal agriculture upon the environment. There are many ways of reducing impact upon climate change. "Livestock are responsible for about 18 percent of the global warming effect, more than transportation's contribution." "At present, there are about 1.5 billion cattle and domestic buffalo and about 1.7 billion sheep and goats. With pigs and poultry, they form a critical part of our enormous biological footprint upon this planet. Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations Through interviews with top experts in the field of medicine, ecology and nutrition, this documentary explains why people in the Western World are subject to the unprecedented epidemic of ill health. The film shows a way out of this cycle of sickness, both human and environmental. We don't think about where our food comes from and what it does to our body and mind or what impact it has on the world around us. 'A Delicate Balance -The Truth' is a succinct production featuring candid, heartfelt interviews with some of the world's leading experts (including mainstream researchers, doctors, nutritionists, cattle ranchers, environmentalists and politicians) from Harvard to Cornell to Tufts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Delicate Balance was made in order to help reduce the unnecessary loss of human life, to reduce the suffering of animals across the planet and to help empower people to make environmental change.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365351159000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364083038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie and Discussion: "A Delicate Balance"</name><id>110725602</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365345000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/110725602/</event_url></item>