<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>130 Dartmouth St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.346551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-262-4393</phone><name>Firefly</name><city>Boston</city><id>762905</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075652</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello!  I've been a member of the meetup for quite a while now, and this will be the very first meetup I'm organizing.  I saw that there are no brunches planned so far this month, so I figured it was time I planned one.  I hope with this short notice that we still get a full group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've picked Firefly, which is on Dartmouth Street in the Back Bay.  It is right down the street from the Orange Line Back Bay T stop, and I believe the is garage parking available within a block of the restaurant, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant's website is:  &lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fireflyanamericanbistro.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fireflyana...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Firefly, 130 Dartmouth Street, Boston, MA  02116.  617-262-4393&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Sunday, October 12, 2008, at 12:00-Noon.  Reservation is under my name, &amp;quot;Annette&amp;quot;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will email my cell phone number to those that RSVP yes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;RULES of Engagement for Brunch&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; added by Tonya&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.        Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must contact Annette directly by calling or texting her cell. She will email her cell to all who RSVP Yes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the bar--I have a big head of curly, curly blond/brown hair!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224437854000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223589257000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Firefly - Sunday Brunch - Backbay</name><id>8932578</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223827200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/8932578/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/6/global_5829334.jpeg</photo_url></item>