<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Garden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381464</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495--7461</phone><name>Phillips Auditorium (Center for Astrophysics)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>789230</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.126188</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lately we've heard heated debates about fictitious &amp;quot;death panels&amp;quot; in health care reform. But the brontosaurus in the tea house nobody wants to talk about is overpopulation. So Hollywood steps in and does it for us. Here we witness a dystopian future society that maintains equilibrium by demanding death of everyone upon reaching a certain age. And the hero of our story, why he's just about to have that very special last birthday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Logan's Run&amp;quot; is one of several free classic Sci-Fi Movie screenings to be held at the Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics. The showings are held in the Phillips Auditorium of the Center for Astrophysics, 60 Garden Street, Cambridge, about one mile west of Harvard Square. No reservations are necessary; however, seating is to the capacity of the auditorium (120) . Entrance to the auditorium is at the west of the Center complex, near the Madison Street entrance and large parking lot. The Center also can be easily reached by public transportation. From the Harvard MBTA Station (Red Line), take any bus or trackless trolley going west on Concord Avenue (Arlmont Village and Belmont Center buses, Huron Avenue trolleys) and get off at &amp;quot;Observatory Hill.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on turnout, we might head into Harvard Square for a bite to eat afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Full details here: &lt;a href="http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events/movie_night.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cfa.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Info: &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0074812/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom "spot" Callaway</member_name><member_id>2590946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258932896000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251741157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SciFi Movie Outing: Logan's Run</name><id>11248132</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258759800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/11248132/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/global_8154265.jpeg</photo_url></item>