<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;(1957) dir Akira Kurosawa, w/Toshiro Mifune, Isuzu Yamada, Takashi Shimura  [110 min]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Akira Kurosawa's stunning reconception of Shakespeare's MACBETH is a dark samurai drama, set in feudal Japan. As the film begins, two soldiers--Washizu (Toshirô Mifune) and Miki (Minoru Chiaki)--find themselves lost in a dense forest during a powerful thunderstorm. Seemingly unable to leave the woods, they encounter a ghostly old woman who predicts that Washizu will soon rise to power. At the goading of his ruthless wife, Asaji (Isuzu Yamada), Washizu embarks on a murderously ambitious path and quickly fulfills the prophecy. However, his ascension is cursed by his brutal actions and soon opposition arises to challenge his blood-stained rule. One of the finest Shakespeare adaptations to appear in any medium, Kurosawa's &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;THRONE OF BLOOD&lt;/span&gt; is covered in an entrancingly macabre web. The always-amazing Mifune gives one of his greatest performances as the haunted yet unrelenting Lord Washizu, while Yamada portrays the eeriest version of Lady Macbeth to ever grace the screen or stage. A master of reinterpretation, Kurosawa incorporates strong elements of Japanese Noh drama into the film, and the result adds to the somber and chilling mood. The film's highlight, however, is the tense and skillfully paced finale, which features Washizu literally up against the wall as he faces an army of vengeful archers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perfect for Easter Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/throne_of_blood/" target="_blank"&gt;Rotten Tomatoes Review&lt;/a&gt; - 97% rating&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Akira Kurosawa's remarkable 1957 restaging of Macbeth in samurai and expressionist terms is unquestionably one of his finest works—charged with energy, imagination, and, in keeping with the subject, sheer horror. Incidentally, this was reputed to have been T.S. Eliot's favorite film.&amp;quot;  By  Jonathan Rosenbaum  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we'll go to a nearby eatery for discussion in old English,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be perched on a throne at the front of the Brattle holding a Meetup Sign following the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269805845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Throne of Blood</name><id>13016262</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270415700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13016262/</event_url></item>