<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>146 Upper State St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06473</zip><lat>41.406390</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Haven Green</name><city>North Haven</city><id>324006</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.864950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You May Be Right (I may be crazy) - but I love Billy Joel. The top Billy Joel Tribute band, Big Shot, is playing as a part of North Haven's &amp;quot;Music under the Stars,&amp;quot; Tues, July 24 at 7pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't be a Stranger - the concert is free, and supposedly they even set up a little dance floor. I've seen them perform before; they do a great job with the many Top 100's that Billy has written. (Ask them to play something less popular though and half the band hasn't heard of the song...) but even if it's not Billy himself, It's still Rock and Roll to Me. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come Just the Way You Are - (though I would also recommend a blanket/chair and something to eat/drink?) the concert starts at 7; I'll probably be there around six with cards or something to stake out a good place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Devorah is your contact: (203) 314 -4329.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And yes, I fully realize that my use of song titles in this post has allowed me to rise to a new level of dorkiness....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;The North Haven Green is located between Washington Ave and Upper State Street, off I-91. From New Haven: I-91 North To Exit 11. Take a Right off the exit. Take your first Right at the light. Bank of America is on the corner. About 100 feet ahead on the Left is the Girl Scouts, which is next to a bank. This is great parking. If you miss that driveway, the funeral home next door also has ample parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(additional info about the venue: There's also a bus stop right across the street from the Green, if you're taking the CT Transit C-bus from New Haven. Parking around the Green consists of about 8 spaces! Best to come early and park at one of the lots mentioned above.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185491017000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184601362000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Billy Joel Tribute Band on the North Haven Green July 24, 7pm</name><id>6031270</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185318000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6031270/</event_url></item>