<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Corner of Main Street and Wheelock Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03755</zip><lat>43.702431</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Collis Center Room 218</name><city>Hanover</city><id>1065503</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.289337</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's been way too long since our last meet up! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Wednesday, October 6, 2010 starting at 6 PM we'll be co-hosting a delicious potluck with the Dartmouth Animal Welfare Group and the Dartmouth Graduate Vegetarians and Vegans!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE? Come meet us on the tables under Collis Porch at Dartmouth College, Hanover, NH. Collis is the building with big columns on the intersection with Main Street and across from the green. If it's cold and rainy outside we'll be upstairs in COLLIS ROOM 219.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHO? We welcome vegans, vegetarians, respectful omnivores, and anyone who is just interested in learning more about us! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT to bring?  Vegan dishes are preferred but not mandatory. We ask all dishes to be labeled for courtesy. Reusable plates, cups, and utensils will be provided. If you have any questions on vegan recipes or ingredients contact Lola or I and we'd be happy to answer your questions!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHY? Being veg is more fun with friends! We'll be talking to new students on campus and connecting with like-minded people in the area. As a group we can have an awesome time while also making a difference for the animals, the earth, and ourselves. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your ideas for future meet-ups! Keep you eye out for possible upcoming events like World Vegan Day on Nov. 1st, a field trip to the new vegan restaurant in Concord, NH, film screenings, and speakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you this Wednesday! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kimberly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Porch or Room 219</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lola</member_name><member_id>915277</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286407211000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pioneers of Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-430</urlname><id>650201</id><group_lat>43.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.2699966431</group_lon><name>NH/VT Vegan Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286246344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vegan Potluck</name><id>15004016</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286402400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-430/events/15004016/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/b/global_18505291.jpeg</photo_url></item>