<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Carnival celebrations may be over however the spirit of the season will be on display at Ryles with the lively powerful sound of Bloco AfroBrazil. Here's yet another chance for you to experience the baddest, loudest, funnest indoor carnival around. Yes, I am a GIGANTIC fan which is apparent by the fact that each time this group parties, I place it on the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonOnyxbirds/events/34850172/"&gt;Onyxbirds&lt;/a&gt; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/34850772/"&gt;Portuguese&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;meetup calendars because it always exceeds expectation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's pack the place because the more the merrier and also your presence will convince Ryles to keep the Bloco AfroBrazil party on their schedule. Bloco AfroBrazil is a percussion ensemble that always puts on a spectacular show combining traditional Brazilian grooves like Samba and Ax&amp;eacute; with Funk, Rock, Jazz and even Hip Hop; add to this, the AMAZING Brazilian singer, Ju Marciano's sultry vocal skills and beauty as well as talented and beautiful dancers and you got a recipe for FUN, Brazilian style!! Wear your dance shoes or socks and leave your worries at the door!! Bring your friends....I guarantee a funtastic time, that is if you like your music strong and your party loud. In the past Free Brazilian Beginner Forr&amp;oacute; and Ax&amp;eacute; dance lessons and performances have been offered from 8:30 PM until 9:30 PM then Marcus and Bloco AfroBrazil turn up the heat and the sound at 9:30 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the drumming, singing and dancing start, group conversation is difficult. Let's just enjoy the party!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to get in the mood, try a refreshing Guarana, Caipirinha or Caju Amigo, which are well known Brazilian beverages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;$10 cash cover charge at the door&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You must be at least 21&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;but you don't have to drink, just enjoy each others company and an AMAZING! show.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.afrobrazil.org/index.php?CLm=10&amp;amp;CLd=1&amp;amp;CLy=2011&amp;amp;c_num=AB"&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rylesjazz.com/month.cfm?month=10/2011"&gt;Ryles website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;From Points West:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Take I-90 (Mass Pike) to Exit 18 bearing right toward Allston/Cambridge. At the end of the exit pass through two sets of lights traveling over the Charles River, continue straight onto River Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Take River Street through Central Square crossing Over Massachusetts Avenue where River Street turns into Prospect Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 At Fourth traffic light (Hess Gas Station) take LEFT onto Hampshire Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Ryles Jazz Club is located at 212 Hampshire Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;From Points South:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Follow 93 North into Downtown Boston.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Take Exit 26, Storrow Drive.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 At the bottom of the Exit proceed onto Storrow Drive.&amp;bull; Bear LEFT on Storrow&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive and take the first LEFT hand exit (Kendall Sq.).&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Bear RIGHT on the exit ramp following the signs for Kendall Square Cambridge, 3N.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Pass over the Longfellow Bridge and continue straight onto Main Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Follow Main Street straight onto Broadway (The Marriott Hotel will be on your left).&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 At the Fourth set of lights take a RIGHT onto Hampshire Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Continue on Hampshire Street for 0.6 miles.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Ryles Jazz Club is located on 212 Hampshire Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;From Points North:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Follow 93 North into Downtown Boston.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 At the end of the exit ramp at the light, take a LEFT following the signs to the&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Museum of Science. Take the first RIGHT following Route 28 North (The Museum of Science will be on the left).&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Proceed past two sets of lights, at the third light bear LEFT onto Cambridge Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Continue approximately 1.1 miles on Cambridge street, take LEFT onto Prospect Street.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Take first RIGHT onto Hampshire Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Free in the two S&amp;amp;S Restaurant lots on Hampshire Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) Free behind the 7-11 (store) on Hampshire Street across from Hess Gas Station on Hampshire Street near Prospect Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) Municipal lot on Springfield Street off of Cambridge Street behind 1369 Coffee House at 1369 Cambridge Street and Ole Mexican Grill at 11 Springfield Street meter parking in effect 6pm til 10pm at $2/hour max 4 hours&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;buy ticket from machine in lot&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;then place in window&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4) Hampshire Street, Beacon Street and Cambridge Street parking&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;READ SIGNS TO AVOID HAVING YOUR VEHICLE TICKETED AND/OR TOWED&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5) Last resort Cambridge Hospital garage $7 for 3 hrs $8 for 4 hrs $10 for 5 hrs $13 for 6 hrs (prices as of July 2010)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create your route at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 69, 83 and 91 buses run through (or near) Inman Square&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317520215000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316984748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brazilian Happy Hour Party at Ryles Saturday October 1st at 8:30 PM</name><id>34916642</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317515400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/34916642/</event_url></item>