<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SPRING HAS FINALLY SPRUNG! APRIL ALLOWED US AND OUR PUGGIES TO PLAY OUTSIDE IN THE BEAUTIFUL WEATHER AND HOPEFULLY WE WILL GET A COUPLE MORE BEFORE WE ARE FORCED TO STAY INSIDE TO KEEP OUR BABIES COOL IN THE AC!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although Kelly, Albert and I will be away for the May Pug Meetup as our trusty Assistant Organizers have a wonderful play date planned...I heard a rumor the theme was May flowers! So make sure you don't miss it as I know Julie is working hard preparing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO, important announcement for JUNE... have been talking with Pug Rescue of New England, and they ARE DEFINITELY scheduled to come to our June Pug Meetup to educate us on the importance of their wonderful Pug rescue so make sure to RSVP early for this one because it is certain to fill up FAST!. Tammy the founder, along with a couple of her volunteers will be attending and also bringing a few pugs in foster care up for adoption.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly, Albert and I will be back for our Second Annual &lt;b&gt;July Pug Meetup Cookout scheduled for the JULY 24th&lt;/b&gt; so make sure to mark your calendars as this one fills up super fast and space IS limited because it is at our own home in Grafton......much more to come on this very special event.....see you all soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly and I truly enjoy being the Organizers of the Grafton pug Meetup. We hope that we have met each of you individually, and if we have not, please come up and introduce yourself at the next one. We are constantly trying to come up with new treats for our precious pugs, and ideas to keep it informative and interesting. We welcome all suggestions. It seems to be very personal and we all have tons of fun.  We always welcome new members to come join in the fun and excitement at watching our little puggie friends romp and play in the spacious room at the Gibson Kennel in Grafton. Note: &lt;b&gt;this is a PUG Meetup&lt;/b&gt;...as not all breeds play well together.  There are other small breed Meetups, but this is for PUGS ONLY!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******A receipt of current vaccinations must be brought with you in order to enter the play area (kennel rules)*********  (The owner of the kennel did request we have this on-hand)    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will ask for a $5 fee per family for each Meetup&lt;/b&gt; to cover Meetup costs and any leftover money will be donated to Animal related charities. These donations go toward paying the monthly dues, snacks and to keep this website going so we can all see when the next Meetup is taking place.  We will also do special events from time to time to keep it fun and interesting!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all and I look forward to playing again with all you pug lovers out there and your pups! =)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will introduce ourselves...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erin maguire</member_name><member_id>3828727</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth Mott</member_name><member_id>6811754</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>10300396</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275489369000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Puggy Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pug-569</urlname><id>252667</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6900024414</group_lon><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270136930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>fdfdnynhbmc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275152400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pug-569/events/13058557/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/b/global_10981051.jpeg</photo_url></item>