<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;How do some people get so lucky?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is it that allows one couple to have an easy, successful, happy, loving relationship that lasts?  Is it luck? I certainly hope not!  Is it just love?  I don’t think so, or the divorce rate would be a lot lower.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And how is it you get annoyed by someone’s behavior and someone else doesn’t?  How do some people find it so easy to understand and forgive negative behavior?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turns out that there are certain beliefs and attitudes that support an easier aligning and allowing for relationship success – &lt;u&gt;any kind of relationship&lt;/u&gt;.  And once you understand the premise behind these beliefs, they are very desirable and easy to accept.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These beliefs will help you with:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Ending the who’s right and who’s wrong arguments.&lt;br /&gt;• Putting an end to “That’s not what I said!” and “You’re not listening!”&lt;br /&gt;• How to have more understanding and patience for undesirable behaviors, and how you can deal with them more positively and effectively.&lt;br /&gt;• How to understand your partner better.&lt;br /&gt;• How to keep your relationship fresh and new and last through time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn’t that be nice?  I can tell you from over 20 years of personal experience that it is.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Well, wait no longer! Join us in our half-day workshop, Fundamentals of Relationship Success, and you’ll have the opportunity to learn and practice some of the most important beliefs and skills needed to have a solid foundation for happy, successful relationships -&lt;u&gt;personal and professional, romantic and platonic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fundamentals of Relationship Success: a half day workshop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday morning, March 6th, 9:30 am -12:30 pm, Wayland Wellness, 15 East Plain St., Wayland, MA 01778&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**$55 per person.&lt;br /&gt;**Bring someone with you and pay only $90 for two people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your friends and make it a fun and life enriching Saturday, with lunch together afterwards!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that you need to register and pay in advance for this event.&lt;/b&gt;  E-mail me at annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com with the names, e-mails and phone numbers of who will be attending, and we will send you the appropriate PayPal link to pay the fee.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagerly looking forward to creating new possibilities with you!&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark &lt;br /&gt;Helping you align towards greater harmony, happiness and success!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268239618000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266518345000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fundamentals of Relationship Success</name><id>12639323</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267885800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/12639323/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/5/global_13181317.jpeg</photo_url></item>