<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>After work hike. New State Road Trail loop is about 2.8 miles. Mostly easy hike great for beginning hikers. Some wet areas, a few small hills, great Hockanum River and marsh views, water birds, three unusual mature trees to see. This hike is a new hike and experimental in this first offering by this hiking group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park at Laurel Marsh parking lot on south side of Middle Turnpike West (Route 44) just east of I-84, Exit 60, and meet there at &lt;b&gt;5:30 PM&lt;/b&gt;. The lot is not well marked but can be seen with a low but heavy wooden fence. The hike should take about 1.5 hrs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a flashlight or headlamp to help for the last bit of the hike as it is getting dark earlier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids are welcome. Dogs on leash are fine if well behaved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; to parking and start: South side of Middle Turnpike West (Route 44) just east of I-84, Exit 60 in Manchester, CT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Manchester&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=870+Middle+Tpke+W&amp;amp;zipcode=06040" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hiking trail map and trail information&lt;/b&gt; (Note: We are parking at Laurel Marsh parking at south part of loop, across the street):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hockanumriverwa.org/LPCM_NewStateRoad.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hockanumri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hockanum River Watershed Association&lt;/b&gt; -preservation group for the areas affecting the river:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hockanumriverwa.org/HRWA_Home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hockanumri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Old dark green Dodge Caravan.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254001288000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253668379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at New State Rd. Trail in Manchester CT</name><id>11442364</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253827800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11442364/</event_url></item>