<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>689 Somerville Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.385498</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Desera Interactive</name><city>Somerville</city><id>689370</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113244</lon></venue><fee><label>Workshop fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I'm repeating a series of introductory level digital photo editing workshops I've taught for the BPC. This would be relevant to anyone looking to get started in digital photo editing, or who would like to better understand the basic features of their photo editing software.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Workshop fee is $30. Payment is due when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;Date: Sunday, 10/4/09&lt;br /&gt;Time: 7 - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;Location: a small Somerville office, near Porter Square&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This first workshop is suited for people with no, or very little, working knowledge of Photoshop or other digital photo editing software. The session will introduce file formats (JPEG, RAW, PSD, TIFF), and how to prepare your photographs for print or web display.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photoshop CS3 will be used in the workshop, but the demonstration will also be relevant to users of Adobe Elements, Adobe Lightroom, Apple iPhoto, and other versions of Photoshop. Computers are not available in the conference room, but the emphasis of this workshop is on the concepts of digital image processing, not software training in specific applications. All participants will receive a detailed booklet of the information covered, and practice tutorials and files on a CD-R to try at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Workshop outline:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- What should you use Photoshop for?&lt;br /&gt;- Which version of Photoshop do you need?&lt;br /&gt;- The difference between JPEG and RAW&lt;br /&gt;- Settings for scanning prints and slides&lt;br /&gt;- Tour of the Photoshop interface&lt;br /&gt;- Rotating and correcting barrel distortion&lt;br /&gt;- Cropping and constraining aspect ratio&lt;br /&gt;- Automatic color and contrast correction&lt;br /&gt;- Undoing mistakes with the history palette&lt;br /&gt;- Backups and file management&lt;br /&gt;- Optimizing images for print output&lt;br /&gt;- Optimizing images for screen display&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Kelleher</member_name><member_id>1381167</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254957378000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Digital Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-arts</urlname><id>303063</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Digital Arts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254084033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Digital Photo Editing 101: The Basics</name><id>11480321</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254697200000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-arts/events/11480321/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/2/global_2958562.jpeg</photo_url></item>