<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/photos/7628772"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/photos/7628772"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 8.25 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duration: 3.5 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Difficulty: difficult (lengthy but mostly flat)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Blaze orange is required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Vin Gormley Trail is hike #4 in Ken Weber’s “Weekend Walks in Rhode Island”. It is a 8 ¼ mile hike around Watchaug Pond, primarily in Burlingame State Park. Most of the hike is on woodland trails, but there are also sections on paved roads. This hike should take about 3.5 hours to complete. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The hike will start on the eastern shore of Watchaug Pond where there is a large parking lot. From there we will walk through the Audubon Society’s Kimball Wildlife Sanctuary, and then through the Burlingame Camping Area. After that we will be on woodland trails in Burlingame State Park that include crossing a little covered bridge. Along with the yellow blazes of the Vin Gormley Trail, about 4 miles of this hike also have the blue blazes of the North South Trail. The terrain is mostly flat, with a short hilly section along some rock ledges. Some parts of the trail will could be wet, so wear hiking boots. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

With limited spring turkey hunting going on, blaze orange is required. It will also keep us visible on the residential roads on this hike. Bring water and snacks as always. Also bring bug spray for the ticks and other insects that are already active.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions: Follow RT 1 southbound west of RTs 2 &amp;amp; 112. Follow signs for Burlingame Park until taking a right on Prosser Trail (it is a paved road). Follow Prosser Trail for 0.6 &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/5/9/8/event_112281912.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;miles, and take a left into the park’s entrance. Park at the far end of the large parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Burlingame State park (not the campground)Prosseer Trail to sanctuary Rd.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368444192000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367879249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vin Gormley Trail Weber Hike # 4</name><id>118065302</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368279000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/118065302/</event_url></item>