<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>371 Summer St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.393651</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dilboy VFW Hall in Davis Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1104348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119526</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Halloween is just around the corner, and we have travelled to the End of the Universe to bring you a fantastic party!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &lt;span style="color : #44305d"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/32016682/"&gt;Boston Sci-Fi &amp;amp; Fantasy Meetup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is teaming up with Nerd Fun Boston to throw an incredible Halloween Party!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From 7:00 PM until Midnight on October 14th, we're converting the Dilboy VFW Hall in Davis Square into a spooky, otherwordly, and nerdy party experience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There will be food, candy, games, music, dancing, and a costume contest (with cash prizes)!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Admission is $25 per person.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://spot.fedorapeople.org/party-flyer.png" alt="http://spot.fedorapeople.org/party-flyer.png" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event isn't cheap, but we've tried to make it as affordable as possible. This event will be listed on both the Boston Sci-Fi &amp;amp; Fantasy Meetup and the Nerd Fun meetup. Because of the laws of the Town of Somerville, this event has a maximum capacity of 100 people, so each group's meetup will have a 50 person limit! Please RSVP and pre-pay early!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food&lt;/strong&gt; is being catered by Dom's Catering of Malden. We'll have a spread of appetizers including Cheese, Fruit, Veggies and Dip, Finger Sandwiches, and Chips and Salsa. The dinner menu will consist of a choice of four hot Italian entrees (Cheese Lasagna w/Meat Sauce, Vegetarian Lasagna, Chicken with Broccoli &amp;amp; Ziti, and Chicken with Mushroom and Alfredo Sauce (Gluten-Free)), served buffet style with Garden Salad and Hot Rolls. Oh, of course, we'll have desserts and Halloween Candy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every partygoer gets a free bottled water to go with their food, but all other &lt;strong&gt;drinks&lt;/strong&gt; must be purchased from the VFW bar (this is due to the laws of the Town of Somerville). They have a full bar, and their drinks are cheap! Pricing is $2.00 for water/soda/juice, $3.75 for most domestic beers and wine, $4.25 to $4.75 for single liquor drinks and imported beers, $5.50 for two liquor drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If the party wasn't enough, we're having a big costume contest with $$$ prizes. First place is $100, second place is $75, third place is $50, so come in costume and be prepared to compete! There is no "theme" for the party or the contest, so let your imagination run wild.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Dilboy VFW&lt;/strong&gt; is located a short walking distance from the Davis Square T stop, but it also has a private parking lot that we will be able to use (it is surrounded by a chain-link fence, is well lit, and there are clear signs to lead you to it). Please note that the front entrance to the VFW will not be accessible for this event, so you must enter at the back (where the parking lot is). We'll have signs outside in case you get lost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, while we have to charge a cost for this party, we've tried very hard to keep costs as low as possible. No one is making any money off this event, all of the money we collect is going into making this party a fantastic night to remember, so &lt;strong&gt;please RSVP and prepay on the meetup site&lt;/strong&gt;. (Since I know people will ask if it is possible to not pre-pay and pay in person on the night of the party, the answer is no, unless we have not sold out, and we'll announce that change if it happens before the event.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>20</waitlist_count><updated>1318948449000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314985959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Halloween Party at the End of the Universe</name><id>32024842</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318633200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/32024842/</event_url></item>