<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>401 Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.343983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 236-0746 </phone><name>REI</name><city>Boston</city><id>846863</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102784</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sorry for the short notice but just found the notification for this sale in my inbox. Treat someone you know (or yourself for that matter) to some new-to-you clothing, gear, and equipment at a reasonable price.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The sale starts at 10:00 AM but admittance will be determined by numbered tickets which will be handed out on a first-come, first-served basis beginning at 8:30 AM. If you show up at 10:00 AM without a ticket you will likely miss out on the best deals.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;REI Boston is overflowing with great winter gear deals, so we have scheduled a Special Members-Only Used Gear Sale (Formerly the Garage Sale) for Saturday, December 8th. Checkout tons of imperfect merchandise. Prices are slashed 30-60% but firm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you are wondering what clothing, gear, and equipment you might need for winter hiking check out our list of stuff for winter day hikes by clicking &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An REI membership is required to purchase. Not a member yet? A lifetime membership is only $20 and can be purchased on the day of the sale! Don't miss out on the Incredible Bargains! ALL SALES ARE FINAL- NO RETURNS OR EXCHANGES.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can't make it to REI Boston on the 8th? Be sure to check out our marketwide (ALL Mass area REI locations) Year-end Used Gear Sale on Saturday, December 29th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354990243000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354932025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Used Gear Sale - REI Boston ONLY</name><id>94535432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354978800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/94535432/</event_url></item>