<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our February breakfast will be set up differently than our regular single speaker format. WBOA will be hosting a roundtable event, featuring our resident experts, who will be offering several short and informative sessions on topics important to small business owners. This meeting format will allow us to move about the room and interact with the speakers- a refreshing change of pace!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Using LinkedIn to Hook New Clients&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Christine Parizo, Principal Copywriter, Christine Parizo Communications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn has over 135 million members worldwide, and any of them could be your next client or a valuable resource for your business. Learn how to harness your LinkedIn profile to land clients and build your professional brand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress &amp;amp; Anxiety &amp;ndash; Don&amp;rsquo;t Let It Ruin Your Day!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Mary-Anne DiBlasio, Founder &amp;amp; Holistic Health Practitioner, Western Mass Wellness Center&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As working women, we face a variety of stressors. Mary-Anne DiBlasio will lead a discussion on the things that threaten to derail our day and how to manage our stress so that we can be productive, successful, and happy. Ten Tips for Sending a Press Release Janice Beetle Godleski, Beetle Press Participants will learn the basics of writing and sending a press release to local media, as well as a few media &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;ts&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listening to and Responding to Your Deepest Yearnings&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Karen Ribeiro, business and life development coach, Author of the Inner Fortune system&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do you really want? Learn to identify and clarify your deepest yearnings. A rich discussion will follow about our personal and professional yearnings that may lead to dynamic collaborations and peace of mind!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Favorite Money Saving Tax Tips for Small Businesses&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Susan Kelley, MBA, EA, &amp;#8232;Kelley Tax Services&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you claiming all the expenses you possibly can (legally!) for your business? Would your expenses stand up under audit? Now's the time to review your 2011 expenses and make sure you are not paying one dime more than necessary!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330088926000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327455940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Breakfast Roundtable</name><id>49503292</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329396300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/49503292/</event_url></item>