<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday October 18th   6:30-9:30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork Mixer returns from a 3 month hiatus, this time we are taking the party  to the brand new   trendy &amp;amp; stylish  ALIBI Bar &amp;amp; Lounge located at the newly renovated Liberty Hotel conveinently  across the street from the Charles MGH T stop off the red line.  The buzz surrounding this venue has been tremendous, this venue has received stellar reviews from many media outlets such as the Boston Globe, Stuff at Nite and the Improper Bostonian. I recommend going on to www.alibiboston.com and see for yourself how unreal this place is! Also as an added bonus we will  have the opportunity to see my hometown Cleveland Indians take on the Boston Red Sox in game 5 of the ALCS on television. So please come and join the group as we kickoff the start to another festive weekend!  Besides what more could you ask for,  Great people ,drinks, venue, and playoff baseball on a Thurs nite! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if you have not been to any or a few of our events whether an Afterwork Mixer, New Member meetup, or even a nite on the town in the city with the group, I encourage all of you to come this Thursday and meet many of our wonderful members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet  at the main bar.  Please look for me upon arriving my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, with this being Boston's new afterwork hotspot  this venue is guaranteed to fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation &lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Charles MGH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192933277000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192410696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Afterwork Mixer: The New  ALIBI  Bar &amp; Lounge </name><id>6550681</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192746600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/6550681/</event_url></item>