<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361406</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857.453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft N.E.R.D. Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1210878</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our February 2010 JavaScript Meetup will be held on Thursday, February 25th at Microsoft Research Center located at One Memorial Drive in Cambridge. When you arrive security will direct you to the correct floor. There is also parking available at a cheap evening rate in the building. Parking is also free on the street in front of the building at 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 6:30 PM our fellow member Mitcho (mitcho.com) will share his knowledge of JetPack.  Project Jetpack is Mozilla's recent initiative to explore new ways to make extending the browser easier. Jetpack lets web developers and browser hackers alike use the open web stack of HTML/CSS/JS to modify the Firefox browser itself. Come see Jetpack in action and learn about recent developments in the project from mitcho, a Mozilla Jetpack Ambassador right here in the Boston area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hear he is an awesome presenter.  Learn more about him at his website &lt;a href="http://mitcho.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mitcho.com...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation | demonstration, we will go around the room introducing ourselves and asking the group for advice | opinions on any JavaScript-related issues members are facing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Microsoft will provide pizza again. What a generous organization! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP and bring guests.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marsh Sutherland</member_name><member_id>3795141</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267311782000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>JavaScripters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>javascript-2</urlname><id>884541</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>The Boston JavaScript Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254582734000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mitcho's talk on Extending the Browser with Jetpack</name><id>11536445</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267138800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/javascript-2/events/11536445/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/f/global_2825455.jpeg</photo_url></item>