<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 53</address_2><address_1>410 Quincy Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.233500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Viking Club</name><city>Braintree</city><id>1196898</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.977100</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join members and guests of the SSFMG for our first Line Dance Lesson as a group.  You don't have to be a cowboy (or girl) or own boots to take line dance lessons and get a nice cardio workout.  A couple of the line dances are done to non-country songs so don't be shy.  The instructor is good and will go over steps until you are comfortable.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginner lessons run from 6:30-7:30 pm and include 3 line dances.  In the Spring, when your EO's checked out these line dance lessons we learned a few dances, including Eye Candy and the Cowboy Charleston, arguably two of the easiest line dances.  The last hour and a half includes intermediate line dance lessons and line dancing.  We recommend arriving for the beginner lessons and staying for a little while anyway to check out the intermediate dances.  Dance lessons are offered every Wednesday night except the 4th Wednesday of the month so if you like tonight's lesson (or are unable to attend) this is something we can put on the calendar again.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Line Dance Lessons  &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, September  29th, 2010  &lt;br /&gt;6:30-9pm  &lt;br /&gt;The Viking Club  &lt;br /&gt;410 Quincy Avenue  &lt;br /&gt;Route 53 (Southbound)  &lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184  &lt;br /&gt;Instructor Susan's # 781-340-1314  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Meeting Place: We'll scope out a table or two to put our coats, outdoor shoes, and water.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Alternate Meeting Place: On the dance floor!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Event Organizer: Alison  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Cost: $8 per person (CASH ONLY)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Min/Max: There is currently no minimum or maximum as this room holds a lot of people and the EO is planning to attend.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Guests: Welcome!  Up to 2 per member.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*RSVP Deadline: Tuesday, September 28th @ 8pm  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Case of Inclement Weather:  &lt;br /&gt;This is an indoor event and it is up to the instructor regarding canceling in case of severe weather.    &lt;br /&gt;**Please check back here (or the Message Boards) for an update on weather conditions.**  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on the Southbound side of Route 53 directly across from Dunkin Donuts and Super Shine, about 1 mile from the Quincy line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the hall near the back of the building.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285938123000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284688159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Line Dance Lessons</name><id>14798898</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285799400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/14798898/</event_url></item>