<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(A few hundred feet East of Mt. Clinton Rd)</address_2><address_1>Rte 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.234306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Highland Center at Crawford Notch</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>1839181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.421936</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;The objective of this mega-day hike is to traverse the section of the AT that runs from I-93 to Rt. 302 through the Pemi area.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; While we'll visit five official 4,000-footer summits along the way - Lincoln, Lafayette, Garfield, South Twin and Zealand - we will not be availing ourselves of such interesting nearby opportunities as Liberty, W.Garfield Ridge, E. Garfield Ridge, Galehead, and North Twin.&amp;nbsp; With that compromise and a &lt;strong&gt;fast pace&lt;/strong&gt;, the plan is to complete this 29-mile, 8800' elevation gain trip almost fully within the 16 or so available daylight hours (of course, this should not stop you from bringing your headlamp!).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Due to the size of this Saturday hike and its associated physical demands, we will be camping as a group on both the nights before (Friday) and after (Saturday).&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We will be meeting up In Crawford Notch in the late afternoon on Friday to spot cars, so you will need to be able to head out early (around 1pm, in the case of Bostonians, for example) to make it there on time and ahead of the weekend traffic.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Once you're registered and confirmed, we'll be sending you the detailed trip plan, including the exact meet-up time, location and directions, recommended packing list, and carpooling contact list.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; In the event of a grim weather forecast for Saturday, we may on Friday morning decide either to cancel the trip or delay it by a day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;Because of the pace, distance and elevation gain, this is a very advanced, very strenuous trip.&amp;nbsp; You need to be an experienced hiker who has recently completed trips of similar distance and elevation at a substantially faster-than-book time pace.&amp;nbsp; If you are not, please do not sign up.&amp;nbsp; Also, w&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;e start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, or if you want to hang back or head off on your own, this is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; the trip for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Signing Up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;To sign up, be sure to answer all RSVP questions clearly and completely.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; After you sign up, we'll follow up with you by phone to ensure that this is an outing you'll enjoy.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; As a result, we'll agree either to continue your active status on the trip ('going' or 'waitlisted' depending on how many are ahead of you), or else move you to 'not going'.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;As part of your participation in this hike, you will need to sign the AMC &lt;em&gt;Acknowledgement and Assumption of Risks &amp;amp; Release Agreement&lt;/em&gt;, which you can review &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease-2.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Also as a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity, you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting in the Crawford Notch area on Friday afternoon, the day before - exact time and location TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309742136000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308286165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Traverse the Pemi Area via the AT !  (Very Strenuous)</name><id>22526651</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309597200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/22526651/</event_url></item>