<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View beautiful fall foliage and spend a relaxing day with friends on the Charles River!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are planning to go kayaking/canoeing on the Charles River in Dedham on Sunday, October 4th, weather permitting. I have access to a number of kayaks and canoes at Noble and Greenough School (Nobles). There is no cost and no experience is necessary. See the photo section for some snapshots of last year's trip. About 20 people showed up last year and the autumn leaves and scenery were great. We had maybe 10 kayaks and a couple of canoes, and people took turns going on the river and playing ultimate frisbee. It's also possible to do other sports, such as softball or soccer. Other people have access to the kayaks too, so I can't predict exactly how many will be available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch: Pack a bag lunch and drink, or purchase from a local deli (We'll make a trip for those that want to buy lunch) Picnic tables are available.&lt;br /&gt;Wear: clothes and shoes you don't mind getting wet (last year I think just one person got really wet, but the inside of the kayaks are likely to get a little wet. The water is not deep, but everyone must wear a life vest while in a kayak/canoe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those with a car, Nobles is located at 10 Campus Drive, just off Pine St. in Dedham MA. That is just off exit 18, route 128. See: www.nobles.edu for directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those coming via mass transit, take the orange line south to the last stop, Forest Hills. I can pick up people there at 10:30, but please let me know that you are coming and your contact info just in case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the event of rain, we will postpone the event for 1 week (October 11th). Check your e-mail Sunday morning if the weather looks iffy.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From the entrance, go straight down the hill and park by the gym. The dock is past the gym.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob G</member_name><member_id>4202053</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1254871885000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253294319000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charles River Canoe/Kayak trip/Picnic/Ultimate frisbee </name><id>11406725</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254668400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/11406725/</event_url></item>