<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The first guest speaker of the year for the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. is Dr. Kelly Korreck, an astrophysicist from the Harvard Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics who works on the Solar Dynamics Observatory ( SDO ). The talk will be in Room 104 of the Science Building on the campus of Anna Maria College in Paxton, MA 01612 with outdoor oserving after the event through large telescopes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topic : SDO: Our Eyes on the Sun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sun, our closest star, provides the Earth with light and heat for life as we know it. NASA’s Solar Dynamics Observatory (SDO) launched February 2010, explores the causes of solar variability and its impacts on Earth. Using the 3 scientific instruments aboard SDO, the Atmospheric Imaging Assembly (AIA), the Extreme Ultraviolet Variability Experiment (EVE) and the Helioseismic and Magnetic Imager (HMI), an image of the Sun with 10 times greater resolution than high definition television is taken every 0.75 seconds! These images reveal a dynamic complex solar corona that is over a million degrees in temperature. By combining the increased spatial resolution and the fast cadence of the images, coronal mass ejections, billions of tons of hot plasma, can be studied as it is hurled from the Sun towards the Earth. We will discuss these eruptions as well as reasons as to why they affect every day life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bio : &lt;br /&gt;

Kelly E. Korreck, PhD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Korreck is an Astrophysicist at the Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics in Cambridge, MA. She is a part of the Solar-Stellar X-ray Group. She received her PhD in Space Physics from The University of Michigan-Ann Arbor. Her research has included jets associated with symbiotic stars, shocks in supernova remnants, x-ray detectors and flares on the Sun. Her current research focuses on plasma dynamics of the solar corona and its propagation through interplanetary space as the solar wind and the effect it has on the Earth in the form of Space Weather. She is the science and operations lead for the SWEAP Investigation aboard NASA’s Solar Probe Plus mission. She is also the SAO Project Scientist for the High Resolution Coronal Imager Sounding Rocket. She is a member of the American Astronomical Society, American Physical Society, and the American Geophysical Union.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351384449000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350905271000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SDO : Our Eyes on the Skies!</name><id>88025972</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>3600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351380600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/88025972/</event_url></item>