<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I know that some of our members are participating in this event and supporting them would be a great way to support the source of the weather reports that most of us use before heading out into the wilderness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are participating please RSVP yes to this event and list the link to your donations page so that others in the group can help support you and your efforts.  I am sure they would appreciate a donation of any amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not too late to get involved &amp;ndash; there&amp;rsquo;s a kick-off party Friday night, tours of the Observatory on when you get to the top, and then an after party with live music Saturday night. If you want to &amp;ldquo;seek the peak&amp;rdquo; and get your own donations then visit the official website (&lt;a href="http://www.seekthepeak.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.seekthepeak.org&lt;/a&gt;) to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you aren&amp;rsquo;t able to climb but would like to volunteer there may be a way for you to get involved too. To learn more contact Karen Hemeon, Events Coordinator, at khemeon@mountwashington.org or (603) 356-2137 x 230.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Seek the Peak?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since 2001, hikers of all ages and abilities from across the nation have converged on 6,288-foot Mount Washington, New Hampshire for Mount Washington Observatory's Seek the Peak Hike-A-Thon fundraiser. Welcoming as many as 500 hikers to the Northeast&amp;rsquo;s tallest peak, Seek the Peak has emerged as New England's premier hiking event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by Subaru and Eastern Mountain Sports, Seek the Peak is a fundraiser for the nonprofit Mount Washington Observatory. Over the event's history, Seek the Peak has raised nearly $700,000 for the institution, helping it maintain its famous weather station on the summit of Mount Washington and continue its important work collecting weather data, performing scientific research and educating the public about the science of weather and climate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boasting world-class alpine trekking and stunning views to the Atlantic Ocean, Canada, the Adirondack mountains and beyond, Mount Washington is the pinnacle of the New England hiking scene. Scaling its windswept summit as a participant in Seek the Peak offers an immensely rewarding physical challenge, while benefitting a great cause.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311614549000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>What a great way to support the source of the weather reports that most of us use before heading out into the wilderness.</why><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303347082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seek the Peak - Hike-a-thon to support the Mount Washington Observatory</name><id>17379688</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311415200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/17379688/</event_url></item>