<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Quarry Hills Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.196896</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-689-1900 </phone><name>Granite Links Golf Club</name><city>Quincy</city><id>632999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064384</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SUCCESS IN SALES Networking Event!&lt;br /&gt;Are you a business owner or sales leader looking to network with your peers? &lt;br /&gt;Have you realized how important it is to know the basics of selling?&lt;br /&gt;Would you benefit from hearing from experts in the field?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you find yourself thinking any of the following . . .&lt;br /&gt;- I need to find new ways to set myself apart at networking events&lt;br /&gt;- I'm excited about what my business will look like if improve the amount of referrals I get &lt;br /&gt;- I wish I could find a more effective way to differentiate my business or service&lt;br /&gt;- I know I could help more people if I worked more on perfecting my skills&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If so, then this is the event for you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alongside your peers from Successful Anonymous Networking, AKA &amp;quot;The Success Addicts&amp;quot;, join Peter Oliver of Sandler Training at this Networking Workshop.  Peter will address these sales-related challenges in a no-pressure setting that will help business owners and sales professionals identify common obstacles in selling and suggest ideas on how to address them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our two goals for this session are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;- Provide an opportunity to for you to network with your peers &lt;br /&gt;- Provide a forum to learn how improve your results around finding new opportunities&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited to first 50 attendees.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;****You must pre-register for the event at this link to secure your spot!***&lt;/b&gt; ---- &lt;br /&gt;Register At: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/2vsfnte" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/2v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;^^^ Register HERE ^^^ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;^^^You must pre-register for the event by clicking this link to secure your spot^^^&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date and Time: &lt;br /&gt;Sept 28th at 3:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Granite Links Golf Club - Member Grill Room&lt;br /&gt;100 Quarry Hills Dr&lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA 02169&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.granitelinksgolfclub.com/club/scripts/library/view_document.asp?GRP=6106&amp;amp;NS=PUBLIC&amp;amp;APP=80&amp;amp;DN=DIRECTIONS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.granitelin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda: &lt;br /&gt;3:30 Introductions/Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;4:00 Presentation and Group Exercises&lt;br /&gt;4:45 Facilitated and Coordinated Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Trainer&lt;br /&gt;Sandler Training is a world leader in innovative sales and sales management training. For more than 40 years, Sandler has taught its distinctive, non-traditional selling system and highly effective sales training methodology, which has helped salespeople and sales managers take charge of the process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our training is designed to create lasting “performance improvement” rather than the motivational “quick fix” typical of many seminar-based training programs. To help you accomplish your goals, Sandler provides “reinforcement training,” a system that combines quality materials along with access to ongoing training workshops and individual coaching sessions. Through our local training centers, we provide continuing face-to-face support and reinforcement of the world’s most successful selling system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Sandler, we understand that business success is directly related to the effectiveness of upper- and mid-level managers within an organization. Sandler’s management solutions help managers at all levels become more effective communicators, better mentors and coaches, and competent managers of change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sandler has been awarded the #1 ranking for training programs in Entrepreneur Magazine’s “Franchise 500” nine times since 1994, the most recent being for 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join our Linked In group:&lt;br /&gt;Search: Sandler Training Boston Metrowest in the www.linkedin.com groups&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosted By:&lt;br /&gt;www.adventus.sandler.com&lt;br /&gt;www.MeetUp.com/SuccessfulAnonymous&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>VandD Partnership</member_name><member_id>10820762</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285768262000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Success Addicts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>successfulanonymous</urlname><id>1551084</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Successful Anonymous</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283918130000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SUCCESS IN SALES Networking Event</name><id>14693741</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285702200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/events/14693741/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/3/global_13312019.jpeg</photo_url></item>