<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of 133 and 1A</address_2><address_1>26 Main St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01969</zip><lat>42.707548</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stephanie's Village Pancake House</name><city>Rowley</city><id>862761</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.881822</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's go to breakfast at Stephanie's Village pancake house and have a great breakfast and talk w/some friends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;2.5.10 UPDATE: Please note I had to change the time for Breakfast to 11:30am!  Please still try to show up up to 10 minutes early if you are able to.  With the amount of people that we will have (17-20, seeing we have this scheduled on 3 groups!), we will be getting 1 big room for all of us!  The restaurant is NOT be able to do separate checks so please remember to pay your portion of the bill including tax and tip, and we also ask that you don't leave until the check is figured out!  Thank you!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Depending on the amount of RSVP's we may not be able to get 1 big table for all of us, so you may be sitting at a table w/only some of us from the group, I hope this isn't a problem, if it is please change your RSVP, this event will be posted on 3 Meetup sites, please &lt;b&gt;ONLY&lt;/b&gt; put your RSVP on &lt;b&gt;one&lt;/b&gt; of the sites you may be taking up a spot that someone else could have!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie's Village Pancake house has a great menu, with a variety of different breakfast items, pretty much something for everyone, great waffles, and omelettes, they have a really big special's board remember to check it out you may just find something you never thought of on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breakfast is at 11:00, by rule they do not sit everyone until the whole party is there, if you are able to show up a little early that would be good! If your plans change then please update your reservation as early as you are able to, you may be taking a space that someone that wants to go can't have. You can check the site for directions and to check out the menu at www.villagepancakehouse.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to show up for this event, after the 15 minutes we will be sitting down!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Snow may cancel this event please check back for updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you!!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the waiting area as soon as you step in the 2nd door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266033020000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262227264000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's get together for Breakfast!</name><id>12181061</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265560200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12181061/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/2/global_12428690.jpeg</photo_url></item>