<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt Auburn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365641</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga Studio</name><city>Watertown</city><id>752617</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183571</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dear All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are inviting you to an evening of light, love and enchantment. Experience the extraordinary power of sound created by the combination of  crystal healing bowls and tantric meditation for deep emotional and spiritual healing. In this workshop, Saraswati and Gypsy Jay, traveling crystal bowl magician,  will show you how resonating to certain sounds, tones and frequencies can help create a more ecstatic and harmonious you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tantric scriptures say that we are made of sound. We can hear the sound of our pulsation, if we listen with our inner ears. We can listen to the sound of the pulsation of concepts, bodies, feelings. During tantric practice we can make the pulsation of our auras louder, faster, higher. Using the breath, and locks, or bhandas, bija mantras and vocal toning we can intensify our frequency. It can become so loud, it wakes us up, and we smile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Imagine what happens when our practice is accompanied by a powerful sound of crystal bowls - they immediately move you into a meditative, blissful, expanded state of consciousness. Each note is healing, activating and illuminating your chakras. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Crystal Bowl Tonal Keys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.crystalsingingbowls.com/images/body2.JPG" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;B# - above the crown, higher spirituality &lt;br /&gt;B - crown chakra - connection to Source, where we move out of duality back into the Oneness &lt;br /&gt;A# - pineal gland, main center for anchoring the light of enlightenment in the brain &lt;br /&gt;A - third eye chakra, the intuitive all seeing eye&lt;br /&gt;G# - main endocrine system support (thyroid, pineal, pituitary), anchoring light into the brain&lt;br /&gt;G - throat chakra, expression, creativity, thyroid support &lt;br /&gt;F# - divine/high heart, unconditional heart, unity, support thymus gland and immune system&lt;br /&gt;F - heart chakra, loving, support human love&lt;br /&gt;E - solar plexus chakra, working with the mind and internal organs&lt;br /&gt;D# - integrating spiritual plane into physical, pancreas support&lt;br /&gt;D - sacral chakra, emotional body&lt;br /&gt;C# - sexuality, spirituality, grounding, adrenal support&lt;br /&gt;C - root chakra, grounding&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jay Schwed travels around the world and gives crystal bowls performances and workshops. During Jay's performances, audiences not only hear angels, but also see them. We are lucky to have Jay visit us. Please, review Jay's latest video: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJtkL9bn9KE" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;. More info about Jay www.healingcrystalbowls.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jay: Our work together will ignite the passion in all attending and not physically attending and also opening the high heart that connects all things to the one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot;I enthusiastically recommend to my friends that you treat yourself to a beautiful, inspiring and healing evening with Jay and his magical bowls! I am always lifted and positively altered after listening to him play. Jay also personally &amp;quot;walks his talk&amp;quot; and lives his healing art. I am proud to know him as an artist and friend.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;-- Ray Johnston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “Bathe in the center of sound as in the continuous sound of a waterfall.”, Vigyan Bhairav Tantra, from Osho&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - 10pm&lt;br /&gt;Goddess Special Price $15&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luba Evans</member_name><member_id>7320465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255368082000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250559368000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra of Sound: The Song of Crystal Healing Bowls </name><id>11135284</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251502200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/11135284/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/f/global_10260255.jpeg</photo_url></item>