<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bwps.org" target="_blank"&gt;The Boston West Photographic Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presents a Special Event&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Creative Macro &amp;amp; Impressionistic Photography with Charles Needle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, October 16, 2010 7:30 p.m. at the Marist House, 518 Pleasant St, Framingham, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: BWPS Members free, non member $10 at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don’t miss this special event!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Program&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover the unlimited possibilities of creative close-up and impressionistic photography in this special presentation. Speaking to standing-room-only crowds at NECCC in 2010 and 2009, Charles Needle presents his award-winning creative macro and impressionistic photography – and the techniques behind the images – in a special event for BWPS members and guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to showing his images and discussing the specific techniques used to create them, Charles’s presentation covers macro basics (equipment, exposure, depth-of-field, composition and lighting), how to use props to enhance your macro photography, soft-glow and composite montage techniques, and multiple-exposure close-ups. He also demonstrates how to create impressionistic, painterly images in-camera using camera movement, multiple-exposure montages, Lensbaby, long exposures and shooting reflections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Artist&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles Needle is an award-winning, Seattle-based fine-art nature photographer, author and workshop leader blessed with a unique eye for design and artistic interpretation. For more than a decade, his popular two-day and intensive five-day “Art of Nature” creative macro workshops and “Garden and Flower Photography” workshops have attracted students worldwide. He also designs and markets tools specifically for creative macro photography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A FujiFilm USA Talent Team member and North American Nature Photography Association (NANPA) Showcase Award winner (four years in a row), Charles teaches more than a dozen location workshops annually, including international destinations such as Giverny, France where, through special arrangement, his workshops enjoy private access to Monet’s Garden – the very birthplace of impressionism. He also leads destination workshops to Keukenhof Gardens in the Netherlands, Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Glacier National Park, Georgia’s Callaway Gardens, and other destinations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles is the author of the eBook Creative Macro Photography: Professional Tips &amp;amp; Techniques. Published in July 2010, it is already receiving rave reviews as one of the most comprehensive, unique books on macro photography ever published.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles’s photographs have been published in Nature’s Best and Outdoor Photographer magazines, the 2010 Inner Reflections engagement calendar, and are in private, corporate, and public collections worldwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles Needle’s website, including his upcoming macro, impressionistic and destination workshops is located &lt;a href="http://www.charlesneedlephoto.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.charlesneedlephoto.com&lt;/a&gt;. Information about his book Creative Macro Photography: Professional Tips &amp;amp; Techniques, is at &lt;a href="http://www.charlesneedlephoto.com/creative-macro-photography.html" target="_blank"&gt;www.charlesneedlephoto.com/creative-macro-photography.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information and a sample of Charles Needle's work can be found on the Boston West Photographic Society website at &lt;a href="http://www.bwps.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bwps.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bwps.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alan J. Kidawski</member_name><member_id>5162177</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Iadarola</member_name><member_id>5198329</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Lane</member_name><member_id>5229126</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287184126000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286505107000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creative Macro &amp; Impressionistic Photography with Charles Needle</name><id>15041737</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287012600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/15041737/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/global_14013533.jpeg</photo_url></item>