<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Look, I know, I know, you don't want to play frisbee. Neither do I, really. The nice weather? The sun shining? The birds flying through air, the bees doin' it while buzzing around? Gross. Nobody wants to see that. What ever happened to the freezing feet, the hail bouncing off your skull and leaving little dents, the snow blinding you and the wind knocking you off your feet? Those were the days, the halcyon days. The days where men were men and giants were giants. The days of yore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And I know, I know, you're tired, hungover, depressed, fat and lazy. Me too! God, I wish I could just sit around on my butt like a cow, chewing cud and digesting green grass with all four of my stomachs. I wish! To lazily wander through the pasture, hardly moving a foot an hour, getting occasionally pushed over by young hoodlums -- it sounds like bliss! Like paradise. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But it's sad, really. Our evil Boston Frisbee Dictator* is making us, nay!, forcing us, to play with those putrid weighted discs. To toss them around without meaning, without care, for hours on end -- it's a torture worse than burning alive in the fiery pit of hell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, I do apologize in advance, but unless you want to feel the wrath of Our evil Boston Frisbee Dictator*, I'd recommend you come and at least pretend you're having fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Chris M. &amp;amp; Kelli C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Namely, Joe Baz. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boring, tired, old information below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us this Tuesday to enjoy a beautiful night of spring frisbee. We'll be meeting at 8PM at the Cambridge Common baseball diamond which is located a couple blocks north of Harvard Square. We generally play from 8-10PM and then go out for food and drinks. Before attending our events, please review our &lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/350/about/"&gt;About Us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd recommend you bring a light-colored shirt for visibility's sake and a change of clothes. We supply all of the equipment necessary so there's really nothing else you need to bring besides your smiling face. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Organizers pay out of pocket for the frisbees, lanyards, glowsticks, field cones and first aid kits. Please consider bringing a couple bucks or visiting our Amazon Wishlist to support our equipment costs. Our group is free and will always be that way but your optional donations are certainly appreciated!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Surprisingly, they're aren't many large groups playing Frisbee in the dark.  We're by the softball field -- you'll find us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelli</member_name><member_id>4908325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210896411000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Chris' deadly good looks, of course.  And the Frisbee fun.</why><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210368902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Horrible, mind-blowingly boring Illuminated Frisbee on the Common.</name><id>7908218</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210723200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7908218/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/c/global_3460060.jpeg</photo_url></item>