<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0b2a40"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moonrise Kingdom&lt;/em&gt; is the latest from Wes Anderson. It boasts a star-studded cast. And some laughs. Reviewers are saying it’s the best Anderson has done since &lt;em&gt;Rushmore&lt;/em&gt;. Let’s see if they’re right.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0b2a40"&gt;*****From the theater website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0b2a40"&gt;Set on an island off the coast of New England in the summer of 1965, director/co-writer Wes Anderson's (&lt;em&gt;The Royal Tenenbaums&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Rushmore&lt;/em&gt;) comic romance/drama &lt;em&gt;Moonrise Kingdom&lt;/em&gt; tells the story of two twelve-year-olds, Sam (Jared Gilman) and Suzy (Kara Hayward), who fall in love, make a secret pact and run away together into the wilderness. As various authorities try to hunt them down, a violent storm is brewing offshore—and the peaceful island community is turned upside down in every which way. Also starring Bruce Willis as the local sheriff, Captain Sharp; Edward Norton as Khaki Scout troop leader Scout Master Ward; and Bill Murray and Frances McDormand as the young girl's parents, Mr. and Mrs. Bishop. Also starring Tilda Swinton, Jason Schwartzman, and Harvey Keitel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;*****&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I will purchase my ticket by 5:45 p.m., then wait at the foot of the stairs in the theater lobby. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for me carrying a red purse that slings from one shoulder to the opposite hip.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; At about 6:10, I will move into the theater auditorium (can’t miss the previews). You can find me there, if you are late. &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The movie starts at 6:30 p.m. Note that this movie is playing on two screens, and we are meeting for the 6:30 show.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;After the movie, I will wait in the theater lobby to gather everyone. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Look for the red purse&lt;/span&gt; (not as big as a backpack).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If we decide to go out after the movie, be prepared to add 25% to the cost of your order for both the tax and the tip. Restaurants in the area add the gratuity to the check automatically. Bring cash to make division of the check easier.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend this event so I know who to look for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Marianne&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and my red shoulder purse. You can catch up with me at three different points. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339425221000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339123526000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moonrise Kingdom</name><id>68266942</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339364700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/68266942/</event_url></item>