<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok as a backup paln for rain... Its doing that Again i see&lt;br /&gt;But just in case Lets still meet at Nevers Park.. &lt;br /&gt;as a meeting location.&lt;br /&gt;I want to know where it is anyway and have it listed again later...among other evening walks in the general area.to be listed soon...Hocanum linear trail...case mountain...etc...&lt;br /&gt;OK back to this particular event...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time to relieve some stress the day after Income Tax Day!  If you got a refund...GREAT!  If you had to pay Uncle Sam some more...DAMN!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;yep then its MacDonalds dollar menue dinner for you...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF ITS DRY OUT: Then continue as planned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;but lets meet at that lot if you want to go to the mall for excersize instead too..that way we can find ourselves..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, we'll take a walk on the trails at Nevers Park in South Windsor.  Gravel trails that wind through fields, woods and past ponds.  Meet in the parking lot at 6 pm for a 30-40 min walk.  Wear comfortable shoes and bring water.  We'll meet in the parking lot.  (This part of event will be cancelled if it's raining.   In which case, meet at Hooters at 7 pm)  Directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF ITS RAINING:  &lt;br /&gt;Im not a Mall person...but look at the bright side...its got a lot of fun things in there..(laugh and maybe buy some thing)..we would be in the area there anyway, Its DRY inside...its excersize...&lt;br /&gt;and, yes the food court isnt the greatest..its got something for everyone....Hooters..well thats an option too but it looks like no one wants to go.. so besides i want to see new sport stuff anyway..isnt Dicks new store there... (like i need more kayak /sport Junk)...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok i always found the best place to park at that particular mall is at the sears automotive /tool end..the lot is usually less crowded there and its easy to relocate yourself in the place for that fast get away......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This following part we can discuss at the walk: inside or outside location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After our walk, we'll go to Hooters for eats.  Great wings!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't or don't want to go on the walk, meet at Hooter's at 7 pm for dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO NEVERS PARK---&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford (20 mins):&lt;br /&gt;I 84 E exit 62 Buckland St.  Turn Left at end of exit ramp.  Go straight 2.5 miles thru many lites.   Turn right at lite onto Sand Hill Rd.  Take second left onto Abbe Rd. Ext.  Park in lot on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From points North:&lt;br /&gt;I 84 E exit 63. At end of exit turn Left onto Deming St.  Follow road 1.7 miles.  Turn right onto Sullivan Ave. Go .7 miles. Turn right onto Sand Hill Rd at lite.  Take second left onto Abbe Rd. Ext. Park in lot on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DIRECTION TO HOOTER'S---&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford (13 mins):&lt;br /&gt;I 84 E to exit 62.  At end of exit turn LEFT onto Buckland St.  Go to THIRD lite.  Take a LEFT.  Hooters on LEFT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from points North:&lt;br /&gt;I 84 W to Buckland St/US44/Middle Tpke West exit- Exit 62 &amp;amp; 60.  Take exit 62 toward mall and Buckland St.  Turn right at end of exit.  Hooters on right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177020115000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171819867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Back up Plan for A Walk in the Park and Eats at HOOTERS</name><id>5492053</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1176847200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5492053/</event_url></item>