<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>($5 for BBF card holders)</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The first settlers to arrive in &amp;quot;Boston&amp;quot; actually landed in &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Charlestown" target="_blank"&gt;Charlestown&lt;/a&gt;, so it was the first capital of the Massachusetts Bay Colony before the Puritans crossed over to Boston in 1630.  Come on this tour to hear the story of John Winthrop and his band of one thousand Puritans and why they moved out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But even without them, Charlestown continued to flourish.  Hear the story of this town and the very bad day they had in June 1775 - when the Battle of Bunker Hill led to a major conflagration and Charlestown was burned to the ground. Once again, Charlestown rallied and the tour will describe how the town flourished during the nineteenth century. It was an era when the Bunker Hill Monument was built and many of Charlestown's  citizens distinguished themselves.  Eventually you will learn of the annexation of Charlestown to the City of Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet your guides at the main gate of the Charlestown Navy Yard (Gate One) and be advised a walk up Bunker/Breed's Hill will be included in the tour. The tour is $12 person ($5 for card-carrying &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot members&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may want to follow the tour by getting a drink at the Warren Tavern, where you can raise a glass to Dr/Gen Joseph Warren, an unsung hero of the Revolutionary War.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for folks with Boston By Foot badges, bags, hats, etc.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246876974000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241633390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charlestown: Where Boston Began</name><id>10353162</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246483800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/10353162/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/global_8514328.jpeg</photo_url></item>