<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01864</zip><lat>42.577489</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kittys Restaurant</name><city>North Reading </city><id>795105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;The R rated hypnotist, Frank Santos Jr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.27.10 UPDATE: Seeing that we have a big turn out for this event I was able to get us all a discounted price.  We will now be paying $18.00 per ticket, remember to tell them that you are with the Meetup.com group!!  This event is posted on all 3 of our meetup sites and as of now we have 15 people that have called in to reserve their seat(s).  I also requested 1 big table for all of us, if you haven't called in to reserve your seat, please do so, so they know that we will need a bigger table or another table for all of us.  Also we can bring a camera's or video camera's, so grab your camera, have some laughs and meet some new people!!  Looking forward to this and see you all!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;UPDATE 1/9/10: To reserve your ticket you will need to call in your own reservation at the phone number below, when you call leave a message and they will call you back to get your information, when you call tell them &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&amp;quot;you want to reserve your ticket with the Meetup.com group&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;!  They will be putting us all at 1 or 2 tables (depending on the amount of people we have attending the event, we have this posted on all 3 of our groups.)  When you call they will need a credit card # to reserve your spot.  They will &lt;b&gt;NOT&lt;/b&gt; charge your card all that does is hold your spot.  When you get to the restaurant then you can pay for your ticket with cash.  We have been told that this is the week that the reservations start coming in so you want to make sure you don't miss this event.  If you don't call and want to pay at the door the night of the event you can do that but be prepared that if the event is sold out, then you will not be able to get it and that you may not be sitting with the rest of us from the group(s).  It only takes a minute to call in your reservation.  If there is a bad storm then they may cancel the show, we will be watching the weather before hand, but seeing that you are paying at the door then that shouldn't hold you back from calling ahead of time!  PLEASE remember to put on you RSVP that you have called in your reservation seeing that we need to get a count to the restaurant!  See you all there!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little bit about Frank Santos: Be amazed when you, your friends or strangers across the room become stars of the show, as I make them believe that they are singers, dancers and much, much more.  This is a performance where the audience becomes the show.  My performance has limitless variations and can please every appetite.  This is a hilarious, energetic and unique show that you will never forget!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little bit about the restaurant: Kitty's restaurant has been a fixture in North Reading for over 60 years. Join us for family-style Italian cooking with one of the largest menus in the North Reading area. Our menu has something for everyone, from grilled cheese and delicious pizza to home-style lobster pie. Whether you are a regular at Kitty's or just find yourself visiting North Reading, MA we look forward to seeing you. Enjoy our spacious dining rooms, or sit in our barroom where you can enjoy, good friends, our full bar, Keno &amp;amp; MA State Lottery, and root on the local sports teams playing on one of our HD TVs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out Frank Santos Jr's Website at &lt;a href="http://www.franksantosjr.com/homepage.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.franksanto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info and reservations for any show, please call 978-430-2990.  Full Kitty's menu available before and during the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20 per person.&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 6:30pm and the show starts at 8:15pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meetup early get settled, grab a bite to eat and sit back and enjoy the show!  We will only wait 15 minutes for you, if you are running late please come on in and find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the date gets closer I will call and see if I can reserve a few tables for us and I will update the site accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are responsible for getting your own ticket, paying your portion of the bill, tax and tip!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE: Bad weather may cancel this event, please check back for updates!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come out and get a really good laugh!&lt;br /&gt;We Look forward to seeing you!!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come on in and look for the table(s) with the Meetup sign(s).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265376261000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258930154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The R rated hypnotist, Frank Santos Jr.</name><id>11934076</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264895100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11934076/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>