<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On Thursday February 4th we will be starting a new set of Artist's Way meetups!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have not yet attended one of our meetups, and would like to talk with others who use Julia Cameron's creative guide &amp;quot;The Artist's Way,&amp;quot; here's a great opportunity to jump in. The original book (and follow-up volumes by Cameron) have proven a valuable resource for those seeking to support their creative work, whatever the discipline or medium.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tools and exercises are practical and inspiring, whether you are just starting out on a creative journey, are returning to a pursuit you set aside, or are a creative veteran continuing down the occasionally-rocky path of an artist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have attended earlier Artist's Way meetups, you likely discovered how helpful it can be to compare notes with others -- here's a chance to rededicate yourself to the journey.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Artist's Way Meetup Group assembled in June of 2009 with the goal of creating a Cluster Group and network based on Julia Cameron's books. We have a friendly core group of members who meet to discuss the books and encourage each other through creative challenges. We're always glad to welcome other fellow-travellers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On February 4th, the group will meet to renew and refocus the group's goals and parameters. And, whether or not you can attend this introductory session, we'd very much like your input on what you'd find most useful in an Artist's Way meetup. So, please take a moment and register your preferences in our poll &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Artists-Way-Cambridge/polls/222473"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;**Please note that we are STILL MEETING AT 7pm**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;If you are able, please bring a $5 donation to the Gallery for the use of their space -- thank you!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will greet you at the door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brooke</member_name><member_id>8390120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265934243000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Artists and Creators!</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Artists-Way-Boston-area</urlname><id>1471304</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Artists Way Boston Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262308290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Creative Fresh Start</name><id>wjxfmyndbgb</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265328000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Artists-Way-Boston-area/events/12187573/</event_url></item>