<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Garden St and Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.376808</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Common</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>697110</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120445</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Who doesn't enjoy a good pillow fight???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year, over 70 cities worldwide (including Budapest, Cape Town, Caracas, Chicago, London, Los Angeles, New York City, Orlando, Paris, Stockholm, Valencia, Vancouver, Washington DC.) participated in the First Annual Pillow Fight Day, with over 1200 people of all ages battling it out in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pictures from last year's event can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.bostonmagazine.com/party_pictures/gallery.html?gallery=248690" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonmaga...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston was the 3rd largest Pillow Fight in the world, right behind NYC and San Fran. And its happening again this year. This time, let's try to place in 1st!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DATE:  April 3, 2010&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION:  Cambridge Common in Harvard Square (&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/pillowfight" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly/pillowf...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;TIME:  3:00pm (at the sound of the airhorn) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We are planning to meet in front of the Lowes/Sony theater on Church Street  between 2:30 and 2:45 so we can chat a bit and head over together (while trying to be inconspicuous!).  I'll be wearing bunny ears and will have a meetup sign.  We'll make our way to the common at 2:45. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizers are really emphasizing getting there (in the vicinity of the statue on the common) 5 minutes early and remaining inconspicuous as this event depends on everyone going in at once! There will be a signal when everyone should rush in at exactly 3pm!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizers are asking each participant to bring a trash bag to assist with clean-up.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  Let's try to oblige and not make the city of Cambridge mad.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please try to be at the theater by 2:45, but if you're late, you're all set 'cuz you have everything you need to know!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in the afternoon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Melissa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RULES:&lt;br /&gt;1. Bring a pillow, a soft one is preferred.&lt;br /&gt;2. Don't hit anyone without a pillow&lt;br /&gt;3. If you are wearing glasses, make sure you take them off.&lt;br /&gt;4. Don't hit people with cameras (or glasses)&lt;br /&gt;5. No feathered pillows - let's keep the mess low.&lt;br /&gt;6. Go all out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costumes are, of course, encouraged. This event is child-appropriate!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're meeting @ Sony/Lowes theater on Church St. I'll be wearing bunny ears and have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melissa G</member_name><member_id>5191305</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270761606000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270136032000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Pillow Fight Day - April 3</name><id>13058408</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270319400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13058408/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/9/global_14063369.jpeg</photo_url></item>