<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>58 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.655319</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rockport Community House</name><city>Rockport</city><id>3201751</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.622498</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We hope you'll join us for the Thacher Island Art and Photo Show opening reception. It's a wonderful opportunity to view work from members of the CAPE and Seacoast Photographers Group, along with other North Shore artists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year’s show will once again be held at the lovely &lt;strong&gt;Rockport Community House.&lt;/strong&gt; (58 Broadway, Rockport, MA 01966)&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opening Reception:&lt;/strong&gt; Thursday, August 23,  from 7-9 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Show dates and times:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 24-25:   10 am – 8 pm &lt;br /&gt;

August 26:   10 am – 3:00 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information for those interested in participating:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need not have attended the island portion of the event in order to participate. There is a $25 donation in order to participate. (those who attended the island portion need not pay this again) Please see the information below for details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2012 Thacher Island Art and Photo Show&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Show Hours: Thursday August 23: opening reception: 7 – 9 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Friday &amp;amp; Saturday August 24 &amp;amp; 25: 10 am – 8 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Sunday August 26: 10 am – 4 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Location: Rockport Community House, 58 Broadway, Rockport MA &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;General show information:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

• Artists need not have been to Thacher Island, nor do the artworks need to be of or about the island and its lighthouses. &lt;br /&gt;

• The show is a fundraising event for the Thacher Island Association. Proceeds will help fund the Thacher Island Association’s restoration and maintenance projects on Thacher and Straitsmouth islands; all donations are tax-deductible. &lt;br /&gt;

o The Thacher Island Association requests a donation of $25.00 per artist to participate in this show. (If you attended the Art and Photo days on the island this year, the $25 you paid at that time includes participation in this show.) &lt;br /&gt;

o The Thacher Island Association will retain 40% of the proceeds from all sales. You may certainly choose to donate a greater percentage! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Drop-Off Schedule:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday August 22: 10:30 am – 5:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;

All art should be delivered to 58 Broadway, Rockport, between these hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

• You may enter up to three (3) framed works to hang, and up to a maximum of ten (10) flat pieces to be displayed in the bins. We will make every effort to hang as much work as we can, but space is limited.  &lt;br /&gt;

• Each piece should be identified with Title, Artist, Medium, Price. &lt;br /&gt;

• Notecards, postcards or groups of small works should be individually priced, and accompanied by an itemized list with prices. Please provide a suitable display – basket, rack, etc. There is no limit on the number of these pieces allowed. &lt;br /&gt;

• Please submit the following information to thacherart@gmail.com* by Sunday August 19: &lt;br /&gt;

Artist Name: &lt;br /&gt;

Address: &lt;br /&gt;

Phone: &lt;br /&gt;

E mail: &lt;br /&gt;

Total number of pieces: &lt;br /&gt;

Special instructions: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Description of each piece: &lt;br /&gt;

Title: &lt;br /&gt;

Media: &lt;br /&gt;

Framed size: &lt;br /&gt;

Price: Donation amount: &lt;br /&gt;

• A current one-page artist biography may be submitted. Do not attach to the art - these will be available in a binder for viewing by patrons.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Pick up unsold work at the Community House 4:30 – 6 pm on Sunday, August 26th. The Thacher Island Assoc. will have to remove everything from the building by this time! Please be sure to reclaim your unsold work! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Art Liability:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The Thacher Island Association and the Thacher Island Town Committee will not be responsible for art work lost, stolen or damaged. Every care and consideration will be taken in the handling of your work. &lt;br /&gt;

have great sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345774489000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344697638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thacher Island Art &amp; Photo Show</name><id>77301182</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345762800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/77301182/</event_url></item>