<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Main Street Art&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;in Newfield, NH&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;invites artists from the Seacoast Photographers Meetup Group to participate in a photographic exhibit entitled:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yin &amp;amp; Yang: A Combination of Opposites to Make the Whole. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;A black &amp;amp; white exhibit by local seacoast photographers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The opening reception will be September 14, 2012 and will run through October 20, 2012.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who Can Participate:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The show is open to any photographer who is a member of the Seacoast Photographer's Association. That's this Meetup group  - if you're a member of this group, you may participate. If you're not a member, sign up before the Call to Entry Submission Date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submissions:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Be sure to download and print &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/1528260/Yin%20and%20Yang%20Show%20Application.pdf"&gt;the Application&lt;/a&gt; included in the Files section (click the "More" navigation link near the top of this page, then select "Files" from the drop-down menu) of this Meetup group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Subject matter must be suitable for all age audiences and be represented in black &amp;amp; white - not sepia or selenium toning, or anything except black and white and shades of gray between.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Submit up to 3 digital images (JPG) and the $10 fee to arrive no later than 5PM on July 20th via:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt; to:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:mainstreetart@newfieldsart.org"&gt;mainstreetart@newfieldsart.org&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;or&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CD Mailed&lt;/strong&gt; to:  Main Street Art, P.O. Box 252, Newfields, NH 03856.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Files should be titled as: &lt;strong&gt;LastName_FirstName_01 Title.jpg&lt;/strong&gt;.  The number ("01" in the example) must correspond to the number on your submission form.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All entries will be judged for suitability by an independent panel of judges. Submissions that do not meet the guidelines (e.g. are not black and white, include something not suitable for all audiences, etc.) will be rejected by the judges. In the case that there are more submissions than space, the judges may reject pieces at their sole discretion. &lt;span&gt;Every artist submitting an entry form is guaranteed that at least one work will be in the September exhibit, assuming that the work adheres to all the guidelines related to subject, media, and framing.&lt;/span&gt;The decision of the judges is final.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All applicants will be notified of the judges' decisions via email by July 31st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanging Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 All works must be framed with white matting, and be wired for hanging. The maximum framed size allowed is 16” x 20”. Mats should be cleanly cut, frames should be fully intact and unmarred, glass should be thoroughly cleaned, and a wire for hanging should be attached. Sawtooth hangers or other methods of hanging are not acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drop-Off of Accepted Works:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Drop off your framed pieces at the Main Street Gallery on either Thursday, September 6th between 5PM and 7PM, or Saturday, September 8th between 9AM and Noon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Main Street Art Gallery is located at 75 Main Street in Newfields, NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exhibit: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; The opening reception is set for Friday, September 14th from 5PM-7PM. Invite your friends, family, and colleagues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the five-week photography exhibit, the gallery will be open on Satursdays from Noon to 3PM. We plan on Saturday ArtTalks on various topics of interest running from Noon to 1PM. If you are interested in sharing your photographic knowledge or special skill, contact&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="mailto:Tracy@tracyphillipsphotography.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tracy@tracyphillipsphotography.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volunteers:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This opportunity is brought to you in large part thanks to many months of hard work by volunteers from this group. When you see the following (listed alphabetically), please be sure to give them your thanks; they've been working very hard on your behalf:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Scot Langdon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deb McLarnon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Joe Perna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tracy Phillips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Debbie Thompson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cynthia Tokos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And all of the efforts so far have been toward planning and logistics. We can use more volunteers to staff the Saturdays the gallery is open, hanging, take-down, reception, and more. If you would like to volunteer your time, your help will be greatly appreciated by all.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in, you can't miss us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb </member_name><member_id>7653029</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cynthia</member_name><member_id>8758507</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debbie T</member_name><member_id>10849369</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>tracy</member_name><member_id>11265621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Perna</member_name><member_id>12948944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scot Langdon</member_name><member_id>14079065</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347846798000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338903634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yin &amp; Yang Photo Exhibit by Seacoast Photographers Group (that's us!)</name><id>67825562</id><headcount>150</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347656400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/67825562/</event_url></item>