<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We're on for The Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao by Junot Díaz&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;This is the long-awaited first novel from one of the most original and memorable writers working today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Things have never been easy for Oscar, a sweet but disastrously overweight, lovesick Dominican ghetto nerd. From his home in New Jersey, where he lives with his old-world mother and rebellious sister, Oscar dreams of becoming the Dominican J. R. R. Tolkien and, most of all, of finding love. But he may never get what he wants, thanks to the Fuk — the curse that has haunted the Oscar's family for generations, dooming them to prison, torture, tragic accidents, and, above all, ill-starred love. Oscar, still waiting for his first kiss, is just its most recent victim.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Diaz immerses us in the tumultuous life of Oscar and the history of the family at large, rendering with genuine warmth and dazzling energy, humor, and insight the Dominican-American experience, and, ultimately, the endless human capacity to persevere in the face of heartbreak and loss. A true literary triumph, The Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao confirms Junot Diaz as one of the best and most exciting voices of our time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;fans&amp;quot; have pushed us out of the Au Bon Pain, so we're heading back to the Clear Conscience cafe in Central Square.  Besides, I missed the couches:-)  Will be limiting the numbers again, so please please be respectful of your fellow readers and change those maybe's to no's if your plans become more finalized.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228783457000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224714066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: The Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao by Junot Díaz</name><id>9013299</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226966400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/9013299/</event_url></item>