<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>SKETCH-CRAWL ANNOUNCEMENT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: 2-3 hours starting at the posted time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE SCENE: We'll start at the scenic Pond next to the Griffin Photography Museum and meander our way to the scenic Mill Pond and along the river until we reach the Mystic Lakes. For years the Middlesex Canal was used as a working canal for transportation of mill goods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE CRAWL: We'll meander along our route, stopping 20-30 minutes at each site. Depending upon the time of day and how long we are out there, we may stop for a coffee or lunch break.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE TO MEET: At the posted time, with 15 minutes leeway for late-comers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;FROM 93:&lt;br /&gt;1. Take the Fellsway West Winchester exit. &lt;br /&gt;2. Off the ramp, continue around the rotary until you see &amp;quot;South Border Road&amp;quot; to your right. If you came from 93N it will be your first right.&lt;br /&gt;3. Straight 2 miles to the lights.&lt;br /&gt;4. Straight down the hill to the next lights.&lt;br /&gt;5. Straight to the rotary&lt;br /&gt;6. At the rotary take a right and continue straight till the pond and museum are on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM 128:&lt;br /&gt;Call me&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SOCIAL (OPTIONAL): Winchester Center Starbucks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  THINGS TO BRING WHICH ARE OFTEN FORGOTTEN: &lt;br /&gt;                        Paper towels, mosquito repellant, food, water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF LOST: If you become lost getting there, call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LAX: We meet at the time above. You have 30 minutes additional slack, after which we may leave to the painting site without you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INCLEMENT WEATHER: It is up to you to determine if the weather makes painting untenable. Although, I will try to leave a message on my voice mail if I myself do not intend to be there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Emerald&lt;br /&gt;617/968-0627&lt;br /&gt;westpointusma@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Emerald, CFA</member_name><member_id>3007793</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220379267000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>painter-84</urlname><id>576650</id><group_lat>42.4500007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Plein Air Artists Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219575269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SKETCH-CRAWL: Winchester Middlesex Canal</name><id>8608610</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220205600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/painter-84/events/8608610/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/c/global_1743932.jpeg</photo_url></item>