<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>101 North Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01756</zip><lat>42.122640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-473-7539</phone><name>Maple Farm Sanctuary</name><city>Mendon</city><id>669262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.566860</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Join us for our 4th Annual Picnic Fundraiser!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday, October 18, 2009&lt;br /&gt;1:00-5:00 pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a day of fun on Sunday, October 18th to help support Maple Farm&lt;br /&gt;Sanctuary. It will be an afternoon to enjoy the beautiful farm, foliage, music, raffles, speakers,&lt;br /&gt;friends and of course the animals. The family-friendly event will feature a presentation from&lt;br /&gt;Maple Farm Sanctuary co-founder Cheri Ezell-Vandersluis who will share the compelling&lt;br /&gt;story of how she and her husband, Jim, abruptly ended their profitable generations-long meat&lt;br /&gt;and dairy farming business to create a safe haven for animals Please welcome our &lt;b&gt;guest&lt;br /&gt;speaker, Harold Brown,&lt;/b&gt; a former beef farmer and founder of FarmKind who has made the&lt;br /&gt;transition from animal based to plant based agriculture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For a $10.00 donation per adult&lt;/b&gt; (children under 12 free) please come and picnic in&lt;br /&gt;the fields behind the barn (bring your own blanket or chairs). There will be some sandwiches,&lt;br /&gt;drinks and desserts as well, but make sure you get there early as we may run out!.&lt;br /&gt;Maple Farm Sanctuary is an animal sanctuary providing lifelong homes for abused, abandoned and&lt;br /&gt;unwanted farmed animals while promoting veganism and respect for all life through public information. They&lt;br /&gt;will live the remainder of their lives in peace, free to roam and meander the land.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maple Farm Sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;101 North Ave, Mendon, MA 01756&lt;br /&gt;www.maplefarmsanctuary.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is free parking at the farm. Sorry but please leave your dogs at home so our animals stay calm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256229802000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250655996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maple Farm Sanctuary Annual Picnic - Mendon, MA</name><id>11145723</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255885200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/11145723/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>