<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Yes its a Holiday Weekend and many people have a host of different things to do..&lt;br /&gt;I see Saturday as a good day for something to do outside, Sunday... maybe cloudy /rainy..too soon for a good idea and Monday..that's family day..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So here is something else i like to do and have not listed this kind of event here before since some of you don't kayak, some interested and some do it all the time..&lt;br /&gt;Here is another group event that might be of enjoyment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By all means post a comment, wether going or not going, your thoughts about more of these kind of events outside of the hike wine and pot luck dinners, etc. Those will be all summer...(some inside is ok too, obviously)&lt;br /&gt;Sorry no Happy Hour Stuff here..ITS OUTSIDE things till the cold winter.....the other groups do happy hour stuff and bar stuff all the time, every night....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White water rafting is soon so keep that in mind too.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK TO THE REAL EVENT:&lt;br /&gt;Salmon Cove is off of the Connecticut River located in East Haddam/Haddam CT&lt;br /&gt;The area has a easy parking and good launching facilities.&lt;br /&gt;The cove portion is pretty wide open and the river goes all the way up to the Leesville Dam to the fish ladder .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This area is good for Recreational Paddlers who want to see something different than just a lake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other places are on the list..just thought this is one place to do a good recreational paddle..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a few kayaks available for those who don't have one,&lt;br /&gt;I know there are a few other members that have a spare one also so..ya might as well come and enjoy the day on this supposed to be sunny SATURDAY..sunday looks cloudy/maybe rain..dont know...too far in advance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain...of course cancles the event, cloudy..lets just wait and see...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have one recreational for a biginner..Pungo 12 foot&lt;br /&gt;one transitional Tourlite 15 footer (i think Elaine will use this one)&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind dancer 18 footer..a true cadilack on the water..stable and smooth..&lt;br /&gt;Cobra expidition 18 footer, not really for beginners..Need paddle pants for this one.&lt;br /&gt;I usually use this one because i can get in the water quickly and do a rescue or you can easily grab onto this boat....&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro 18 footer...some beginners can handle this one but its pretty much a true sea kayak..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will try to get to the dam area if there is enough water flow but if not, its still a good place for novices and those who have some experience also, everyone can learn and enjoy the company of each other...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are all kinds of birds here, trees and marsh like areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;From Route 9 north or south: take exit 7, go east on rte 82 for 3.5 miles  (pass the goodspeed opra house) and turn left (north) onto rte 149. Go 1 mile to the marked access on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From hartford take rte 2 south,&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2 south: Take exit 16, Go south on rte 149 for 10.5 miles to the marked access on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2 north: take exit 18, go west on rte 16 for 4.3 and turn left (south) onto rte 149. Go 7.2 miles to the marked access on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For mapquest users and gps: use #110  rte 149 or E Haddam Moodus road, east haddam ct....(it gets you close enough) look at your maps anyway before taking the trip. ya might get weird travel routes..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some snacks and some water, if its sunny out...sunscreen...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let us know if you need a kayak and which type is your preference..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180972596000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179937861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Trip on Salmon Cove and Salmon River, East Haddam CT</name><id>5809942</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180199700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5809942/</event_url></item>