<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Thanks to the members who suggested a walk along freedom trail.  I checked the weather and Sunday will be sunny.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I seriously urge newcomers to Boston to join in getting to know what is one of Boston's greatest pride (after the soxes).  We will meet at the Visitor information Booth @Boston Common and walk over following the trail to Fanuiel Hall, have lunch and try to finish the rest of the trail. We can take it nice and easy and do as much as we can. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring your caps and cameras to do some down the nose touristy stuff ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Freedom Trail is a 2.5 mile red-brick walking trail that leads you to 16 nationally significant historic sites, every one an authentic American treasure. Preserved and dedicated by the citizens of Boston in 1958, when the wrecking ball threatened, the Freedom Trail today is a unique collection of museums, churches, meeting houses, burying grounds, parks, a ship, and historic markers that tell the story of the American Revolution and beyond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. Rain cancels this event. I will email out my cellno to those who have rsvped Yes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing right by the booth between tremont and west st.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218553953000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218041841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Freedom Trail Walk</name><id>8489863</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218378600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/8489863/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/9/global_4274761.jpeg</photo_url></item>