<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Waterhouse St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Commons</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>749006</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121445</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Outside Drumming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK - We're going to brave it.  We're going to send out requests for good weather.  We've going to meet  outside!  I know, with the weather being the way it has, it's a risk, but I'm willing to chance it - care to join me?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6:00-8:30pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be gathering at the central area where there are benches.  If you want to guarantee yourself a seat, then I suggest you bring one.  Otherwise, it's first-come, first-served.  We'll play from 6-8:30pm and &lt;u&gt;no later&lt;/u&gt;.  We don't want to risk getting the cops called on us for the noise.  (Could happen anyway, but if we keep it during the evening hours, we should be OK.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rain?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yeah, it might rain.  But it might not.  If it rains, we won't go.  I'll send a note to the list if we cancel it due to weather, but it will be sunny!  I swear!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring Friends!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're still growing the group and we want to see as many people as possible come out.  Please join us and bring a friend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring Drums&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unlike at the church where we usually rent a car, Don and I will be coming via T and carrying our drums by hand, so we're going to be limited in how many drums we can bring.  Please bring your own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge Commons - you know, by Harvard Square in Cambridge - the big green space in the middle of all the racing cars.  It's an adventure, right?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Beginner's Class&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry, we've only got 2.5 hours - we're going to rock out the whole time.  Come anyway - you'll figure it out.  We'll help.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the sound of the drums!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelle Sparta</member_name><member_id>1953058</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248025902000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Rhythm Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-drum-circle</urlname><id>617617</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245861260000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drumming On Cambridge Common</name><id>10725722</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246399200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-drum-circle/events/10725722/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/a/f/global_8680271.jpeg</photo_url></item>