<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 Exchange St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.879723</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-723-4266</phone><name>GAMM Theatre</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>450230</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.379850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;Updated 01/07/12 -- Tickets Purchased.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this Meet-up we will return to the Gamm Theater for "Festen." Here is the description on the Gamm's website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"&lt;span&gt;Helge is turning sixty, and everyone is coming home for the party. His eldest son, Christian, whose twin sister, Linda, recently committed suicide, will raise the first toast&amp;hellip; and reveal a shocking family secret. Trapped for 24 hours within the walls of the lavish country estate&amp;mdash;rocked by revelations that shatter the veneer of respectability&amp;mdash;even the disbelieving guests are choosing sides as the truth painfully unfolds. Adapted from the award-winning 1998 Danish film by the same title (released in the U.S. as &amp;ldquo;The Celebration&amp;rdquo;), Festen redefines tragedy for a modern age. For mature audiences only.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;"&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $46.75 (including Gamm's Convenience Charge.). Seating is reserved. (Prices at Gamm have gone up for 2011/12.&amp;nbsp; They are now $42.00 plus a $4.75 convenience charge.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;RSVPs for this Meetup will close on Friday, January 6th. I will purchase the tickets on the 7th.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Gamm Theater at 7:30 PM. I will also provide my cell number in case you need to reach me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payment Options &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you RSVP, there will be a question asking how you wish to pay for your ticket.&amp;nbsp; Please note that I must have payment prior to January 7th so I can purchase our tickets.&amp;nbsp; I'm open to any option other than a personal check.&amp;nbsp; Here are my preferred choices:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) If you're going to another Meetup with me prior to 1/7/12, you may pay me in cash or cashiers check at that time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) I can provide my mailing address and you can send me a cashiers check or money order.&amp;nbsp; (No personal checks.)&amp;nbsp; Remember, though, that I need it before 1/7/12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) Provide your e-mail address and I will send you a Paypal Invoice.&amp;nbsp; You may use that invoice to pay by credit card or direct bank debit.&amp;nbsp; Note that you do NOT need a Paypal account to pay by credit card.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refund Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full refunds (including the convenience charge) will be provided if you change your RSVP to "NO" &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;on or before 01/06/12.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full refunds (including the convenience charge) will be provided if the play is sold out and we are unable to get tickets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Once tickets are purchased on 01/07/12, no refunds will be provided.&amp;nbsp; You will be responsible for the disposal of your ticket if you're unable to attend.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside front entrance</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329012269000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317755717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Festen</name><id>36133612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329006600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/36133612/</event_url></item>