<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&lt;h2&gt;Come One - Come All! &lt;/h2&gt; We'll be creating sacred space and sharing in the energies of our connection. Whether you are an experienced drummer or just starting out, there is space for you in our circle. And what would a circle be without dancers? So come and join us for this joyous celebration of life. &lt;/b&gt; - Bring your drums, rattles, Native American flutes, digeridoos, etc. We will open up the room and get it rocking with the rhythms. There will be space made for both heart-pounding beats and softer rhythms with room for voices and instruments. Suggested donation of $5 to cover the costs of maintaining this Meetup group, and the costs of electricity and heat for the church. &lt;b&gt;If you have instruments to share, please bring them!&lt;/b&gt; url=http://www.maldenuua.org/]The First Parish in Malden[/url]&lt;/b&gt;, a Unitarian Universalist congregation, is located three blocks west of the Malden Center T station at 2 Elm Street (intersection with Pleasant Street), just off Route 60. Convenient, free parking is available between the church and the Beebe Elementary School. Visit MaldenUUA.org for directions and map. We run this event once each month on the third Sunday of the month. &lt;b&gt;I look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;/b&gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe</member_name><member_id>9541111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358725479000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Rhythm Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-drum-circle</urlname><id>617617</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294519007000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Drum and Dance Monthly Meetup</name><id>qwhfqyrcbbc</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358704800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-drum-circle/events/96431922/</event_url></item>