<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Late Breaking NEWS!!!! The Boston Globe is doing an article on the Boston Karaoke Meetup and will be joining us to experience our Karaoke Meetup first hand.  They will also have a photographer on hand to take pictures.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course, you can choose not to be in any pictures if you are shy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But if you decide to let the Boston Globe take your pictures, you might become famous with your picture in the Boston Globe... It's fun for your friends and family to see you in a major metropolitan newspaper.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yeah!&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to RSVP by Midnight November 1st to keep your admission fee to $10.00 only.  Anyone who RSVP's after that time will have to pay $20.00.  This is looking like a great meetup with already 13 people who are definitely coming....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can't wait.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Phil&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Boston Karaoke Meetup Members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am pleased to announce the November 3rd, 2007 Meetup at 8:00-10:00PM! We're having it at the Limelight in Boston. Space is limited, so please RSVP right away so we can reserve a spot for you.  The regular admission fee is $20.00 per person, but if you RSVP by November 1st that you are coming, the cost is only $10.00 for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members range from semi-professional to first-time karaoke singers. We have excellent performers who provide high quality entertainment for us all, we have beginners who are surprisingly good but nonetheless want a supportive environment to try out their talents. Then there are the rest of us in various stages of development. All experience levels are welcome and supported.  I've received a lot of interest for another Meetup so please sign up early so you don't miss out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, I will be posting pictures from this meetup.  Please come back and take a look at the fun everyone had.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an added bonus, the Boston Globe is doing an feature article on the Boston Karaoke Meetup club and will be there with photographers.  Please join me in making the  Boston Globe feel welcome at our club. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, I look forward to meeting all of you at the Boston Karaoke Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Meetup Coordinator, &lt;br /&gt;- Phil&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip L</member_name><member_id>1522860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194900722000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonkaraoke</urlname><id>212993</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Karaoke Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192675588000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November 2007 Boston Karaoke Meetup</name><id>6570534</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1194134400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonkaraoke/events/6570534/</event_url></item>