<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 Fenway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338776</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum</name><city>Boston</city><id>668992</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098230</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Whats not to love about great music, art, drinks and appetizers ?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who've never been,  The &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isabella_Stewart_Gardner_Museum" target="_blank"&gt;Gardner is not your typical museum&lt;/a&gt;.  Its the former mansion of the late &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isabella_Stewart_Gardner" target="_blank"&gt;Isabella Stewart Gardner&lt;/a&gt; who was an art patron back in the late 1800's in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her house has been kept as a museum of her collections, and has been open to the public for many years, also hosting classical chamber music performances.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;After Hours&amp;quot; events are lots of fun.  Gwen and I love this place and would love you to join us.  The after hours events at the Garnder are really classy and are great for conversation, as they are not as noisy and cramped as a typical bar would be . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's more info on the event and the website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gardnermuseum.org/afterhours/event_may.asp" target="_blank"&gt;Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum Event - After Hours&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May 20th, 2010 – Spring Splendor&lt;br /&gt;The Gardner’s central courtyard might be one of the coolest places in Boston (well, at least we think so!), filled with plants and works of art – it is here we can see Isabella Gardner’s love of living things. So gardens at the Gardner at the theme tonight with all kinds of green ways to explore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Courtyard Music: from courtyard tonight from 5:30-7pm and then again from 8:15-9pm&lt;br /&gt;    * Viewfinder Conversations: Join a discussion about John S. Sargent’s famous portrait of Isabella Gardner (every half-hour), plus other impromptu gallery discussions (6 to 8:30PM)&lt;br /&gt;    * Sketching in the Galleries: Drop by the Dutch Room and sketch for a while, from 6-9pm.&lt;br /&gt;    * Hands On: Swing by the outside gardens and pot up a few nasturtium seeds to take home and grow. Yeah, yeah, we know it’s a little hokey, but you’ll love it! Who wouldn’t want to grow one of Gardner’s favorite flowers? (Weather dependant.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing between the Atrium and Entrance, and I will wear a "MEETUP" name tag so you'll see me.  Also I'll announce the day or so before what im wearing. </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274397017000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272417999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jazz, Art and Cocktails at the ISGM</name><id>13313244</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274392800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/13313244/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/3/global_14685667.jpeg</photo_url></item>