<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>La Vita Gustosa in East Haddam, CT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tasty life is what “La Vita Gustosa” means in Italian at this Ristorante Italiano. This restaurant is located a short walk from the East Haddam (42B) airport. After parking the plane and dropping a $5 landing fee in the honor box, a short walk up the road into the center of town of about ¼ mile will bring you to the classic Italian restaurant. The Goodspeed Opera House is across the street. Many of the patrons of the restaurant dine before going to the opera house. Dining can be formal or casual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group could enjoy the patio during a warm late-summer night. The restaurant has a full service bar for the non pilots as well as live entertainment on weekends. There are are also numerous tables inside the establishment.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food, there is plenty of food!  All of the entrees were under $19.00 with many in the $9-15 dollar range.  This restaurant serves the center of town and is supported only by a small percentage of pilots. Most of the business is from the townspeople and it has survived a long time attesting to the good food. And Like Matt says our flyouts seem to be all about food!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.navmonster.com/apt/42B" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.navmonster...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check out the runway page.  This is one of the shorter fields we will be flying to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Goodspeed airport has a runway 14/32 and sports a 2120 x 50 foot runway. You want to make sure you have your short field techniques under control and keep your speed on target to be comfortable with the landing. There are no instrument approaches and fuel is unavailable. The restaurant can be contacted at 860-873-8999 and they accept reservations. Their website is &lt;a href="http://www.lavitagustosa.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lavitagust...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>show up at the terminal, Twin City rampside, Charley's hangar, or the active runway...You'll find us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Bortle</member_name><member_id>6715847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283552538000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275140392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ristorante Italiano !!! need I say more?</name><id>13631555</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283376600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/13631555/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/global_16974269.jpeg</photo_url></item>