<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Wheelerville Rd, off Route 4</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05701</zip><lat>43.643330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brewers Corner, Bucklin Trailhead</name><city>Mendon</city><id>8047622</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.931320</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them may result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;What we're doing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is to climb one of the 4,000 foot summits in VT—Killington Peak (4,241 ft) hitting Pico peak (3,957 ft - one of the New England Hundred Highest) along the way. From its bare summit, Killington Peak reportedly has some of the best views in all of New England: the Green Mountains, Lake Champlain, White Mountains, Taconics, and even the Adirondacks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are out-of-shape and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;- all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dogs are permitted -&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;provided they are experienced "hikers" are not disruptive to others on the trail. Please email us re: your dog if you hope to bring one.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; traverse trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 10 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 2,600 feet&lt;/strong&gt; - it should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 6.2 hrs to complete.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; After spotting cars at Brewers Corner/Bucklin Trailhead on Wheelerville Rd, we will begin our hike at the Sherburne Pass Trailhead (across from the Inn at Long Trail on Route 4), and take the Sherburne Pass and Long Trails to Pico Peak, and then continue on to Killington Peak, then descend the Bucklin trail to Brewers Corner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using a trail map and the Internet. You should also become familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions—or heavy rain—will cancel this trip.&lt;/span&gt; I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=43.602521593464054&amp;amp;lon=-72.81927108764648&amp;amp;site=btv&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(noaa.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;list of items needed for a day hike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Appalachian Mountain Club&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or out on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be meeting at Brewers Corner/Bucklin Trailhead on Wheelerville Rd off of Route 4, in Mendon, VT.  According to Google Maps this spot is about 170 miles from Boston and it should take about 3 hours 20 min to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;&lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=Wheelerville+Road,+Mendon,+VT&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=43.63446,-72.854462&amp;amp;spn=0.068457,0.167198&amp;amp;sll=43.627875,-72.851372&amp;amp;sspn=0.136928,0.334396&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFa-LmQIdRdmn-ymDwdtsWi_giTEUQ8NHFA57yw&amp;amp;oq=Wheelerville+Rd&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;z=13"&gt;driving directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt; (google.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1343746056000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341441736000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VT4K - Killington &amp; Pico Peaks (Intermediate)</name><id>71975662</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343570400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/71975662/</event_url></item>