<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 Arborway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.308380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-1718</phone><name>Arnold Arboretum</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>595034</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's take a walk at the Arnold Arboretum and enjoy a beautiful Saturday. The Arboretum (in all of its T-accessible glory) is a large park with many exotic trees, plants and flowers. There are some medium-sized hills, but no dramatic elevation. Directions and more information can be found here: &lt;a href="http://arboretum.harv..." target="_blank"&gt;http://arboretum.harv...&lt;/a&gt;. Additional points: - We will move along at a moderate pace, and the whole walk should take about 2 - 2 1/2 hours. - Last time people found parking to be fairly easy on the Arborway (the same street as the park is on) and the nearby Forest Hills T Station. - Find us near the main entrance at 11:00 a.m. We will wait until 11:15 a.m. and set off with those present. Karen The Arnold Arboretum of Harvard University is the oldest public arboretum in North America and one of the world&amp;#146;s leading centers for the study of plant biodiversity. Its mission is to integratively examine plant diversity&amp;#151;from genomic, developmental, organismic, evolutionary, and ecosystem perspectives&amp;#151;in order to foster greater understanding and appreciation of plant life in its full complexity. Established in 1872 and planned and designed in collaboration with Frederick Law Olmsted, the Arnold Arboretum is a National Historic Landmark and one of the best preserved of Olmsted&amp;#146;s landscapes. Founded as a public-private partnership between the City of Boston and Harvard University, the Arnold Arboretum is a unique blend of respected research institution and beloved public park in Boston&amp;#146;s Emerald Necklace. Occupying 265 acres, the Arboretum&amp;#146;s living collection of trees, shrubs, and woody vines is recognized as one of the most comprehensive and best documented of its kind in the world. The living collection is supported by comprehensive curatorial documentation, herbaria containing more than 1.3 million specimens, extensive library and archival holdings, and a 43,000-square-foot state-of-the-art research center. These facilities and holdings, along with 75 full-time staff, provide the basis for research and education by Harvard faculty and students, Arboretum scholars, and visiting scientists from around the world. Free and open to the public every day of the year, the Arboretum is a safe and accessible community resource that is utilized by thousands of visitors each year. As a university-based living collection, the Arnold Arboretum has the opportunity to share a wealth of knowledge with the public in a way that is engaging, substantive, and long-lasting. Outreach enrichment efforts include&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318781837000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316987704000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Arnold Arboretum 125 Arborway, Jamaica Plain, MA (map)</name><id>34921372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318777200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/34921372/</event_url></item>