<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I can't make this one so I'm hoping someone will volunteer to be the organizer.  If you're willing, please include a note in your RSVP.  Thanks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Times aren't posted for next weekend yet so please check back on Saturday morning for the actual time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.australiamovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.australiamovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.australiam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the movie: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Nicole Kidman, Hugh Jackman, David Wenham, Bryan Brown, Jack Thompson &lt;br /&gt;Director: Baz Luhrmann &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An English aristocrat inherits an Australian ranch the size of Maryland. When English cattle barons plot to take her land, she reluctantly joins forces with a rough-hewn cattle driver to drive 2,000-head of cattle across hundreds of miles of the country's most unforgiving land, only to still face the bombing of Darwin by the Japanese forces that had attacked Pearl Harbor only months earlier. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Critics:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Luhrmann brings an unapologetically over-the-top and operatic aesthetic to the table.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Kenneth Turan&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...the banal story and predictable arc seems a departure for director Baz Luhrmann (Moulin Rouge!), whose work is usually more inventive.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;USA Today&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Claudia Puig&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...the beauty of the film's stars and landscapes, the appeal of the central young boy and, perhaps more than anything, the filmmaker's eagerness to please tend to prevail, making for a film general audiences should go with, even if they're not swept away.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Variety&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Todd McCarthy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228781116000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228067754000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Australia</name><id>9251212</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228608000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/9251212/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/b/global_6472123.jpeg</photo_url></item>