<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Braintree, MA</address_2><address_1>128 Town Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.203080</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>n/a</phone><name>Braintree High School</name><city>Braintree</city><id>172533</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.021370</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>85.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Belly dance is for real women with real women's bodies, and anyone can learn to belly dance. An ancient art that is extremely accessible, versatile, sexy and fun, belly dance gently exercises the whole body while improving coordination, grace, flexibility and posture. Classes include a warm-up of rhythmic limbering, movement rehearsal and specific dance conditioning exercises. A breakdown of all essential movement vocabulary will be introduced as students explore the many aspects of belly dance, including hip work, isolations, floor work, veil and drum solo.  &lt;a href="http://www.braintreeadulted.com/courses/wdance.html#belly" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.braintreea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Deadline for Class Registration:&lt;/b&gt; The deadline to register for this class is Tuesday, January 19th (sorry for short notice)  We need 7 people to register for this class to take place.  I will be dropping my registration off on Monday of next week, so if you need me to do it for you I can meet you and get the information from you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To register do the following:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DROP-OFF:&lt;br /&gt;There is a drop-off box in front of the main office at Braintree High School. Enclose your registration form and payment in an envelope and address it to Community Continuing Education. Braintree High School hours are 9:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m., Monday through Friday.&lt;br /&gt;IN PERSON:&lt;br /&gt;Stop by the Braintree Community Continuing Education office at Braintree High School. The office is diagonally across from Rm. 101. Regular office hours are 6:00 p.m. to 8:30 p.m., Monday through Thursday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duration of class:&lt;/b&gt; 1 hour and 15 minutes.  Every Monday for 8 weeks, starting January 25th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Recommended Attire:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear comfortable dance or exercise clothing and plan to dance in bare feet, or soft dance shoes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Optional wear:&lt;/b&gt;  includes skirts or harem pants, cropped half tops and tank tops or decorated bra tops, fringed or coined belts, jewelry and make-up. Bear in mind you won't want to feel hindered while dancing. Hip belt, veil, finger cymbals to each class.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fees:&lt;/b&gt; $85 per person for 8 weeks. Membership fees - free for everyone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Minimum/maximum attendance:&lt;/b&gt; Minimum of 7 people (incl. organizer). May cancel if less than 7 people rsvp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadlines:&lt;/b&gt; Tues, Jan 19th at 5pm. After that time please email or contact an organizer directly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt;  Braintree High School, Town Street. Click here for directions: &lt;a href="http://www.braintreeadulted.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.braintreea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please enter the school through the main entrance of the building near the flag pole. All others doors are locked.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chandra</member_name><member_id>4844140</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1264873975000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263565418000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Belly Dance Class - for 8 mondays</name><id>12327327</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264468500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/12327327/</event_url></item>