<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>[b]Update[/b]

The time of the movie is 6:10. I will be at the thater lobby at 5:40. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be waiting by the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where the tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand. We'll head into the move 10 minutes before showtime.


[b]Original Description[/b]

I have been fascinated by the premise of this film since I saw the trailer earlier this year, and with Bill Murray starring, I just gotta see it.

I strongly suggest buying your ticket ahead of time at fandango.com. Be sure to pick the right date! It's a Saturday! I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. For new folks, if you miss the gathering before the film, no worries, we regroup after the film just outside the room where the film shows. And then we go out to discuss the movie over munchies and a beer. Or two. 


[b]Synopsis[/b]

For generations, the people of the City of Ember have flourished in an amazing world of glittering lights. But Ember's once powerful generator is failing... and the great lamps that illuminate the city are starting to flicker. Now, two teenagers in a race against time, must search Ember for clues that will unlock the ancient mystery of the city's existence, and help the citizens escape before the lights go out forever.

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/0hF72jiaj5Y&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See description for how to find me...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230918594000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222733366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>City of Ember</name><id>8860331</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223761500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8860331/</event_url></item>