<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the Museum of Science website&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/events_activities/lectures&amp;amp;d=4187" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/ev...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;: Cahners Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With Terrence Masson, ACM SIGGRAPH 2010 Conference Chair; director, Game Design, Northeastern University; author, CG101: A Computer Graphics Industry Reference&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Ever wonder who coined the phrase 'computer graphics' or how PIXAR got its name? Animation and visual effects producer Terrence Masson draws on more than two decades of experience to explore the history of computer graphics. Hear behind-the-scenes stories about the people and companies that formed the CG industry and about the tools and techniques that are currently creating a buzz. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Mr. Masson is also chairing the 2010 SIGGRAPH conference — the premier international event on computer graphics and interactive techniques. Get a sneak peek at this year's event, which will bring together the most respected technical and creative people who are excited by research, science, art, animation, gaming, interactivity, education, and the Web. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Seating is limited. Seating passes are available to the general public in the Museum lobby beginning at 5:45 p.m. on the evening of the program; first come, first served. Museum members may reserve a limited number of seating passes in advance by calling between 9:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m. on Monday and Tuesday the week of the program only: 617-589-3169&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheryl White, who helps organize the lectures, is going to put aside 20 Will Call tickets for T.J. Maher to pick up for our group. T.J. should be standing in the front lobby by 5:50 pm if you want to grab a ticket, or if you are a Museum of Science member, you can reserve your own tickets if you wish. Although the doors will not open until 6:45 pm for the general seating, by 6:30 pm they will allow a few of us to go upstairs and reserve seats for our group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Terrence Masson's website&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.visualfx.com/visualfx.com.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.visualfx.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;My really really short bio&lt;/u&gt; :&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I mainly build (and optimize) animation studios now ... but I have also enjoyed two decades of fun in a wide variety of areas ... I’ve directed award winning short animated films, was the sole developer of the original South Park CG animation technique, built a pre-vis department for Douglas Trumbull, fed Boba Fett to the Sarlac and flew the Millennium Falcon for George Lucas ... among many other things.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As a member of the Producers Guild of America,  Visual Effects Society and an ACM SIGGRAPH Pioneer I enjoy a worldwide collection of great friends&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Terrence Masson's book &amp;quot;CG 101: A Computer Graphics Industry Reference&amp;quot;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/CG-101-Computer-Graphics-Reference/dp/073570046X" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;CG101 is the first comprehensive resource guide written in plain language for all levels of computer graphics users. It is also the first and only detailed behind-the-scenes history about the people and companies that have formed today's industry. Hundreds of contributors and in-depth interviews give a never-before-seen look into the earliest years of CG right up to present day. In addition to the historical perspective, CG 101 includes detailed tips and tricks, demo reel guidelines and CG job descriptions to help those looking to get into the business. The hundreds of software tool descriptions all have extensive contact information, including Web addresses and phone numbers for easy reference&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to be able to reserve your own ticket&lt;/b&gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Become a member of The Museum of Science! &lt;a href="https://store.mos.org/index.php?action=memb_buy;c=1" target="_blank"&gt;https://store.mos.org...&lt;/a&gt; For $75.00 you and a friend or loved one, with a Basic 2 membership, can visit the museum an unlimited amount of times and their everchanging list of special exhibits. If you plan on visiting the museum twice in the next year, it pays for itself with the two free Omni theater tickets and free Laser show or Planetarium show. You also get highly discounted admission to the Harry Potter exhibit currently showing, along with the ability to make reservations for free lectures such as this one on the Monday and Tuesday the week of the lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Museum of Science in the News:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Museum of Science to Transform Planetarium into New England's Most Technologically Advanced Digital Theater&lt;/u&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/visitor_info/museum_news/press_releases&amp;amp;d=4063" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/vi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;December 01, 2009&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;—$9 Million Renovation of Charles Hayden Planetarium will begin January 2010— &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;BOSTON—The Museum of Science, Boston today announced it will undertake a year long physical and technological renovation of the Charles Hayden Planetarium starting January 4, 2010. The $9 million transformation will include the installation of new and more powerful technologies. Plans include a 57-foot dome, a new interior, surround sound system, and the latest in high-definition immersive video and digital acoustic capabilities. Following renovations, the Museum will offer the most technologically advanced digital theater in New England. The transformation, which is slated for completion in early 2011, is being funded through the Charles Hayden Foundation and private donations, with significant support from the Massachusetts Cultural Facilities Fund, Suffolk Construction, and the Highland Street Foundation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The centerpiece of the new Planetarium will be the Zeiss Starmaster, a custom-built optics system that replicates the night sky and re-creates cosmic phenomena such as solar eclipses. Museum staff will use the Zeiss Starmaster along with a full-dome video display system and digital animation technology to create original programming that simulates not only traveling through space, but also swimming through the ocean with sharks or flowing through the human heart with blood cells. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The purchase of this $2 million projector was made possible through the support of the Charles Hayden Foundation. An additional final capstone gift of $1 million brought the Foundation's contribution to one-third of the total $9 million renovation cost. [ &lt;b&gt;MORE&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/visitor_info/museum_news/press_releases&amp;amp;d=4063" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/vi...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Museum of Science, Boston&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Museum takes a hands-on approach to science, engineering and technology, attracting about 1.5 million visitors a year via its programs and 700 interactive exhibits. Founded in 1830, the Museum was first to embrace all the sciences under one roof. Highlights include the Thomson Theater of Electricity, Charles Hayden Planetarium, Mugar Omni Theater, Gordon Current Science &amp;amp; Technology Center, 3-D Digital Cinema and Butterfly Garden. Reaching 25,000 teens a year worldwide via the Intel Computer Clubhouse Network, the Museum also leads a multi-museum, $20 million National Science Foundation-funded nanotechnology education initiative. The Museum's &amp;quot;Science Is an Activity&amp;quot; exhibit plan has been awarded many NSF grants and influenced science centers worldwide. Its National Center for Technological Literacy® aims to enhance knowledge of engineering and technology for people of all ages and inspire the next generation of engineers, inventors, and scientists. The Museum is ranked #3 by Parents Magazine in its list of the country's Ten Best Science Centers&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maps &amp;amp; Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/visitor_info/maps_and_directions" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/vi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You get discounted parking if you are a member of the Museum of Science &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/visitor_info/parking_information" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org/vi...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;By T&lt;/b&gt;: &amp;quot;Take the M.B.T.A.'s Green Line subway to Science Park station. This will be the Green Line's Lechmere-bound 'E' train. The Museum is diagonally across the street (O'Brien Highway), just over the Charles River Dam draw bridge&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264810354000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262646303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Terrence Masson, lecture, "Living in a CG World" @ Museum of Science</name><id>12221342</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264636800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12221342/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/d/global_12505149.jpeg</photo_url></item>