<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take your Flintstones Vita Mines, eat your Oats, Wheeties or Special K for this one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I AM SEEING WINDS IN OUR FAVOR, IN THE MORNING IT WILL BE PUSHING US OUT AND IN THE AFTERNOON PUSHING US BACK WITH SLACK TIDE ON THE WAY BACK&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check for weather updates or changes: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHVN&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Weather: &lt;br /&gt;Saturday:  Sunny, with a high near 74. North wind between 5 and 9 mph. &lt;br /&gt;Saturday: N wind 6 to 11 kt ( Blowing us to the islands) becoming variable and less than 5 kt (to blow us back). Sunny. Seas around 1 ft.&lt;br /&gt;(Wind will do a complete reversal about 12-1 pm or so in our favor)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOUR BOAT RIDES LOW TO THE WATER -  BRING A SPRAY SKIRT IF YOU HAVE ONE, IF NOT BRING A SPONGE. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOUR RECREATIONAL YACKS SHOULD DO OK SINCE I HAVE TAKEN YOU OUT IN VERY SIMILAR CONDITIONS AND MOST OF YOU HANDLED IT JUST FINE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AS USUAL WE CAN ADJUST COURSE AND MAKE ASSESSMENTS AS WE GO ALONG SINCE THIS ISLAND TRIP HAS MANY DIFFERENT COURSES TO TAKE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I originally planned to do a 10 mile trip but can easily modify it to 5 OR whatever if we need to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CT Coastal Kayaking does tours here too if you cant make my event.&lt;br /&gt;They have a great map of the islands:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctcoastalkayaking.com/files/thimbletour.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctcoastalkayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year i think just unloading at the Stony Creek town boat ramp &amp;amp; you figure out your self where to park in town  is easier than last years muddy trip. Be cautious of getting a ticket in some spaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park where you can, IE. Thimble Islands rd, Three Elms rd, Buenavista rd. etc. Good Luck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE: I have chosen &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;10:00 am&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; be at the site to unload, etc. in hopes to get the better parking. Yeah its earlier than my other events but its still early in the fall season and tourists are still  visiting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The After party location is being chosen based on availability and utility (this time of year a nice BIG fire and more private place seems to fit us better), I do not feel Stony Creek beach is private enough.&lt;br /&gt;7 Falls or CIP are among the choices right now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: Be sure to check your own maps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS address: apx #207 Thimble Islands Road, Branford CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Generic Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East : I-95 South to Exit 56, which is the Stony Creek exit. Take a left at the end of the exit ramp onto East Industrial Road and proceed .3 miles. Then turn left onto Leetes Island Road and continue 1.6 miles. At the four-way intersection, continue straight onto Thimble Islands Road and proceed 0.7 miles on Thimble Islands Road, &lt;br /&gt;At the intersection of Three Elms Rd, the put in is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;Please unload and find a parking spot in town somewhere. ? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West (New Haven Direction) : I-95 North to Exit 56, which is the Stony Creek / Leetes Island rd. exit. &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp, take a right onto Leetes Island Road and continue for 1.5 miles. At a four-way intersection with Stony Creek rd, --&amp;gt; continue straight for 0.7 miles on Thimble Islands Road, &lt;br /&gt;At the intersection of Three Elms Rd, the put in is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;Please unload and find a parking spot in town somewhere. ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides. Low 7:39 am  High 2 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU CANT MAKE MY EVENT - THE BRANDFORD AND STAMPFORD KAYAK GROUP WILL BE HAVING THEIR THIMBULL ISLAND TOUR ON THE 25&amp;quot;TH OF SEPT.&lt;br /&gt;Join them if you want, same place for parking, same places to see, just a bit later date..weather ? maybe perfect maybe not so? its a gamble but another chance to go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;###&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Paddle &amp;amp; Paddle Leash, Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doughnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any &amp;quot;Wide Butt&amp;quot; (greater than 17&amp;quot;~18&amp;quot; butts) yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;Don't laugh, its serious, some will not fit in a yak thats too small (ie the Greenlander Pro--maximum butt and hips width of 12 inches limit) of an opening and i will feel sad you cant go..etc..the other option is to maybe trade with someone, etc, if you need to.&lt;br /&gt;This has worked in the past very well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a positive confirmed yes and by persons i have some idea to match a boat to a  paddle skill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS IS A GREAT SPOT AND GENERALLY IS EASY TO PADDLE BUT AT TIMES THE WEATHER ISN'T THAT NICE OUT HERE EITHER AND YOU NEED SOME SELF RESCUE SKILLS AND BE ABLE TO ANTICIPATE CURRENTS WAVES AND WIND&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NO FIRST TIMERS ON THIS TRIP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybee's obviously can't reserve any yaks &amp;amp; if ya reserve one and don't show up, ya won't ever get a second chance to again unless its some real good excuse. Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer. They could get stolen too easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please if using my yaks avoid stepping on the floor of them to get in and out and NEVER DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. (Kate has to repair all the damage you make to the fiberglass and Gel coatings by doing this.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only Novices in short wide cheap plastic boats do that kind of thing because they simply don't know any better or don't care.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way &amp;amp; you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro to impress the others who don't know how. Then you may laugh at the ones that fall in on entry - exit who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: Always enter- exit any kayak while being parallel and close to shore.&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for most of you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes , paddling  style, and  fit adjusted, if you have your own please bring it.&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;I only have one &amp;quot;GOOD&amp;quot; life jacket for someone that can fit in it.&lt;br /&gt;Its a Medium Kokatat* Ladies MsFit  Tour: (this is also purchased by guys since it has a great fit and versatility) Its really too small for me, but i like the way it works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/product/751058" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/pr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with the CHEAP Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles because they are Hollow and light (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths (220-230) and types (strait, or ergonomic bent, small and normal shaft dia's.) of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;You choose your preference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some  SOLID metal ones for that.)&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourite &amp;quot;Yak Pad's&amp;quot; optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer 18', Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----AVAILABLE-----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---  ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro 18', Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt;12 Inch Butt Max width between hip pads..&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--- if you ready for it..---  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--- reserved by al-r--.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Advanced Composite  (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the medium size cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (43 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----AVAILIABLE  ----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--- ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light Version (Very Thin Fiberglass and floor reinforced), Yellow, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest of the Eliza Series and also with the smallest cocpit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR JOANNE---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped 15.3'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model and largest cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; ----RESERVED FOR LAURA Z  ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cedar Strip Night Heron by Guillemot Kayaks 18'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with NOVICE/INTERMEDIATE and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (50 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----AVAILABLE-----&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---- --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me wearing my ORANGE HUNTING HAT near the boat launch ramp.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284305687000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284047593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>KAYAKING THE THINBULL ISLANDS SATURDAY SEP 11 2010 @  10:00 AM snack on Island</name><id>14711492</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284213600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14711492/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/1/global_13936689.jpeg</photo_url></item>