<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Survivor Island&lt;/strong&gt; - Bootstrap financing strategies during challenging economy and business environments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, May 15, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Survivor Island – &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Bootstrap financing strategies during challenging economy and business environments!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfmay12.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 - 9:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;

Location: Emerging Center at Foley Hoag the Bay Colony Corporate Center, Waltham, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our panel of entrepreneurs will review and discuss what worked and didn’t work as they went forward to raise money for their business in this very challenging environment. They will review both successful and unsuccessful experiences, sharing the learning’s about their approach and what they recommend to others from their perspective. Come and join us for an interesting and informative set of presentations and discussions about financing your business in these uncertain economic times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panelists include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/mm_may2012_clip_image001.jpg" alt="Description: Description: David Jacobs" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;David Jacobs, &lt;strong&gt;Chief Operating Officer Scion Medical Technologies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dave Jacobs joined Scion Medical Technologies in 2011. Dave was previously Vice President of Operations at Interlace Medical, a medical device start-up that was acquired by Hologic in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to Interlace, Dave was the VP of Engineering and Operations at Intact Medical, a venture capital financed start-up that develops and markets an RF-powered breast biopsy device, and before that he was Director of Operations for ACT Medical, a contract engineering and manufacturing company serving the needs of the medical device industry. His background also includes managing R&amp;amp;D, Engineering, Quality and Operations in several rapidly growing technology companies in the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, Dave has been an adjunct professor of Operations Management at Bentley University, teaching both graduate and undergraduate students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/May2012Mtg/morris.jpg" width="121" height="147" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Barry Morris, Founder and CEO, NuoDB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barry is an accomplished software CEO with over 25 years of industry experience in the US and Europe, running private and public companies ranging from startup to 1000+ employees. He loves to build companies around industry-changing paradigm-shifts in technology. Prior to founding NuoDB, Barry was Chairman &amp;amp; CEO of StreamBase Systems where he took an MIT project and turned it into the market pioneer and leader in Complex Event Processing. Barry joined IONA Technologies in its’ early days and led Ireland’s most successful software company through its strongest period of growth. Barry’s early experience includes technical, management and business development roles in several leading technology companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/mm_may2012_clip_image002.jpg" width="100" height="111" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bob Voosen, Founder and President ESC Company&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob started ESC in 1997 to address the opportunity to use access control equipment as a data gathering tool to increase employees' efficiency and productivity. Bob designed ESC Systems turn an expense into a profit center. Customers include Dr Pepper, Comcast and Notre Dame University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to ESC, Bob was Executive Vice President at IEI, where he turned a two person distribution company into a Nasdaq traded, design, manufacturing and marketing entity with leading products in alarm sensing and access control. Products included private labeled devices for Amway, Schlage, Yale and Sargent Lock and embedded electronics for bath and kitchen appliances for Nutone. Sales covered the US, Europe, Asia, South America and Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before IEI, Bob was a manufacturers representative with 11 product lines covering 5 states. 9 years with 3M New business ventures division preceded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob holds multiple patents with several patents pending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MODERATOR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/mm_may2012_clip_image002_0001.jpg" alt="Dick Andersen" width="93" height="93" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dick Andersen. Director, Joppa Global Marketing Partners&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dick provides brings decades of experience in strategic marketing, product management, and operations expertise to Joppa clients. Most recently the President and COO of NextChoice, he was responsible for the overall direction and operations of the company. Prior to NextChoice, Dick held executive positions at technology companies in the New England Area including VP level positions at TotalView Technologies, HighStreet Networks and NetSilicon. Dick Andersen also spent over 20 years at Compaq/Digital rising to Director level developing and leading marketing programs to several industries and leading teams delivering a complete portfolio of software, networking and management products. Dick holds a BS in Electrical Engineering from Northeastern University and a Masters of Business Administration from Suffolk University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/7_contact.htm"&gt;Map and Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337258292000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314976433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Start-up Survivor Island - Bootstrap financing strategies during challenging eco</name><id>qnlkbcyqhbtb</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337121000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32004762/</event_url></item>