<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Wattaquadock Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.430644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.nashobawinery.com</phone><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>731361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.614016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come pick apples, drink wine, beer and/or spirits and be merry with the Boston Atheists! (Heathens, blasphemers, and poets of all kinds welcome as well ;). ) Who could pass up an afternoon of drunken hayrides, fingers purpled and sticky with both wine and apples, mouths heavy with the fruit of the branch and vine, faces pink with chill and bellies overfull with swiped apples whose slothful stomachs are henceforth carted around in unnecessary concentric circles in the rickety truck-back drawn by John Deere.  (Okay, the hayride is a personal favorite of mine, but we can always dream&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/laughing.gif' border='0' alt='laughing' /&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Nashoba Valley Winery features apple picking and a wine tasting and tour on Saturday, September 25, 2010 at 12 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nashobawinery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nashobawin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$7 per person for the tour and money (preferably cash) for apples.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I suggest we drive and offer rides to those less fortunate (carpool) to our destination. Please respond to this post if you need a ride, and in one of the best of worlds, a kindly fellow Atheist will offer. It's about 30 miles from Boston proper. It's located at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 92 Wattaquadock Hill Road&lt;br /&gt;Bolton, MA 01740-1238&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;rlz=1R2GGLL_enUS337&amp;amp;wrapid=tlif12844777865772&amp;amp;um=1&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;q=nashoba+valley+winery&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=nashoba+valley+winery&amp;amp;hnear=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;cid=0,0,10842396939720928579&amp;amp;ei=RpOPTMutJoP-8AbRgsSRDQ&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;oi=local_result&amp;amp;ct=image&amp;amp;resnum=2&amp;amp;ved=0CCIQnwIwAQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpool Organization&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please respond to this message in the comment box below if you need a ride so that we can get an accurate count of those who need rides. Not having a ride is not a good excuse for not going! Also, please respond in the comment box below if you have a car and are willing to provide a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;APPLE PICKING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open 10 a.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gala, Courtland, Macoun, Rhode Island Greening, Mutsu, and Empire are among the apple types available for picking in September. Apples are $15 per peck (anyone know how much a peck is)? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOURS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guided tours of our wine-making facility are held every Saturday and Sunday throughout the year. The first tour on Saturday and Sunday starts at 11:00 a.m. with additional tours conducted approximately every hour. The last tour of the day starts at 4:00 p.m.   Reservations are not required nor are they accepted.  Thus, I suggest we get out there by 12 p.m. to give us enough time to tour the winery and then pick apples. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what Nashoba says about their tours:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Explore our production facility and discover the process we use for making our highly-acclaimed fruit wines, brandies and distillates. Our friendly, knowledgeable staff specializes in providing our guests with a unique glimpse of the winemaking process. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our tours conclude with a tasting of four wines selected by our staff plus 2 additional selections from standard wines.  The tour includes a commemorative wine glass for you to take home. Premium wines and ports may carry an additional fee. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are not required and a small fee of $7.00 per person (21 years of age and older) is charged.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TASTINGS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to the tour, there are further tastings for those who wish to skip the apples. Nashoba describes below: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Unfamiliar with our wines?  Looking for the perfect wine for dinner? You’ve had the Blueberry Merlot and Plum wine, but want to try the Baldwin Apple Wine?  Well then, step up to the tasting bar – try before you buy!  All of our guests (21 years of age and older) are welcome and encouraged to enjoy samples of our delicious and unique grape and fruit wines.  Our knowledgeable staff is happy to serve you and answer all of your questions and help you make your selections.  There is a $4.00 fee for our tasting bar which includes a complimentary tasting glass plus five - 5/8 of an ounce tasting of any five of our standard wines.  Premium wines and ports may carry an additional fee. Reservations are not necessary.  The tasting area is open seven days a week during store hours (10 - 5 pm). &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilie</member_name><member_id>4710889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285509179000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284478141000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Apple Picking at The Nashoba Valley Winery!</name><id>14766189</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285430400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/14766189/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>