<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>333 Western Ave</address_2><address_1>Horace Mann Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01085</zip><lat>42.127860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Westfield State University</name><city>Westfield</city><id>1475135</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.784197</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"PodCamps are un-conferences about social media and online networking. They are an open and collaborative events with discussions and interaction from attendees. Anyone with something to contribute or with the desire to learn is welcome and invited to join. Some sessions will be planned ahead of the event, but plenty of spaces will be open for the topics YOU want to discuss and learn. PodCamp is NOT just about podcasting, but about all social media/networking, and its relevance and usefulness to community, business and otherwise. This PodCamp is all about blogging, Facebook, Twitter, Flickr, podcasting, videocasting/YouTube, and any other online community tools."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PodCamp Western MA will be held Saturday, February 5, 2011 from 9:30 am to 4:00 pm at Westfield State University. The cost is $25 ($10 for students) and you get a T-shirt and lunch out of the deal. There are a limited number of available spots so the sooner you register the better!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can learn more, check out the session ideas people have submitted (or submit one yourself), and register at &lt;a href="http://podcamp.westernma.biz/" target="_blank"&gt;http://podcamp.wester...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296920855000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295415335000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PodCamp Western MA</name><id>16103212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296916200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/16103212/</event_url></item>