<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>299 Harvard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343056</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Brookline</city><id>4865882</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122498</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry, this is kind of a late posting for an NT Live show, but I hope you still can make it. I enjoyed this book, and am interested in seeing how the National Theatre brings it to the stage. As with all NT Live shows, advance ticket purchase is strongly recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the film/play:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Haddon’s celebrated, multi-award-winning novel is beautifully and imaginatively adapted into a stage play for the first time by Simon Stephens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christopher, fifteen years old, stands beside Mrs. Shears’ dead dog, Wellington. It has been speared with a garden fork, it is seven minutes after midnight and Christopher is under suspicion. He records each fact in his book to solve the mystery. He has an extraordinary brain, exceptional at math but ill-equipped to interpret everyday life. He has never ventured alone beyond the end of his road, he detests being touched and he distrusts strangers. But his detective work, forbidden by his father, takes him on a frightening journey that upturns his world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Haddon’s novel was Whitbread Book of the Year in 2003, and has now sold over 2 million copies around the world. Marianne Elliott co-directed the globally successful stage production of War Horse for the National, for which she won a Tony Award in 2011. Simon Stephens, twice Best Foreign Playwright of the Year, is the author of many original plays and adaptations, including Harper Regan and On the Shore of the Wide World, both directed by Marianne Elliott at the National Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate running time: 2h30m w/one intermission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at the Panera at 6, and head to the line by 6:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a Meetup sign at Panera.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348021869000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347206749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Theatre Live: The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Nighttime</name><id>81577142</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348005600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/81577142/</event_url></item>