<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>CALLING ALL VIRGINS!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join my friend and I for a night of kinky fun that does not involve taking our clothes off!!!   On Saturday, July 12th at 10:30 PM, I will be hosting the greatest midnight movie of all time, THE ROCKY HORROR PICTURE SHOW!!!!!&lt;br /&gt; Now before making a commitment to join this wonderful event, please keep a few things in mind:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVERYBODY IS RESPONSIBLE FOR HIS OR HER?S OWN TRANSPORTATION.  That being said, if you have a car and you are willing to drive people home at around 2:30 in the morning, please let me know when you sign up.  Of course, calling for a taxi ahead of time is always an option as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU ARE UPTIGHT, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP FOR THIS EVENT.  There will be a lot strange happenings going on, in and out of the theatre.  I would tell you more but, that would spoil the fun!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have only seen this movie on television or on a DVD and never seen it on the big screen, you are in for one hell of an experience!!!  See all of you ?unconventional uncoventionists? on Saturday, July 12th!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR MORE INFORMATION, CLICK HERE (IF YOU DARE!!!): &lt;a href="http://www.fullbodycast.org/index2.html" target="_blank"&gt;Full Body Cast Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in front of the theatre with a Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Walter</member_name><member_id>3779246</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216089335000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214871200000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LET'S DO THE TIME WARP!!!! Rocky Horror Picture Show at the AMC Loews</name><id>8249608</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215916200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8249608/</event_url></item>