<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Conference call this Monday night at 8 pm to talk about what we can do better next time, and what worked well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This call is open to everyone!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(605) 990-0015, access code 771-858-638&lt;br /&gt;Meeting ID: 771-858-638&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We connected with SO many people at the Oyster Festival this weekend. It was very successful.  More folks were receptive to our messages, then not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well over a thousand brochures and handouts went to many thankful people.  I can't tell you how many said we are so glad you are here talking about this to everyone.  Numerous, hundreds, of  petitions will go to Senators Dodd and Lieberman this Tuesday to tell them we want them to sponsor S604 to audit the Fed.  Committees of Safety spoke to folks about  a parallel money system, for the states.  They had many  petitions signed as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All volunteers, thank you very much for your time and discussing our message, very deeply many times, with so many people.  Rosie Haas, Walter Reddy, Dave Flowers, Rick Aielleo, Charlie Krause, Phyllis Mason, Shelia,  Gallo, Judy R.; and Rick Aeillo, Jim Palmer, Henry B., Walter G, Sean Murphy, Walter Reddy, who attend our marketing meetings to hammer out our talking points and to assist with the edit of our new Hidden Taxes and Personal Privacy Brochures; and for the &lt;b&gt;many&lt;/b&gt; rewrites to get the edit right, Jim Azzola, Jim Palmer. and Rick Aiello.  You guys were all awesome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rosie recorded a short video towards the end of the Festival, to premier on Youtube for your viewing pleasure soon.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;barbara g. and Jim Azzola Coordinators.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special  thanks to Jim Azzola. He layed out the money for the booth and the cost of printing our brochures, T-shirts and an awesome Campaign for Liberty Banner.  If you can donate to his chip in please do.  This was an expensive event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We plan to have more outreach events in the future. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;barbara g.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>barbara g.</member_name><member_id>7156348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253146337000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252894051000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oyster Festival Outreach Booth WE DID IT !!</name><id>11364851</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252972800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/11364851/</event_url></item>