<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What's in a Link, Revisited - William A. Woods&lt;br /&gt;Massachusetts Open Data Initiative - Kate Geyer&lt;br /&gt;Business Model for the Semantic Web - Michael Uschold &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's in a Link, Revisited - William A. Woods&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;William will discuss ideas about representing meaning in computer representations based on his classical paper &amp;quot;What's in a Link: Foundations for Semantic Networks&amp;quot; - 1975 [1] and his review &amp;quot;Meaning and Links &amp;quot; in 2007 [2] in a historical context.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;William A. Woods is a Distinguished Software Engineer at ITA Software, Cambridge, MA and a member of the Cambridge Semantic Web Meetup Group. &lt;a href="http://parsecraft.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://parsecraft.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[1] &lt;a href="http://oai.dtic.mil/oai/oai?verb=getRecord&amp;amp;metadataPrefix=html&amp;amp;identifier=ADA022584" target="_blank"&gt;http://oai.dtic.mil/o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[2] &lt;a href="http://www.aaai.org/ojs/index.php/aimagazine/article/view/2069" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aaai.org/o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Massachusetts Open Data Initiative: First Steps - Kate Geyer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Commonwealth of Massachusetts responded to the federal Transparency and Open Government mandate with the Massachusetts Open Data Initiative.  Starting with a wiki catalog, we're moving towards working with the web &amp;amp; open standards to make public data easy to find and easy to use and working on incorporating semantic web technologies into our catalog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mass.gov/data" target="_blank"&gt;http://mass.gov/data...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate Geyer is currently an SOA Intern at Commonwealth of Massachusetts Information Technology Division and a member of the Cambridge Semantic Web Meetup Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Model for the Semantic Web - Michael Uschold [Lightning Talk]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael's objective for this lightning talk is to make a case for better understanding of what business models make the most sense for companies leveraging semantic technology. How should we be thinking about business models and how will semantic technologies be powering them? What are successful business models of companies to date where semantic technology plays a critical role in the value proposition of the company. Will there be any long tail business models for semantic technology? What kinds of business models are likely to be successful in leveraging linked open data? In what sectors? Are there any other issues that you believe are important?&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Star Conference Room. 4th Floor, Stata Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marco Neumann</member_name><member_id>2316446</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271198327000</updated><rating><average>4.42000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Semantic Web Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1336198</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge Semantic Web</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265760733000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What's in a Link - Revisited, Massachusetts Open Data Initiative &amp; BM for the SW</name><id>xmbklynfbmb</id><headcount>51</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268175600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Cambridge-Semantic-Web-Meetup-Group/events/12565297/</event_url></item>