<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-225-0888</phone><name>Tommy Doyle's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>835734</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE: Check this page before the meetup as the venue might change!! &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are reviewing a new book from a relativley unknown author this month. Hank Fox is not a typical atheist. He comes from a modest background as a ranch a ranch hand, mule packer, wilderness guide, carpenter, truck driver, meat cutter, roofer, and a lot of other stuff - and he writes from that perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author might actually come out to Boston for this event, so let's read his book and give him our best critical analysis. Celebrating reason from all walks of life, I think this guy has something to say - though he proves you don't need a PhD to say it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://hankfoxbooks.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Red&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Neck&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span&gt;Blue&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Collar&lt;/span&gt;, Atheist: Simple Thoughts About Reason, Gods &amp;amp; Faith&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, is a look at atheism from a unique new viewpoint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An entertaining new approach to the subject of unbelief. The field so far has focused on the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; of atheism &amp;mdash; this one looks at the &amp;ldquo;how.&amp;rdquo; Putting it simply, here are some of the things an atheist might think, and the way he or she might think them. Though atheist writing has a decidedly intellectual image, author Hank Fox proves you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a Ph.D. to free yourself from the clutches of religion. Coming from a writer who has lived and worked the blue collar life, the book shows that religion is really a body of fairly simple ideas &amp;mdash; wrong ones, it turns out &amp;mdash; so easy to consider and dismiss that unassisted teenagers can reason their way out of it. Red Neck, Blue Collar, Atheist provides both a roadmap and a friendly companion for that journey. Filled with subtle humor, rich in metaphor, and written in an engagingly informal tone, the book examines the subject in two dozen chapters such as Sundae Worship, The Parable of the M&amp;amp;Ms, Batman Almighty, The Wellspring of the Gods, Sucking Up to the Virgin Mary, The Evidence of True Things, The Headwaters of Reality, and Saying Goodbye to Gods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boston Atheists Table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300576330000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271883248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book &amp; Brew (Red Neck, Blue Collar, Atheist)</name><id>bmjmnypfbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300572000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/16429604/</event_url></item>