<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;I invite you to join me at these seminars where you will really feel as though you learned something new and fresh and come away with a perspective on your spirituality that brings you closer to the truth within your own self.  You will be so happy that you came.  See you there.  &lt;br /&gt;IN light, &lt;br /&gt;Rev Gabrielle&lt;br /&gt;*** The fees cover the cost of the sirfare to bring the speaker to us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday Seminar: How do we transform?  7pm                                                &lt;br /&gt;How do we transform? Understanding and Using the Law of Attraction &lt;br /&gt;The action of transformation occurs when something larger than you and your small understanding helps you get what you want. In fact, the Universal Law operates for everyone who wants it. If you really want something, anything, you can have it. The Universal Law will be activated by your desire and the God Force will bring it to you. This is the way the Law works for all of Creation. So, if something is not the way you want it to be, and then change it to what you want. It is possible for everyone and it works perfectly for al! Seminar fee: $25; $5 discount for Meet-up Members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday August 3rd 7pm                                                                                                   &lt;br /&gt;Awakening to the Spiritual Life: At some time in your life it dawns on you that things are not what they appear to be. You feel that there must be something more and you long to know. You begin to search for the meaning of Life and your longing causes you to open to God and the spiritual world. Come join us for a workshop that will discuss this great awakening and will lie out what spiritual life looks like. There will be plenty of time for questions and for a firsthand experience of the spiritual world. $25/$5 discount for Meet-up Members! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Saturday August 4th 10am-2pm &lt;br /&gt;Light lunch included                                                                                                        &lt;br /&gt;Seminar: Devotion                                                                                               &lt;br /&gt;God gave each of us intelligence, life, strength, health, feelings and creativity. God gave us the Light to see by, the energy to get things done, and the ability to Love. Devotion is the act of acknowledging that God is the Divine Source and Power behind everything. Join us in a discussion and experience of what it truly means to live a life filled with devotion and love. $35/$5 discount for Meet-up Members! &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541860000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185845446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3 Seminars this weekend: check it out</name><id>6101307</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186182000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/6101307/</event_url></item>