<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be the third monthly topical meeting of the &amp;quot;non-prophet&amp;quot; Atheists of Greater Lowell. The Sunday Morning Topical Meetings were conceived to be a slightly more focused meeting to complement the monthly Wednesday social group meetings. The topical meetings enable a forum for discussion and sharing on topics of interest to atheists. You can come to share, just to listen in, or both.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As one of the organizers of the Sunday Morning meetings, I must apologize for missing the first two meetings! For the August meeting, I have a couple of ideas. First, I would like to encourage everyone to submit ideas for potential meeting topics (at any time before or during the August meeting) so that we can prepare a list of upcoming topics in advance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And for this meeting, I would like to discuss the values of atheists. If we were to craft a mission statement, or perhaps simply a statement of our shared outlook and values, what would it say? Did we join the group for some of the same reasons, or do we all have different reasons? Do we have shared values? Many religious types probably believe what atheists share is an _absence_ of values. But we know better. Like most people and good citizens, we value life, love, freedom of religion (including the absence of religion), and the pursuit of happiness. We love our families and pets. We believe in the separation of church and state. Are there other tenants we share? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your comments, ideas, and inspiration for what is bound to be an interesting discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valerie&lt;br /&gt;starryv0003@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the irreverant bunch of people with some tables pulled together. We don't have scarlet A's on our foreheads, but you might see an "A" on a chest (in the form of an Atheists t-shirt).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Valerie </member_name><member_id>7248057</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251932312000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lowellatheists</urlname><id>13032</id><group_lat>42.6300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3300018311</group_lon><name>Atheists of Greater Lowell</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248294594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Morning Topical Meeting--Athiest Values</name><id>10935158</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250433000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lowellatheists/events/10935158/</event_url></item>