<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Cambridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.509394</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-229-7970</phone><name>Arthur Murray Dance Studio</name><city>Burlington</city><id>845550</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.199287</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boston IBD Seminar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Eric from VT’s DayTrading Workshop - Winter2009 Series&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Session 1, Saturday, January 17, 8:00 AM – 6:00 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Cost: $50 for this entire daylong seminar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Read the sign-up instructions carefully! Do not use the RSVP link in this page!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Eric from VT’s DayTrading Workshop – Winter2009 Series&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After repeated requests from our members, Eric from VT is holding the first in his Winter2009 version of his DayTrading seminars. The Winter2009 Series is designed to provide opportunities for you to practice the methods and bring your trades and questions to follow-up sessions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Winter2009 Series culminates with LIVE trading, together, 9 AM to 4 PM, one market day this coming spring!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will use a discussion site between seminars to post trades to get feedback and for you to get answers for your questions direct from Eric from VT!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Session 1, Saturday, January 17, 2009, 8:00 AM – 6:00 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This first seminar will encompass all aspects of Daytrading in great detail. Plus you will get to ask Eric from VT all your questions to nail down your understanding of the material. Eric from VT constantly works at improving his daytrading instruction and this year’s version is dramatically updated. At this first energetic seminar you will learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;All the nuts &amp;amp; bolts of DayTrading. This seminar will have in-depth coverage of skills &amp;amp; drill-downs on the specifics of each.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Real-Time 1 to 5 minute Charting and Price Pressure Trading will be explained in clear language, using graphs that show the techniques, explained in Eric from VT’s methodical way. Eric wants you to ask all your questions to ensure you understand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eric from VT has developed more techniques he is excited to show you and will answer your trading questions about his new methods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Specialty websites will be toured for how to benefit - like &lt;a href="http://www.gainskeeper.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gainskeepe...&lt;/a&gt; and others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The date of the next follow-up seminar will be scheduled during this first seminar. Eric from VT tentatively plans for them to be the second Saturday of each month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Where:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Arthur Murray Dance Studio, 171 Cambridge St, Burlington MA 01803&lt;br /&gt;The Owner &amp;amp; our nice Host Bill Windeknecht is a Trader and will participate with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Who Should Come:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; This is geared toward people who trade but all are welcome. Please arrive on-time – there is much to be accomplished. You don't have to be a DayTrader to attend, as techniques apply to all trading!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Cost:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; A contribution of $50/person cash to defray my 4yr travel costs from Vermont is appreciated. Please bring exact bills so no change is needed to make things easy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Lunch:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Please bring lunch, drinks &amp;amp; snacks as we'll take short morning &amp;amp; afternoon breaks with a half hour lunch together. Also bring a folding chair(s) if you have them. There will be a &amp;quot;Surprise Presenter&amp;quot; during our morning break and one for our afternoon break.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Style:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Everyone in our group knows Eric from VT’s energetic style. He is fresh, upbeat and direct. Make his lessons be for your benefit!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Found at Bill's website &lt;a href="http://www.amdsma.com/burlington.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amdsma.com...&lt;/a&gt;. Arthur Murray Dance Studio is the second building back. It has two big free parking lots in front and below it. If you get lost just call Bill's Arthur Murray Dance Studio at 1-781-229-7970.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Sign Up!:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; To sign up for Seminar 1 on January 17 please send email to Eric from VT &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;direct&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; at eklofsr@gmail.com.  Include the Full Name(s), Email(s), Tel(s) &amp;amp; Cell(s) of each person attending. Space is limited so sign up as soon as possible! Many people are already registered. &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do not use the RSVP link in this announcement.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Be &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;sure&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you can absolutely make it there on January 17 before signing up. Seating is on a first-to-RSVP basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 5+ great years of Day Trading Eric from VT says he may be retiring at the end of 2009 so he looks forward to enjoy sharing what he has learned with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to forward this seminar announcement to anyone who may be interested or can benefit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eric from VT’s DISCLAIMER:&lt;/b&gt; Anything I say or present are NOT suggestions to buy/sell stock, do your own homework to make your own decisions &amp;amp; any trades you make are at your own risk!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;If you have a seminar or workshop that you would like to offer to our members, please contact us. We are looking for cost-effective - or free - seminars.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This building is the 2nd building back and has two big parking lots.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232587445000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231294575000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BostonIBD Seminar: Eric from VT's DayTrading Workshop - Winter2009 Series</name><id>9464034</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232197200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9464034/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/3/global_6852995.jpeg</photo_url></item>