<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Ocean Gateway Pier</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.662996</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvest on the Harbor</name><city>Portland</city><id>1384846</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256878</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;I'm attempting to fill the 4:30-9:30 volunteering slot on Thursday, October 21st, however, there are multiple dates and times available for volunteering. Please see the FAQs below for more information.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.harvestontheharbor.com/sites/default/files/harvest_logo.png" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is Harvest on the Harbor?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvest on the Harbor is is the premier food and wine tasting event in Maine and it's happening October 21st through the 23rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is put on by the Greater Portland Convention and Visitors Bureau and their mission is to stimulate the economic vitality of Greater Portland by promoting Greater Portland as a preferred destination for visitors and locals alike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to put on this event, they need a number of volunteers to help out with all of their events.  It is an excellent way to meet some other people with an interest in food and wine.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There's a bonus for volunteering!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can get a free ticket to the Saturday events by working a volunteer shift.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I will NOT be attending or organizing this event.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ALL questions and concerns should be addressed directly to Chris Cooper, the Volunteer Coordinator for this event. Here is Chris' contact information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Chris Cooper&lt;br /&gt;Volunteer Coordinator&lt;br /&gt;Harvest on the Harbor&lt;br /&gt;Greater Portland Convention &amp;amp; Visitors Bureau&lt;br /&gt;94 Commercial St. Suite 300&lt;br /&gt;Portland, Maine 04101&lt;br /&gt;Ph: 207-772-4994 ext 239&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvestontheharbor.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvestont...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How do you sign up for this volunteering opportunity?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;First&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, RSVP Yes to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Second&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, click the following link and sign up to volunteer through Harvest on the Harbor: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvestontheharbor.com/volunteer/find-out-about-volunteer-opportunities" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvestont...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please read the following FAQs about this event!&lt;br /&gt;FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS FOR VOLUNTEERS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  What are the requirements for volunteering?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   Volunteers must be 21 and older, have a friendly personality, be a strong team player and be very reliable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  What types of jobs might I be volunteering for?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   Harvest on the Harbor requires an enormous amount of volunteers to make this a successful event. Volunteer jobs might involve: registration assistance, greeting guests, distributing programs or wine glasses, ticket-taking, coat check, assisting wineries with supplying water and ice to their table, directional assistance, help with seating, assisting chefs with prep work or passing out samples, turn seminar rooms or helping to set up and break down, along with a list of miscellaneous logistical assistance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  What are the dates of the event?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   Harvest on the Harbor is Thursday, October 21, Friday, October 22, and Saturday, October 23, 2010. Volunteers are needed for all three days. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  What are the times volunteers are needed?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   Projected volunteer times are as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Thursday: 8am-2:30pm and 4:30pm-9:30pm&lt;br /&gt;    * Friday: 10:30am-2:30pm and 4pm-8pm&lt;br /&gt;    * Saturday: 10:30am-3pm and 3pm-8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: These times are approximate and are subject to change. Please check back as the event draws near for an accurate volunteer schedule.&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:&lt;/b&gt;  Will I be compensated for my time volunteering?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;  Yes, all volunteers will be receiving one ticket to the Savory Samplings at the Marketplace on Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Volunteers who complete a shift on Thursday or Fridayreceive a ticket to the Marketplace – Session I.&lt;br /&gt;    * Volunteers for Saturday, Marketplace – Session Ireceive a ticket to Marketplace - Session II.&lt;br /&gt;    * Volunteers for Saturday,  Marketplace – Session IIreceive a Harvest on the Harbor apron and a complimentary ticket for Marketplace - Session II which can be given to a friend or family member (these tickets will be available approximately 30 minutes prior to the opening of Marketplace – Session II and held in the name of your guest at will-call)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  Can I attend the Savory Samplings at the Marketplace Session I if I am volunteering later in the day?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;  We ask that all volunteers who are working at Savory Samplings at the Marketplace Session II refrain from attending Marketplace Session I. Understandably it is not appropriate for volunteers to be sampling wine, beer, and spirits prior to working as a volunteer. Thus we are offering both a complimentary ticket for a friend or family member and a complimentary Harvest on the Harbor apron for those people volunteering during Marketplace Session II.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  Can I volunteer for more than one shift?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;  You are welcome to sign up for multiple shifts over the course of the three-day event.  If you wish to work multiple shifts please make a note in your inquiry or contact the volunteer coordinator directly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;______________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  What should I wear?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   Volunteers will be asked to wear white shirts, black pants, and comfortable shoes. Volunteering for Thursday and Friday evening requires black, semi-formal cocktail attire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;______________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  Where should I park and does it cost anything?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   You will receive a complimentary parking pass within close proximity of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  Are there any rules or policies I should be aware of while volunteering?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   While you are volunteering, please refrain from drinking any alcoholic beverages, and from sampling food from exhibitors, before and during your shift, as they have budgeted for a specific amount of attendees. We invite you to get the full Harvest on the Harbor experience and purchase tickets to any our events to fully take advantage of all that Harvest has to offer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  What is the cancellation policy if I can't make it?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   If you cannot fulfill your commitment, we ask that you allow us at least one week to fill your spot. It is incredibly important that we are not short-staffed for this event, and last-minute cancellations make it very difficult for us to fill your spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:  Should I be prepared to bring anything with me?&lt;br /&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt;   In order to enter the Harvest on the Harbor event area, a valid I.D. will be required. There is no storage space for personal items, so please plan to leave those in your vehicle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This event is sponsored by:&lt;br /&gt;Zeus's Closet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myzeusscloset.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myzeussclo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;What does this mean to you?! They are covering your $1 meetup fees for this event!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will not be attending. You will be coordinating your volunteering with Chris Cooper.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287752056000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285349748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer Opportunity - Harvest on the Harbor October 21st-23rd</name><id>14883583</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287691200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/14883583/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/global_18438149.jpeg</photo_url></item>