<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>32 Vassar Street</address_2><address_1>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 155</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1119883</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exciting times in retail!  BILLIONS of RFID tags now deployed for item-level apparel annually.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;Retailers today experience up to &lt;strong&gt;96% savings&lt;/strong&gt; in inventory taking time utilizing RFID rather than bar code methods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGNIFICANCE?&lt;/strong&gt; RFID for item-level apparel achieves an inventory accuracy retailers can count on -- 99% or more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Register at&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-circle-event-rfid-gets-fashion-forward-but-its-time-to-move-it-further-back-to-the-source/"&gt;http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-circle-event-rfid-gets-fashion-forward-but-its-time-to-move-it-further-back-to-the-source/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f1f3c ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/news/rfid-in-fashion/"&gt;PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; -- RFID GETS FASHION FORWARD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f1f3c"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;with Michael Liard&lt;/strong&gt;, Vice President of VDC Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/news/rfid-in-fashion/"&gt;http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/news/rfid-in-fashion/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With passive UHF RFID being implemented by a growing numbers of retailers and brands, RFID technology at the item level in fashion apparel and footwear is a hot-right-now application market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator&lt;/strong&gt;: Michael Liard, Vice President Auto-ID &amp;amp; Data Collection, VDC Research&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jerry Glinnen&lt;/strong&gt;, Compliance Manager, Lifetime Brands, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Arguin&lt;/strong&gt;, Senior Director of RFID Development, r-pac&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zander Livingston&lt;/strong&gt;, Co-Founder and CEO of Truecount Corporation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT's NEXT?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do we move tagging closer to the source? How are vendors, solutions providers and tagging bureaus helping retailers and their partners RFID-enable their items and, ultimately, their stores and supply chains?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key questions, strategic issues and market challenges will be discussed during our session include the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Not all tags (chips, inlays, labels) and readers are created equal – what are the differences in reliability and performance and what do retailers and brands need to know? &lt;br /&gt;

 - How to adopt RFID without disrupting brand owners? &lt;br /&gt;

 - Costs of chips, inlays, tags and readers have come down, but what is the true lifecycle cost of implementing RFID solutions? Quantifiable benefits? Where, when and how to apply RFID tags or deploy readers? Where does serialization factor into the cost equation? &lt;br /&gt;

 - Now that we can effectively capture data in retail in-store and supply chain environments, how do we effectively leverage and manage the influx of data (especially as more apparel and footwear items are tagged)? What is the impact of Big Data? &lt;br /&gt;

 - How has industry consolidation impacted the market and product development (most notably among inlay/label converting)? &lt;br /&gt;

 - Which retail categories are next for Item Level Tagging (ILT) – e.g., housewares, consumer electronics)? &lt;br /&gt;

 - Where does SmartEAS (hybrid RFID and EAS) “fit in” today? Are RFID/EAS-enabled woven labels the future? &lt;br /&gt;

 - What will it take to move RFID closer to the source and establish tagging at point of manufacture as opposed to closer to the retail store floor?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;SPEAKER BIO's&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Michael Liard, Vice President Auto-ID, VDC Research&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Michael is VDC’s Vice President of the firm’s AutoID research practice. Michael serves as VDC’s lead analyst and consultant on all proprietary research and consulting engagements involving AutoID product, market or channel development. Michael has covered the broader automatic identification industry, including research and analysis for barcode, RFID contactless, NFC and RTLS technologies and solutions for more than a decade. Prior to VDC, Michael was employed by ABI Research as Practice Director, RFID. He also worked for Accenture (formerly Andersen Consulting) in their Organization and Human Performance practice. Michael has contributed to and has been cited in various industry trade press and national publications, including national TV appearances. Michael has also been a speaker at a number of industry-related conferences. Michael was presented the “Excellence in Journalism Award” by AIM Global in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jerry Glinnen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, Compliance Manager, Lifetime Brands, Inc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lifetime Brands is a leading global provider of kitchenware, tabletop and other products used in the home. The Company markets its products under such well-known kitchenware brands as Farberware®, KitchenAid®, CasaModa®, Cuisinart®, Cuisine de France®, Guy Fieri®, Hoffritz®, Kizmos™, Misto®, Pedrini®, Roshco®, Sabatier®, Savora™, and Vasconia®; respected tabletop brands such as Mikasa®, Pfaltzgraff®, Creative Tops®, Gorham®, International® Silver, Kirk Stieff®, Sasaki®, Towle® Silversmiths, Tuttle®, Wallace®, V&amp;amp;A® and Royal Botanic Gardens Kew®; and home solutions brands, including Fred®, Elements®, Melannco®, Kamenstein® and Design for Living™. The Company also provides exclusive private label products to leading retailers worldwide. &lt;a href="http://www.lifetimebrands.com"&gt;www.lifetimebrands.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Arguin, Senior Director of RFID Development, r-pac&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Mr Arguin has over 20 years experience working with cutting edge engineering and technology. He has formal education including advanced degrees in various disciplines of Engineering and Management. Mr. Arguin currently works as Senior Director of RFID Development at r-pac International, the premier supplier of RFID tags to retailers and suppliers worldwide. Previous to r-pac, Mr Arguin worked with Conair Corporation beginning in 2002 and accepted the position of Director of Engineering and Technology for Conair’s subsidiary, USA ID in 2006. Mr. Arguin’s work experience has ranged from sophisticated large scale computer systems for DoD projects, to large dot-com infrastructures in start-up businesses, to the present with RFID and GPS technologies in the cargo security and supply chain space.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368578293000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365442657000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RFID Gets Fashion Forward but It’s Time to Move It Further Back — to the Source!</name><id>113313212</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368568800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/113313212/</event_url></item>