<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Climates&amp;quot;, is the latest film from Turkish director Nuri Bilge Ceylan. I have seen his previous film &amp;quot;Distant&amp;quot; which I found to be an intriguing study of the cultural clash between town/city and tradition/Westernization. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Climates&amp;quot;, hailed as &amp;quot;the only masterpiece of the [2006 Cannes] festival&amp;quot; by the New York Foundation for the Arts, is the story of a searing relationship between a man and a woman (played by the director and his wife, Ebru Ceylan) that becomes a psychological portrait of an insecure man. At the close of her rave review, New York Times critic Manohla Dargis compares Ceylan to Michelangelo Antonioni, commenting that &amp;quot;while [Ceylan?s] films are similarly personal, they're more accessible? The mysteries of his work are those of the heart, the head, the soul.&amp;quot;  HFA Website&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I saw Ceylan's previous movie &amp;quot;Distant&amp;quot; a couple of years ago at the MFA and was taken in by his tale of a villager who must move to Istanbul to find work and I'm really looking forward to seeing this, his newest film. Here, Ceylan plots the death of a relationship-ok, I admit not the cheeriest of subjects, but one that should provide an arena for discussion afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a review from The Chicago Tribune describing Climates &amp;quot;as sharp and lovely as the best Chekhov short stories.&amp;quot; &lt;a href="http://metromix.chicagotribune.com/movies/mmx-070216-movies-review-climates,0,3180544.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://metromix.chica...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will be holding a Meet-up sign near the front row after the film and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179788799000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177370166000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Climates- A Drama from Turkey at HFA</name><id>5701589</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179615600000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5701589/</event_url></item>