<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>NH Route 171</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03254</zip><lat>43.724678</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MT SHAW</name><city>MOULTONBOROUGH</city><id>4331822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.330719</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Trail Description -Mount Shaw Trail About Trail Descriptions Mount Shaw is the highest point of the Ossipee Mountains, a volcanic ring dike lying between Ossipee, Squam, and Winnipesaukee Lakes. Much of the W flank of the mountain is covered with carriage roads of the former Plant estate, better known as Castle in the Clouds and now owned by the Lakes Region Conservation Trust. There are limited N views from the summit and S views from nearby Black Snout and other points. This trail offers a shorter approach from the S than the route via carriage roads, but the trailhead and the first part of the trail are on old woods roads across private property open only through the generosity of the landowner -please repay this kindness by passing through gently. The middle section is a footpath which ascends at a usually moderate grade, while the upper part is on carriage roads of the Plant estate. There is another Mount Shaw in the White Mountain National Forest near Chatham, but the trails to it are long abandoned. Distance: About 3.5 miles one-way Elevation gain: About 2300 feet Hiking Time Estimator Maps: USGS Melvin Village LRCT trail map posted at Shannon Brook trailhead kiosk and available from LRCT or Castle in the Clouds gift shop Location: Lakes Region NH 2003-2004 map K-8 DeLorme NHA&amp;amp;G 40-J61H7 -TuftonborolMoultonborough Tuftonboro is on NH Route 171 between Ossipee and Moultonborough Trailhead: NH Route 171 about 2.0 miles E of Castle in the Clouds entrance and about 1.8 miles E of Shannon Brook Trail kiosk, elevation about 670 feet Trail goes up a woods road on the E side of Fields Brook (across the bridge from Sodom Road); there is no sign at the trailhead 43.7108&amp;deg;N, 71.2917&amp;deg;W (WGS84) From 1-93 Exit 23, take NH Route 104 E about 8 miles until it ends at Meredith. Turn L on US Route 3 and go .8 miles to a traffic light just beyond the public docks. Turn R on NH Route 25 and go 10.1 miles passing through Moultonborough village. Turn R on NH Route 109 and go 2.2 miles, then turn L on NH Route 171 and go 3.9 miles passing SodomRoad. The trail starts on the far (E) side of the Fields Brook bridge, there is a woods road L with wide spots for parking but no trail sign 1e kiosk and parking lot are on the S side of NH Route 17l, and the trail starts on the N side Far End: Summit of Mount Shaw, elevation about 2990 feet Owner: private and Lakes Region Conservation Trust Maintainer: Lakes Region Conservation Trust and other Special regulations: No camping, fires, motorized vehicles Description From the parking lot, follow the obvious woods road past the boulders and stay on the main road avoiding forks. At about .4 miles there is an attractive gorge in the brook to the L and an unsigned junction is reached. The R fork with red-and-green blazes leads to some viewpoints on the next ridge E, sometimes called Tate or Big Bald Mountain, while the Mount Shaw Trail follows the red blazes on the L fork. After an eroded section on sidehill following a pipeline, the trail becomes a woods road again and runs parallel to the brook -there are side roads Land R so follow the blazes carefully. At about 1.6 miles the trail crosses the brook diagonally and continues parallel on the far side. The woods road peters out and the trail crosses the brook again and climbs more steeply, reaching one of the old carriage roads at 2.5 miles. The remainder of the hike follows former carriage roads which were traditionally part of the Mount Shaw Trail but have been renamed as part of the LRCT system. The trail follows the carriage road R .2 miles to a junction where a branch carriage road leads R .2 miles to a S viewpoint called Black Snout. (Black Snout is labelled on the LRCT map but not the USGS map.) The trail follows the main carriage road sharp L another .4 miles to another junction where the trail turns sharp R; the carriage road ahead takes a circuitous route to Castle in the Clouds and Mount Roberts. The trail makes two more switchbacks to a clearing at 3.5 miles near the summit of Mount Shaw. There are fine views of the Sandwich Range from here.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ww will be in a silver four door legacy Subaru</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321876460000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320693642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT SHAW AND BLACK SNOUT</name><id>40298482</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321714800000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/40298482/</event_url></item>