<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location offers 3 to 4 paddling environments all in one small area making it a good place to paddle in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A SUNDAY Event for a change...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am  making like MOSES by splitting the sea from the river just like Gilligan did too....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather: Sunday: Sunny, with a high near 86. West wind between 3 and 9 mph.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday: Sunday: Variable winds less than 5 kt becoming W 5 to 9 kt in the morning. Sunny. Seas around 1 ft.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the latest update on weather:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHVN&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Saybrook Point starting with August 29, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Su  29     High   1:58 AM     3.1   6:13 AM     Set 11:02 AM      84&lt;br /&gt;    29      Low   7:47 AM     0.8   7:27 PM    Rise  9:19 PM&lt;br /&gt;    29     High   2:21 PM     3.7&lt;br /&gt;    29      Low   8:43 PM     0.8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We may catch a small amount of the Zipper..&lt;br /&gt;so i may reverse the course of my plan..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;but if no waves..this is the plan:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip starts off by taking a Right from the boat ramp and heading into the marsh, we keep going through the maze to a river, take a right at this river, follow it to where we decide we had enough.&lt;br /&gt;on the return pass our entry point and go to the Big River and head to Poverty Point, take a left there and head for Gilligans Island for our Lunch and relaxing spot..&lt;br /&gt;We need someone to be Mary-Ann. LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a blanket and umbrella for this spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location for the Put In:&lt;br /&gt;GPS, Mapquest and others, use 415 Smith Neck Road, Old Lyme CT to get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I- 91 South  to Exit 22 S for rte 9&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take rte 9 all the way to I-95 NORTH Exit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you stay in the right side of the 2 lanes - it will merge right before the underpass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cross the CT River bridge to the first exit --- Exit # 70. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp, turn RIGHT onto Route 156/Shore Road and continue 1.7 miles.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Turn RIGHT onto Smith Neck Road, ( Be cautious, there is a yellow diamond sign that partially blocks the street name view till almost  right at the street) and proceed .7 miles (to its end) there will be a big parking lot and drop off area by the water.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Poop House usually stinks bad, hold breath, don't look in bottom.&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring the sunscreen, hats, gloves (if you need perfect looking hands for work) or for  blister free paddling, and whatever else you need for the outside.&lt;br /&gt;Don't wear cotton to avoid being wet or cold if you get wet. SOME OF YOU WILL GET WET&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some POT LUCK food..and your favourite beverages for the group Barbie-q after.&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you really like and some more. We might like it and will eat it even if its a doubble with someone else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Group Pot Luck barbie-q is the second half to a  PERFECT outing also right by the river after the paddle...(if you didnt get a chance to paddle with us this is also open to people interested in meeting us&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...Bring chairs..and whatever else you like to sit around on.&lt;br /&gt;The grill is loaded and ready for action..., BRING SOME SCRAP WOOD TOO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Paddle &amp;amp; Paddle Leash, Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doughnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any &amp;quot;Wide Butt&amp;quot; (greater than 17&amp;quot;~18&amp;quot; butts) yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;Don't laugh, its serious, some will not fit in a yak thats too small (ie the Greenlander Pro--maximum butt and hips width of 12 inches limit) of an opening and i will feel sad you cant go..etc..the other option is to maybe trade with someone..etc ..if you need to.&lt;br /&gt;This has worked in the past very well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a positive confirmed yes and by persons i have some familiarity with ?..(ie paddle skills matched to the boat, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybee's obviously can't reserve any yaks &amp;amp; if ya reserve one and don't show up, ya won't ever get a second chance to again unless its some real good excuse..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer. They get stolen too easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF USING MY YAKS YOU CANT LOOK LIKE A BONEHEADED BEGINNER AND STEP INTO or out of THEM VIA THE FLOOR (yes the lightest kayaks have thin fiberglass and your feet will go through them) OR DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. ( In an 18 foot long boat you will still be 10 or so feet out in the water at a greater depth.) Only Novices in short wide cheap plastic boats do that kind of thing.  :-)~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way and you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro and impress the others who don't know how. Then you may laugh at the ones that fall in on entry and exit who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: Always enter and exit while being parallel to shore.&lt;br /&gt;-----------------&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for most of you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes , paddling  style, and  fit adjusted...if you have your own please bring it..&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;I only have one &amp;quot;GOOD&amp;quot; life jacket for someone that can fit in it.&lt;br /&gt;Its a Medium Kokatat* Ladies MsFit  Tour: (this is also purchased by guys since it has a great fit and versatility) Its really too small for  me...but i like the way it works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/product/751058" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/pr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths (220-230) and types (strait, or ergonomic bent, small and normal shaft dia's.) of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;You choose your preference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some cheap metal ones for that.)-&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourite Yak Pad's optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer 18', Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with Novice and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR KATE ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro 18', Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt;12 Inch Butt Max width between hip pads..&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--- if you ready for it..---  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--- reserved by al-r--.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Advanced Composite  (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the medium size cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (43 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----  ----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR SEV ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light Version (Very Thin Fiberglass and floor reinforced), Yellow, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest of the Eliza Series and also with the smallest cocpit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR JOANNE --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;HULL IMPROVEMENTS ARE IN PROGRESS -- WILL BE FINE FOR SUNDAY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped 15.3'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model and largest cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; ----RESERVED FOR ANNA  ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cedar Strip Night Heron by Guillemot Kayaks 18'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with beginner/intermediate and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (50 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR HELENA --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok see some of you there.&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my ORANGE HUNTING HAT  unloading at the boat ramp.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283340569000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282660333000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>KAYAK @ Lou Tennant Riv + Gilligans Island  for lunch - Pot Luck BBQ @ 7 Falls</name><id>14524093</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283095800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14524093/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>