<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>765 Commonwealth Avenue</address_2><address_1>BU School of Law, 1st floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.350833</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barrister's Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>1082487</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106667</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A talk with 2009 Nobel Laureate in Literature Herta Müller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free and open to the public. Reception to follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Herta Müller is the 2009 winner of the Nobel Prize for Literature. She was born in 1953 in a German-speaking town in Banat, Romania, where her parents were members of the German-speaking minority. Her father served in the Waffen-SS in World War II, and her mother was deported to a work camp in the Soviet Union in 1945. At university, Ms. Müller opposed the regime of Nicolae Ceausescu and joined Aktionsgruppe Banat, a group of dissident writers who sought freedom of speech. She emigrated to Germany in 1987 after years of persecution and censorship in Romania. Her early works depict village life and the repression its residents face. Her later novels, including The Land of Green Plums and The Appointment, approach allegory in their graphic portrayals of the brutality suffered by modest people living under totalitarianism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moderated by Askold Melnyczuk and William Pierce. Melnyczuk is founding editor of AGNI and the author of three novels, most recently The House of Widows. He has published stories, poems, translations, and reviews in The New York Times, The Nation, The Partisan Review, Grand Street, Ploughshares, Poetry, and The Boston Globe. Among his many honors are the Lila Wallace-Readers’ Digest Award in Fiction and the McGinnis Award in Fiction. Pierce’s fiction has appeared in Granta, Ecotone, and elsewhere. He is senior editor of AGNI, where he contributes a series of essays called “Crucibles.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cosponsored by BU’s Center for the Study of Europe, AGNI, and the Goethe Institut Boston.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336864207000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336070486000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nobel laureate Herta Mueller, in conversation with Melnyczuk &amp; Pierce, at BU</name><id>63285102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336852800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/63285102/</event_url></item>