<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Parking area is on left at 1.6 miles. AMC hiker shuttle stops here.</address_2><address_1>Take Rte 3 to Trudeau Rd intersection, follow Gale River Rd (FR 25) SE, left at .6 miles, sharp right at 1.3 on Gale River Loop</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03574</zip><lat>44.226086</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Gale River Trail head</name><city>Bethlehem</city><id>282395</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.632120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>3 4000 ft peaks with a great workout and view. I thought that climb up North Twin Mountain was tough, but I'm ready to go again. The summit of South Twin is one of the best views and Galehead is &amp;quot;downhill&amp;quot; from there. The Galehead hut will be open for a final rest stop /water fill up before we descend.&lt;br /&gt;12.0 miles, 3,700 feet gain , 7:50 AMC booktime&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/3/7/event_2011543.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will spot cars at the North Twin and Galehead trail heads. Please allow extra time for the car shuttle so we can start this long hike on time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Car Camping near the N twin and Galehead trailhead Saturday night is available first come first serve. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/garfield.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hike information: Galehead Mountain and the Twins&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The days are getting shorter.  As the sun goes down so does the temperature. Remember to pack your jacket/pullover and everyone should pack a headlamp and extra batteries even if you don't think you would ever need one.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will Meet at Gale River trailhead, park cars here. (This is the end of the hike)  beware the Gale River Loop Rd is open from the North only. The bridge is still washed out from the south - A few cars will shuttle hikers to the North Twin Trailhead</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253150548000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248732915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet me at the Twins and Galehead</name><id>10971284</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252845000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10971284/</event_url></item>