<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Christmas party will be Saturday evening Dec 11 at the Applehill Farm on Joslin Street in Leominster from 6-10 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to arrive around 6:00 for a social hour and a cheese and cracker basket and a cash bar. A plated dinner will begin between 6:45 and 7:00. The choice for the meal will be a Roasted Boneless Prime Rib of Beef or a Boneless Parmesan Crusted Chicken. It will include Roasted Red Potatoes, Chef's choice of Vegetable, and rolls and butter. There will be a chocolate truffle for dessert. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost for the evening will be &lt;b&gt;$35&lt;/b&gt; per person. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your wife, husband, girlfriend, boyfriend, solo, or all of the them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP and respond with your choice of meal and send your check to the FPA in care of Russ Hume at 151 Wilder Road, Leominster, MA 01453. We will need to communicate our numbers and meals to the Applehill Farm by December 4, so please get your RSVP in as soon as you can. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of parking behind the facility, they just recently expanded it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the past we've had over 50 attendees. This has been a lot of fun. Come on and join your fellow pilots and spouses and friends for some Holiday (barony)Chair. No metar date on this one and no Santa TFR's to worry about.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually sell tickets in advance and will try to again. Look for more details as they are available... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photo's from last years party are on the meetup site. Same date 12-11... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HO HO HO, &lt;br /&gt;Captain Santa and his F.O. Rudolf&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Applehill Farm on Joslin Street in Leominster.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Russ Hume</member_name><member_id>4096811</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292181430000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>43</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287435193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FPA EAA 1454  Annual Christmas Party</name><id>15150585</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292108400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/15150585/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/6/global_11671446.jpeg</photo_url></item>