<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 JFK Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.206066</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Braintree Town Hall</name><city>Braintree</city><id>6981082</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.005219</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join Boston Volunteers and members of the Braintree Area Community as we gather to help start Habitat for Humanity's Braintree Area Local Partnership Committee (LPC)!  We have built 4 homes in Braintree and are organizing a Local Partnership Committee (LPC) in anticipation of another Braintree or local build in the Braintree area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a follow-up meeting to our Kick-Off Meeting on Thursday, May 10th.  The general format will be as follows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-An overview similar to our May 10th meeting (We will do our best to keep this to 1/2 hr so as not to bore those who already heard it on May 10th.  There will be some slightly different information offered.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-We will build upon the conversations from our May 10th meeting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Discussion and Introduction of various Committees and their Chairs/Co-Chairs as well as any open Chairs/Co-Chairs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Breakout into Committee Meetings/Discussions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an exciting opportunity for those who want some hands-on experience with Habitat for Humanity, even if not actually lifting a hammer to physically build a home for a family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please help promote tonight's event!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a. Use the "Share" feature that meetup provides to promote this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b. Like South Shore Habitat for Humanity on Facebook.  You can then RSVP for the event there and share it with your friends that way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c. Download the flier and email it to your network.  If you want some to handout or post please email an Event Organizer to make arrangements.  (This can be found in the Files section.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. This event will be promoted multiple ways, including but not limited to the Boston Volunteers Meetup Group and South Shore Habitat for Humanity's Facebook Page as an Event.  You only need to RSVP once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Some of the same information delivered at the May 10th meeting will be delivered at tonight's meeting as well.  If you do not want to hear it again you can join us @ 7pm.  However, it would be great to have you there for the entire meeting to help build support and rapport.  We will also go into a little more detail about the LPC and break-out into groups for small group discussions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. If you are interested in learning more and possibly participating but are unable to attend tonight's event please email Angela through the Meetup site with your contact info to be added to the email distribution list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us as we learn more about Habitat for Humanity and each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Volunteers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big enough to Deliver, small enough to care&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more: www.BostonVolunteer.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow us: @BostonVolunteer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/BostonVolunteers"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/BostonVolunteers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or Do you have Twitter?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/#!/BostonVolunteer"&gt;https://twitter.com/#!/BostonVolunteer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Habitat for Humanity Braintree Area LPC Kick-Off Meeting Follow-Up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, May 23rd @ 6:30pm-8:30pm (at the latest)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Braintree Town Hall&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fletcher Hall, Lower Level&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 JFK Memorial Drive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Braintree, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;W: www.sshabitat.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Fletcher Hall, Lower Level&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Host(s)/Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: All are welcome!  However, we have set a max RSVP of 20.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Welcome, please keep it to one per person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fees/Costs&lt;/em&gt;: None, unless we go out for a bite to eat afterwards.  Please bring cash to pay for your food and beverages if so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Wednesday, May 23rd @ 10am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions to Braintree Town Hall @ 1 JFK Memorial Drive:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview:&lt;/em&gt; Located near South Braintree Square, directly across from the Thayer Public Library and next to Thayer Academy, Town Hall is a short walk from the Braintree T and a short drive from Route 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;From Routes 24/95/128/93:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Head towards Route 3 South/Braintree/Cape Cod.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Route 3:&lt;/em&gt; Take Exit 17/Union Street/Braintree (it will be your 2nd exit on Route 3 South), take the 1st right off the exit ramp (from Route 3 southbound/3rd right from Route 3 northbound) keeping Motel 6 on your left.  Get in one of the middle lanes and go straight thru the 1st set of lights going under the overpass and keeping the T on your left.  Take a left at the light at the top of the hill and get in the right lane.  Take a right at the next light and an immediate left into the Town Hall parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the Braintree T on foot:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Exit the T heading towards Union Street and South Braintree Square.  Leave the front door, take a left and head towards the street (it's a one way so you may see a bus or taxi heading your way), then go down the steps and take a left heading under the underpass up the hill.  At the top of the hill at the light round the corner to your left heading towards The Fire Station.  At the next light if you walk diagonally across the street you will be at Town Hall.  Basically, cross the street in front of the fire station and then use the signal to cross Washington Street, or use the signal to cross Washington Street and then cross Central Street.  You will be at the Town Hall Mall once you have crossed the street(s).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Fletcher Hall (Lower Level), which is at the end of the hall.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338049714000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337185868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Habitat for Humanity Braintree Area LPC Kick-Off Meeting Follow-Up!</name><id>65044742</id><headcount>18</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337812200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/65044742/</event_url></item>