<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is supposed to be an outstanding movie.Gay Rights Activist. Friend. Lover. Unifier. Politician. Fighter. Icon. Inspiration. Hero. His life changed history, and his courage changed lives. In 1977, Harvey Milk (Sean Penn) was elected to the San Francisco Board of Supervisors, becoming the first openly gay man to be voted into major public office in America. His victory was not just a victory for gay rights; he forged coalitions across the political spectrum. From senior citizens to union workers, Harvey Milk changed the very nature of what it means to be a fighter for human rights and became, before his untimely death in 1978, a hero for all Americans. Co-starring James Franco, Emile Hirsch, Diego Luna and Josh Brolin. Directed by Gus Van Sant (Good Will Hunting, My Own Private Idaho) from an original screenplay by Dustin Lance Black.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we'll go to a restaurant to talk about the movie.  This promises to be fruitful for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  Because I'm putting this up so close to the actual time of the movie, only &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; answers will be available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally:  It's winter and a slow economy.  Movies are a great form of entertainment and more and more people are going, particularly over the weekend.  To be absolutely sure of getting a seat, I suggest that you buy your ticket ahead of time over the internet.  The theater's website makes it pretty simple.  It does cost $1 more, but in my mind, the assurance of a seat is worth the money.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the front left of the theater both before and after the movie.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228309960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Milk</name><id>9272185</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228687200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9272185/</event_url></item>