<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>5322022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Two hundred miles north of the Arctic Circle, Norway, Sweden and Finland converge. The site is unglamorously marked by a yellow concrete block in the middle of the lake, but its relative inaccessibility and lack of information in English served as sufficient inspiration for Rucker Alex to improvise a 60-mile solo backpacking trip across the tri-border area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;For the trip, Rucker became a card-carrying member of the Norwegian Trekking Association, which earned her a key to enter the well-appointed huts. Portions of her route intersected with the 500-mile Nordkalotten trail, remnants of World War I and II history, and climate change scientist research stations. Thanks to a mis-communication with a Norwegian fisherman, she missed the opportunity to wade through the hip-deep arctic streams of  Ice Valley on a 35 degree day, and instead decided to re-route towards a hand-built, wood-fired sauna in the Swedish wilderness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Other highlights on the trail included a hail storm on the tundra within the first two hours hiking, stunning ridge walks and Arctic river crossings, blissfully blue skies, wild roaming reindeer, and conversations with Scandinavian outdoor enthusiasts. Rucker will share photos from the experience and advice on planning adventure trips to relatively undocumented areas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Doors open @ 6:15 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Potluck @ 6:30 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Slideshow @ 7:15 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Join our Google Group and get all the latest updates and cancellation notices for all the shows:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potluck Info:&lt;/strong&gt; Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies  &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome:) Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (w/stovetop, oven, microwave, sink &amp;amp; fridge). Please bring your own cooking pots if needed for stovetop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subway Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Take the MBTA to Park Street Station. Walk through the Boston Common uphill towards the State House on Beacon St. To the left of the State House is Joy St; follow Joy St uphill to the AMC Auditorium Building (brownstone), #4 Joy St on the left hand side. Map: &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; Nearby parking is available at the Boston Common Garage, located underneath the Boston Common. Access is off Charles St, between the Public Garden and the Boston Common. We offer $6 parking tickets at the slideshows (a savings of $5). More info about the Garage is here: &lt;a href="http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4471089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363462711000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347755993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Solo Backpack in Norway, Sweden, and Finland (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>82575892</id><headcount>45</headcount><duration>9900000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352934900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/82575892/</event_url></item>