<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Pleasant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02367</zip><lat>41.939486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-526-2200</phone><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name><city>Plympton</city><id>1084839</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.802394</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/8/c/event_211482892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span&gt;Calcite Crystal Healing Web with Diana McCallum Burke&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Come join us to Welcome Spring!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will learn about Calcite &amp;amp; participate in a Healing Mediation with vibrational sounds of the Gongs. &lt;br /&gt;

 All participants will leave with a Calcite Gemstone for their collection. All are welcome from the experienced crystal worker to the beginner. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Calcite &lt;br /&gt;

 Hardness: 3 &lt;br /&gt;

 Astrological sign: Cancer &lt;br /&gt;

 Calcite grows where water is present. Calcite can be found in limestone and most seashells. Shellfish (such as oysters) make their shells from Calcite. Calcite itself is clear or white. When it grows with other minerals in the Earth, calcite can become a multitude of colors.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Calcite’s properties are associated with energy work and the energy within our body. Calcite can increase, amplify and distribute our energy and remove stagnant energy from our body. It can open and clear our blockages.  &lt;br /&gt;

 Calcite is a great stone for learning as it aids our memory and acts as our personal professor for the arts and sciences. Calcite helps us move past our old patterns providing for all kinds of healing. Calcite allows us to detach from the past, forgive others and start anew. It speeds up our spiritual development. Calcite can remove hindrances and speed up our spiritual development. &lt;br /&gt;

 Calcite benefits us physically by overcoming kidney, pancreas and spleen dis-eases. Being a calcium based stone, calcite assimilates the calcium in our body and is also good for bone dis-orders. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Calcite eases our emotions and provides us with mental growth and clarification. It assists us in changing our negative thinking by seeking out, absorbing and clearing out negative and undesirable energies and turning them positive. Calcite also clears and activates our chakras and removes blockages.  &lt;br /&gt;

 Every color of calcite has its own specific healing properties. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Blue Calcite makes us aware that our unspoken thoughts and words really do impact our thinking and our lives. Blue Calcite helps those with a “defeatest” attitude. Blue Calcite is also good to have around when we need rest and relaxation. Place Blue Calcite on the throat chakra to discourage dissent and encourage clear communication. Blue Calcite is also helpful for body pain and healing. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Green Calcite can provide “balance” and help in stagnant situations. This gorgeous translucent stone is great for getting rid of rigid beliefs and “old tapes” that keep playing in our head. Call on Green Calcite to sharpen our communication skills and provide comfort to our mind. Green Calcite is ideal for eliminating all the dis-eases and ailments associated with negative and angry behavior. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Honey Calcite is a transparent or partly transparent goldish brown color. Honey Calcite lets us remain positive as we make changes in our life. Gain self confidence and courage and heal from past abuses with this honey of a stone. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Orange Calcite has a powerful calming and healing energy that helps us get our emotions back on an even keel. It is great for helping us deal with panic and fear. Orange calcite is especially beneficial for those who suffer from unpleasant childhood experiences, including embarrassment and sexual abuse. Orange Calcite gives the recipient what they need most, be it confidence, inspiration, etc. Orange Calcite removes hindrances and helps us accomplish things. It is also great for removing clutter. Keep Orange Calcite in your office, on your desk or just about anywhere to encourage neatness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darnell</member_name><member_id>10396246</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diana Burke</member_name><member_id>13852651</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364001214000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightenment Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ShantiShala</urlname><id>1534948</id><group_lat>41.9599990845</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8099975586</group_lon><name>Shanti Shala Yoga &amp; Wellness Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362583859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Calcite Crystal Healing Web with Diana McCallum Burke</name><id>107900502</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363995000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ShantiShala/events/107900502/</event_url></item>