<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Clarendon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.348498</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Lyric Stage Company of Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>877854</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.074168</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>32.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;J&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;oin us for some Dickens with music! Lyric Studio productions are always excellent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Producing Artistic Director Spiro Veloudos, &amp;quot;this new, shorter adaptation streamlines the narrative, and captures Dickens' genius for combining exuberant characters, theatrical spectacle, and genuine emotion.&amp;quot; A cast of 25 plays over 150 characters in this remarkable two-part play with music. Winner of both the Tony Award for Best Play and The Olivier Award for Play of the Year, it has never been produced in Boston. We're pulling out all the stops for this incredible once-in-a-lifetime experience that is &amp;quot;teeming with character, atmosphere, and incident, a place where inhumanity rules until, eventually, virtue is triumphant.&amp;quot; (The New York Times) Sponsored in part by a grant from the National Endowment for the Arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Part Two of a two part show running in repertory. (NOTE: For those who missed Part 1 with Culture Vultures (which is most of you) - you could always go see Part 1 on your own, then join us for Part Two! I HIGHLY recommend this show!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner before the show.. which is optional of course. Venue TBD...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the  foyer (on the 2nd floor)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291075807000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288316573000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Life and Adventures of Nicholas NIckleby Part Two</name><id>15266055</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290888000000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/15266055/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/global_18876068.jpeg</photo_url></item>