<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>WE'RE SQUEEZING IN ONE MORE MEETUP - THE NOVEMBER SATURDAY SECOND PUG MEETUP!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pugs are having such a good time, we've scheduled ONE MORE meetup this year, at a new location in Stoughton.  Jeff and Tina Shumate, their two lovely daughters and their two Pugs, Katie the Chair Dweller and little old Reggie have invited us to join them in their big fenced yard in Stoughton.  There's an enclosed outdoor fireplace, so we can stay warm in spite of the weather.  We'll have hot drinks!  There is plenty of parking in the Shumate's driveway and on the street.  Don't forget to bring your chairs!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember that your host provides the soft drinks and paperware for each meetup, but we count on our members to bring the snacks.  Feel free to bring snacks for the Pugs, but try to bring soft snacks so that Clovis can have some too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know. We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR NOVEMBER SUNDAY PUG SOCIAL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Goves' yard is ENORMOUS and perfectly flat, and quite a few of the younger, more agile dogs made full use of it, racing around the entire perimeter.  However, most of the Pugs, being Pugs after all, prudently stayed on or near the deck where the food was, gratefully accepted handouts and ate and ate and ate.  Someone brought a whole tub of homemade tiny doggy apple muffins, and all of the dogs loved them!  Even ancient little Reggie, who could not climb the deck steps by himself, knew perfectly well where the food was and insisted on a lift up onto the deck where the goodies were.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had quite a turnout, in spite of the cooler weather.  The sun came out, and the dogs stayed quite warm, even little Katie, who absolutely refused to leave her chair, where she sat wrapped in a fleece jacket, and quite comfortable right where she was, with all those nice people around to hand deliver her muffins to her.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About 35 people and 30 Pugs were joined by a larger than usual collection of non-Puggie canines.  Not only did we have our regulars, Cletus the French Bulldog and Wizzar the Jack Russell, but also in attendance were Oliver a BIG Boston Terrier, a delightful little poodle, and Wizzar's Rat Terrier sister, Rogue.  With cooler weather, the dogs could safely chase each other around the yard, and who knew that a Pug could wear out a terrier?  Buddy, our very large and very happy rescue Pug did just that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to all the people who brought the goodies - Clovis says the apple muffins were to die for!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your babies. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be soft drinks and something to snack on for the people attending! If you bring treats for the Pugs, please ONLY hand out treats around the central table where everyone can keep an eye on the dogs, DON'T FEED CLOVIS, and PLEASE BE SURE that nothing gets dropped - your organizer has a Pug (yes, that would be Clovis...) who has brain damage which makes it very difficult for him to swallow. I don't want Clovis to choke to death on a stolen treat, and I'm sure no one else does either.. Thank you for your consideration!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. If he starts bullying or being too rough with another dog, give him a time out until he can get himself under control.  We want everyone to have fun!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend. Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis and Cletus's faces when the Puggie meetups roll around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235332882000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226261663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston November SATURDAY SECOND Pug Meetup</name><id>9126802</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227380400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/9126802/</event_url></item>