<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A brief personal anecdote: Mike once brought a friend to LaScala who had never been there before. Impressed with the restaurant's ambience and expecting great things from the kitchen, she decided to backslide on a longstanding humanitarian position and ordered veal, only to have such severe pangs of conscience that she was completely unable to enjoy her dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The moral, fellow diners, is don't put your conscience where your mouth is. But please &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; put your fork where your mouth is when we head to your choice in our &amp;quot;L&amp;quot; restaurant poll, &lt;a href="http://www.lascalarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;LaScala Ristorante&lt;/a&gt; in Randolph, on Friday, April 24th at 6:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on North Main Street (Route 28), LaScala is one of those &amp;quot;been there forever&amp;quot; places that have attained &amp;quot;institution&amp;quot; status. People go there expecting a comfortable, yet elegant atmosphere and a menu full of Italian favorites, and that is what they find, day in and day out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few examples of menu offerings include pan fried escarole (an appetizer), Shrimp Exquisito (shrimp dipped in egg with cheese, sauteed in butter, Marsala and brandy), Pollo Venezia (sliced chicken sauteed in white wine with mushrooms and artichokes), and tiramisu for dessert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us as we head to Randolph to experience an old neighborhood tradition. Just remember to keep your principles intact...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LaScala Ristorante&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1070 North Main St. (Route 28), Randolph&lt;br /&gt;(781)  961-1700&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lascalarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lascalares...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, April 24th @ 6:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maximum number of attendees:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Quite a few pasta entrees are under $10.00, with most other main dishes ranging from $14.95 - $17.95.  Linguini with shrimp, clams and Alaskan crab legs for $26.95 represents the high end of the menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please note that in addition to SSDOMG's usual cash only policy, LaScala has its own: &lt;b&gt;No credit cards are accepted!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Thursday, April 23rd @ 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; LaScala is located on North Main Street (Route 28) in Randolph. Please watch this space for more detailed directions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242428539000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239720270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ooh, LaScala!</name><id>10182384</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240612200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10182384/</event_url></item>