<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Mechanic St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.316513</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mezcal Restaurant</name><city>New Haven</city><id>415557</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.908750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*** Even if you can't stay for happy hour, please stop by to drop off some donations. I'll be at Mezcal starting at 6 pm. Everything you bring will make a huge difference at a time where there are massive food shortages. Thanks for your help!! ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** UPDATE: We are going to do a food drive at this Monday's Happy  Hour.  As we move into winter, now is the time that the soup kitchens need a lot of donations. Please bring nonperishable items to the happy hour at  Mezcal. Always good items to bring are cereals, peanut butter, canned vegetables, soups, etc. Jeanie has graciously volunteered to collect the items and bring them to the soup kitchen on Tuesday (Thanks, Jeanie!!!). Just taking a few minutes at the store and spending a few dollars -like what you would spend on one drink- will help a lot of people in need out!! Thank you for your support. See you at happy hour!**** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is:  &lt;br /&gt;Mezcal Resturant &lt;br /&gt;14 Mechanic St &lt;br /&gt;New Haven, CT 06511 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mezcal is a new Mexican restaurant in New Haven offering authentic Mexican food as well as fantastic margaritas and Mexican beers. They are excited to host the NHC for our first happy hour there so come and check it out! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The owner of Mezcal is offering some great drinks specials: &lt;br /&gt;** ½ price well drinks &lt;br /&gt;** $1.50 off top shelf alcohol including tequila &lt;br /&gt;** chips and salsa &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant is open until 9:30 on Monday nights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact is Andrea (203-641-8083) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...  &lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.  &lt;br /&gt;Ever. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring a friend*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post-party location TBD. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196896128000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193782995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>12/03 Mon. Happy Hour and FOOD DRIVE at Mezcal</name><id>6645748</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196722800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6645748/</event_url></item>