<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.32000017166</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>May was a HUGE success. We had a large turn out with a lot of old friends as well as a several new wonderful puggie families! We raised enough money again to help our friends at Curly Tail Pug Rescue get another banner for their NY branch. The money from the last Meetup is being put to good use for advertising banners for Curly Tail Pug Rescue, so thank you all for your monthly donations. It's only $5 but it goes a long way. So please, make sure to contribute when you can. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We are shooting for July 25th to do our first annual cookout&lt;/b&gt;. I would like to get some feedback as to how many people think they can make the date, if not, we can do it the week before maybe. Also, due to our beautiful puggies lack of tolerance for the heat, I would like to bring up a few &lt;b&gt;VERY&lt;/b&gt; important issues..First, I think we should not start until about 4pm so the mid-day sun is not blazing down on us....secondly, we will have shady secure areas for everyone's pugs to hang out, but PLEASE...if your pug REALLY has a hard time with the heat, feel free to leave them home for this one and just come and hang out with us for the afternoon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each and every one if you have been so incredibly helpful and supportive in terms of pitching in and helping out less fortunate pugs and Kelly and Albert and I just really want this cookout to be a thank you gathering of new friends to come out, relax and have fun at our beautiful home in Grafton. ONE VERY IMPORTANT NOTE: RSVP EARLY......We will only be able to accommodate 40 people. don't MISS OUT! 4-8pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly and I will provide all of the grilling food, and we would love it if we could make the rest like a pot-luck where everyone bring something to pitch in. We will bring a sign up sheet to our June Meetup, but please feel free to email me directly if you can not make the June Meetup, but would like to attend the cookout. Here is an initial list of what we think we will need and if you have a signature dish you would like to bring, by all means bring it and also if there is anything you think we forgot, shoot us an email to let us know. When it comes time to RSVP, please list the number of PEOPLE attending with you including children with a comment in the notes field as to what you plan to bring so everyone can see and we won't double up. If you DO plan to bring children, PLEASE make sure they stick by you and do not feed the pugs ANYTHING. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have plenty of fun activities to do such as lawn games, music, etc... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the list: &lt;br /&gt;Paper Plates &lt;br /&gt;Plastic cups &lt;br /&gt;Napkins &lt;br /&gt;Plastic silverware &lt;br /&gt;Soda &lt;br /&gt;ICE &lt;br /&gt;Salad &lt;br /&gt;Dressing &lt;br /&gt;Appetizer &lt;br /&gt;Chips  &lt;br /&gt;Dip &lt;br /&gt;BUNS-hotdog/hamburg &lt;br /&gt;Condiments-Mustard/Relish/Ketchup &lt;br /&gt;Macaroni Salad &lt;br /&gt;Potato Salad &lt;br /&gt;Watermelon &lt;br /&gt;Dessert &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring adult beverages if you wish and don't forget to bring your pug's dinner if you plan to be there through dinner time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly and I truly enjoy being the Organizers of the Grafton pug Meetup. We hope that we have met each of you individually, and if we have not, please come up and introduce yourself at the next one. We are constantly trying to come up with new treats for our precious pugs, and ideas to keep it informative and interesting. We welcome all suggestions. It seems to be very personal and we all have tons of fun.  We always welcome new members to come join in the fun and excitement at watching our little puggie friends romp and play in the spacious room at the Gibson Kennel in Grafton. Note: &lt;b&gt;this is a PUG Meetup&lt;/b&gt;...as not all breeds play well together.  There are other small breed Meetups, but this is for PUGS ONLY! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******A receipt of current vaccinations must be brought with you in order to enter the play area (kennel rules)*********  (this has not been strictly enforced at the Meetups but, it's better safe then sorry since the owner of the kennel did request we have this on-hand) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will ask for a $5 fee per family for each Meetup&lt;/b&gt; to cover Meetup costs and any leftover money will be donated to the Curly Tail Pug Rescue or any other Pug charity that we all agree on as a group. These donations go toward paying the monthly dues, snacks and to keep this website going so we can all see when the next Meetup is taking place.  We will also do special events from time to time to keep it fun and interesting! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all and I look forward to playing again with all you pug lovers out there and your pups! =)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will introduce ourselves...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erin maguire</member_name><member_id>3828727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248551853000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Puggy Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pug-569</urlname><id>252667</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6900024414</group_lon><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243706660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grafton Pug June Meetup</name><id>10530762</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246122000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pug-569/events/10530762/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/a/global_8419338.jpeg</photo_url></item>