<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>149 Alewife Parkway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.393603</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Summer Shack Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>689448</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.140997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The movies have been announced and the weather has been forecast:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Odd Life of Timothy Green &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Screen 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mendondrivein.com/contentimages/odd_life_of_timothy_green_f.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLAYING:    AUG 17-23&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHOWTIME:  Dusk at approx.  8:10PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PG&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academy Award®–nominated director/writer Peter Hedges (“Dan in Real Life,” What’s Eating Gilbert Grape?”) brings enchantment to the screen with “The Odd Life of Timothy Green,” an inspiring, magical story about a happily married couple, Cindy and Jim Green (Jennifer Garner and Joel Edgerton), who can’t wait to start a family but can only dream about what their child would be like. When young Timothy (CJ Adams) shows up on their doorstep one stormy night, Cindy and Jim—and their small town of Stanleyville—learn that sometimes the unexpected can bring some of life’s greatest gifts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cast: &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/jennifergarner/overview/p230436" target="_blank"&gt;Jennifer Garner&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/joeledgerton/overview/p264023" target="_blank"&gt;Joel Edgerton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/diannewiest/overview/p76163" target="_blank"&gt;Dianne Wiest&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/cjadams/overview/p696461" target="_blank"&gt;CJ Adams&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/rosemariedewitt/overview/p435423" target="_blank"&gt;Rosemarie DeWitt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Director: &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/peterhedges/overview/p31485" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Hedges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;We will meet at the Alewife T Sign at 5:30 to get into cars and take off for a Saturday Night at the Drive-In!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Picture yourself sitting on your lounge chair or blanket, outside, on a glorious summer evening with stars twinkling overhead and a gentle breeze wafting through your hair. Well here we go again!! The group is having another road trip to the Mendon Drive-In and here's to having some fun!! Should prove to be a nostalgic re-visit for some and a first -time experience for others. We'll meet at the large letter T at the Alewife Station outside the Bertucci's Restaurant where Susan and John will coordinate the drivers and passengers. People who are willing to drive for this event, can park in the Summer Shack Restaurant parking lot across the street from the T Station. Those who need a ride, should arrive on the Red Line and wait at the large T.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Since the drive-in charges $20 a carload, both drivers and passengers will be depending on each other to be there and share the cost. The total number of people that can go will depend on the number of people who will be driving. Cars should probably seat 4 people and passengers will chip in for gas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;We'll plan to get there well before sunset and do some tailgating. There's a tasty concession stand there (word is that locals go just for the food sometimes) and you can bring in food and non-alcoholic drinks. Bring Frisbees and other such stuff for a little relaxation before showtime.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;When you RSVP, PLEASE write in the comments if you can volunteer to drive or if you are going to be a passenger. Also, if you're a driver, please indicate how many passengers, not counting yourself, can go with you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Alas, we won't know the movie that is showing until the Monday before. Since we are all in this one together, for better or worse, dropping out at the last minute would be grounds for being removed from the group and would not at all be appreciated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;We'll keep updating this posting with more info and ideas as we get nearer to the big night. The movie will start around 8:30 so we'll plan to meet at Alewife at 5:30. Rain or shine event. Also, for liability purposes, we can only include people over the age of 18.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Here's the link to the &lt;a href="http://www.mendondrivein.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Mendon Drive-In&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Hope you decide to join us for what should be a fun evening,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Susan and John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at the large letter T at the Alewife Station outside the Bertucci's Restaurant where Susan and John will coordinate the drivers and passengers.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345430682000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343005850000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sixth Annual Drive-In Movie Event at the Mendon!</name><id>74472102</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345325400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/74472102/</event_url></item>