<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>94 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.808808</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-4428</phone><name>Newburyport Public Library</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>880292</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870878</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Monday March 12, 2012 at 7 PM at the Newburyport Library Let's talk about what tools we can share, and what we need for tools for our garden season. Does someone have need of a rototiller, garden planning, a truck to haul salt marsh hay? Does someone have a wheelbarrow, a hoe, or experience with double dug gardens they would share? Bring you needs and ideas about available resources to the meeting and we'll make a list of what we have and what we need. Tool sharing involves the following steps: Hold a meeting to find out people&amp;rsquo;s needs and available resources., MARCH 12 Determine the scope of the program; it&amp;rsquo;s often best to start with simpler hand tools. Determine storage&amp;mdash;will tools be stored in homes or in a common space? Determine how costs will be covered for tool purchases and ongoing maintenance. Develop a clear set of lending, repair and tool-return rules. Develop a list of &amp;ldquo;experts&amp;rdquo; who can share skills. Organize a system to track checkout and return of tools. Assign responsibility for maintenance and repair. We'll brainstorm solutions and see what is next! See you then. Visit Edible Garden Group - EGG at: &lt;a href="http://hyperlocavore.ning.com/groups/group/show?id=2710552%3AGroup%3A23072&amp;amp;xg_source=msg_mes_group" class="linkified"&gt;http://hyperlocavore.ning.com/groups/group/show?id=2710552%3AGroup%3A23072&amp;amp;xg_source=msg_mes_group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boiester</member_name><member_id>8570902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331599063000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330789344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tool needs and sharing meeting- Edible Garden Group</name><id>54798032</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331593200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/54798032/</event_url></item>