<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Peruvian Andes Exploration  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The adventure guide company Inkaland Journeys&lt;/b&gt; is putting together two premier Peruvian Andes’ trekking experiences in both the Cordillera Blanca Range for June 20 – 30, 2011 and the Cordillera Huayhuash Range for July 11 - 22, 2011.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both of these incredible treks will take New England Meetup trekking adventurist into this pristine world of unsurpassed beauty. These two spectacular ranges are within Peru’s Parque Nacional Huascaran (was car rahn) and are rated as some of the world’s most magnificent trekking routes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will trek in the land of the Inca’s, be face to face with Peru’s most spectacular spiraling white-capped Andean peaks, meet and interact with the warm, gentle, Quechua (ket chu ah) mountain people, see their stone-thatched dwelling in the natural traditional environment as they have lived for thousands of years as you capture the unmatched adventure travel experience of a life time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you seek to live your best now and want to crystallize your desire for a “national geographic” type trekking experience, then this adventure is not out of bounds for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/3/3/8/event_20089976.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign-up now and experience the life-changing consequences of your decision. Want inspiration? Come preview this adventure trek on &lt;b&gt;Thursday, 1/20/11 at 6:45 PM (presentation starts at 7:00 PM) at the Best Western located at 4 Hall Street, Concord, NH (603.228.4300).&lt;/b&gt; Pizza and soda will be served or BYOB if you desire. I feel confident that you will find the Andes presentation a 10 on the drool scale of “must-do” adventure treks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/7/1/3/event_20266867.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our base camp and launch-point is a one hour regional flight north of Lima to the city of Huaraz (10,170 ft) at the heart of, and gateway to, the Cordillera Blanca and Cordillera Huayhuash ranges. Nice cozy guest houses, tasty meals and supply accommodations are inexpensive in Huaraz. From our Huaraz base we will begin our altitude acclimatization hikes and start our high Andes’ adventure treks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Inkaland Journeys team will safely guide you through this pristine wilderness of very high altitude, white-capped peaks. All of our logistic travel and trek details will be meticulously planned and executed so members simply enjoy the trekking while Inkaland Journeys fully manages the details from the moment you land in Lima to the moment you depart Peru.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of the trekking, and most of the campsites, are above the 13,000 ft tree line with the snowline starting at approximately 15,700 ft so these majestic peaks are right up close. You become the experience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While decent physical conditioning is necessary, accompanied by 2 days of acclimation hikes, only daypacks are necessary since burros carry your personal gear, tents and our cooking/dining equipment and supplies. Professional UIAGM certified guides, assistant guides with rescue horses and mountain cooks making delicious meals are all there to support and facilitate your high Andes adventure experience. Elevate your expectations and become what you think.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Capture the Andes spirit…experience the journey on this unforgettable New England Meetup Andes’ adventure trip.  Come to the presentation, The more the merrier… it holds true for both our group size and our discount.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call Greg Horton at 860.977.5017 for any questions regarding cost and travel logistics and sign up now through inkalandjourneys.com.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tu Amigos, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greg Horton  Partner/Director  &lt;br /&gt;Edita Oncoy   Partner/Director&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When people enter the front door of the Best Western, an employee at the front desk will direct Meetup members to the conference room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg Horton</member_name><member_id>12460394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295790871000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293948432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Peruvian Andes Trekking Presentation</name><id>15882063</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295568000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15882063/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/b/b/global_20266795.jpeg</photo_url></item>