<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.348382</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>1235661</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083769</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Come one, come all! Enjoy the wonderfully literary annual spectacle of Shakespearean culture on the Commons!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and actually good, it will be playing on the commons. Join us at 7 p.m. with a picnic dinner, blankets, and friends for a bawdy good time! The actual show begins at eight, but we strongly encourage you to come early to get a prime seat. We'll be ready as usual to grab a drink afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain date: Friday, July 30, 2010 at 7 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.boston-discovery-guide.com/shakespeare-on-the-common.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston-dis...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:   Near the Parkman Bandstand and ball field on Boston Common.  The Bandstand is sort of behind Frog Pond, near the center of the Common.More of the Bard &lt;br /&gt;Dates and times:  July 28 - August 15.  Tuesday - Saturday performances of Shakespeare on the Common start at 8pm, and Sunday performances start at 7pm. &lt;br /&gt;Cost:  Free; public of all ages invited&lt;br /&gt;For more information:  617-426-0863;  website&lt;br /&gt;Nearest T station:  Green and Red Lines/Park Street &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What to bring for Shakespeare on the Common&lt;br /&gt;What should you bring to the free performance?&lt;br /&gt;At a minimum, bring a blanket to sit on. The elevated, well-lit stage is at the bottom of a gentle slope, so you should be able to see well from wherever you're sitting.  Some people also bring low folding chairs. The area closest to the stage begins to fill up about 2 hours before the performance.  However, the lighting and sound systems make it easy for you to see and hear what's going on.&lt;br /&gt;Lots of people bring picnic dinners, and along with something cold and refreshing to drink.  But if you don't have time to pack a dinner, don't worry.  Food vendors typically hail from some of Boston's favorite eateries, such as Upper Crust, Figaro's, and Ben and Jerry's.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilie</member_name><member_id>4710889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280449139000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278510927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shakespeare on The Common: OTHELLO!</name><id>14027339</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280444400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/14027339/</event_url></item>