<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374401</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-903-7371</phone><name>Private Location #2</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>832579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121895</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever walked up to someone at a social gathering (meetup events, parties, networking events, bars, etc), started a conversation with them, and then realized that you were stuck with nothing left to talk about?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't it be great if you had some simple tools you could use again and again to effortlessly keep the conversation going with the people you're talking to?  Well that's what you're going to learn at this seminar.  Your conversations will flow effortlessly, and people will find themselves being drawn to you and wanting to spend more time with you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Imagine being at a meetup event and gliding around the room talking with anyone and everyone.  Imagine having people approach &lt;u&gt;you&lt;/u&gt; to start a conversation because they see others having a good time talking with you, and they want to see what you're all about.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Here's a small sample of what you'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to smoothly transition from the initial approach to the next conversation topic so that the interaction feels completely natural both to you and the people you're talking to.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What to actually talk about (and which topics people find interesting). &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to use the &amp;quot;oh shit button&amp;quot; to bail yourself out of awkward silences (I use this on occasion, and it works perfectly every time).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The secret to getting people to open to you, even if you just met them.  Once you understand this, you can build deep friendships &amp;amp; relationships with anyone you want.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to instantly make a conversation more interesting just by making one simple change to what you're already doing (this one will surprise you).&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 ways to end a conversation that will leave people feeling good about you. If you've ever wanted to end a conversation with someone, but were worried about offending or upsetting them, then this is perfect for you.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best part is that you will walk away with tools and techniques that you can use right away wherever you go to meet people.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members.  We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 40 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, March 7th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271016608000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267515133000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Keep A Conversation Going After The Approach</name><id>12754466</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267993800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/12754466/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/e/global_13418494.jpeg</photo_url></item>