<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to all of you who attended the August NLP meetup. It was another great meeting, this time focusing on the use of metaphor.  We ended up practicing a problem-solving technique using visual metaphors (ie we drew our problems, our solutions, and the pathway to get from the former to the latter). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For September: this month we?ll be doing 6-step Reframing and the Parts Model.  This is one of the first techniques that Bandler and Grinder (the two founders of NLP) developed through modeling excellence, in this case from the pioneering therapist Virginia Satir.  What I like about 6-step reframing is its usefulness in a wide range of situations, and also its core assumption that every behavior has a positive intention behind it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An important note: as of this meeting, the meeting fee is going up to $10.00.  The fee that I pay to Meetup.com is 2-4 dollars of that (depending on the number of people who show up).  The rest of it is for the time and energy it takes me to develop and teach the monthly meeting.  Please note as well that I will never turn anyone away for financial reasons; if you can?t afford the $10 fee, then just pay what you can.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September?s NLP meetup does not depend on having attended any of the previous NLP meetups. It also does not presuppose that you know anything about NLP. Everyone is welcome, from beginners to experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190502756000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187309102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Neuro Linguistic Programming September Meetup</name><id>6194008</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190329200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/6194008/</event_url></item>