<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Market St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.077868</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-430-9122 </phone><name>Portsmouth Gaslight</name><city>Portsmouth </city><id>750121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757330</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/5/4/event_218187732.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine: Several of your friends are on stage to volunteer for The Comedy Hypnosis Show. Stage hypnotist Ellen Moschetto snaps her fingers and one at a time, your friends fall to the floor into a hypnotic trance. After giving some crazy hypnotic suggestions insanity ensues… Sounds crazy? It is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ellen Moschetto is a critically acclaimed stage hypnotist that has been touring colleges and performing arts centers for over 10 years. &lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Moschetto’s Comedy Hypnosis Show is part stand up comedy, part improvisation, part hypnosis and a little bit of America’s Got Talent mixed together. The show is premiering this Spring at the Portsmouth Gas Light Co. The show delivers an interactive, improvisational and sidesplitting comedy while simultaneously unlocking the unique mysteries of the human mind. It's a musical and fast-paced romp through volunteers' subconscious creative genius that keeps audiences on the edges of their seats.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; Audience members have the option to volunteer or sit back and watch. &lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;In the movies, hypnosis is often depicted as a sinister thing, in which unwilling victims are induced to commit murder and mayhem. Or, it's used to unlock suppressed bad memories of very troubled people. In our show, however, hypnosis can both helpful -- and hilarious.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do not miss the most hysterical, mind numbing show that you will ever see. You can &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt; the show or &lt;em&gt;be&lt;/em&gt; the show. Comedy Hypnosis Show at Portsmouth Gas Light Co Third Floor Club on Friday April 19, starting at 7:00 p.m. Show Tickets are $25 in advance or $30 at the door. Doors open at 6 pm. Tickets can be purchased on-line at www.drinkwaterproductions.com!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a table for meetup members</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary Chick</member_name><member_id>14158649</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366424265000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Men and Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-527</urlname><id>501015</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Cocktail Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364306648000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Hypnosis Show</name><id>111118942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366412400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-527/events/111118942/</event_url></item>