<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 1A</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.002430</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Rye Harbor Boat Launch</name><city>Rye</city><id>8216102</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.747110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/4/2/event_143124642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This skill session is designed to build off skills learned in previous Lake sessions. We will paddle out a Rye harbor and work on basic skills such as assisted rescues, self rescues, bracing as we work our way down to Jenness Beach. At Jenness Beach, we'll work on side surfing small waves at the shoreline and then practice breaking out of the surf zone, before surfing small waves. Low tide is 2:10 pm. Jenness Beach at low tide is generally a good place to learn to surf a kayak and handle the surf zone as the waves tend to be small and rolling, giving long rides on easy waves. (this assumes that the ocean swell is small and winds less than 15 mph) Expect water temperatures about 60 degrees. Light neoprene is suggested ( farmer John or shortie wetsuit ) but not required. Like previous skill sessions, this is a PARTICIPATORY event, no spectators. Return time: 4:30 pm This is currently limited to 10 participants, but I will expand that number as more experienced safety boaters volunteer to help out. Max # will be 20.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minimum REQUIRED equipment: 14 ft or longer kayak with bulkheads or airbags, PFD, sprayskirt, pump, paddle float, and paddle. Recommended: helmet, spare paddle Bring a lunch, sunscreen and plenty of fluids to drink. Plan on staying for the day!....will not allow any paddler to venture back alone to the put in.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The boat ramp is just before the entrance to Rye Harbor State Park</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy Foley</member_name><member_id>7753713</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344911726000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342376124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ocean Skill Session</name><id>73443102</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344780000000</time><rsvp_limit>19</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/73443102/</event_url></item>