<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nhreia.com" target="_blank"&gt;New Hampshire Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPCOMING MEETING:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NHREIA PRESENTS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT:  &amp;quot;THE ART OF THE SHORT SALE&amp;quot; with Bert Cox&lt;br /&gt;WHEN:  NHREIA Monthly meeting - Wednesday, Feb. 13, 2008, 6:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: The Best Western Executive Court,  13500 South Willow St., Manchester, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bert Cox, President and Founder of NHREIA, is an active investor, REALTOR®, and auctioneer and operates in the I-93 corridor from Concord to Nashua as well as Keene and parts of MA. He has been involved in Real Estate since 1985 and currently manages about 15 units. He is an advocate of real estate education and practices creative real estate. His mentors and teachers include AD Kessler, Ron LeGrand, and Robyn Thompson. He attributes his success to a focus on meeting the needs of buyers, sellers and investors; unlike traditional Real Estate practitioners that use the one-size-fits-all approach. His colleagues call him the Renegade Realtor®. He is familiar with buying and selling property in your IRA, short sales, 7-day auctions, rent-to-own, 1031 exchanges, seller financing, zero down payment programs, options, lease options, rehabs, new construction and has considerable expertise on negotiating with, through or around Real Estate Agents.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bert has specialized  in short sales for several years and will share:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     * How to work with distressed homeowners facing pre-foreclosure&lt;br /&gt;     * How to negotiate with the bank&lt;br /&gt;     * How to complete a short sale package &lt;br /&gt;     * How to capitalize on short sales in a down market&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DON'T MISS THIS EVENT...and look for upcoming e-mails, NHREIA is working with the Boston AREIA to provide a much needed all day short sale seminar with National Speaker and Short Sale Expert Curtis Brooks.  Visit www.BostonAREIA.com for more information!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bernadette Trafton&lt;br /&gt;Marketing Director&lt;br /&gt;Home Office: 603-434-0093&lt;br /&gt;Cell Phone:  603-834-4587&lt;br /&gt;www.nhreia.com &lt;br /&gt;www.BostonAREIA.com &lt;br /&gt;Bernadette@BostonAREIA.com&lt;br /&gt;www.BernadetteTrafton.com&lt;br /&gt;CALL 1-888-334-7297 TODAY for your free Credit Restoration Pamphlet and to schedule your FREE Debt Free Analysis!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203118606000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>NHREIA is the fastest growing real estate investment group in NH.</why><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-756</urlname><id>633261</id><group_lat>42.9399986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>NH Entrepreneurs Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199925587000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The New Hampshire Real Estate Investors Association February Meetup</name><id>7075595</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202945400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-756/events/7075595/</event_url></item>