<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Braintree, MA</address_2><address_1>128 Town Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.203080</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>n/a</phone><name>Braintree High School</name><city>Braintree</city><id>172533</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.021370</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Spring has sprung and it is time to get back outdoors!  Join players of all levels as we work on our swing, serve, volleys, and other tennis skills.  We are here to have fun and get back in the swing of things.  If you are looking for a competitive game (so early?) then this is not the event for you.  Today is all about getting back in the swing of things, doing some conditioning exercises, practicing our shots, having some rallies and getting to know one another.  If some folks want to play a game or two as the event progresses that is up to them to do so.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About 15 minutes into the event we will participate in a 10-15 minute Group Stretching and Warm-Up Exercise.  Don't worry about losing our courts, we will spread out over the courts we are using.  This will allow people to do their own thing for a few minutes and allow for late arrivals so we can all do our stretching, warm-ups and conditioning together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Braintree High School offers plenty of opportunity to play tennis on its 6 tennis courts and two practice backboards.  Courts are available for up to 2 hours.  The BHS Tennis Teams and those w/ permits have priority over residents who all have priority over non-residents.  (Hence, why it is important to have your location correct.)  As I am a Braintree resident I will not have a problem with getting us at least one court.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a can of &lt;i&gt;used&lt;/i&gt; tennis balls.  The Event Organizers (EO's) will bring some of our balls from our collection from over the past couple of years.  New tennis balls should be saved for games.  If you are ready to play a couple of games we may do so the 2nd half of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please Note: This is NOT instructional.  Therefore, you should have a basic knowledge of the game, how to use the racket, know the rules and know how to volley.  Ideally, you should be at least a 1.5 or Advance Beginner.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*If you would like to find out your playing level (rating) please note it in your RSVP Comments and Angela will work on this with you towards the end of the event.  Please bring the NTRP rating sheet found in the Files section.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please note in your RSVP Comments if you need a racket or will be more than 1/2 hr late.  This session will run about 1.5 hours.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spring Into Tennis!&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, April 7th, 2010 @ 5:30-7pm&lt;br /&gt;Braintree High School Tennis Courts&lt;br /&gt;128 Town Street&lt;br /&gt;(Enter off Franklin St/Route 37)&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;Sorry, no phone #.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/i&gt;: On the tennis courts.  I may be on one of the courts so look for me and my bag of rackets.  I may have the ball hopper with me, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/i&gt;: Angela &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Min/Max&lt;/i&gt;: Min of 6 participants by 6pm on Monday, April 5th in order for this event to take place.  Max of 14 people.  We can rotate on and off the courts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Guests&lt;/i&gt;: Welcome, 1 per member!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ages&lt;/i&gt;: Normally our events are adults-only.  However, if you have a child or relative who is &lt;i&gt;16+ and they are a level 1.5/AB or better&lt;/i&gt; they are welcome to attend this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Event Fees&lt;/i&gt;: None!  We no longer charge event fees.  In the future we may ask for a $1 donation for tennis balls and supplies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/i&gt;: 6pm on Tuesday, April 6th (Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizers until after the event.  Also, I do not have internet access during the workday.  You can still join us after the RSVP Deadline if there is space available.  Simply RSVP Yes and show-up.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Case of Inclement Weather:&lt;br /&gt;If it is raining the event will be cancelled.  We will check the courts if it rains a day or two before the event.  Heavy rains on Wednesday will cancel.  I will email all Yes RSVPs my cell number at or shortly after the RSVP Deadline to call me after 4pm for any changes. &lt;br /&gt;**Please check back here a couple days before the event for an update on weather conditions.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: On the &amp;quot;Frequently Used Venues&amp;quot; Discussion Thread on the Message Board.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me on the courts w/ my bag of rackets and some tennis balls.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270851177000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268268149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Into Tennis!</name><id>12843469</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270675800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/12843469/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/0/global_3889440.jpeg</photo_url></item>