<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clear Conscience Cafe/Harvest Co-Op Market</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>687911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>With muchos apologies to my Monday night conflict members, I'm stuck this month without an alternative (unless the consensus during our March meeting is to bump it back two weeks..will keep ya posted :-).  We're heading to Monday for April, but will head back to Tuesday come May and hopefully beyond :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The polls state Olive Kitteridge is next in the running.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio/62-9781400062089-0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Publisher Comments:In a voice more powerful and compassionate than ever before, New York Times bestselling author Elizabeth Strout binds together thirteen rich, luminous narratives into a book with the heft of a novel, through the presence of one larger-than-life, unforgettable character: Olive Kitteridge.&lt;br /&gt;At the edge of the continent, Crosby, Maine, may seem like nowhere, but seen through this brilliant writer's eyes, it's in essence the whole world, and the lives that are lived there are filled with all of the grand human drama — desire, despair, jealousy, hope, and love.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;At times stern, at other times patient, at times perceptive, at other times in sad denial, Olive Kitteridge, a retired schoolteacher, deplores the changes in her little town and in the world at large, but she doesn't always recognize the changes in those around her: a lounge musician haunted by a past romance: a former student who has lost the will to live: Olive's own adult child, who feels tyrannized by her irrational sensitivities; and Henry, who finds his loyalty to his marriage both a blessing and a curse.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;As the townspeople grapple with their problems, mild and dire, Olive is brought to a deeper understanding of herself and her life — sometimes painfully, but always with ruthless honesty. Olive Kitteridge offers profound insights into the human condition — its conflicts, its tragedies and joys, and the endurance it requires.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll do the old standby of the Clear Conscious Cafe.  Look for me with book in hand, or a groups of us hovering.  As ever, if we are crowded out and you see no familiar bookclub faces, you can always try Au Bon Pain across the street (684 Mass Ave:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Am bumping back to the 20 limit for RSVP for our winter months with my apologies, but it's just more practical.  Will have a waiting list so &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;please, please please&lt;/span&gt; keep your RSVP accurate to keep someone from missing out if you can't attend.  I haven't been an ogre yet, but if folks are being denied attendance due to your inconsiderateness, I may change into the mean version of Shrek.  I'm also going to start changing any &amp;quot;maybe's&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; a few days prior to give anyone on the waiting list a chance to join in.  So plan to update your RSVPs as your plans become finalized.  As ever, will send out my cell number to my yes's the day or so prior.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Reading!!  I promise, tuesdays in May!! :-)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the book on a table (I hope) or for my grinning and/or anxious face at a table :-)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270821603000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267213195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: Olive Kitteridge by Elizabeth Strout</name><id>12718134</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270508400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/12718134/</event_url></item>