<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>873 Whalley Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06515</zip><lat>41.326642</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.389.9555    </phone><name>Kehler Liddell Gallery</name><city>New Haven</city><id>800189</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.959489</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Its back!!!! ArtWalk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Lets start our evening at Kehler Liddell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Anyone who attended last year will tell you this was an absolute blast!! Multiple Gallery Openings, with Music..., local vendors open late with special events like wine tasting....The end of the night culminates in a dance party at Lyrical Hall, disco ball and all. Great night out and lots to do and see. The fun does not stop there, come back the following day and explore on your own more great events, (Jay Cusano has a tent in the arts alley, please go visit him). This all takes place in Westville Village in New Haven and is not to be missed!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westvillect.org/artwalk2010schedule" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westvillec...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Artist Reception: Matthew Garrett &amp;amp; Gigi Liverant: Photography and Painting&lt;/b&gt;, 6-9pm. Artist Talk: 6pm.&lt;br /&gt;Also....,As you look at art, indulge in the sweet melodies of New Haven's most beloved teachers/musicians and the co-Director of Horns For Kids, Fred Rossomando on the piano.  A percentage of any artwork sold on Friday night will benefit Connecticut's non-profit organization Horns For Kids.  Also The Postcard Challenge.  We invite visitors to buy a 4x6 inch postcard for $5, take it home, design it, and then mail it to the gallery, where it will remain on display AND FOR SALE the months of June and July.  Who says it's hard to break into the gallery world?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Kehler Liddell&lt;br /&gt;873 Whalley Avenue&lt;br /&gt;New Haven, CT&lt;br /&gt;203.389.9555&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;DeSilva Gallery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;899 Whalley Avenue&lt;br /&gt;New Haven&lt;br /&gt;203-387-2539&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reception: Pongratz&lt;br /&gt;Meet the Artist Jacob Pongratz&lt;br /&gt;6-9 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;&lt;b&gt;8 Eyes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographs by 4 extraordinary painters&lt;br /&gt;Mia Brownell&lt;br /&gt;Nathan Lewis&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Mir&lt;br /&gt;Lawrence Mirelli&lt;br /&gt;Jennfer Jane Gallery&lt;br /&gt;828 Whalley Avenue&lt;br /&gt;New Haven,CT&lt;br /&gt;203.494.9905&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://jenniferjanegallery.com/Jennifer_Jane_Gallery/Calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://jenniferjanega...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Annex at the Austin Street Inn.&lt;/b&gt; 5-8pm  Ribbon Cutting and Reception:  Celebrate the opening of KLG’s new off-site exhibition space and tour Westville’s newest B&amp;amp;B.  The group exhibition features the sale of 5 Benefit Silkscreen Prints done by socially committed artists Silvano Lora, Carlos Sangiovani, Asdrubal Dominguez, Manuel Almonte of the Dominican Republic, and Miguel Trelles of New Haven; proceeds benefit Amnesty International. (9 Austin St.). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agolaccio&lt;/b&gt;: a gallery &amp;amp; Yarn Grand Opening Celebration! Meet the artists and enjoy a champagne toast. Bay Quilts Open House - Check out artist/owner's Bonnie Bayuk's custom memory quilts and wall hangings. 910 Whalley Ave.  6:00 - 9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Consignment Corner&lt;/b&gt; Open House &amp;amp; Live Music - Consignment Corner welcomes singer/guitarist Carole Urban for an evening of live music. 16 Fountain St. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rodrick Gilchrist Design&lt;/b&gt; – Open House &amp;amp; Reception: Rodrick Gilchrist Design Fashion Event  - Rodrick will be displaying his men's line with live mannequins. Sweets and champagne will be served. 911 Whalley Ave.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Westside Bar &amp;amp; Grille&lt;/b&gt; – Live Music: 6:00 - 10:00pm  PuRpLE MouNTaiN Live at Westside Bar &amp;amp; Grille - Groovin' originals and covers with a unique rhythmic pulse and sound and roots deep into the Grateful Dead, Bob Dylan, and the Rolling Stones. 883 Whalley Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Odeon Boutique&lt;/b&gt; –  Windows on the World of Fashion: 1960 - 2010: If Clothes Could Talk, accompanied by music from the different decades. 918 Whalley Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Westville Wines&lt;/b&gt; – Wine Tasting at Westville Wines - Wine expert Elliot Brause offers up Sparkling Wines, 837 Whalley Ave. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lyric Hall Antiques &amp;amp; Conservation&lt;/b&gt; - People, Places, Music (9:00-10:00pm): Maggie Barkin, Warren Gohsler &amp;amp; Jeremy Hutchins &amp;amp; Friends Donations welcome and goes to the entertainers; DJ &amp;amp; Dancing to follow at 11:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Neville's Fashion Design Studio&lt;/b&gt; – Reception &amp;amp; Open Studio&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Soho Hair Group &amp;amp; Day Spa&lt;/b&gt; – &amp;quot;Special Effects&amp;quot; featuring live hair models as Window Dressing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wintergreen of Westville&lt;/b&gt; – Live Music &amp;amp; Refreshments on the Patio: Unkle Shoe (5:00-7:00pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wunderlee Arts&lt;/b&gt; – [P3] Paintings, Prints, &amp;amp; Photographs; Don Wunderlee, Oi Fortin, and Catherine Fisher&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lets start at Kehler Liddell, meet in front lobby at 6.  I will wear the BW Scarf with piano keys. If we have not met you yet please make a note of faces coming so we do connect, also I am happy to provide my # for those concerned, just send me note</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273442798000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268835656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ArtWalk - Save the day!</name><id>12900400</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273269600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/12900400/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/c/7/global_14357063.jpeg</photo_url></item>