<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as possible. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. Criteria: NO WHINING, COMPLAINING, ETC. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. starting at Avalon Trailhead (HiCtr) and Mount Willard Trailhead (HiCtr) Back to here hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+12 ft on the Avalon Trail Just after leaving the information center, the Mt. Willard Trail leaves left, and the Avalon Trail ascends gradually and soon crosses Crawford Brook. to the junction of Mt Willard Trail hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+72 ft on the Avalon Trail to Beecher Cascade hike 1.00 mi/53 min/+747 ft on the Avalon Trail Just beyond this crossing, a loop path diverges left, passes by Beecher and Pearl Cascades, and shortly rejoins the main trail. The Avalon Trail continues at an easy grade, recrosses the brook, and begins a moderate ascent. The A&amp;ndash;Z Trail to Zealand Falls Hut diverges right. to the junction of A-Z Trail hike 1.00 mi/1 hr 0 min/+958 ft on the A-Z Trail The A&amp;ndash;Z Trail diverges right from the Avalon Trail and soon descends to cross a steep-walled gully, then climbs steadily, angling up along the side of the brook valley that has its head at the Field-Tom col. The trail crosses the brook, swings right, and soon begins to climb more steeply. It bears left to reach the height-of-land, where the Mt. Tom Spur diverges right. to the junction of Mt Tom Spur hike 0.60 mi/29 min/+356 ft on the Mt Tom Spur The trail leaves the A&amp;ndash;Z Trail at the height-of-land, 80 yd. east of the Willey Range Trail junction, and climbs at easy grades with one somewhat steeper pitch to a false summit, where a side path on the right leads 70 yd. to an open blowdown area with views east and south. Here the main path swings left and reaches the true summit in another 60 yd. A blowdown patch near the summit will permit interesting views west and south into the Pemigewasset Wilderness for a few years. to Mt Tom (Bethlehem) Totals Distance 2.90 mi Time 2 hr 34 min Elev Gain +2234 ft Elev Loss -88 ft Elev Change +2146 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.60 mi/29 min/-356 ft on the Mt Tom Spur The trail starts at the true summit of Mt. Tom, then swings to the right to an open blowdown area with views east and south. The trail descends at easy grades after a brief steep pitch, and meets the A&amp;ndash;Z Trail at the height-of-land (about 80 yd. east of the WIlley Range Trail). to the junction of A-Z Trail hike 0.05 mi/2 min/+6 ft on the A-Z Trail The trail starts to descend gradually, and in 80 yd., the Willey Range Trail enters on the left. to the junction of Willey Range Trail hike 0.90 mi/27 min/+561 ft on the Willey Range Trail The Willey Range Trail begins at its junction with the A-Z Trail in the col between Mts. Field and Tom. It ascends gradually southeast and climbs over a small knob. to the junction of Avalon Trail Totals Distance 4.45 mi Time 3 hr 32 min Elev Gain +2829 ft Elev Loss -472 ft Elev Change +2357 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 1.00 mi/58 min/-869 ft on the Avalon Trail The Avalon Trail begins on the Wiley Range Trail about 90 yd. above the summit of Mt. Field. It descends gradually for a short distance, then more steadily, with restricted views to the northeast. It then passes through a flat, ledgy area. to the junction of Mt Avalon spur hike 0.50 mi/35 min/-657 ft on the Avalon Trail The trail soon passes Mt. Avalon&amp;rsquo;s summit, and a short side path diverges right and climbs steeply 100 yd. to this fine viewpoint. The main trail continues a steep descent through a small col. to the junction of A-Z Trail hike 1.00 mi/53 min/-747 ft on the Avalon Trail The A&amp;ndash;Z Trail to Zealand Falls Hut diverges left. The Avalon Trail continues to descend moderately and crosses Crawford Brook. It then continues at an easy grade and arrives at a loop path that diverges right, passing by Beecher and Pearl Cascades. It shortly rejoins the main trail and recrosses the brook. to Beecher Cascade hike 0.20 mi/8 min/-72 ft on the Avalon Trail to the junction of Mt Willard Trail hike 0.10 mi/4 min/-12 ft on the Avalon Trail After crossing Crawford Brook, the Avalon Trail descends gradually. The Mt. Willard Trail enters right and the trail terminates at the information center. to Avalon Trailhead (HiCtr) and Mount Willard Trailhead (HiCtr) Totals Distance 7.25 mi Time 6 hr 10 min Elev Gain +2918 ft Elev Loss -2918 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL MEET INSIDE THE AMC HIGHLAND CENTER</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331997762000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331552497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT TOM &amp; MT FIELD</name><id>55998132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331992800000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/55998132/</event_url></item>