<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt Auburn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365641</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga Studio</name><city>Watertown</city><id>752617</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183571</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Tantra Without Borders is inviting you to a full day of FREE events in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All workshops are free - you are welcome to come to one of them or to all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the schedule for the day:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 9:30 am - 11:00 pm Kundalini Yoga (Jot Rup Singh)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 11:30 am - 1 pm White Tantric Healing Circle (Luba and Jot Rup Singh)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 1:15 pm to 2:30 pm FunDaMentals of Magic (Michael Zolot)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 3 pm - 4:30 pm From Woman to Goddess (Workshop for Women) (Luba, Volga Bo Olam)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 5 pm - 6:30 pm Mystery of Tantra (Satsang with Luba, Community Gathering)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 7: 30pm - 9:30 pm Saraswati Puja Party (Luba, Violetta, Jot Rup Singh, Volga Bo Olam, Misha Zolot, Tantra Without Borders Crew)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Read below for detailed workshop descriptions)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you a part of the community, we would like to ask you to volunteer and help us with the organization of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new, we welcome your questions. Tantra is such a mysterious topic; it is only natural if you would like to contact us before you come. Feel free to email me at luba.evans@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As many of you know we have been conducting workshops in Boston and New York in the last two/three years. We had so much response and interest that we decided to build Galiana - a tantric meditation retreat on the border with the Berkshire Mountains for our extraordinary community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open House Day will be a wonderful chance for us to reconnect, welcome new people and to present our plans for the next year - both in Boston and Berkshires locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More about classes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kundalini Yoga&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ancient technology of Kundalini Yoga rejuvenates body, mind and spirit with revitalizing exercise/asanas, breath/pranayam, the science of sound/mantra, uplifting meditation and relaxation that promotes health, happiness, and spiritual awareness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kundalini Yoga balances the glandular system, strengthens the nervous system, and enhances creative potential. Through yogic breathing techniques and meditation, peace of mind can be obtained giving an experience of deep inner calm and self-confidence. It gives you the vitality and health that is your birthright. It makes you radiant, peaceful, strong and loving so that you can meet life's challenges with grace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Kundalini yoga classes are suitable for everyone; no prior experience is necessary and you don’t need to be overly flexible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Tantric Healing Circle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awaken your light body and become a channel of pure love during our next community event - White Tantric Healing Circle. The white color symbolizes the purity of consciousness, connection to the source, balance and unity of all colors. The circle is a structure in which we all come together, as one, the energy is evenly spread; it is a place to see and be seen, to speak and be heard, to touch upon the souls of others and be touched by their presence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tantra is a precious gift from the East, which has been traditionally transmitted as a combination of passion and purity. The passion component has been readily embraced in the West, while the purity component has been often overlooked. Purity of intent, warm heart and the splendor of a purified energy body are the foundation of authentic sacred practice of tantra.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to create a solid foundation before we come into more intimate contact with each other, learning how to transform our emotions into wisdom, judgement into acceptance, attachment into unconditional love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be using a series of tantric tools including: silent, guided and active meditation, mantra, mudra breathwork, energy, emotional release techniques and Paratan healing. Paratan healing is an ancient technique from a Living Goddess Tradition. We are teaching it as it is taught by Tantric Master Shri Param Eswaran.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: During white tantric healing circle,you will be working with the male/female polarity within yourself. White Tantric Circle does not build upon polarity between partners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Woman to Goddess&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unveil your deepest essence and discover your true quest, your wisdom, wildness and beauty during this New Moon celebration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this workshop you will learn how to use yoga and other ancient practices to transcend habits of physical and emotional closure, how to open up to new opportunities and attract the right kind of energy into your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will understand the principles which will firmly situate you on the path from Woman to Goddess, the path of rediscovering your femininity and your strength, the path that will bring you to the place you yearn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When we practice together our power multiplies. Being a part of this practice will help you find greater meaning and deepen your commitment to the Goddess in you and to life itself. The time is now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is open to women only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FunDaMentals of Magic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop debut led by Misha Zolot will present Zolot Fluid Reality system, a teaching based on Advaita Vedanta principles, Zealand's “TransSurfing” and famous Russian Simaron School of Magic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“When I was a child I noticed that there is a special indirect way of wishing for something which always brings about a desirable result. I wanted to master that way of wishing, and searched all over the world for the secrets of magic. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Misha's system will teach you how to make things happen. Misha's clients have been using the system successfully to steer their reality to the best possible outcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I was looking for the cat for hours. I remembered about your system and decided to give it a try. I did the technique you recommended, and after that, what do u think happened?? I lifted up my head from the computer and saw the cat coming into the room!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This system is unique, it offers a totally unexpected way of making things happen. It is incredibly joyful and a lot of fun! Magic world of Fluid Reality – you can play it any time, anywhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this workshop participants will gain an understanding of an alternative way of looking at everyday reality, and understand the special interaction that happens between conscious mind, sub conscious mind and physical reality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will go over the basic principles of the Magician's Handbook and practice Metamorphosis, the art of transformation . We will touch upon aspects such as Intention, excess potential, equalizing forces, energo-informational structures, and mental tornados that guide our perceived reality. We will outline and explain basic techniques such as rejection of unfavourable signs, self naming, renaming on the track, and gifting. These concepts are fun and easy to learn!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do not miss this workshop full of surprises, insights and games.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mystery of Tantra&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Stop talking, stop thinking and there is nothing you will not understand&amp;quot; - Sent-ts'an&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is there a spiritual song more beautiful, more passionate, more daring and more mysterious than Tantric practice?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thinks of an eternal embrace of Shiva and Shakti, shiva lingam and Mount Meru. Another thinks of exotic incense, extraordinary hugs, softest hands and outrageous afterglow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another thinks of Tantric Buddha, crazy samurai holding a lazer beam of his consciousness instead of a sword cutting off his ego, burning his projections on the fire of absolute freedom. Beyond good and bad, emptiness and form, pleasure and pain, male and female, samsara and nirvana, transcending duality - he dives through the quanta of the present moment right into eternity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are so many faces and facets of Tantra.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the discourse we will cover the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• What is tantra and what can it do for me?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• What is the difference between Hindu Tantra and Tantric Buddhism?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• What is Tantra Without Borders?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• What is Galiana Meditation Retreat and why is it unique?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• How can I explore tantric practice and become a beacon of light?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saraswati Puja Party&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Puja is a beautiful ancient ritual in which we reach expanded states of consciousness through ecstatic tantric practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We recognize divine qualities in ourselves and our partners, connecting to our true identity, to our light, to our Self.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This puja is dedicated to Saraswati, the Goddess of flow, learning, speech, art and music. As we connect with that aspect of divine energy, we increase the lightness, the playfulness and the creativity of our relationship with each other and with the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Puja practice is traditionallty conducted within a structure of two rotating circles. As you are moving along the circle you will explore how different energies influence you, where and how they resonate in your being. As the circle of practitioners flows through a special sequence of meditations your divine nature will become apparent to you. Your light will shine through every pore and will start to overflow, reflected and multiplied by all, we will enter this divine realm together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drumming, singing and ecstatic dancing and New Moon celebration will follow, together with a community potlock, iastrology, numerology and tarot readings, incredible hugs, sharing, free form socializing and improvisation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Much Love,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Luba Evans (Saraswati)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are not providing gender balance &lt;br /&gt;There will be no nudity or explicit sexual contact in any of the workshops. &lt;br /&gt;We reserve a right to video tape certain parts of the workshops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tantrawith.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tantrawith...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luba Evans</member_name><member_id>7320465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281421099000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280178116000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open House Day :: Tantra Without Borders Day of Free Events</name><id>14220249</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281231000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/14220249/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/4/global_9312116.jpeg</photo_url></item>