<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(First large parking lot on right)</address_2><address_1>93 Ricciuti Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.243389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quincy Quarries</name><city>Quincy</city><id>816334</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.034096</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;Lets go outside to Quincy Quarries on Sunday June 24th for top roping. Lets meet at 11am. If anyone needs a ride, email me or call me on my cell at 781-704-6471. Bring ropes and slings if you have them. You should know how to belay and have a harness with a carabiner and belay device. You should also get a second carabiner to be used to anchor yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Disclaimer: YOU MUST WEAR A HELMET! If you are climbing with us (outside of the rock gym), it will be required for you to wear a helmet, although still come if don't own one. We may have an extra and you can use my helmet when I am not climbing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, there are no facilities. Bring water, food, sunscreen, camera, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave the parking lot area at 11:15am sharp. If you come afterwards, you will just have to walk around and ask for the Rock Climbing Boston Meetup. I will try to set up on the C-Wall, but if its really crowded, I may choose the J-Wall or S-Wall or another wall. For those not familiar with the Quarries, they have several walls or cliffs labeled A through S. Each wall contains several climbing routes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather looks really bad for Sunday, I will send an email out Saturday Night, and we will meet at Metrorock. Otherwise assume we will be at the Quarries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;The Quincy Quarries Reservation is part of the Blue Hills Reservation, south of Boston. Take Route 93/3 to exit 8 in Quincy. Follow signs for Quarry Hills Recreation Complex until you come to Ricciuti Drive, between a Mr. Tux and a large Quarry Hills sign. It's quick going south, but a bit roundabout going north. Turn right on Ricciuti Drive. There is a small parking lot on your right (which is usually full and you will most likely see a line of cars on the opposite side of road where you can park). &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Geoff</member_name><member_id>3444525</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182872256000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182482893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Top Roping at Quincy Quarries Sunday June 24th</name><id>5920791</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182697200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/5920791/</event_url></item>