<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's a free-for-all!&amp;nbsp; What do you want to know more about?&amp;nbsp; What questions do you have?&amp;nbsp; What are you struggling with and would like some help with?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, we have questions on how to get your emotions more into play when deliberately creating; how to be less attached and stressed out when there's something really, really important to you that you want to manifest; and how to develop connections with more people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's your opportunity to have free access and support with two trained and certified, master coaches! And, as always, we'll also open up the discussion to masterminding and sharing your wisdom, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send in your questions with your RSVP and we'll do our best to get your questions addressed. We&amp;rsquo;ll be incorporating Law of Attraction and other success principles and practices into our answers, so even if your question isn't the one picked this time, you're sure to still learn something valuable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let us know if you're open to being coached on the call, and will be available; or if you just want your question talked about. The call will be recorded and made available.&amp;nbsp; We're planning on around 90 minutes for the call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You'll receive the call in # after you RSVP.&amp;nbsp; Be sure to set your account to receive e-mail! (Top of page under "Account" and under the membership and communications link.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to talk and co-create with you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joy to you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>CALL-IN # is 218-339-4600, access code: 488095#  (fee is dependent on your phone service)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298006632000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>We believe in the high value of meeting in-person, but with all the snow, we have minimal parking at our house and we have no other location for our meeting this month.  So let's "meet" via telephone!  We've done it before, and it was still great.</why><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296844960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's a tele-meetup!</name><id>16443561</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297814400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/16443561/</event_url></item>