<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for a trip to Montreal and experience North America's most European city. &lt;br /&gt;As of May 6 total rsvp's from the various sites is 40 Yes and 28 Maybes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone will be responsible for arranging his or her own travel and accommodations. A nice downtown hotel room for 2 starts at $50 Canadian, so it?s not expensive at all. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Individual events for will be posted for you to pick and choose from, such as dinners, sight seeing, and nightlife. Below there are links to a few downtown hotels. Sign up here to say that you will be coming for the weekend, then pick and choose from the other events when they are created. I will also be listing the event on Toronto sites to get those folks to meet us in Montreal, too. The more the merrier! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have stayed at the Hotel Viger and have reservations there for this weekend, it is a nice place to stay. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hotel-viger.com/en/index_eng.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hotel-vige...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://manoirstdenis.com/home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://manoirstdenis....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hotel-europeenne.com/english/services.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://hotel-europeen...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hotel-quartierlatin.com/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://hotel-quartier...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This one is a little more pricey: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hoteldelacouronne.ca/english.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hoteldelac...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link for tourist info: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tourisme-montreal.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tourisme-m...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy a tourist bus pass for just $17 and have unlimited access to the bus and subway system for 3 days, or $9 for 1 day.&lt;br /&gt;Montreal public transit site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.stcum.qc.ca/English/a-somm.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.stcum.qc.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: US citizens travelling overland to/from Canada do not need a pssport for now. The proposed new requirements for passports will not apply to ground travel until 2008. Bring your drivers license, birth certificate or whatever good ID you have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Montreal is 300 miles from boston and takes about 6 hours to drive.  I like to drive halfway to Barre VT, spend Fri night in a motel there, and then get to Montreal the next morning feeling fresh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the events, perhaps Sat afternoon, will be visiting Old Montreal and the Old Port area. This is the loveliest, most european part of the city, with cobblestone steets, a pedestrian mall with sidewalk cafes and bistros, street performers and artists, horse and carriage rides... There is a market with lots of nice clothes and artwork and things. You can spend an afternoon just walking around and seeing the sites. This area is adjacent the old port, where there is rodeo speedboating, jet boats, duck boats, an indoor labyrinth, and you can rent bicycles, rollerblades and segways. There is a bike path along the canal leading into the old port area, so there is parkland with grass, trees and water. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180458887000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168398598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Long weekend in Montreal</name><id>5380617</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180188000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5380617/</event_url></item>