<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>873 Whalley Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06515</zip><lat>41.326642</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.389.9555    </phone><name>Kehler Liddell Gallery</name><city>New Haven</city><id>800189</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.959489</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Yasmina Reza's ART&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Join us for this exclusive performance of Yasmina Reza's ART at the Kehler Liddell Gallery in Westville. Winner of the 1998 Tony Award for Best Play. Winner of the 1996 Olivier Award for Best Comedy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Ticket reservations can be made ahead for $15.00 &lt;br /&gt;at: &lt;a href="https://www.elmshakespeare.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=133&amp;amp;Itemid=133" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.elmshakes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or a ticket can be purchased at the door for $20.00.  I suspect the tickets will go fast, you may want to order ASAP, so you are not turned away on the day of the show.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&amp;quot;…wildly funny, naughtily provocative…&amp;quot; &amp;#8213;NY Post.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&amp;quot;…a nonstop cross-fire of crackling language, serious issues of life and art expressed in outbursts that sound like Don Rickles with a degree from the Sorbonne…Reza is a fiendishly clever writer…'ART' sounds like a marriage of Molière and Woody Allen…&amp;quot; &amp;#8213;Newsweek.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Anyone looking for a play that is funny, sophisticated, stylish, stimulating and moving should go to 'ART'.&amp;quot; &amp;#8213;Independent (London).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The comedy, which raises questions about art and friendship, concerns three long-time friends, Serge, Marc, and Yvan. Serge, indulging his penchant for modern art, buys a large, expensive, completely white painting. Marc is horrified, and their relationship suffers considerable strain as a result of their differing opinions about what constitutes &amp;quot;art&amp;quot;. Yvan, caught in the middle of the conflict, tries to please and mollify both of them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Yasmina Reza is a French playwright and novelist, based in Paris, whose works have all been multi-award-winning critical and popular international successes. Her plays CONVERSATIONS AFTER A BURIAL, THE PASSAGE OF WINTER, ART, THE UNEXPECTED MAN, LIFE X 3 and A SPANISH PLAY have been produced worldwide and translated into 35 languages. Her new play LE DIEU DU CARNAGE, directed by Jürgen Gosch, opened on December 8, 2006 at the Schauspielhaus in Zurich. She translated LA METAMORPHOSE (Stephen Berkoff’s version of Kafka’s Metamorphosis), which was directed by Roman Polanski. Novels include “Hammerklavier,” “Desolation,” “Adam Haberberg,” “Dans la Luge d'Arthur Schopenhauer,” “Nulle Part.” Film: “Le Pique-nique de Lulu Kreutz,” directed by Didier Martiny.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the front of the gallery</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272397596000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266245602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Elm Shakepeare Company Presents "ART"</name><id>12608060</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272223800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/12608060/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/2/global_13124642.jpeg</photo_url></item>