<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Alewife T Station</address_2><address_1>5 Cambridge Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.394234</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-2200</phone><name>Bertucci's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>838765</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.144722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>New England Organizer Meetup for April 2010 time for Review and Planning for a Fun Year Ahead&lt;br /&gt;OK so this group been dead for some time now and I have been busy so I feel bad so sorry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would really like it if we could have a monthly meeting going forward so I am looking for some outgoing members to help out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can run like 2-3 meetings a year at best sorry I am busy.&lt;br /&gt;I was hoping Adam and Angela could try to run at least 2 each as well.&lt;br /&gt;If we could get 3 more members to help we can meet this goal so I am reaching out get help and running 2 meetings a year should not be that tough right??...........Let get moving on this please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group will only be helpful if you make an extra effort to help and to real try to attend the monthly meetings as they happen. WE ARE NEVER GOING TO HAVE A PREFECT LOCATION so instead of complaining about location offer to run a meeting in your area please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok we will  do short introductions and we will not spend too much time crying over spilt milk its NOT a time to complain but a time to reflect and make improvements to this and to your smore importantly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting will be 1 hour long so please do not be late and there will be a 30 minute free period to chat with others and for a short follow-up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is MBTA assessable via the Redline Alewife MBTA Station stop and there is FREE parking across the street from the Bertucci and its marked as such. YOU DO NOT have to pay to park here since we are eating at Bertucci.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bertucci is actual inside connected to one side of the MBTA station but is accessible from the street /side walk too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Subjects of interest:&lt;br /&gt;1. How to increase your membership. &lt;br /&gt; A.Try to define and target your core members.&lt;br /&gt; B. Do you really know and understand them? Do you care?&lt;br /&gt; C. Please write down 5 good and bad traits your members have...I bet you will be surprise we all share these as well!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.  Why do your members really come to your events??....The REAL answers might shock you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.  Meetup fees how do deal with them? &lt;br /&gt; A. Can you get Sponsorship &lt;br /&gt; B. How to go about it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. RSVPing and No shows how to deal with them?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. How to pick a good Meetup event location? &lt;br /&gt;  A. Are there free places?&lt;br /&gt;  B. Are ther places that will pay you to go to them?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Do you realize the power of your Meetup group and what can it really do?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. Again we all should be using the message boards as well to help each other&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That should keep us busy for1 hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok so please let me know if you can make this its important and will help us all. You are NOT alone in your Meetup issue we all go through these!&lt;br /&gt;Thanks and ciao&lt;br /&gt;Biagio&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271196862000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Organizers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NEOrganizers</urlname><id>321127</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>New England Meetup Organizers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268080421000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Organizer Meetup for April 2010</name><id>12819897</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271023200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NEOrganizers/events/12819897/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/a/global_13341098.jpeg</photo_url></item>