<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;These tickets usually cost $50 each but I have ten free ones for Nerd Fun members!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Dinosaurs: Ancient Fossils, New Discoveries" Join the Innovators on Friday, June 3, to&amp;nbsp;Enter the Modern World of Paleontology -&amp;nbsp;Museum of Science, Boston - Registration table in main Museum Lobby. 6pm. Casual business attire. Complimentary parking in MoS garage. Ages 21+ Only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buffet Dinner and Bar, Welcoming Remarks by&amp;nbsp;Innovators Chair and Vice Chair, Matt Fates and Greg O&amp;rsquo;Shaughnessy, Presentation by Nick Longrich, Donnelley Fellow, Department of Geology and Geophysics, Yale University, followed by&amp;nbsp;Exhibit Viewing (private preview.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Examine in greater detail than ever before the array of investigative tools that scientists use to reinterpret many of the most persistent and puzzling dinosaur mysteries: What did they look like? How did they behave? Did they go extinct? Explore newly discovered fossils, walk through a diorama of a 130-million-year-old forest, marvel at life-size cast skeletons, tool around with high-tech computer simulations, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Dinosaurs: Ancient Fossils, New Discoveries" is organized by the American Museum of Natural History, New York, in collaboration with the Houston Museum of Natural Science; California Academy of Sciences, San Francisco; The Field Museum, Chicago; and North Carolina Museum of Natural Sciences, Raleigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Innovators are the Museum of Science&amp;rsquo;s dedicated group of philanthropic younger members (up to age 45) who enjoy unparalleled access to pioneering initiatives in science and technology as well as opportunities to develop their own skills in nonprofit leadership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please note that the MBTA Green Line "Science Park" and "Lechmere" stations are currently closed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Up registration table in main MoS lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracey</member_name><member_id>11551904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>17</waitlist_count><updated>1308157493000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306506491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinosaurs - Ancient Fossils, New Discoveries</name><id>19948951</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307138400000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/19948951/</event_url></item>