<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This was one of the nicest parks we have visited yet, with a beautiful pine forest, lakes, and a hilltop view of Boston. So I am happy to return to it.  This time we will climb on top of breakheart hill and scale the hazardous ridge trail.  This is not a beginners walk so keep that in mind and make sure to wear your hiking boots&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:00 inside the Chris P. Dunne Visitor Center, 177 Forest St, Saugus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will go for lunch at Borders Cafe, &lt;br /&gt;817 Broadway Saugus, MA 01906-3207&lt;br /&gt;781-233-5308&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bordercafe.com/locations.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bordercafe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Need a ride? Please ask for a ride from another participant in your rsvp, indicating what area you are in. &lt;br /&gt;If you still need a ride, please email me&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breakheart Reservation is a 640-acre hardwood forest with jagged, rocky outcroppings, two fresh-water lakes, and a rambling section of the Saugus River. Seven rocky hills, over 200 feet high, provide vistas of Boston, southern New Hampshire and central Massachusetts. An extensive trail system through the woodlands guides visitors to various areas of the reservation. Fishing in Silver and Pearce Lakes, hiking the trails and birdwatching by the Saugus River are popular year-round activities. The supervised swimming area at Pearce Lake, one of the few fresh- water swimming spots north of Boston, draws crowds in the summer. In addition to its natural resources, the reservation has a rich cultural history.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luba</member_name><member_id>3354277</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233504134000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232463987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakheart Hill walk- Advanced Walking Version (hike)</name><id>9562703</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232809200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9562703/</event_url></item>