<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 College St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01610</zip><lat>42.236149</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fitton Field - Holy Cross</name><city>Worcester</city><id>791073</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.811050</lon></venue><fee><label>5.00</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Worcester Tornadoes Click and Shoot Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;August 14, 2009 – Fireworks and Spongebob Squarepants&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 6:00 PM  We are going to need everyone to meet outside of the gates&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost $5.00 per person&lt;br /&gt;MUST PRE PAY – no refunds!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We met with the folks over at the Worcester Tornadoes this week to discuss having a click and shoot at one of the games. Looks like we have a real good opportunity not only to witness the game at a group rate discount but we got some serious benefits offered as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s the scoop!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you sign up and pay for this event by August 1st, all photographers will be given “full access credentials” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– So what does this mean? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will get a full tour of the facilities.&lt;br /&gt;Then during the game have access to the whole stadium- including dug outs, press box, stadium seating, kids corner, and vending. (Please note however that the Locker Rooms are OFF LIMITS – no one goes in there. Period.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll also meet the current photographer for the Tornadoes, Gianna. You can ask her questions about her experiences photographing for the Tornadoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also have excellent seats if you want to sit and watch the game. If you have a family member or a friend who would like to attend the game they will get the same price on the tickets and can join you in the stands. The seating section we have reserved is in the Yellow grandstand seating section of the arena. (If it rains ticket holders can attend a game at a later date - so we would go Saturday the 15th- same time same place.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In exchange for the all access passes we have been asked by the Tornadoes to please share our photos with them. They would love to use them for the photo gallery section of their web site. You can have your © Name listed on the photos. &lt;b&gt;So if you agree to the all access passes – you’ll be asked to give Donna Dufault a cd of your images as Jpegs to share with the Tornadoes. The deadline for this is August 27th- our next meetup meeting.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We asked about “Model Release” issues – Turns out there is a statement on every ticket- and it is the policy of the Venue (Tornadoes), that if you attend any function in their facilities you automatically agree to being photographed and have a “release on your likeness” by simply entering the building. So we are covered!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Photo Ops:&lt;br /&gt;The Fans &lt;br /&gt;The pre game events&lt;br /&gt;Action shots of the players&lt;br /&gt;The stadium and all its glory&lt;br /&gt;Crew members&lt;br /&gt;Kids Corner&lt;br /&gt;Fireworks session after the game&lt;br /&gt;The food vendors&lt;br /&gt;Mascot- Twister&lt;br /&gt;Spongebob Squarepants&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Game Time is 7-9PM &lt;br /&gt;But we have to meet ahead of time to hand out tickets, get the tour, get set up with credentials, and sign wavier forms. So you MUST meet us at 6:00pm at the gate and we will need to go in as a group. Please do not be late, or you will miss out!!! No refunds!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We think this will be an incredible evening of fun and an excellent chance to get cool photos. We hope you’ll join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scott&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the front gate.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254439168000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245966374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Tornadoes Click and Shoot Event</name><id>10736577</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250287200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10736577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/8/d/global_9341773.jpeg</photo_url></item>