<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our next meeting will be on November 10 (Thursday), 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be sharing our best tips of the trade for helping us all recover from this illness.&amp;nbsp; I will be ending the&amp;nbsp;meeting with a short hypnotherapy&amp;nbsp;session to help us all feel less pain and more relaxed.&amp;nbsp; The script is based on a tape cassette I produced some 13 years ago which I am now updating for CD production.&amp;nbsp; My Arizona group&amp;nbsp;was surprised at the pain reduction they felt after we finished with the hypnotherapy session.&amp;nbsp; It is really an excellent way to repattern a disordered Fibromyalgia brain!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone wants a &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; session with the LaserTouchOne or to try the Lifewave Pain Patches (I have recently incorporated both into my practice as they reduce pain and inflammation and trigger points and the use of both actually heal pain issues) I will make two appointments at the Senior Center before our 7 PM meeting.&amp;nbsp; If you want one just e-mail or call me at 623-251-7547.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this time doesn't work for you and you want to make an appt. at my office we can do that as well for another time during the week I am in town (November 8-14th).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this time I want to extend a deep felt thank you to Gaston Gingues for his continued paper assault on us all.&amp;nbsp; Gaston brings incredibly relevant and helpful Fibro/CFIDS information to the group every time he attends and he makes my life incredibly easy as a result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you all soon,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betsy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS Small donations to defray my costs are always welcome!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Timmerman</member_name><member_id>3507700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321027911000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People With Fibromyalgia</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fibromyalgia-301</urlname><id>586410</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>The Reading Fibromyalgia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318102946000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Attend our Support Group</name><id>36655052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320969600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fibromyalgia-301/events/36655052/</event_url></item>