<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boston Common</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.355160</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Lowe's Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>796560</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066467</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The movie schedule has been published and I've bought my ticket.  The movie is scheduled to begin at 3:50.  I will be in the lobby until about 3:30, then I will be in the theater as close to the center as possible.  I will try to save some seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is scheduled to last 2 hours and 37 minutes, so come prepared to sit.  We'll be having dinner around 7:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing all of you,  Shirley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;John is scheduling this for the previous week.  But alas, I cannot attend.  This is for those of you who are also not available 1/12/13.  I don't know the exact time, yet; but when I do, I'll let you know.  We'll go at a time when we can have dinner after and a good discussion.  We will probably go to Tommy Doyle's, as they are quiet enough for a discussion (good for us, bad for their business) and the food is good enough.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here's the synopsis:  For a decade, an elite team of intelligence and military operatives, working in secret across the globe, devoted themselves to a single goal: to find and eliminate Osama bin Laden. Zero Dark Thirty reunites the Oscar winning team of director-producer Kathryn Bigelow and writer-producer Mark Boal (The Hurt Locker) for the story of history's greatest manhunt for the world's most dangerous man.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Zero Dark Thirty is in fact a thrilling work of journalism come to life...&lt;/span&gt;This is a film about a fierce woman's pursuit to solve a problem and the people involved in the procedural tactics of getting that work done. It just happens to be that this work is based on the story of the world's greatest manhunt." - Aaron Neuwirth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside the doors until 15 minutes before movie begins, then in the theater as close to the center as possible</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359242446000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356977473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zero Dark Thirty Again</name><id>97211272</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358628300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/97211272/</event_url></item>