<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Plum Island Turnpike</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.798267</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>6 Plum Island Turnpike</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>5302122</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847076</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please mark your calendars! Lots of other rides on Saturday so let's try for Sunday, Mother's day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet up in Newburyport, MA near Plum Island and bike around the beach, reserve area plus possibly Downfall Wildlife Management Area. We'll end the ride with refreshments at a pub in Newbury port and toast the moms (both present and not). More details on the route will follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ride will be 20-30 miles long, cover bike trails &amp;amp; surface roads. I'm thinking we'll ride down refuge road to Sandy Point State Reservation. The ride itself will be 3-4 hours long. We'll average about 13-15 miles per hour while moving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Approximate route to our ride is 30 miles long:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/LJ2SH"&gt;http://goo.gl/LJ2SH&lt;/a&gt; I ask that we do our best to stay together on the ride, and we have clear checkpoints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newburyport, MA is 38 miles from Woburn and the NEWBURYPORT STATION Train Station is nearby our start location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our meeting location has a visitor's center and education center, plus bathrooms. There are restrooms in parking Area 1 and 4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bike helmets are required!&lt;/strong&gt; Recommended: water, spare tire, repair kit, sun screen, snacks, energy food, layers of clothing etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are responsible for your own safety!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The southern half of Plum island is covered in gravel roads which would make using a road bike very difficult. We'll place the gravel portion of the ride towards the later half of the ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hybrid or Mountain bikes are highly recommended for this ride.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The park requires a $2 entrance fee for each bicycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you out there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Douglas M.</member_name><member_id>9031252</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337445897000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336143924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ride Scenic Plum Island this Mother's day</name><id>63410732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336930200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/63410732/</event_url></item>