<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>135 Wildwood  Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06415</zip><lat>41.521028</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-608-1855 / 203-808-5829</phone><name>Lake Hayward Pavillion</name><city>Colchester</city><id>1047202</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.334462</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are winding down the summer season with a bash on Lake Hayward in East Haddam/Colchester. Thanks to one our member's, Tess Flynn, we have access to the pavillion, trails, beaches (3), basketball courts, tennis courts...you can also enjoy hiking, canoeing or kayaking (bring your own boat, please) volleyball or just relaxing. All up to you! What a great day! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a BYOB event...we are also asking you to bring a dish or contribute grilling meats ( hotdogs, hamburgers or chicken). I will be coordinating the food so we will have a variety. You will be asked what you will contribute when you RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are asking guests to bring beach chairs, coolers, ICE, and any games you may want to play (softball, horseshoes, bocce balls, etc.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The day's itinerary will go something like this... 3 pm-5pm for activities...5 pm -7 pm chow time...7 pm -10 pm entertainment!!! THAT'S RIGHT WE WILL HAVE A DJ FOR YOUR DANCNG PLEASURE! Do we know how to throw a party or what????????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, a little about Lake Hayward...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lake Hayward, a crystal clear and pure natural spring-fed lake, is bordered by wooded shores and sunny seasonal cottages nestled among a few year-round homes. To add to the serenity of Lake Hayward, many years ago gasoline motorboats were banned, and now one can hear only the hum of little electric motors among the chirping of the Lake's peep frogs. During the summer months many enjoy swimming, fishing, kayaking, canoeing, paddle boating, row boating, and sailing, both in sailboats and on sailboards. During the winter months you will see ice fisherman and ice skaters on the lake with an occasional small fire for winter warmth. What an idyllic spot...and we can enjoy it for the day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come join us at Tess' hideaway for good times...good food ...good company!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A special &amp;quot;Thank You&amp;quot; Tess!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 84 West:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take 84 East to RT.2 East.&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 19 off of Rt.2 (Rt.11)&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 6 of Rt.11 (Lake Hayward Rd)&lt;br /&gt;Right at the end of ramp&lt;br /&gt;Left at 3 way stop sign - follow all the way down to the lake&lt;br /&gt;At the stop sign, you'll see the pavilion on your left and a parking lot on your right. Park at the lot and proceed to the pavilion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us at the pavillion/look for the red balloons</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tess</member_name><member_id>8065797</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253144626000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>105</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251240003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAREWELL TO SUMMER... PARTY / PICNIC AT LAKE HAYWARD!</name><id>11199900</id><headcount>83</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252782000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/11199900/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/9/1/global_10391009.jpeg</photo_url></item>