<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>McNamara Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05757</zip><lat>43.475468</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forget-Me-Not Farm</name><city>Middletown Springs</city><id>295920</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.075294</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ATTENTION CAMPERS and those interested in sustainable living!!! (And those who want to see &lt;b&gt;Dar Williams&lt;/b&gt; perform a free, solar-powered concert!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SolarFest blends art, education, and grassroots activism to inspire the conservation of Earth's limited resources, to promote renewable energy, and to support the creation of sustainable communities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since its inception in 1995, SolarFest has built a strong foundation for promoting artistic excellence and community-building while providing both general and detailed information on a wide range of sustainable living topics . We raise more than a few eyebrows when we explain how our entire weekend festival, including the sound and lights on our main stage, runs on renewable energy , primarily solar with wind and biodiesel in the mix.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SolarFest 's reputation as New England's most entertaining energy and music festival is growing just as it should: reasonably and sustainably. We combine superb family entertainment with presentations by some of the region's most knowledgeable renewable energy experts. We thicken the mix with how-to and hands-on workshops on sustainable living, a special children's activity tent, and a wide variety of food, craft, and renewable energy vendors. Our featured performers represent a far-ranging spectrum of styles and traditions from around the world. We provide plenty of space throughout the weekend for serendipitous encounters, conversation, dancing, hiking, camping, relaxation, and an overall celebration of our planet's beauty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Ticket Prices&lt;br /&gt;Weekend Pass (Friday, Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday: $35&lt;br /&gt;Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday Pass: $30&lt;br /&gt;Friday Only: $10&lt;br /&gt;Saturday only: $25&lt;br /&gt;Sunday only: $20&lt;br /&gt;Vehicle Camping $20 per vehicle for the weekend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy your tickets online until July 1; after July 1, you may purchase tickets at the gate. Volunteers camp for free! If you would like to volunteer for SolarFest 2008, send email to volunteers@solarfest.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;I plan on going up this year on Thurs, July 10 and staying until Sunday July 13. My cousin is getting married in Old Saybrook, CT on Saturday July 12 (the nerve!) so I will be driving my carbon-offsetted (thanks Dev!) car to CT on Saturday, going to the wedding, then driving back up in time for the bonfire and concert Sat night, then returning to CT on Sunday. Since carpooling is the obvious choice, I MAY have room for you if you only want to come up Saturday night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camping at this festival is non-technical. Your car is 200 yards (at most) from your campsite and the solar hot water showers are a short walk away. (this is a working farm, so most campsites will be in the pastures on the hill). NO GLASS permitted, so bring your keg cans! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm driving Dev and Sven, so spots in my car are taken! There is &amp;quot;preferred parking&amp;quot; for hybrids and electric vehicles! For more info on the festival, go to the &lt;a href="http://www.solarfest.com" target="_blank"&gt;website.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring spending cash ($30-40 above ticket price), bring a great attitude, and most of all, bring sunscreen and a hat! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to see the meetup page from last year's Solarfest, click &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/calendar/5855810/"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 300 volunteers this year, and you will find us by our yellow t-shirts! Red t-shirts are for Security folks. Color coding is good! We'll be camping in/near the volunteer section; I might put up an &amp;quot;NHC&amp;quot; sign to make us easier to find!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;And if you're smart like Kim, you'll remember to bring a notebook and (working) pen to take notes at the many workshops!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I've got a silver car, and silver + red tent!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>2576129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216244106000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214181899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Solarfest - New England's Renewable Energy Festival + Camping!</name><id>8193799</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215784800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8193799/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/1/global_4547857.jpeg</photo_url></item>