<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Unit BA</address_2><address_1>76 Winn St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.482142</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Art of Living Center</name><city>Woburn</city><id>883345</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.155789</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us this Thursday for an evening of Satsang (Chanting and Knowledge) with this amazing Swami from the Art Of Living Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where - Art Of Living Center at 76 Winn Street, Woburn Ma. When - 7:00pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to the public, so feel free to bring your friends and forward this meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SPEAKER BIO&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swami Pragyapad is a scholar of the Vedas and ancient Indian wisdom, and has made presentations internationally on Yoga and Meditation. He has also initiated and managed large social-welfare projects on education and youth empowerment. Swamiji is a long time Devote of HH Sri Sir Ravi Shankar, and has dedicated his life to teaching the most advanced programs offered by the Art of Living Foundation. Known as the "Smiling Swami," Swami Pragyapad easily transfers wisdom to those around him with his amazing presence, and concise knowledge sessions. SPEAKER BIO After graduating from the Indian Institute of Technology (IIT), Mumbai, the quest for something better led Pragyapad to the Art of Living - and it transformed his life. The real joy is bringing a smile on someone&amp;rsquo;s face and not wanting anything for yourself. &amp;ldquo;The formula for happiness is simple. If you think more about yourself, you will feel depressed, but if you think about serving others, you experience completeness&amp;rsquo;".&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anuj Madan</member_name><member_id>6404070</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319760427000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonmeditates</urlname><id>1257412</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>"Boston Meditates" Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319578736000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chanting and Knowledge</name><id>38707422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319756400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonmeditates/events/38707422/</event_url></item>