<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance is pleased to co-sponsor this event with the &lt;a href="http://www.bibf.org" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Israel Business Forum&lt;/a&gt; (&amp;quot;BIBF&amp;quot;).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amit Nisenbaum, Global Operations and Strategy Manager at &lt;a href="http://www.betterplace.com" target="_blank"&gt;Better Place&lt;/a&gt;, will discuss his company's efforts to build the infrastructure for electric vehicles in Israel, California, Hawaii, Denmark and elsewhere.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To attend this event, you must register in advance at &lt;a href="http://www.bibf.org/nisenbaum.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bibf.org/n...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to BIBF, Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance members can attend for the discounted price of $15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Amit Nisenbaum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/amitnisenbaum" target="_blank"&gt;Amit Nisenbaum&lt;/a&gt; holds a B.sc degree in Computer Science and Industrial Engineering from the Technion – Israel Institute of Technology and earned his MBA from the Johnson Graduate School of Management at Cornell University. While at Cornell Mr. Nisenbaum served as a principal at BR Ventures, Cornell University’s Venture Capital firm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Better Place is the leading EV services provider. Headquartered in Palo Alto CA Better Place has local presence in Israel, Denmark, Australia, Canada, Japan and several other geographies. Amit Nisenbaum is managing the relationship between Better Place global and its local subsidiaries. Previously Mr. Nisenbaum has served as a project leader at the Boston Consulting Group, leading strategy consulting projects out of its Boston office. Mr. Nisenbaum has over twenty years of leadership experience in diversified industries varying from Cleantech through SW and Telecommunication to education. In the past he has held senior Business Development, Product Management and Account Management positions at ECTel Inc. (NASDAQ: ECTX) and Vsoft Inc., a software company developing broadband video services infrastructure. Mr. Nisenbaum also served as the VP of R&amp;amp;D at I-Scraper Ltd., an online collaboration services provider.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259000135000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257131046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Global Operations and Strategy at Better Place: A Presentation by Amit Nisenbaum</name><id>11766559</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258412400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/11766559/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/e/global_11589662.jpeg</photo_url></item>