<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi there, we've mentioned that besides having our regular Tuesday monthly meetups at Dave's loft, we'll be expanding get-togethers at other venues and times.  Folks who have asked for this, we've heard you.  This is especially for you!  ;o)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our Meetup is from 11:00 AM - 1:OO PM.  Please RSVP ONLY if you know for sure you can join us.  Limited to a small group.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Details to meeting place on campus will be emailed later to folks coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=============&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Intuition and Law of Attraction: Creating Our Heart's Desire&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intuition opens up our pathway to joy &amp;amp; inner wisdom-- which then brings us in alignment with our heart's desire.  Through the energy of joy, love &amp;amp; gratitude, we magnetically attract the gifts of the Universe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Law of Attraction becomes very powerful when you feel tremendous joy &amp;amp; excitement and have a deep knowingness of what you want.    Since your emotions are your guidance system, accessing your Intuition (your sixth sense, your vibe or gut feelings) can affirm whether what you want to attract is right for you or not.  You no longer have to rely exclusively on other peoples' advice &amp;amp; opinions or be in a state of confusion, doubt...  &lt;b&gt;Intuition, our invaluable inner compass, helps us to clear the path to attain our heart's desire.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ji Hyang, a sixth sensory practitioner,&lt;/b&gt; shares intuitive insights &amp;amp; tools that you can use to begin and/or expand your connection with your Intuition. Our desire is that you develop the ability to trust &amp;amp; follow your intuition consciously, mindfully &amp;amp; consistently instead of occasionally &amp;amp; sporadically.  This moves you to authentically have more clarity of your purposes and desires.  Trusting your vibes allow you to have the confidence to know &amp;amp; attract more of what you truly want in your life and live with more ease &amp;amp; grace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our Boston Law Of Attraction Meetup is very pleased to offer this get-together with JiHyang's &amp;quot;Trust Your Vibes&amp;quot; community.&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;i&gt;Thank-you very much, Ji Hyang, for your gift of time, knowledge &amp;amp; facilitation of this wonderful adventure into our Intuition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; About Ji Hyang:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Ji Hyang&lt;/b&gt; is a Buddhist Chaplain and Director Of Spirituality &amp;amp; Education at Wellesley College, MA.  She is a certified six-sensory practitioner who's here to support soul growth &amp;amp; personal empowerment.  Ji Hyang has studied extensively with Sonia Choquette.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sonia is a unique and extraordinary spiritual teacher, intuitive guide and masterful catalyst and has been a personal Intuitive advisor to leaders like Louise Hay, Julia Cameron, Caroline Myss and Dr. Wayne Dyer.  www.soniachoquette.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do check our Message Board for info/ discussions from members. You're welcome to post LOA-related topics/ discussions there too.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223511515000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222186781000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special BostonLOA -"Trust Your Vibes" Meetup ; open only  to 13 members</name><id>8815914</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222614000000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/8815914/</event_url></item>