<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Lexington Street,New Brtian Ct</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06052</zip><lat>41.653061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 229-0257</phone><name>New Britain Museum of American Art</name><city>New Britain</city><id>607055</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.810188</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A Day at the Museum - New Britain Museum of American Art&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its is getting cooler out, so it is time to start exploring our wonderful museums!!  Saturdays at New Britain Museum of American Art are free from 10am until noon.  Lets take in the MC Escher exhibit, also NEW/NOW: Jon Rappleye: After Eden and much more.  We can have lunch at Cafe on the Park at the  museum at noon if you wish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MC Escher:&lt;br /&gt;    From July 16 through Nov. 14, 2010, the New Britain Museum of American Art proudly presents M.C. Escher: Impossible Reality. One hundred and thirty works of this artist of worldwide fame will be on view including seminal and instantly recognizable pieces such as Ascending and Descending, Drawing Hands, and the extremely rare lithograph stone for the making of Flat Worms. The exhibition will be organized into multiple sections among them Impossible Worlds, Infinity, Metamorphosis and Tesselation.&lt;br /&gt;    Maurits Cornelis Escher (1898-1972) has earned worldwide acclaim as a master printmaker, draftsman, book illustrator, and muralist. Though never having studied extensively in mathematics, the mind-bending techniques and impossible realities depicted in M.C. Escher’s works prove him a brilliant mathematician. Much of Escher’s work is intuitive; without focusing on labels, Escher created what came to him instinctively.&lt;br /&gt;    M.C. Escher: Impossible Reality features the artist’s woodcuts, lithographs, sculptures, as well as rare preparatory drawings for an in-depth view of not only the finished product of Escher’s iconic works, but also each of the mediums he entertained and his varying creative processes for each. A robust schedule of related programming is being planned, which includes a symposium, lectures, film, and music. Studio classes will also focus on Escher and the Museum Shop will showcase Escher merchandise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nbmaa.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=32&amp;amp;Itemid=56" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nbmaa.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cafe on the Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nbmaa.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=28&amp;amp;Itemid=52" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nbmaa.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the lobby at 9:45/ will wear the bw scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287138876000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282947426000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Day at the Museum</name><id>14566278</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286631900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14566278/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/b/global_17499931.jpeg</photo_url></item>