<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be the very first Meetup for The Framingham Spanish Language Meetup Group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll use the time to get  to know each other, talk about being Spanish Speakers, and discuss what we want out of our Meetups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is open to people from novice to expert speakers.   The only requirement is that we help each other to gain mastery in the Spanish language.  The venue can be changed depending on where the group wants to meet more conveniently in a public place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need to sign up before showing up so I can plan ahead for the expected attendees.  Since my office is not large, I would like to limit the initial group to 10 people on a first come, first served basis.  Late signups will be pt on a list.  If there are more people that sign up, I will find another place to accommodate the group.  In the first meeting, I will have coffee, bagels, donuts available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like the meeting to go for no more than two hours as I know people are busy on weekends.  I am sorry that I cannot have meetings in the evenings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pardon me for not writing in Spanish at this time.  If you have questions, please feel to email me at staff@nurse-exchange.com or cpmxl@yahoo.com.  Thank you very much.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Melencio</member_name><member_id>2726681</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540243000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Castellano Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-581</urlname><id>232171</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>The MetroWest-Greater Boston Castellano Speakers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1147532860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Framingham Spanish Language June Meetup</name><id>4934849</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1149357600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-581/events/4934849/</event_url></item>