<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;When is an event not an event? Hmm.... When we don't go to a restaurant to discuss afterward! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Into Great Silence &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Into Great Silence is only playing one night at The Brattle and is  nearly 3 hours long, getting  us to the restaurant at 9:30 which is too late on a weeknite for any long discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a film  the group saw last Spring and it is still mentioned often in conversations at other events. Everyone who saw it was strongly impressed. ( I missed it due to an emergency). Brattle has chosen it as part of their Recent Raves selections- great movies that you might have missed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4 Stars! One of the transporting film experiences of this or any other year.  Ty Burr, The Boston Globe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enthralling is not necessarily the word you would expect to use to describe a documentary about an enclave of nearly silent monks but German filmmaker Gröning makes his film just that. This beautifully filmed, award-winning film is an examination of life inside the headquarters of the reclusive Carthusian Order of French monks, a 17th-century monastery high in the Alps outside Grenoble, France.  Brattle Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rhythm of work, prayer and reflection,the attitude described as &amp;quot;joyful penitence&amp;quot; flows in a cycle that feels not so much ancient as timeless. The film's achievement is to capture, within a brief, elliptical span, this slow, delicate rhythm.  NY Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/ac2/wp-dyn?node=cityguide/profile&amp;amp;id=1121493&amp;amp;categories=Movies&amp;amp;nm=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.washington...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, we'll meet as usual near the front row when the film is over and talk about it for a bit, who knows- maybe get a cup of decaf somewhere. I'm trying hard to resist saying we may just give each other a nod of assent... darn, I said it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As is our custom, Tom will be standing near the front row at the movie's conclusion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198882402000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Into Great Silence:   A non-event Event</name><id>6984560</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200526200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6984560/</event_url></item>