<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*** &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Emergency hike&amp;quot; to take advantage of the highest snow totals from last night while we still have it!&lt;/b&gt; Should be lovely out! ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sessions Woods is a beautiful wildlife management area that specializes in conservation education.  There are many trails throughout the area.  We are going get there and assess conditions to decide on what loop to take (could be up to 4.5 mile loop). We could see the beaver marsh and lodge and then pick up the Tunxis Trial around the pond and perimeter of Sessions Woods.  There are no hard ups.  There are also some beautiful glades of trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Education Center where there is plenty of parking and bathrooms!  If we are lucky maybe some deer will cross our path.  We should not be out more than 3 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here's what I strongly suggest you bring and wear&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* Water proof hiking boots (&lt;b&gt;There is about 6&amp;quot; snow out there people&lt;/b&gt;!)&lt;br /&gt;* Gators or snow pants, or rain pants advised (to keep legs dry)&lt;br /&gt;* Gloves&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* A light snack&lt;br /&gt;* Water&lt;br /&gt;* Camera&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we decide to snack or hang out after the hike we will fly by the seat of our pants then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To get there&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;Sessions Woods is at 341 Milford Street (Route 69) in Burlington.  It is 3.3 miles from Rt. 4 and 3 miles from Rt. 6 in Bristol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Burlington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=341+Milford+Street&amp;amp;zipcode=06013" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/wildlife/pdf_files/maps/maps_other/swtrail.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sessions Woods&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2723&amp;amp;Q=326220" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260288545000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260107869000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Sessions Woods/Tunxis Trail in Burlington, CT</name><id>12028493</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260115200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12028493/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/b/global_5697371.jpeg</photo_url></item>