<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3484 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.306435</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-2345</phone><name>Doyle's Cafe</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>846002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Fourth Jamaica Plain Story Slam of the season at Doyle's @ 3484 Washington Street, Jamaica Plain, MA @ 7:00pm The theme is &amp;quot;Gifts &amp;quot; Abstract or concrete, what us the story of the best gift you were ever given? Special guest Michelle Carlo Michele Carlo is a writer/performer who has lived in four of the five boroughs of NYC and remembers when a slice of pizza cost fifty cents. She has been published in Mr. Beller&amp;#146;s Neighborhood&amp;#146;s Lost &amp;amp; Found: Stories From New York, Chicken Soup For The Latino Soul and SMITH magazine, and told her stories everywhere a person can tell stories in NYC&amp;#151;including the MOTH&amp;#146;s GrandSlams and Mainstage, the PEN American Center&amp;#146;s World Voices Festival and Electric Literature&amp;#146;s online site Broadcastr, along with First Person Arts in Philadelphia and The Story League in Washington DC. Her memoir Fish Out Of Agua: My life on neither side of the (subway) tracks was published by Citadel Press in August 2010. www.michelecarlo.com Doyle's is located in the Jamaica Plain neighborhood of Boston, accesible by the Orange line and close to the Sam Adams Brewery! Nearest transit: Green Street (Orange Line) COMING SOON: see eventbrite to reserve tix. On April 11, 2012, 7-9PM All the finalists will gather at Coolidge Corner, main Theater to compete for a week in a medeival townhouse in Tuscany and other prizes. &amp;quot;Because have a life, you have a story. Bring it!&amp;quot; L Listen to our podcasts at iTunes and podcast webpage. And check out our video archive to get an idea about 5 minute stories &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/video" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/forum/topics/story-slam-rules-pr-what-is" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/forum/topics/way-to-be-sure-to-tell-at-a" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;#8232;Other massmouth slams this season: Mondays: Club Passim in Cambridge, MA and Semi finals in March 2012 Tuesdays: Somerville, Cambridge and other venues Semi-finals in March 2012 Semi Finals: in March 11th for JP events Finals: WED APRIL 11th the Finals will be at Coolidge Corner Theater main theater Brookline, 7-9PM&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323652549000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322159421000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>massmouth story slam - "Gifts" </name><id>42276892</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323648000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/42276892/</event_url></item>