<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Sawyer River Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03812</zip><lat>44.068192</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Signal Ridge Trailhead (2 miles down Sawyer River Rd off Rte 302)</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>2334221</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.387932</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are going to climb Mt. Carrigain (4,700 ft) via the path less traveled - a 13.5 mile loop of the Signal Ridge, Carrigain Notch, and Desolation trails. On a clear day, the views from Mt. Carrigain across the Pemi and Sandwich wildernesses can't be beat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike is geared for people who have some experience with Moderate/Intermediate hikes (7-10 mile hikes with up to 2,500 feet of elevation gain) but who are looking to step up their hiking into longer, more advanced level hikes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;moderate-paced&lt;/strong&gt; loop, we'll&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;hike 13.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,900 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. Book time for this hike is about 8.5 hours - and we hope to finish in about that time. This trip is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start at the Signal Ridge trailhead. A few miles in, we'll fork right onto the Carrigain Notch Trail and wrap around to the Desolation Trail. We'll take the Desolation Trail up to the summit and then descend via the Signal Ridge trail and take that all the way back to the trailhead. &amp;nbsp;There are several water crossings on this route which can be tricky at times, so wear waterproof boots or be prepared for wet feet. Also, the Desolation trail is &lt;em&gt;very steep&lt;/em&gt;, rocky and rough and some find this climb difficult (but we think it'll be fun!) &lt;em&gt;*Note - if you are just interested in peakbagging Carrigain for your list and aren't comfortable with steep scrambles, then the traditional route (out and back via signal ridge) is a shorter, easier, gentler way to get this summit and our planned route is not the right hike for you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we have hiked Carrigain via Signal Ridge several times, this will be our first time on Carrigain Notch and Desolation trails. We've researched this route - but we expect all participants to bring a map &amp;amp; compass, and be familiar with the planned route. You are responsible for your own safety!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To sign up for this hike, you should be an intermediate/moderate hiker who has recently completed trips of at least 7-8 miles and 2,000 feet of elevation gain - at book time/average pace or faster. Please answer all RSVP questions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions (steady rain and/or thunderstorms) will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Footwear: Sturdy hiking boots/trail runners. (Be prepared for water crossings with waterproof boots, or water shoes, or change of socks. Poles are also helpful.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip (2-3 Liters recommended).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Bug Spray. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will meet at the Signal Ridge Trailhead - 2 miles up Sawyer River Road, off of Route 302 near Bartlett, NH. Google maps indicates this location is &lt;strong&gt;175 miles and 3 hours&lt;/strong&gt; from Boston.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1311025907000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309197399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Carrigain Loop (the path less traveled) INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED</name><id>23693831</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310905800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/23693831/</event_url></item>