<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWER STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry to say this, but I have to make tonight's movie a NoOrg. I have too much to do and not enough energy to do it all. Hope you understand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This means you can self-organize, but that no discounts will be offered for the tickets/snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you enjoy the movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Company Men came and went from the Framingham AMC before we could attend a showing, so I'm changing this week's movie to Tangled. Rapunzel meets Disney in 3D. It's supposed to be cute. And I'm up for cute! How about you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts @ 8:15, so &lt;b&gt;let's meet in the ticket lobby at 7:45&lt;/b&gt;. Then I'll buy us all tickets and MIB glasses and we can head in to get snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are going to be a bit more expensive (I think it's &lt;b&gt;$12 instead of $8&lt;/b&gt;. which is the same amount of discount as usual) for the 3D version.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, if we're up for it, let's head to Friday's, as I have a little coupon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for the change of movie! If I could have helped it, I would have! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810079612/details" target="_blank"&gt;The Company Men&lt;/a&gt; is a must-see for movie fans in the Boston area. Several scenes were filmed with Kevin Costner in Framingham, on Mansfield St. and Prindiville Ave. It's a movie about our &amp;quot;new&amp;quot; economy and how real families are dealing with limitations pressed upon them and how breadwinners are forced to redefine what really matters in life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bobby Walker is living the American dream: great job, beautiful family, shiny Porsche in the garage. When corporate downsizing leaves him and co-workers Phil Woodward and Gene McClary jobless, the three men are forced to re-define their lives as men, husbands, and fathers. Bobby soon finds himself enduring enthusiastic life coaching, a job building houses for his brother-in-law which does not play to his executive skill set, and perhaps the realization that there is more to life than chasing the bigger, better deal.  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for The Company Men!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292464569000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289943399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NoOrg -- Tangled in 3D (was The Company Men)</name><id>15468825</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292460300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/15468825/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>