<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A long lost member, Jason Green-Lowe, is returning for a visit.&amp;nbsp; Some of you may remember him as the guy who brough games in to playtest.&amp;nbsp; But, whether you knew him before or not, you are wecome to the party.&amp;nbsp; I want to give him an event to remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe's: &lt;br /&gt;With the option to RSVP 'maby' gone, I am having problems planning for the correct number of people.&amp;nbsp; So if you are a maybe, just say so when you RSVP and I'll take it from there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring (select all that apply ;) &lt;br /&gt;Games - We have plenty, but we don't have them all &lt;br /&gt;Food (non-snacks) - We can refrigerate or heat whatever you want to bring. I will be doing a big batch of pasta (vegan) and home made sauce again. No meatballs this time so that is open if anyone wants to bring some. &lt;br /&gt;Food (snacks) - If you bring it, it will probably get eaten. &lt;br /&gt;Drinks (non-alcoholic) - Sometimes everyone brings some; sometimes no one does. "You pay your dime you take your chances." &lt;br /&gt;Drinks (alcoholic) - I'm not driving and we'll have plenty of room for those who want to crash, but we're not big drinkers ourselves. &lt;br /&gt;Chairs - I did manage to get more chairs and can now seat&amp;nbsp; in the mid 20's. Keep this in mind and check the RSVP count before you come. Feel free to bring your own chair if you want to guaranty a seat. You can even bring them and leave them if you have any you want to get rid of. &lt;br /&gt;Donations - I will once again have the donation boxes out in the hope of paying for the food and making future events better. &lt;br /&gt;Other - Bring anything you like as long as it doesn't get anyone in trouble with the law &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Travel/Parking:  &lt;br /&gt;Parking  - I live close to the beginning of the   street, so at soon as you make  the turn start looking for parking. Most   of the parking in the area is  resident only, but I will have parking   permits by the front door for  everyone to park on the street. We have a   driveway and it is clear enough for two people to park  tandem without a problem. &lt;br /&gt;Train - we live 6-8 minute  walk from  the back exit of  Alewife (from the platform, go up the stairs in the  direction the  trains come). Just walk away from the main road  (the only  one you can  see from that exit) When you come to a fork in the  trail  take the  middle one. Clay street is a straight shot from there.  Turn  left at  Clay and we are on the left in a brown building.  &lt;br /&gt;Bus - nearby is the 350, 77, 79, 83, 87, 88, 89 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Call me if you have any questions at all. Ben 617-997-3545 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;P.S. I have a gas stove/oven, a crockpot, a smallish microwave, and a fondue pot if you want to bring anything that needs heating up. Just give me a call to make arrangements. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Warmus</member_name><member_id>5401423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302440453000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Whether you want to celebrate your friends who have games or you want to celebrate your friends by playing games, you're welcome to come by.</why><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300124225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrating friends with games (read that however you choose)</name><id>16916769</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302368400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/16916769/</event_url></item>