<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Pocahontas Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03905</zip><lat>43.071270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fort Foster </name><city>Kittery Point</city><id>845838</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.686638</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waves crash on rocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that jut straight out of the sand. A long wooden pier takes you far out into the water.Spectacular views of Whaleback Lighthouse and Wood Island beckon. On a clear day you can almost touch the Isles of Shoals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seacoastnh.com/Travel/Scenic_Walks/Fort_Foster/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/3/8/event_93872312.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Fort Foster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a sublime, 88-acre coastal park situated at the entrance to Portsmouth Harbor. We'll walk along the shore and through woods here for about 2 hrs. Then we'll drive the mile or two down the road to a portion of Rachel Carson Wildlife Refuge where there's a beautiful trail along Chauncey Creek. It winds through pine forest with views of the salt marsh and leads out into Brave Boat Harbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is flat, easy hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After party&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.locococos.com/"&gt;Loco Coco's Tacos in Kittery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Pets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; from the Kittery traffic circle take Route 103 North/East. It's called Whipple Rd. then Pepperell Rd. *Go about 2 miles and you'll cross a bridge over the entrance to Spruce Creek. *About 1.5 miles after the bridge, bear RIGHT away from Rt 103 onto Chauncey Creek Rd. *Go about 0.5 mi. and turn RIGHT onto Gerrish Island Lane. *Cross the bridge over Chauncey Creek and bear RIGHT onto Pocahontas Rd. *Follow Pocahontas about a mile to the park entrance on your right. *Park along the road. GPS: 43.071270, -70.686638.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/c/e/event_93872462.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The fort's hulking gray&lt;/strong&gt; military structures only enhance the dramatic views of the Piscataqua River and the ocean. They are so forlorn, cold and useless. Yet in winter, coated in a few inches of snow, the concrete bunker, once mounted with deadly artillery guns, blends into the rocky scenery. This expansive military complex was set up, initially, as the high-tech defense of the Portsmouth Naval Shipyard. After the Spanish American war, the goal was to hit the enemy four miles out to sea. Each new war brought enhancements. By WW II the harbor between Fort Foster and New Castle was strung with 5,000 pound mines, ready to be detonated beneath an enemy ship. The fort is named for a NH Civil War general whose picture is hanging in the state capitol in Concord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354568453000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353123711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kittery Coast &amp; Taco Loco</name><id>91757342</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354467600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/91757342/</event_url></item>