<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 Cranberry Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.839191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-2526</phone><name>Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Carver</city><id>727813</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.691455</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Start the new year off right with us.  We will hike the East Head Reservoir, which is a rolling trail of 2.5 miles.  The East Head Reservoir trail starts right near the Forest headquarters parking lot on Cranberry Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, more than 14,000 people got out on First Day hikes in state parks across all 50 states. The DCR is having first day hikes in 8 locations this year on New Year's Day. (Not officially announced yet.) Unfortunately, Myles Standish State Forest isn't on the list for this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we'll have our own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dress warmly. Thin breathable layers are very helpful on cold days because people generally warm up quickly and then have to start shedding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good warm boots are certainly helpful if there is snow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had thought to have a campfire at the end to get warm. Unfortunately, the DCR offices will be closed and we are not allowed to have one. That probably also means that the bathrooms will be locked, so plan accordingly. Perhaps we can agree on a place to go afterwards to get warm. (suggestions welcome)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deer hunting season ends on December 31st, so hunters should not be an issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bescherer</member_name><member_id>650729</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357226232000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354295801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Day hike</name><id>93497462</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357054200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/93497462/</event_url></item>