<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;Neverwhere&lt;/i&gt; by Neil Gaiman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Neverwhere's protagonist, Richard Mayhew, learns the hard way that no good deed goes unpunished. He ceases to exist in the ordinary world of London Above, and joins a quest through the dark and dangerous London Below, a shadow city of lost and forgotten people, places, and times. His companions are Door, who is trying to find out who hired the assassins who murdered her family and why; the Marquis of Carabas, a trickster who trades services for very big favors; and Hunter, a mysterious lady who guards bodies and hunts only the biggest game. London Below is a wonderfully realized shadow world, and the story plunges through it like an express passing local stations, with plenty of action and a satisfying conclusion. The story is reminiscent of Douglas Adams's The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, but Neil Gaiman's humor is much darker and his images sometimes truly horrific. Puns and allusions to everything from Paradise Lost to The Wonderful Wizard of Oz abound, but you can enjoy the book without getting all of them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279547381000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276188425000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Neverwhere</name><id>13760798</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279148400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/13760798/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/a/global_15625274.jpeg</photo_url></item>