<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Prudential Center </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.348694</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hynes Convention Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>979821</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082511</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>7News and CW56 along with Partners HealthCare would like to welcome you to the 3rd Annual Health and Fitness Expo taking place at the Hynes Convention Center in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Browse the website for exhibit information, health news and more  &lt;a href="http://www.bostonhealthexpo.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonheal...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to check this site daily as our list continues to grow. And we add more information from celebrity appearances, fun activities, speakers and more.  Partners HealthCare Welcomes You!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Partners HealthCare is pleased to join 7 NBC and CW56 in presenting the Boston Health &amp;amp; Fitness Expo as part of our mission to improve the health of the community. Founded by Brigham and Women's Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital, Partners HealthCare is a not-for-profit system of teaching, community and specialty hospitals, physicians, community health centers and other health care services committed to improving the health of the community and advancing the field of medicine through teaching and research.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to our founding hospitals, Brigham and Women's Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital, many other Partners HealthCare members are participating in the Health &amp;amp; Fitness Expo, including: Faulkner Hospital, Newton-Wellesley Hospital, North Shore Medical Center, McLean Hospital, Partners Home Care, Spaulding Rehabilitation Hospital, as well as CIMIT, and MGH Institute of Health Professions. &lt;a href="http://www.partners.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.partners.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246285101000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244382770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Health and Fitness Expo!</name><id>10595677</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246111200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10595677/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>