<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Gott Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.687389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 546-2997</phone><name>Halibut Point State Park</name><city>Rockport</city><id>744966</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.631871</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's go out to Halibut Point State Park in Rockport and hike the trails, looking at the breathtaking views and end with a picnic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Visitor's Center and walk around the quarry.  Hopefully mother nature will cooperate and we will see some really nice foliage.  Here is a little bit about the park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halibut Point is a uniquely beautiful coastal seascape. Looking seaward on a clear day, the view stretches from Crane Beach in Ipswich to Mount Agamenticus in Maine and the Isles of Shoals off the coast of New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Formerly the Babson Farm granite quarry, the park is managed for scenic, historic and conservation purposes by the DCR and the Trustees of Reservations. An adjacent property, Sea Rocks, is owned by the Town of Rockport and open for public use. Here you can explore the park's trails and tidepools, picnic on its rocky ledges, enjoy its sweeping views, and learn about Cape Ann's historic granite industry&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After we walk the trails, there are many picnic benches at the visitors center that we can have a picnic.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not a hiker?  Please join us for a picnic after our hike.  Depending on which trail(s) we chose to hike, we should be back at the visitors center by 12:30-1:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;When you RSVP for this event, please include what you will be bringing for the Picnic and whether you will be joining us for the hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children &amp;amp; Dogs are welcome to attend, please keep in mind that Dogs must remain on leashes....children do not have to be leashed &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the case of inclement weather, please check this website prior to leaving for the event.  Any cancellations will be made at least 2 hours prior to start time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions about this event, please contact the event organizer(s).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the visitors Center</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255797662000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252367748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking and Picnic at Halibut Point</name><id>11313138</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255359600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11313138/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/1/b/global_10595659.jpeg</photo_url></item>