<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1156 Chapel St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308716</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-432-1234</phone><name>"New Theater" at Yale Repertory</name><city>New Haven</city><id>306047</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.932830</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Theatre Now!!  The Carlotta Festival at Yale School of Drama's The Wendy Play&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:  Friday, May 18th at 8:00 pm.   &lt;br /&gt;Meet 7:30 pm at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yale School of Drama's New Theatre&lt;br /&gt;1156 Chapel Street&lt;br /&gt;New Haven, CT&lt;br /&gt;203 432-1234&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Followed by conversation/discussion of the play at a favorite near-by pub or coffee house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:  The Carlotta Festival plays are showcases for MFA students at Yale School of Drama.  The Festival was created from an endowment by Carlotta O'Neill, Eugene O'Neill's wife, to feature student playwrights. Student productions at the Yale School of Drama are just fantastic!!!  Some of the best productions I have ever experienced --- far better than most of the professional productions I have seen at the Rep!  If you are a theatre lover, these are not to be missed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price:  $18.00 a ticket -- general admission seating&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME SENSITIVE PURCHASE: &lt;br /&gt;The New Theatre only holds 120 people and many of these seats will be held aside for New York agents/theatre critics. Tickets are on sale NOW.  Tickets will go very fast.  Call the box office at 203 432-1234.  Ask for the date and time of the play for their computer doesn't list them by the play name. You can ask the ticket agent to double check the name of the play when they print out the tickets. These tickets will probably only last a few weeks...try to purchase them NOW if interested.  I imagine all tickets should be sold out by 4/21/07.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Contact:   Meredith.  You can reach her at 203 773 3352&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541277000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176410170000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Wendy Play" at Yale School of Drama 8pm</name><id>5664124</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179531000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5664124/</event_url></item>