<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 North Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.207016</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>State House Plaza</name><city>Concord</city><id>11137502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537689</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, April 13, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

1:00 to 3:00 &lt;br /&gt;

At the State House in Concord, NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great line-up of speakers &lt;br /&gt;

Join us to help secure your liberties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by the Granite State Patriots &lt;br /&gt;

For additional info: (Phone, Facebook, website, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RAIN or SHINE! No cancellation or rain date!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time for all liberty-loving Americans to realize that our Republic is in great jeopardy. The recent attacks on our 2nd Amendment will eventually turn into gun confiscation if we don't make a stand. Furthermore, we are witnessing the erosion of many of our Constitutional Rights by politicians who have no regard for their Oath of Office. That is why we have named this rally "Honor Your Oath."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

It is up to "We the People" to make it clear to those who would violate their oath that we want them to step down or to be forcibly removed from office. Time is running out. We need a massive turnout to send a clear message that the Sleeping Giant has awakened and we are coming. Remember: "All it takes for evil to prevail is for good men to do nothing." It's time to join the fight. Will you be there? &lt;br /&gt;

 x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365884193000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363017029000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HONOR YOUR OATH RALLY</name><id>108706352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365872400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/108706352/</event_url></item>