<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Medford Ma</address_2><address_1>Mystic River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.420162</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 718-9600</phone><name>Tennis Courts</name><city>Medford</city><id>239202</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110382</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you for all you interests in gathering for a tennis meet up.&lt;br /&gt;I have looked into an area in west medford that has 5 courts new outdoor courts&lt;br /&gt;that will hopefully accomodate us?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is located on the mystic river.&lt;br /&gt;I have tried to link a map to this site but am unable so :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you proceed off rt. 93 north and take the Mystic Vally Parkway exit toward medford/ Arlington you will eventually reach boston avenue.  ( where Tufts is located )  if you proceed straight through mystic vally Parkway there will be a rotary stay right of the rotary and continue on mystic vally prkway this is Arlington roughly 1/4 mile there will be agulf station and a set of lights take a right at the light and go over the bridge to your right will be a basketball court and then the 5 courts tis street is Mystic River Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;hope all can make it&lt;br /&gt;bring your rackets and volly together&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;( this is the third time I have typed this message !! I hope you get it this site keeps freezing everytime I type a link )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I really hope all can meke it and meet up with a few tennis partners!!&lt;br /&gt;Look foward to meeting more tennis partners myself&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if any questions please feel free to email me at laf620@rcn.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;hope the weather hold out&lt;br /&gt;if not I will canel due to the rain if any&lt;br /&gt;but I am hoping for sunny skys and meetin all&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laura&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Kenger</member_name><member_id>4819069</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541396000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tennis Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tennis-240</urlname><id>432728</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Somerville Tennis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178547599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5 outdoor courts ?? ANY ONE GAME ! time any time after 4:30 till dark??</name><id>5751240</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179952200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tennis-240/events/5751240/</event_url></item>