<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Set among a small circle of friends and neighbors in a Parisian suburb, &lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;35 Shots of Rum&lt;/span&gt; is a gloriously delicate and sublime new film from the great French filmmaker Claire Denis (Beau Travail, Chocolat). Lionel (Alex Descas), a metro conductor, lives with his daughter Josephine (Mati Diop), a beautiful university student, in a bustling apartment complex. They have been sharing the same space for many years and have grown accustomed to one another's company. Josephine has begun spending time with Noé (Grégoire Colin), a handsome young neighbor, while Lionel is being drawn into a romance with a longtime friend, taxi driver Gabrielle (Nicole Dogué). As their lives are pulled in different directions, father and daughter realize they must confront a painful aspect of their past in order to embrace what lies ahead. Sumptuously shot by frequent Denis collaborator Agnès Godard, this warm, funny and enchanting film casts a lovely spell unlike any other movie this year. Original music by Tindersticks (Denis's Trouble Every Day and Nénette and Boni).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cinemaguild.com/35shots/" target="_blank"&gt;35 Shots of Rum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NYT Critics' Pick - Rotten Tomatoes 94% Rating&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ms. Denis has long been interested in France’s former colonies, particularly in Africa. In films like “Chocolat” (her 1988 debut, not to be confused with the more recent Juliette Binoche-Johnny Depp confection) and “Beau Travail” (1999) she has examined some of the political contradictions and psychological pressures of this colonial legacy, but in “35 Shots of Rum” it remains in the background, like those classroom discussions. Which is not to say that matters of race and nationality are irrelevant to the movie, only that their relevance is implicit, either too obvious or not pressing enough for the characters themselves to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In its modest scope and mellow tone, “35 Shots of Rum” resembles Olivier Assayas’s “Summer Hours,” another recent film by a French director who has sometimes trafficked in provocation and extremity. Both movies embed extraordinary thematic richness within a simple, almost anecdotal narrative framework, and both achieve a rare eloquence about the state of the world by means of tact and reticence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“35 Shots” is more eventful,  but its real drama is in quiet moments, in glances and whispers captured by Agnès Godard’s exquisite and expressive cinematography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John will be sipping just one shot of rum (or pumpkin spiced beer) at the &lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;Cambridge Brew Company&lt;/span&gt; as early as 6:15 for folks who want to meetup early and sit together.  He strongly suggests you buy your tickets online (&lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" target="_blank"&gt;Kendall Tickets&lt;/a&gt; as this is the opening night of a great film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, John will lead the group to &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Tommy Doyle&lt;/span&gt;'s for 34 more shots of rum and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be silently holding a questionably pathetic homemade Meetup side at the front of the theater at the end of the film.  We'll gather the group together to walk over to Tommy Doyle's.  If you're new to the group, you can't miss us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255893530000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>35 Shots of Rum</name><id>11654911</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256944500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11654911/</event_url></item>