<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197-203 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.743869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 246-5700</phone><name>The Alchemy Juice Bar &amp; Growing Green Co-op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1035078</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There is something in music that is universal. Something that can deeply touch the heart and soul of any human, at any time, at any place. What is it? In most of cultures sound and music were considered sacred. If we look at the symbolic descriptions of the beginning of this universe, we can mostly see the same - &amp;quot;In the beginning there was a Word&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;The Ã“m signifies the beginning, middle and end&amp;quot;, etc. The &amp;quot;word&amp;quot; means here primordial vibration. Music is considered to be a reflection of that Infinite vibration which is the source and the moving Power of the manifest universe.&lt;br /&gt;In a unique mixture of rhyme, reason, and rhythm, Hip Hop music evokes renewal and fresh energy. The beats of the music are similar to that of a heartbeat, which allows practitioners to match their body’s rhythm with that of the music, making the entire practice one long meditation.&lt;br /&gt;There no doubt that music can be transformative and inspiring – two of the words yoga advocates often use to describe a good practice. And adding a modern soundtrack to an ancient art might open it up a wider audience, perhaps one that is scared off by the silence and solemnity they perceive yoga to demand.&lt;br /&gt;Join us in practicing yoga with this celebratory twist. We’ll be flowing through sun salutations and grooving to the rhythm and beat of the Universe. Rather than just hitting the play button to begin class, we’ll have a LIVE DJ leading the tunes behind his ones and twos.&lt;br /&gt;After the hour-long practice stick around for a special viewing of the documentary &lt;a href="http://www.ayurvedafilm.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ayurveda: The Art of Being&lt;/a&gt; . &lt;img src="http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/517ZMYE9AEL._SL500_AA240_.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both are by donation. Regardless of the size of your donation, we know it comes from the heart.  &lt;br /&gt;Your heart will soar, and your body will thank you for the sweet gift of so mindfully dedicating every breath and every pose through a practice of Hip Hop Yoga. &lt;br /&gt;“ I for one would jump at the chance to try a yoga class accompanied by a skilled DJ.” hip hop beats Reporter and fitness expert Pete Estabrooks of The Calgary Herald&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>zoraida</member_name><member_id>9306539</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258326830000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257040340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hip Hop Yoga and Film Screening</name><id>11758520</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258153200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/11758520/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/e/global_11546654.jpeg</photo_url></item>