<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>suite 660</address_2><address_1>460 Totten Pond rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.395260</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Aprigo</name><city>Waltham</city><id>862093</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.256368</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi All,&lt;br /&gt;I'm happy to announce the September meetup - I've had multiple requests for topics / speaking opportunities,  guess this group is getting traction!&lt;br /&gt;For the September meet-up we have two presenters:&lt;br /&gt;1. Javed Ikbal (principal and co-founder of zSquad LLC)- will talk about:&lt;br /&gt;  &amp;quot;Marketing, Uncertainty and Doubt: Information Security and Cloud Computing&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;   What is the minimum security due diligence that a company needs to do before putting it's data in the cloud?&lt;br /&gt;   Since 2007, Amazon has been telling us they are &amp;quot;.. working with a public accounting firm to ... attain certifications such as SAS70 Type II&amp;quot;  but these have not happened in 2+ years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On one side of the cloud security issue we have the marketing people, who hype up the existing security and gloss over the non-existing. On the other side we have security services vendors, who hawk their wares by hyping up the lack of security. The truth is, there is a class of data for every cloud out there, and there is also someone who will suffer a data breach because they did not secure it properly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will look at Amazon's EC2, risk tolerance, and how to secure the data in the cloud.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Javed is a principal and co-founder of zSquad LLC, a Boston-based information security consulting practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 Charles Wegrzyn - CTO at TwistedStorage Inc. (Check actually built an Open source cloud storage system back in '05)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Twisted Storage is open source software that converts multiple storage&lt;br /&gt;repositories, legacy or green-field, into a single petabyte-scale cloud&lt;br /&gt;for unstructured data, digital media storage, and archiving. The Twisted&lt;br /&gt;Storage Enterprise Storage Cloud provides federated search, electronic&lt;br /&gt;data discovery with lock-down, and policy-driven file management&lt;br /&gt;including indexing, retention, security, encryption, format conversion,&lt;br /&gt;information lifecycle management, and automatic business continuity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257292737000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-cloud-services</urlname><id>1460349</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>Boston Cloud Services - All things Cloud,  SaaS, PaaS, XaaS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249670863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September meetup of the Boston Cloud computing group</name><id>11059697</id><headcount>56</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253745000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-cloud-services/events/11059697/</event_url></item>