<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;This is a rescheduled hike - I am determined to get Hale in before winter!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at parking area at the entrance to Zealand Road at 7:30am.  I have confirmed that Zealand Road will be closed down on 11/15/10.  This means that the beginning and end of the hike will require an extra 3.5 mile walk along the road each way.  I estimate this will take about an hour (if you think my estimate is off, let me know).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not a traverse, so no carpooling to another trailhead is necessary.  We'll ascend to the summit of Hale via the Hale Brook Trail, take the Lend-a-Hand Trail to Zealand Falls Hut and take the Zealand Trail out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for winter cold and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This can be dangerous in cold weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. This is known to be a very wet trail, so come prepared to stay dry!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some form of traction and head lamps will be required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunrise is at 6:56am.  Sunset will be at 4:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This hike is below treeline and unexposed.  The summit of Hale is open but wooded and without a view.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; I expect the hut to be open.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is a shorter and somewhat easier hike for a 4,000 footer.  In regular conditions, the Lend-a-Hand Trail is an easier descent from Mt. Hale.  The Zealand Trail is pretty flat.  The road walk is long but not expected to be strenuous.  If you are in hiking shape, accustomed to  long distances and have proper gear (traction and clothing), this should be a manageable hike for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I am not a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around.  The mountain will be there another day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog in cold weather.  I will have my two dogs with me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike.  I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views (although I've been told Hale really doesn't have any) &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors, SO if the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), I will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;  I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book time is about 6 hrs, 7.7 miles, excluding the road walk.  The road adds an additional 7 miles and 2 hours. Plan on it taking 8 hours, possibly more in winter conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit &lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hale Brook Trail (to the summit of Hale)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;4054'&lt;br /&gt;2.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;2hrs 15min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail climbs from Zealand Rd (FR 16) at a a parking area 2.5 miles from US 302 to the bare summit of Mt. Hale, where there are good views over trees that have been steadily reclaiming the formerly bare summit in the more than 30 years since the fire tower was removed.  The trail is relatively easy, with moderate grades and good footing and passes through a very find birch forest much of the way.  The trail leaves the parking area, crosses a cross country ski trail then ascends steadily to cross Hale Brook at .8 miles.  It continues the steady climb, then swings left at 1.1 miles and ascends gradually across the steep slope above Hale Brook, recrossing the brook in its rocky bed at 1.3 miles.  Now the trail ascends by several switchbacks, crossing a small brook at 1.7 miles.  Still ascending and curling gradually to the right, it enters the conifers and attains the summit from the east.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lend-a-Hand Trail (We are doing this IN REVERSE)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;2.7 miles &lt;br /&gt; 2 hours&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail connects Zealand Falls Hut with the summit of Mt. Hale, which offers good views.  The grade is fairly easy but the footing is rather rough for a good part of its distance, particularly for those trying to balance heavy packs since there are a great many log bridges along a very wet section.  The trail takes its name from a journal for charitable organizations that was edited by Edward Everett Hale, the Boston pastor and author for whom Mt. Hale was named.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail diverges right (north) from the Twinway at .1 mile above Zealand Falls Hut and climbs steadily, crossing a small brook three times.  After about .5 miles, the grade becomes easy in a long section with numerous log bridges where small brooks flow in and through the trail.  At 1.5 miles, the trail enters a scrubby ledgey area and ascends moderately.  In a rocky area at 1.9 miles, a ledge 15 yards right of the trail offers a good outlook towards Carrigan Notch.  At 2.4 miles, the trail climbs another rocky pitch and continues in dense coniferes to the summit clearing where the Hale Brook Trail leaves east (right).  Many of the rocks around the former fire tower site are reputed to be strongly magnetic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zealand Trail (We are doing this section IN REVERSE)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;2.8 miles&lt;br /&gt; 1 hr 45 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leaving the parking area, the trail follows the railroad grade, then a bypass that is somewhat rough.  It then returns to the grade and approaches Zealand River at .8 miles near some ledges in the stream.  Here it diverges right from the grade and continues on to the west bank then makes the first of several brook crossings at 1.5 miles.  The trail now passes through an area of beaver activity, staying mostly on the railroad grade and at 2.3 miles, the A-Z trail enters from the left.  The Zealand Trail crosses the outlet brook and skirts Zealand Pond, ending at 2.5 miles where the Ethan Pond Trail continues straight ahead on the old railroad grade and the Twinway turns right to Zealand Falls Hut .2 miles away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;--------&lt;br /&gt;7.7 miles (+7 miles of road walk)&lt;br /&gt;6 hours  (+ 2 hours of road walk)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN  (OR EXPERIENCED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic with two dogs &amp; usually a Meetup Sign in the window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290954876000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289696164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Hale - Zealand Falls Hut Loop Hike</name><id>15438888</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290864600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15438888/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/5/global_3608437.jpeg</photo_url></item>