<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Monument Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.461451</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Monument Square</name><city>Concord</city><id>576772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.349414</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This will be faster paced ride with rolling hills, and a few steep climbs.  You MUST be able to maintain an &lt;u&gt;overall average pace of 16MPH&lt;/u&gt;.  (some areas we will be going as high as 20+mph, and much slower for the hills... 16MPH average).  Expect the route to last approx 2.5 hours depending on how many breaks we take.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To make this ride enjoyable for everyone, please be sure that you can maintain that speed... if you are not sure what pace you can keep, please don't let this ride be your speed test.  I would like to keep this group together and it becomes difficult when the skill levels are vastly different.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/482869/Monument%20Sq%20Meet-Up%20Spot.jpg"&gt;Monument Square&lt;/a&gt; in Concord, MA.  Be there at 9:30am, where we can say hello as I hand out cue sheets and we will be on our way no later than 9:40am.  We should finish around lunchtime, and we can decide then if we want to grab a bite to eat in Concord Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each person should bring an extra tube that fits their bike, plenty of water, and it is a good idea to have an energy snack to keep you going.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks again to JRA Cycles for sponsoring our group and making rides like this free of charge.  Be sure to head over to their shop to say thanks!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have my brown bike with blue wheels</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Ramos</member_name><member_id>4466935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280690031000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280487388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lost Lake - 40 Miles - Sunny Sunday!</name><id>14261769</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280669400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/14261769/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/5/global_14205189.jpeg</photo_url></item>