<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>State Beach Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.840154</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978) 462-4481</phone><name>Salisbury State park</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>1105920</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.839958</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Capri Italian Grille is located very near Salisbury Beach State Reservation. Both the restaurant and the beach allow dogs at this time of year. (In fact, the restaurant allows dogs all year round!) Lets meet up at the beach first, at the very last of the parking lots on the map. It's the one at the mouth of the Merrimack River, where you can usually see harbor seals. There are picnic tables in the lot, at least there were last time Ron, Rufus and I were there. If we meet there at 1:30, that will give us time for a nice romp before lunch. &lt;br /&gt;

 Capri Italian Grille doesn't open until 2:00, and I have cleared with them that our group will be arriving at about 2:30. It may be that some people will just want to enjoy the excellent food and drink offered and skip the beach, which is OK. You can expect the rest of us and our tired but happy dogs to turn up about 2:30, and you can sit down inside and get a head start on us. &lt;br /&gt;

I'm going to try and put maps to both places into this announcement, but I'm not sure I know how. I will be sure to include a map to beach at least. &lt;br /&gt;

You can find more information about and directions to Salisbury Beach at www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/salb.htm. &lt;br /&gt;

Those of us who are on the beach can caravan to the restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;

You can find out more about Capri's, and see their menu, by looking for Capris Italian Grille on Google. &lt;br /&gt;

P.S. There is also a beach behind the restaurant itself, but the one we're meeting up at is much safer for the Cavaliers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karla Rab</member_name><member_id>10717717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335213628000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334107821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Play on the beach, then have lunch at Capri Italian Grille!</name><id>60066842</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335115800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/60066842/</event_url></item>