<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>See below</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.350000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Location in your congressional district</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>554524</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.550000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Congressional District Map, find your district: &lt;a href="http://www.sec.state..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sec.state....&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location of each District Caucus: &lt;a href="http://www.massgop.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massgop.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, Massachusetts does have Republican Caucuses and you must be a Registered Republican (by Feb 13th) to vote. Come to the caucuses and help us elect Ron Paul supporters as delegates to the national convention. We do realize that Ron Paul has acknowledged that it's very unlikely he'll win the nomination, but we're doing this because he has encouraged us to continue the revolution and still get as many delegates as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open and registration (checking to see if you're registered Republican by February 13th) begins at 9 am. Doors close, and the caucus begins at 10 am. No late registration is allowed so please come early. Look for a Ron Paul supporter that will have a slate of Ron Paul supporters to vote for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The primary decides how many delegates are bound to each candidate, but doesn't decide who those delegates will be. That decision is made at the district caucuses on April 5th. Even though the delegates will be bound to another candidate, we can still make sure that there are Ron Paul supporters in those spots. Doing this will show Republicans locally and nationally that Ron Paul supporters are numerous and organized. As delegates, Ron Paul supporters may be able to make some changes to the party and the platform at the national convention, and some may be able to vote for Ron Paul since Romney has suspended his campaign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the caucus, any registered Republican can nominate himself, herself, or someone else to be a delegate. The caucus chairman takes down all the names of all those nominated and then allows each 3 minutes to speak if they desire. After they've all had a chance, everyone votes by paper ballot for 3 delegates. The 3 highest vote getters become delegates. The process is then repeated to choose 3 alternates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of the districts have already had an open meeting and put together a slate of Ron Paul supporters. The other districts will be meeting shortly.  You can contact your district organizer to find out about your district:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/950430/RonPaulDistrictCaucusOrganization.doc"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A slate includes 3 delegates and 3 alternates for each district. These are the six people we want to vote for. We discourage any other Ron Paul supporters from running for a delegate/alternate spot because it will dilute our votes. There will be at least one clearly identified Ron Paul supporter at each caucus with printouts of the names of our slate. It will not be titled &amp;quot;The Ron Paul Slate&amp;quot; but will contain only Ron Paul supporters. Look for that person if you don't know who to vote for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to make it clear to everyone that we are not going to be lying or breaking rules. We will not be calling ourselves &amp;quot;Ron Paul delegates&amp;quot; because the primary voters did not allot them to Ron Paul, but we will stay true to our principles. We are concerned Republicans that are trying to make a difference in the party and become delegates to the national convention. Just as they are supposed to, the delegates will vote for the candidate they are bound to by law on the first round of voting at the national convention.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you at the caucus. &lt;br /&gt;Let's continue the revolution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Robinson &lt;br /&gt;Unofficial Ron Paul Coordinator for the MA Republican Caucuses &lt;br /&gt;603-512-2969 &lt;br /&gt;matt.robinson1@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Robinson</member_name><member_id>2983158</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207573927000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206477590000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mass Caucuses</name><id>7601040</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207400400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/7601040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/b/global_2993979.jpeg</photo_url></item>