<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 1A</address_2><address_1>675 Ocean Blvd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03870</zip><lat>43.041522</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-7406</phone><name>Odiorne Point State Park</name><city>Rye</city><id>1004721</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.715843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hike by the Sea &amp;amp; or Dinner, &amp;amp; or Dancing  Saturday Apr. 27th., 2 pm. &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=650+Ocean+Blvd%2C+Rye%2C+NH" target="_blank"&gt;Odiorne Point State Park&lt;/a&gt; 650 Ocean Blvd&lt;span&gt;. Route 1A&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span&gt;Rye&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span&gt;NH.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Hike, Dinner optional. &amp;amp; Dancing at 7 pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Host for the HIKE: Steve Ob1.  603-491-1962&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;A Dog &amp;amp; Child Friendly Event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did this hike a week or so. But, we are dancing just up the road from the hike. Plus, it is to be a nice day to get out and about. So why not do a little hike before dinner. Then head up to Portsmouth's newest night spot. &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/110176022/"&gt;Check it out, and RSVP by CLICKING HERE.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/110176022/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Odiorne Point State Park offers one of the most beautiful natural settings along New &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/e/0/event_229028672.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hampshire's coastline. So, come and join us for an easy 2 to 3 hour hike through beautiful Odiorne Point. The trails and visit The Seacoast Center at Odiorne Point State Park are a great place to explore, with its 350-acres of hiking trails through multiple habitats. We will meet at 2 pm. in the parking lot in front of the path to the Science Center. There we will start by hiking  through parts of the extensive network of trails that wind through the dense vegetation, rocks and rock beaches, as we traverse the park. There are spectacular views of the ocean and the rocky shore, with evidence of past military occupation. ALSO! We usually go out afterwards to get some drinks and eat. So, please plan to join us there also. ( optional )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you wish to go in an visit the Seacoast Science Center? It will cost around $5. per person. ( optional ) That will take you deeper into those habitats with a tide pool touch-tank. There are also interpretive exhibits, a 32-foot skeleton of a humpback whale, amazing views of the seashore, a rare blue lobster in their "Gulf of Maine" exhibit hall and much more. This will be an opportunity to enjoy learning things you never knew about the coastline and all of its creatures.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367096984000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366990631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike by the Sea &amp; Dinner &amp; Dancing</name><id>116318982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367085600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/116318982/</event_url></item>