<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*If the RSVP is full, please put yourself on the wait list, as more spots will open up as the event date approaches*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join our nightlife mixer event at M Bar and Lounge at the Mandarin Oriental!  The hotel has been open for a few months and its bar scene has become a must-go venue.  This is a great place to meet new and current members in a low key setting, all are welcome and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 6:30pm in the main bar area at the Mandarin Oriental, finding the group should not be difficult.  Recommend getting there early as the bar tends to fill up quickly, and hotel management is strict about headcount.  This is an upscale venue so PLEASE dress appropriately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If traveling by T, Copley and Hynes are the closest T stop on the green line.  Back Bay Station for the orange line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The Organizer reserves the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout.*&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1238714470000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237047416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Back Bay Nightlife Mixer at the Mandarin Oriental, This Wednesday, Mar 18!</name><id>9952909</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237415400000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/9952909/</event_url></item>