<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sorry, this event is now full ~ Maybe next time!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Noncooks think it's silly to invest two hours' work in two minutes' enjoyment; but if cooking is evanescent, so is the ballet ~ Julia Child&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who love great food this is an event not to be missed!  Join us for a very unique experience where we'll learn how to cook an authentic, homemade Italian meal followed by a scrumptious feast!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Becky Brown is a culinary instructor of Italian cooking at Manchester Community College.  She has lived, worked and trained in Italy and has graciously offered to teach us how to cook some of her favorite Italian dishes at her home in Manchester.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Cost is $40/person and must be paid in advance.  Each participant will be asked to bring a bottle of their favorite Italian wine.  Recipes for all dishes prepared will be handed out to those that attend. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Menu includes:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Veal Saltimbocca (sautéed veal, prosciutto, sage and white wine)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Asparagus risotto  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Fig and herb stuffed pork chops with apple reduction  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Cappuccino panna cotta with chocolate whipped cream &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt; &lt;b&gt; &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;~ Important Notes ~&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Paid, First Reserved &lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 10 people (including instructor) &lt;br /&gt;There will be absolutely NO REFUNDS for any reason! &lt;br /&gt;Menu may be subject to change at instructor's discretion &lt;br /&gt;The exact location in Manchester will be sent once you pre-pay&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please sign up on the &amp;quot;Waiting List&amp;quot; and your RSVP will be changed to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; once your check is received.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;   &lt;/center&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the instructor: &amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;In Italy, Becky worked in Orvieto which is the Umbrian region of Italy. Most of her techniques have a direct relationship with ingredients and cooking methods that she learned while there. This class will be more of a sharing of her experiences of Italian cooking that she learned while living in Italy&lt;/i&gt;.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Exact address will be emailed to all that have paid in advance</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292085328000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288663669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Italian Cooking Class &amp; Feast! (11/13/10)</name><id>15305636</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289683800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/15305636/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/6/global_19325510.jpeg</photo_url></item>