<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Brown University Campus</address_2><address_1>Manning Hall Gallery</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02901</zip><lat>41.823799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-863-2065</phone><name>Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology</name><city>Providence</city><id>889536</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.413300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join the Rhode Island Atheist Society on a visit to the Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology at Brown University.  Their current exhibit is &amp;quot;Reimagining the Americas&amp;quot;.   From their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;The Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology at Manning Hall hosts changing exhibitions curated by Brown University students working with the Haffenreffer Museum’s staff. Reimagining the Americas, the Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology’s newest exhibit which opened May 29, 2010, brings together innovative anthropological ideas and evocative artifacts from the Amazon to the Arctic to plumb the cultural diversity of the Americas before European contact and explore the forgotten histories of its indigenous people. Building on recent discoveries and methods developed by archaeologists and anthropologists over the past decades, Reimagining the Americas uses cutting-edge perspectives to illustrate intriguing, often complex, histories through artifacts of ceramic and stone, jade and gold, bone and textiles that illuminate the past and expose themes that resonate with present and future concerns. From the arrival of humans in the Americas to the rediscovery of ancient Amazonian cultures and the deciphering of lost histories written by the Maya and Aztec, Reimagining the Americas challenges us to rethink the past and to recognize 13,000 years of indigenous achievements before Europe looked to the west.&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission to the museum is free.  For more specifics about the museum check out their website: &lt;a href="http://www.brown.edu/Facilities/Haffenreffer/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brown.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If there is interest perhaps we can get together for a cup of coffee after the visit.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at the front entrance to the museum.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287339863000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist</urlname><id>12929</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285460712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society - Visit to Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology </name><id>14895998</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287334800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist/events/14895998/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/0/global_13237216.jpeg</photo_url></item>