<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 Garfield Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06320</zip><lat>41.353439</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>VFW Post 189</name><city>New London</city><id>1581005</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.109718</lon></venue><fee><label>$30 in adv</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>at the door</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Host is Dan Reale, CT Libertarian Party Chairman.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; We are fortunate to have former Libertarian presidential candidate and all around Constitution scholar &lt;strong&gt;Michael Badnarik &lt;/strong&gt;delivering the keynote speech. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; During the first half of the convention, we will conduct our business meeting and then proceed to consider substantial changes to the bylaws. These changes will facilitate LPCT's substantial growth in the coming years while providing you the opportunity to participate more locally. These changes include the formation of the county affiliates that will be responsible for nominating principled Libertarians to local office. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; Only registered dues paying members of the LPCT can participate in the business meeting and process to consider bylaw revisions. Members of the general public may attend the entire convention or part of it. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Other speakers will include Josh Katz, Robert Jones, U.S. Senate Candidate Paul Passarrelli and Walter Reddy. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Joshua Katz teaches mathematics, history and economics. He is a widely read Libertarian writer, contributor to LewRockwell.com and a guest on Fox News with Andrew Napolitano. Robert Jones is the author of Secure the Blessings of Liberty and a real estate attorney in Connecticut. He is the former chair of the Libertarian Party of Arkansas. Paul Passarrelli is an engineer from Norwalk, and he focused on alternative energy projects that utilize solar and geothermal technologies. Walter Reddy is the founder of the Committees of Safety, and he is currently working on a project to reintroduce gold and silver as an alternative currency. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Ticket prices will be $30 if you preregister and $40 if you pay at the door. Dinner at 5PM will be pizza and takeout from local restaurants. The LPCT will not be paying for dinner unless 150 attend, in which case the LPCT will pay half. If 150 preregister in advance, the LPCT will pay for all of the food. Bear in mind that it's easier to place orders if everyone preregisters. We will post a notice on www.lpct.org once 150 people have preregistered for the convention. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Also bear in mind that the hall can only hold 215 people, and you can only guarantee a seat if you register in advance. More information will be posted on www.lpct.org/Events.html. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Convention Schedule (Subject to Change) &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 12 PM - Business Meeting Called to Order &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Minutes of Previous Convention&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Treasurer and Committee Reports&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Forming a Platform Committee &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; State Central Committee (SCC): Determination of the size (10 to 40 Members). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Listing of members willing to serve and their attendance records of the previous year. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Selection of Judicial Committee members (2 for a 3 year term and other vacancies to be filled) &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; SCC called to order to select Officers &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Adjourn Business Meeting &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Chair to Address Convention for Ten Minutes &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Selection of delegates to national convention &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; *Orders for dinner at 5 PM, if any, shall be finalized and placed for delivery if not previously done so &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1 PM Amending the Bylaws (Or if Earlier, Conclusion of Business Meeting) &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;The procedure to amend the bylaws shall per section be as follows: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The Secretary shall read the proposed change in the context of the full article, with deletions and insertions indicated. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A statement will be made by the bylaw committee representative. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; There will be 7 minutes of debate, during which time the bylaw committee representative is not a recognized speaker, but may speak after any other speaker in rebuttal. During this time, the proposal is not amendable. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; There will be a vote on the proposal. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 5.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; If it passes, it is final. If it fails, a vote will be taken on whether or not to consider amendments. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 6.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proposed amendments shall then be voted on. If they fail, the process shall continue on. If any pass, a vote is held on the amended proposal, without debate or further amendment. &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 7.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The process continues to the next proposed change in the above order. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Proposed changes affect the Article and sections of the bylaws follows:&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Article Three, Sections 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 8, 9 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Create New Sections: 10, 11, 12 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Article Four, Sections 1, 2 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Create New Sections: 6 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Article Five, Sections 3, 4, 8 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Article Seven,Section 3 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 5 PM Dinner (Pizza and Takeout)&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 6:00 PM Speaker: Paul Passarelli, Candidate for U.S. Senate &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 6:10 PM Selection of Chairs for County LP Affiliates &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 6:30 PM County Affiliates Break Off and Select Officers &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 6:45 PM County Affiliates Report Officer Names to Secretary &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 6:50 PM Speaker: Josh Katz on Left Libertarianism &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 7:10 PM Speaker: Robert Jones on Growing the Party and Presenting the Message &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 7:30 PM Speaker: Walter Reddy on putting sound money back into circulation &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 8:05 &amp;ndash; 8:30 PM Q and A with Walter Reddy &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 8:45 PM Keynote: Michael Badnarik &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 9:30 Q and A with Keynote &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; 10 PM Convention Closes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307246439000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301249669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT Libertarian Party Annual Convention</name><id>17075533</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304784000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/17075533/</event_url></item>