<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The annual Mystical Art and Talent Show is an absolutely unique event to which all artists and dreamers are invited! It's a chance to meet a greater visionary community, enjoy creative works, and potentially even share your own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Dreamers meetup gets a section to display any dream related art along with statements of explanation, and what counts is the sincerity not the skill, because this is an audience that is fascinated with transcendent experience. Contact carl@soulstirring.org if you want to present anything, also there will be tables for networking materials if you have some to bring, otherwise just see details below to join the audience and tell your friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The unique Mystical Art and Talent Show continues to give hope for a future of diversity in inspiration. Drawing upon dreams, meditations, religion, nature, and more: a full evening's presentation of an amazing variety of original paintings, readings, story, and song by many local spiritual artists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, 50 Quincy St. Cambridge, MA. This a lovely Gothic stone chapel across from Harvard's Sanders Theatre (Memorial Hall) in Harvard Square. Not wheelchair accessible yet, sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For directions and more information see: &lt;a href="http://www.soulstirring.org/" target="_blank"&gt;soulstirring.org&lt;/a&gt;. Please note that the little side parking lot is for artist pickup/dropoff only during the show, so you need to find other parking locally (we wish we had a big lot but this is Harvard Square!). For parking tips and participating artists guidelines see &lt;a href="http://www.soulstirring.org/index_guidelines.html" target="_blank"&gt;soulstirring.org/guidelines.html&lt;/a&gt; Event is Saturday, October 13, 2012 at 7pm-9:30pm (your $5-$10 sliding scale admission will help defray many costs)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two approximately 45-minute segments of performer presentations, with a twenty minute break around 8pm. Paintings and drawings with artist statements displayed on the walls. Refreshments and reception to follow; book signings, postcards, information sharing, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350491558000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349444690000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Mystical Art and Talent Show 2012</name><id>85638992</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350169200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/85638992/</event_url></item>