<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology Transfer&lt;/strong&gt; - Nuts and Bolts - How to Get Great Technologies Out of Great Universities That Are Ready to Run&lt;/span&gt; and Make A Successful Business Out of Them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;The process of transferring technologies from Universities and Medical Research Facilities to a successful business can be a complex and at times frustrating process. However, the benefits of having access to a rich source of new developing technologies that can be commercialized into a profitable business far outweigh the difficulties one may encounter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the next EntreTech Forum we will explore this process from both sides and answer the questions you may have from accessing the viability of a technology, to negotiating the agreement to commercialize the technology, to funding and forming the company. Our panel of experts will review the keys to success and the potential pitfalls to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists Include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rebecca Menapace -&lt;/strong&gt; Director, Research and Licensing, Partners Healthcare - Rebecca manages the research and licensing team for MGH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lita L. Nelsen -&lt;/strong&gt; Director, Technology Licensing Office, MIT - Her office manages over 500 new inventions per year from M.I.T and Lincoln Laboratory. Typically, they negotiate over 100 licenses, and start up over 20 new companies per year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heather Keith&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-&lt;/strong&gt; CEO/Founder Strohl Medical Technologies, Inc. Strohl Medical is licensing intellectual property from Tufts University&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Hartung, President and CEO Cognoptix&lt;/strong&gt; - Paul is a longtime life sciences executive with a proven track record in launching successful startup businesses and leading Fortune 500 organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do startups, inside or outside of research organizations bring developing technologies to market? How do startups and investors value and assess ideas to launch new technologies? What is the process for development teams to engage in launching a venture? What examples of successfully commercialized ventures can early startups look to for ideas and guidance with challenging issues? How do you effectively assess market viability of an idea? What are the process and pitfalls of working with universities, private and governments’ research areas? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In the next EntreTech Forum we will delve into the process of Technology Transfer to answer these questions and more. Startups from all fields are encouraged to join us. We will discuss innovation in medical technology as a case study to illustrate the transfer process through to commercialization. The forum’s panel will draw from leaders in industry, academic and government fields. The panel’s goal is to help startups better understand, utilize and leverage their experience in commercializing the technology transfer process. Please join us for what will be an informative and interactive discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfjan2013.eventbrite.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358303470000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348155552000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Technology Transfer</name><id>83283172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358292600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/83283172/</event_url></item>