<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our group is diverse, talkative, and very upbeat. Come out and see what it is all about while we make 10-12 lunches for the Braintree Habitat for Humanity volunteers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Estella, co-organizer will provide her cozy home for this event on March 15 from 10:00 a.m. to 11:30 a.m. and promises to make it easy, quick and festive. This meetup is a little different than most of our meetups since we are asking for donation of food, $$ and/or time.  We will also need a few volunteers to help deliver the lunches that Saturday. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, come on down, SSDOMG, and smell the coffee!  Yes, that is right, Estella will brew a tasty pot of gourmet coffee, throw in some munchies, and some great music.  We look forward to seeing 6-8 smiling faces all ready to MAKE LUNCHES for volunteers!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Food Items Needed to Make Lunches&lt;/b&gt;: 3 cans of tuna or tuna salad, 1 lb of turkey cold cuts, 1lb of roast beef, 1 lb of cheese, 3-4 loaves of bread or 15 sandwich rolls, mayonnaise, mustard, baggies for sandwiches, cookies or other small pre-packaged dessert or individual packages of chips, trail mix, etc. , bottled water or other drinks, and brown bags to hold lunches.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please write what you will bring with your RSVP message, and read the other messages so as not to duplicate food items. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are unable to attend but would like to make a contribution please note it in your RSVP Comments and one of the Event Organizers will follow-up with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: In order to attend, your Profile must be complete and you have attended at least two Meetups since November 2007. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Logistics: &lt;br /&gt;Building Lunches for Braintree Habitat for Humanity &lt;br /&gt;Estella's House, Braintree &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 15, 2008&lt;br /&gt;10-11:30am: Building Lunches&lt;br /&gt;11:30am to 12:30pm: Volunteers to deliver lunches in Braintree&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: No Event Fee, just donations of food, $$ and /or time &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: 8 volunteers maximum &lt;br /&gt;Guests: Group Members Only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/b&gt;: Wednesday, March 12th @ 8 pm; Please be sure to include what food item you are bringing in your RSVP Comments so we know how to plan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Co-Organizers: Estella and Jeanne&lt;br /&gt;Directions &amp;amp; Phone #: To b emailed to all Yes RSVPs shortly after the RSVP Deadline&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When and Where: &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 15, 2007, Directions to follow RSVP &lt;br /&gt;? Info/Map&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You will have directions right to Estella's front door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205762763000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Do you want to meet new people? Do you like to socialize and network? Well the South Shore Dinning Meetup Group would like to give us all an opportunity not only to do the above, but to also do it for a good cause, relax and have some fun.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203734997000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Building Lunches for Habitat for Humanity Volunteers</name><id>7389935</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205589600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7389935/</event_url></item>