<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>276 Edmands Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.330697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-405-1686</phone><name>Ann and Mark's home</name><city>Framingham</city><id>972696</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449002</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;We have a very special guest to lead us in this meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie Curtis is a brilliant colleague of ours from Pennsylvania.  He teaches hypnosis, NLP, energy psychology, and stress management to health-care professionals, therapists, and other interested persons, and, of course, is into Law of Attraction big time, too.  He's also a profound writer, and his book, &lt;u&gt;Seeing the World Through Softer Eyes&lt;/u&gt; is coming out soon.  I'm sure it will be amazing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie will be teaching you how to look at the overall experience of your life, even when there is chaos and intensity, through softer eyes.  The objective is to give you the practical skills to step back and gain the perspective necessary to meet the challenges of your life more successfully and with a deeper peace, like a reed that bends in the wind, so in balance that you're able to meet the challenges of life without feeling weakness and without having to resort to the use of force.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Knowing Charlie as I do, I believe this is another way of saying how to move through your life without resistance, and to stay peaceful and allowing no matter what.  Sound good?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He'll be guiding us through the &amp;quot;Soft Eyes&amp;quot; exercise/process as well as a guided meditation that I'm sure will move us all into deep, deep relaxation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He will also be gifting each of us one of his CD's from his new book!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;PLEASE, PLEASE, only sign up if you know you can and will attend.  We can only take a maximum of 20 people in our space, and do not want to exclude anyone unnecessarily because of a no-show.   Help us reach our goal of 100% attendance for those who rsvp &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait for this!  Thank you, Charlie!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1285112749000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279826060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seeing the world through "soft eyes"</name><id>14182709</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282086000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/14182709/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>