<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>943 Namquid Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02888</zip><lat>41.741898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-572-3390</phone><name>Game On!</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1111698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Get your game on every other Wednesday with D&amp;amp;D Encounters, an ongoing mini-campaign where you&amp;rsquo;ll play two encounters every other week at your local game store. Earn exclusive rewards as you gain Renown Points for accomplishments made during each season!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, our fifth exciting season of play, the heroes will head to the beleaguered town of Duponde and attempt to free it from the sinister clutches of the forces of shadow and darkness. They&amp;rsquo;ll get into the action quickly by creating a D&amp;amp;D character using the D&amp;amp;D Essentials&amp;trade; or Player&amp;rsquo;s Option: Heroes of Shadow&amp;trade; rules options, or grab a pre-generated character provided in the kit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Dark Legacy of Evard" brings the legendary wizard and master of Shadow  magic out of the game's past and firmly establishes his heritage for the  current age. Someone disturbs the tomb of the creator of shadow spells  such as &lt;em&gt;Evard's black tentacles&lt;/em&gt;, and suddenly an entire town  begins to slide out of the natural world and into the Shadowfell. Can  you unravel the mystery and fend off the dangers of Shadow before it's  too late? This is a D&amp;amp;D Encounters season that you won't want to  miss!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get ready to experience the deadly secrets of the master of shadow magic in the Dark Legacy of Evard!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have friends or family interested in D&amp;amp;D and looking for a great introduction to what 4th edition has to offer, have them come and join us for an evening of adventure at Veteran's Gaming in Warwick.  Sessions will start at 6PM and should run from 2-3 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who played in Seasons 1, 2, 3, or 4 Rewards Cards and Fortune Cards earned in those adventures are fully legal for use in all subsequent seasons.&amp;nbsp; This season includes the use of Fortune Cards, which will be on sale at Veteran's for those who are interesting in giving their character that extra edge to turn the tide of battle.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanios</member_name><member_id>4187193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308172788000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303323263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>D&amp;D Encounters Season 5:  Dark Legacy of Evard</name><id>gcvwqypjblb</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307570400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/17377024/</event_url></item>