<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One City Hall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.359377</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>City Hall Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>877405</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058043</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There's nothing like spending a sunny Sunday with Boston By Foot!  Let's meet at the Government Center flags to learn about some awesome Boston women!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the 17th century to present day, women's contributions to Boston did not always garner the attention they might deserve. On this walking tour, you will learn who they were and what they achieved against the backdrop of the Boston's downtown historic sites from the arrival of Anne Pollard in 1630 through the 20th century.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Abolitionist, poet, and Beacon Hill resident Julia Ward Howe, most famous for writing The Battle Hymn of the Republic, was considered the “Queen of Boston” because she was born three days before Queen Victoria. She also introduced the idea of a Mother's Day following the Civil War.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lucy Stone, the first Massachusetts woman to receive a college degree, became a leader of the suffrage movement and lent her name to women who kept their maiden names after marriage.&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Josepha Hale was the real force behind the completion of the Bunker Hill Monument and the first to publish Mary Had a Little Lamb.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just the beginning -- learn about these and the dozens of other women such as Susan Dimrock, Marie Zakrzewska, Fannie Farmer, Elizabeth Cary Agassiz, Isabella Stewart Gardner, Esther Forbes, Mary Porter Hemenway, and Abigail Adams. Their contributions in medicine, nutrition, education, art, literature, philanthropy, and women's rights helped make Boston and America what it is today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $15/person or $5 for BBF members.  FMI about becoming a BBF member, please visit the  &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member" target="_blank"&gt;BBF website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the flags in front of City Hall on City Hall Plaza.  I will be wearing a Meetup sticker and carrying more with which to stick you!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Megan</member_name><member_id>10021028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258485459000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258131495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Women of Boston Tour with Boston By Foot</name><id>11866940</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258311600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11866940/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/6/global_11786726.jpeg</photo_url></item>