<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;On a long enough timeline, the survival rate for everyone drops to zero&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;His name is Robert Paulson! His name is Robert Paulson!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What:&lt;/b&gt; Screening on Fight Club, preceded by a lecture by anthropologist Richard Wrangham &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When:&lt;/b&gt; Monday, February 8 at 7:00 pm (get in line at 6:15 pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; Coolidge Corner Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: $9.75 regular admission; $7.75 for seniors, students, and Museum of Science members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will probably be there by 6:00 pm. The line outside to wait for the doors to the theater to open starts to form at 6:15 pm rain or shine. Most of us should probably be there then. People hate it when we cut in line just to be together. The screen is on the other end of the stage so we should probably sit in the center rows. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the screening&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;David Fincher’s &lt;b&gt;Fight Club&lt;/b&gt;, based on the novel by Chuck Palahniuk, was one of the most talked about films of the 1990s for its controversial takes on violence, manhood and corporate culture.  Startlingly aggressive and intensely provocative, this cult favorite twists and turns, all the way through to its surprising end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Edward Norton plays the unnamed narrator, an alienated 30-something stuck in a dull white collar job. Tormented by insomnia, he finds temporary emotional release by visiting disease support groups, where he encounters a fellow imposter named Marla (Helena Bonham Carter).  A chance encounter with Tyler Durden (Brad Pitt), a subversive soap salesman, frees the narrator from the banality of his existence.  The two become friends and roommates, bonding over their mutual disgust for consumer culture and their unusual weekly ritual: they fight each other for fun.  Soon they form Fight Club, an underground group where young men channel primal aggression into brutal, bare-knuckled brawls that leave them feeling exhilarated and alive.  As chapters sprout up in other cities, Fight Club morphs into “Project Mayhem&amp;quot;, a nationwide group that spirals out of control. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;For all of their many virtues, men are more violent than women, a tendency they share with their closest male primate relatives.  Guest speaker &lt;b&gt;Richard Wrangham&lt;/b&gt;, the Ruth Moore Professor of Biological Anthropology at Harvard University and co-author of &lt;i&gt;Demonic Males: Apes and the Origins of Human Violence&lt;/i&gt;, has spent decades studying chimpanzee cultures in the wild and comparing chimp cultures to human ones. It turns out that violent social behavior is common among chimpanzees and deeply rooted in male human genes.  In ways that sound eerily familiar, male chimps fight one another directly for access to females and hunt and kill members of rival groups.  Join us as Dr. Wrangham discusses why men like to fight, what makes human violence unique compared to other primates, why we are wired to relish certain kinds of aggression more than others – and why we shouldn’t assume that male violence is inevitable.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With Science on Screen, the Coolidge presents a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, paired with exciting introductions by notable scientific figures. This monthly series is co-presented by The Museum of Science, Boston and New Scientist magazine&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Wrangman's Demonic Males: Apes and the Origins of Human Violence&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Demonic-Males-Origins-Human-Violence/dp/0395877431" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[Amazon.com] Contradicting the common belief that chimpanzees in the wild are gentle creatures, Harvard anthropologist Wrangham and science writer Peterson have witnessed, since 1971, male African chimpanzees carry out rape, border raids, brutal beatings and warfare among rival territorial gangs. In a startling, beautifully written, riveting, provocative inquiry, they suggest that chimpanzee-like violence preceded and paved the way for human warfare - which would make modern humans the dazed survivors of a continuous, five-million-year habit of lethal aggression. They buttress their thesis with an examination of the ubiquitous rape among orangutans, gorilla infanticide and male-initiated violence and hyenas' territorial feuds, drawing parallels to the lethal raiding among the Yanomamo people of Brazil's Amazon forests and other so-called primitive tribes, as well as to modern 'civilized' mass slaughter. In their analysis, patriotism ('stripped to its essence... male defense of the community') breeds aggression, yet, from an evolutionary standpoint, they reject the presumed inevitability of male violence and male dominance over women&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Nearby metered public parking is available behind the theatre (on Center St. one block from Harvard St.) and along Beacon Street. Meters are free after 6:00pm and on Sundays and holidays. Please note that the lots tend to fill up on weekends or during large events, so please plan a little extra time to find space. We strongly reccomend public transit for events and films you anticipate will be very busy! Additional Parking at an hourly rate is available across Beacon and Centre Streets at the Courtyard Marriott Hotel garage on Webster St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] By train: take the Green Line (C branch to Cleveland Circle) trolley from downtown to Coolidge Corner via Beacon Street. The Coolidge Corner stop is at Harvard Street, 5-10 minutes from Kenmore Square&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265847165000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263831325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fight Club w/ Richard Wrangham lecture @ Science on Screen, Coolidge Corner</name><id>12352143</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265673600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12352143/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/4/global_12687092.jpeg</photo_url></item>