<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>DW Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.759998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pheasant Lane Mall</name><city>Nashua</city><id>371168</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.470001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;It's time to Revolutionize NH and let people know the Ron Paul campaign is alive and growing. The timing is right! This is event is scheduled for the weekend before Ron Paul arrives with 30 + members of his family to do the lit big drop. Let's stir up some curiosity before Ron arrives in NH with his family!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this event is going to have the effect we are hoping to have, we will need serious participation. 10 people holding banners does not make a revolution. 70 or more people will draw media attention! Let's do this! Our intention is to get passers by to realize there is something exciting going on that they need to find out about.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet on the sidewalk on DW Hwy, in front of the Pheasant Lane Mall in South Nashua.(Please be considerate to the local businesses when choosing your parking space). We will line the sidewalks with supporters holding banners and signs, from the mall up to the corner of Spit Brook and DW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have the banners and signs. We just need YOU. Please get the word out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hold Sunday the 23rd as a rain date. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be a lot of fun! &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190655659000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189641633000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revolutionize DW Highway</name><id>6347761</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190476800000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6347761/</event_url></item>