<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Gott Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.687389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 546-2997</phone><name>Halibut Point State Park</name><city>Rockport</city><id>744966</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.631871</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Friday is suppose to be a beautiful 66 degree day out so let's get out and enjoy it!  We will walk for no more than 2 hours.  If there is interest we can grab a snack locally (please let me know if you have any recommendations for inexpensive places to eat in the area).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Halibut Point is a uniquely beautiful coastal seascape. Looking seaward on a clear day, the view stretches from Crane Beach in Ipswich to Mount Agamenticus in Maine and the Isles of Shoals off the coast of New Hampshire. Formerly the Babson Farm granite quarry, the park is managed for scenic, historic and conservation purposes by the DCR and the Trustees of Reservations. An adjacent property, Sea Rocks, is owned by the Town of Rockport and open for public use. Here you can explore the park's trails and tidepools, picnic on its rocky ledges, enjoy its sweeping views, and learn about Cape Ann's historic granite industry. Join us for this walk along the seaside. There may be  a per car parking charge at Halibut Point State Park, so carpooling is encouraged.The group will meet in the parking lot at Halibut Point State Park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Info at &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/halb.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/halb.htm&lt;/a&gt; Park Directions Halibut Point State Park is located in Cape Ann in north-eastern Massachusetts. From the South and West: Take Rte. I-95/128 north to Rte. 128 north toward Gloucester and Rockport. After crossing the Annisquam River bridge, go three quarters around the first rotary, following signs for Rt. 127 north (Annisquam and Pigeon Cove). After approximately 6 miles, turn left at the park sign and the Old Farm Inn onto Gott Ave. From Downtown Rockport: Drive north on Rt. 127 approximately 3 miles, turning right onto Gott Ave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Walking, hiking, and additional activities may involve many risk including but not limited to muscular skeletal injury, accidents or illness, increased blood pressure, hydration issues, heart attack, or even catastrophic events and death. By joining this walk you agree that you understand the risk involved; including, but not limited to risk of property damage, risk from physical activity, heat and hydration, variety of terrain, use of public parks/facilities, weather and forces of nature.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;You state that you are medically fit to participate in the activities you attend with the group and are responsible for your own heath, safety, and well being at all times.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;You are responsible for providing all your own supplies, understanding your limitations, knowing how to care for yourself during walks and other physical activities, and seeking medical assistance as needed.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;You acknowledge that you are responsible for your own expenses should an injury, accident, or emergency occur.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;You agree to personally assume all personal risks in connection with your participation in these activities. You on behalf of yourself, your representatives, and your heirs and minor children agree to release, hold harmless and indemnify this meetup group, it's members and organizers, organizers and participants of related meetup groups, and other individuals associated with meetup  activities, from all liability, loss, claims, damages, and causes of action arising out of or connected with your participation in the activities offered by this meet up meetup group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trish O'Flynn</member_name><member_id>3013556</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366404501000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366238366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halibut Point State Park</name><id>114868132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366393500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/114868132/</event_url></item>