<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>**WILL NOT BE MEETING AT MIT.   GO TO  CHARACTERS BAR AND GRILL INSTEAD**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The room we normally have at MIT we normally have is not available on the 19th, nor is the room we have used once or twice in the event this one is taken.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore Beantown Gamers is going on a little field trip this week to Characters Bar and Grill.  Don't worry about the commute people, as it is only across the street, at the Marriott Cambridge Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the T:&lt;br /&gt;Take the red-line to Kendall Square station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're coming outbound (from Park Street), exit at the gates at the front of the train. Take the escalator. Proceed into the hotel directly in front of you.  Turn right. Take the escalator to the 2nd floorl Turn right and go down the hallway until you see Characters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're coming inbound (from Central Square), exit at the gates at the rear of the train. Take the stairs or elevator straight up. There will be a street directly behind ytou, Turn around, cross the street, once you reash an open area, look to the right. You will see Characters bar and grill on the second floor.  There are entrances both directly into the restaurant as well as inside the hotel (see above)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a suggested donation of $1.00 that goes towards site fees.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for tables with games on them</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Becki</member_name><member_id>4147212</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295544430000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279416992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mid week burnout? come play games!</name><id>bxsbpypcbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295481600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/15782094/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>