<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Reservation Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03037</zip><lat>43.104870</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Pawtuckaway State Park</name><city>Deerfield</city><id>632081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.204970</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Although the park is technically closed to pets it is the off season and the park isn't officially open.  As we will also be using one of the back ways into the park that shouldn't be an issue.  I am interested in doing about a 5 mile hike that would take in both the Boulder Field near Round Pd and the Fire Tower on South Mountain.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although a 5 mile hike is a little longer than what we usually do the terrain and trails there that we will go on aren't really that difficult and the elevation gain and loss isn't all that much (probably about 500 feet or less).  Unless a 5 mile long hike is an issue for you on hiking rating systems this would likely be considered an easy hike based on the trail difficulty factors.  If any of you have hiked Mt. Major this should be an easier hike than that as the elevation gain is at least half of Mt. Major's&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When thinking of a Boulder Field as it was described it made me think of a field (meadow) with huge boulders in it.   This &amp;quot;field&amp;quot; is actually fully wooded and field takes on more of the meaning of any region characterized by a particular feature which in this case is an area were huge 30 foot boulders were strewn about as the result of glacial activity in the past.  In any case the rock formations are quite interesting and unexpected given what the rest of the terrain is like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please do bring something simpler to eat if you would like for a lunch as although it is not exactly picnic weather we could stop to eat at some point.  Likely near the fire tower if it is not to windy up there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I haven't quite decided the exact starting point yet but will have it posted by Friday night as I haven't had a chance to check out the second way into the park.  The starting point will be either off of (167) Deerfield Rd. in Nottingham or off of Reservoir Rd. in Deerfield.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Manchester either starting point is under 25 miles away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the White Suzuki Grand Vitara with the DOGPARK license plate where Reservation Road intersects with North Mountain Trail.  This will be approximately 1.8 miles once you turn onto Reservation Rd off of Rt. 107 (Raymond Rd)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289702079000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289530577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pawtuckaway State Park -  Boulder Field and S. Mtn. Fire Tower.</name><id>15422498</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289667600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/15422498/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/2/global_19353362.jpeg</photo_url></item>