<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>9.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November Lean Workshop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6:30pm -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Early Bird&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Presentation: Customer Development 101&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those new to the concepts of Customer Development and The Lean Startup, we'll start the evening with a talk about the basics of customer development and lean startups at 6:30pm. Come to listen to the presentation, or hang out and network over pizza!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7pm - Brett Durrett,&amp;nbsp;VP of Engineering at IMVU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/#!/bdurrett"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/a/e/event_67275022.jpeg" width="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.imvu.com"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/c/2/event_67276322.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuous Deployment takes continuous integration one-step further, where every commit goes live to production servers. &amp;nbsp; When this process is described it is frequently met with skepticism around site reliability and the ability to scale a business this way, but it works, it scales (with challenges) and it is embraced by the entire organization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMVU is a leader in Continuous Deployment, with over 5 years of experience scaling this process to support a technical staff of 50 and a business of more that $40 million in annual revenue. &amp;nbsp;Brett G. Durrett, Vice President of Engineering &amp;amp; Operations for IMVU explains the basic mechanics of Continuous Deployment and discusses the value it creates for the entire company. &amp;nbsp;Specific topics that will be covered:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why practice Continuous Deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What a Continuous Deployment system looks like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to practice Continuous Deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees will understand that releasing to customers 20+ times per day is possible and that it does scale from individual developers to large companies. &amp;nbsp;In addition, they will understand how they can make Continuous Deployment successful at their company, from both a technology and cultural standpoint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Brett G. Durrett has over 20 years experience leading development of software and systems ranging from large-scale Internet services to video games. He serves as VP of Engineering at IMVU where he leads the engineering and technical operations teams. Prior to IMVU, Brett served as the Director of Engineering, VP of Operations and General Manager for the virtual world at There.com. Brett was also co-founder and CEO of the game developer Asylum Entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's with the $9 registration fee?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Lean Startup Circle Boston, we've been fortunate to produce high quality events with great speakers who volunteer their time to share lessons learned at an awesome venue with dinner for all attendees each month - for free. Many thanks to Microsoft BizSpark for graciously donating their facilities and for feeding us each and every month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For our November event, your $9 registration fee will go toward speaker related costs, including his travel from San Fran, which is being done for the opportunity to share lessons learned with us. We think it's worth the price of admission, and we look forward to returning to our normal free model in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew, John, Abby&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Prendergast</member_name><member_id>8455139</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Mamet</member_name><member_id>8758381</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abby Fichtner</member_name><member_id>11818323</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323281888000</updated><rating><average>4.67999982834</average><count>22</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lean-Startup-Circle-Boston</urlname><id>1533572</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Lean Startup Circle Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>104</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319682223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lean Startup Circle Boston November Meetup</name><id>38880362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321572600000</time><rsvp_limit>125</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lean-Startup-Circle-Boston/events/38880362/</event_url></item>