<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>July 28, 2010&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hi! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am sure you are having an enjoyable summer: joy, peace and family R&amp;amp;R.   How are you making out with this hot and humid weather? Personally, I don't complain much, since it reminds me of the years I spent in Taiwan and China... and so no reason to complain.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Just a share some news. After much delaying, I will be going back to Italy to visit with my mom and family for the next 2 month +. I will be leaving on August 2 and coming back on October 25th. I am looking forward to spending time with my mom, even though I am still concern about the progress of our renovation project. God will provide. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While away, Teriann Rafal has agreed to chair our upcoming meetings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the summer break our Interfaith Book Club gatherings will resume on Sunday September 12 at 4:00pm. Meeting place is still the PEACE ABBEY - Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We finished reading and sharing on THOMAS MERTON'S book: &amp;quot;THE INNER EXPERIENCE - Notes on contemplation.&amp;quot; So, at the next meeting, we have to choose our new reading material. Bring any book that provoke, challenge or inspire you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given that I will not be present, I am suggesting the following books: &lt;br /&gt;1) God is not One: The eight rival religions that run the world and why their differences matter, by Stephen Prothero.&lt;br /&gt;2) A History of God: The 4000 year quest of Judaism, Christianity and Islam, by Karen Armstrong.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teriann, is suggesting the following: &lt;br /&gt;Exploring The Spirit of Maine, by Karen Wentworth Batignani.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come with your suggestions and I am sure you will choose a great book. Let me know of your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, mark your calendar... and I hope you can make our upcoming meeting:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;TIME: September 12th at 4:00PM&lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to choose the date for the following meeting.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Blessings on you and yours. Enjoy the summer and walk with the Divine. I will think of you, while enjoying my time with my mom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144&lt;br /&gt;pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284326202000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280363372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ENJOY THE SUMMER!</name><id>14246969</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284321600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/14246969/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/global_4353546.jpeg</photo_url></item>