<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Stata Center, Room 32-141</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9591052</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089844</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MIT Enterprise Forum Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing Solutions Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monday Nov. 5, 2012, 6:00 – 8:30 pm at the MIT Stata Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;PLEASE &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;REGISTER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; AT THE MIT ENTERPRISE FORUM OF CAMBRIDGE &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;www.mitforumcambridge.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISRUPTIVE INNOVATION&lt;/strong&gt;: The Internet of Things Plus Long-range RFID and Sensors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPROVING THE RETAIL FLOW OF GOODS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;RANGE MATTERS! TAG SIZE MATTERS! SENSING (often) MATTERS! All at a very low cost!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TODAY'S PROBLEMS&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Human beings expend great energies manually collect visibility data. The data on the Internet has been largely created by human beings -- typing, bar code scans, digital photos and more. Initial deployments of RFID solutions have relied heavily upon human intervention. Manual data collection is very time consuming and error prone. Implementing RFID solutions seamlessly across the enterprise is a lot of hard work!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE SOLUTION - Smaller, Cheaper, Faster, Better!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Long-range, low cost RFID takes the human out of the data collection loop. Today's market for visibility solutions is soaring. The "Internet of Things" is hitting the mainstream. Today sensors, cameras, RFID bar codes and a variety of visibility viewing platforms are commonplace throughout the working world. In 2012 over 4 Billion long-range RFID tags are expected to be produced for retail apparel at the item level. We are experiencing the initial stages of an onslaught of BIG DATA which is automatically generated by an abundance of highly distributed wireless devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Long-range RFID to track elements of the physical world couples with ubiquitous connectivity to the Internet to distribute BIG DATA and view information generated by these equally ubiquitous digital identifiers and sensors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TODAY'S CHALLENGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;End users are confronted by an overwhelming number of questions such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What to buy?  What's good? What to avoid?  Typical pitfalls?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How best to organize?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to install the systems?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;'Peaceful co-existence' with legacy systems and business processes . . . POS, bar code, inventory management . . . How to blend the new with the old? Seamless adoption, integration and deployment?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How best to analyze BIG DATA?  For what purpose?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;'Fit' with other innovative technologies?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Costs?  Tags, Infrastructure, Installation, Integration . . . .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;******&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPEAKERS&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sprague Ackley&lt;/strong&gt;, Technologist, Intermec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Christophe LOUSSERT&lt;/strong&gt;, VP, RFID integration, TAGSYS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greg Morello&lt;/strong&gt;, CMO, Port Logistics Group (PLG)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thomas Reese&lt;/strong&gt;, Sr. Director, Business Development, Intelleflex Corp.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MODERATOR: Michael Ohanian&lt;/strong&gt;, retired President of Intermec Technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implementing RFID without disrupting already successful bar code systems?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;H. Sprague Ackley, Technologist, Intermec&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 There are many ways of encoding RFID data, yet none seem compatible with the data in existing bar code applications:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• The two main data encoding methods, GS1 and ISO, offer different and incompatible methods with current bar coding applications. &lt;br /&gt;

 • There’s a recent a major breakthrough in simplicity. GS1 just published a definitive guideline. &lt;br /&gt;

 • How to progress towards a seamless future?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tag Miniaturization and Integrated Software Platforms&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Christophe Loussert, Vice President RFID integration, TAGSYS&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 U.S. retailer mandates for item-level RFID are triggering paradigm shifts for RFID technologies. Tag miniaturization enable small-size, long range RFID. Modular and scalable software platforms enable new processes such as bulk encoding for serialization, enabling full virtualization of the supply chain and enabling in the future full production line sharing. TAGSYS RFID technology transforms the way consumers and companies connect, communicate and interact with goods. It's critical that RFID is implemented efficiently with minimal size, cost and space requirements, particularly in high-end consumer-oriented products – yet still operate effectively in challenging environments. &lt;br /&gt;

 • Breakthrough UHF RFID designs - how innovative applications of RF achieves new levels of size, performance and reading distance. &lt;br /&gt;

 • BENEFITS: enables broader deployment of RFID for applications where tiny and non-intrusive tags are pre-requisites, such as the luxury retail market. &lt;br /&gt;

 • A LIVE demonstration of an integrated platform combining NFC and RFID technologies,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improving the flow of goods within the Retail Supply Chain&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;• Christophe Loussert, Vice President RFID integration, TAGSYS&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;• Greg Morello, CMO, Port Logistics Group (PLG)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 TAGSYS and the Port Logistics Group, Inc. (PLG) jointly present “Value Added Logistics Solutions”. PLG is a 3PL provider to brands such as Macy's, YOOX, and others. PLG combines the energy and enthusiasm of a start-up with the perspective and experience of a tested veteran. Founded in 2008, PLG has quickly become one of the fastest growing companies in the industry. PLG was named a “Top 100 3PL” by Inbound Logistics magazine and has 16 Gateway Import, Distribution and Storage facilities strategically located within the US. PLG does "Value Added" 3PL Services with- and for their customers such as Receiving, Storage, Work-In-Process, Picking, Packing, Exceptions, Shipping, Data and Information Technology. &lt;br /&gt;

 • Hear about a detailed overview of an actual deployment, &lt;br /&gt;

 • Key benefits and technical challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thomas Reese, Sr. Director, Business Development, Intelleflex Corp.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intelleflex provides on-demand data visibility solutions for cold chain and asset management. Its XC3 RFID products enable a range of solutions for fresh, frozen and packaged foods, and pharmaceutical temperature monitoring, asset tracking, personnel monitoring retail, healthcare and other applications. These real-time monitoring solutions can help organizations reduce shrink or loss, more closely track and manage assets, reduce cost of operations and increase profitability.  www.intelleflex.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After the presentations by the panelists&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;there will be ~30 minutes of Q &amp;amp; A.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A ten minute walk from the Kendall Square T-stop (Red line subway) in Cambridge, MA</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352231144000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349201832000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DISRUPTIVE INNOVATION: Impact of Long-range RFID &amp; Sensors on Internet of Things</name><id>85147972</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352156400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/85147972/</event_url></item>