<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(edge of Portal Park</address_2><address_1>Causeway St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.365706</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Station T stop</name><city>Boston</city><id>856572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060636</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This tour was originally developed for children but truly appeals to all ages, come along and bring all your school-vacation-looking-for-something-to-do young friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bells, Bridges &amp;amp; Locks offers you the opportunity to discover the things that move in, around, and over the Charles River Basin. From the Boston Garden along the Bulfinch Triangle, over the Charles, and to U.S.S. Constitution, you will experience the art, technology, and nature of this historic area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the tour we will get a close up view of Boston's new cable-stayed landmark, the Leonard P. Zakim Bunker Hill Bridge, the locks of the Charles River Dam, and the revitalization of the lower basin.  Not to mention, discuss the alewife herring and its anadromous behaviour, the harbor crossing of a certain Mr. Revere and the exploits of the Boston Ice King.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This small area of Boston is packed with amazing things to see!  Dress warmly and enjoy a real journey of discovery.  The tour lasts 90 minutes and costs $15 ($5 for &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot members&lt;/a&gt; -- see web site). It meets at the corner of Portal Park on Causeway Street - just next to the North Station T entrance kiosk closest to the Boston Garden.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Boston By Foot badges, bags, hats, etc.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266768775000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232395102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bells, Bridges and Locks Tour</name><id>9557238</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234724400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/9557238/</event_url></item>