<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>990 Great Plain Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02492</zip><lat>42.280225</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-449-4050</phone><name>Masala Art</name><city>Needham</city><id>1157180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236439</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Info about the restaurant and the book:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Restaurant for February:  Masala Art in Needham&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Masala Art offers a buffet &amp;quot;featuring South Indian crepes.&amp;quot;   The buffet cost is $14, plus $1 for the meetup, plus  tax and tip -- figure $18 per person (plus any extras, beverages, etc., ordered by individuals).  If you opt to order from the menu, cost of your food plus 26 % (Tax and tip) + $1 to support the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book for February:   Toss of a Lemon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Journalist, playwright and short-story writer Viswanathan's absorbing first novel, based on her grandmother's life, goes deep into the world of southern India village life. Starting in 1896, the story follows Sivakami, a Tamil Brahmin girl, from her marriage at the age of 10 through her long widowhood, while Indian political and social life lumbers through immense changes. Before he dies, Sivakami's astrologer husband, Hanumarathnam, foresees his death in the malignant interactions between his stars and his son Vairum's. Though he trains a trustworthy servant to assist Sivakami until their son comes of age, the world that Hanumarathnam leaves behind is rapidly changing, and the family is not entirely fit to survive it; Vairum, especially, suffers the pain of a father's disaffection and, later, a widowed mother forbidden to touch any human being during daylight hours. Irreconcilable conflicts between tradition—especially the strict caste rules of Brahmin life—and the modernizing world lead predictably to alienation and tragedy, but on an epic scale. Viswanathan is especially adept at unobtrusively explaining foreign customs and worldviews to Westerners while wholly respecting the power and significance they hold for practitioners.&lt;br /&gt;Copyright © Reed Business Information, a division of Reed Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Book on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266328229000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256573294000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February 2009:  The Toss of a Lemon, by Padma Viswanathan</name><id>11714299</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266080400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/11714299/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>