<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.360067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Suites</name><city>Boston</city><id>968618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;D.E.N. - Deals Exchange Network&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  **Deal or NO DEAL** - Get your deals analyzed by a panel of local real estate experts!  To be a candidate to submit your deals - email Bernadette (Bernadette@bostonareia.com) today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then,  Jack Lavoie will present Appraisal Issues and Techniques for Investors&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most important skill an investor can master &lt;br /&gt;How to estimate the After Repaired Value (ARV) &lt;br /&gt;The real cost of pricing your house wrong &lt;br /&gt;How to track and forecast trends in your local market &lt;br /&gt;How to choose your comps and where to find them &lt;br /&gt;Now to analyze apartments and income property &lt;br /&gt;What types of property to RUN away from &lt;br /&gt;Dealing with bank appraisers when you are selling &lt;br /&gt;Retailing your house to an FHA buyer &lt;br /&gt;Finding local rental and vacancy rates &lt;br /&gt;Property analyzing the deal &lt;br /&gt;Cap Rates and Gross Rent Multipliers 101 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jack Lavoie is not only an experienced investor, but a licensed real estate broker, auctioneer and certified appraiser.   Jack has taught many courses to local investors and brokers on investing, short sales, creative financing , appraising and more. He has bought and sold 70+ properties himself and assisted other investors acquire hundreds. Jack’s appraisal background makes him a master at analyzing deals and is the appraiser of choice of brokers, attorneys and investors in NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jack currently owns and manages Jack Lavoie Real Estate and ALX Realty Investments, LLC. Next month he will be launching the Manchester (NH) Real Estate Investors Club and will serve as the education director.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: 1st Tuesday of Every Month 6:30 PM - next DEN 4/6/2010 - Enjoy Networking, Deals, Prizes and Fun!!! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Doubletree Suites, 400 Soldiers Field Road, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHAT:  Networking, Deals Exchange, Featuring: &lt;br /&gt;              &lt;br /&gt;Cost: $25 for visitors, FREE for Members of Boston AREIA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;***SAVE THE DATE - BRING YOUR DEALS - BRING LOTS OF BUSINESS CARDS AND COME PREPARED TO NETWORK!*** &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270765970000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268762076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DEN - Deals, Exchange Network </name><id>12892302</id><headcount>73</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270593000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/12892302/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/b/global_1787963.jpeg</photo_url></item>