<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>225 South St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01267</zip><lat>42.708329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413.458.2303</phone><name>Clark Art Institute</name><city>Williamstown</city><id>800201</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.216465</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Road Trip!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Lets take a ride up to Williamstown for a day at this great little museum in the Berkshires.&lt;br /&gt;Working on organizing carpools from New Haven/Hartford areas (if interested). Arrival at 12:00, picnic lunch on the beautiful grounds, Guided tour and lecture. The cafeteria is available before we head back to CT or we can do more picnicking.  Admission should be $15.00 or under, depending on whether we get enough for a group admission.  Follow the site for details as they unfold for specifics and carpooling possibilities and departure times if carpooling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Picasso Looks at Degas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lecture at 3:00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Diana Widmaier&lt;/b&gt;: Picasso in Conversation with Richard Kendall&lt;br /&gt;Art historian and author of the forthcoming catalogue raisonné of Pablo Picasso sculpture Diana Widmaier Picasso will discuss her grandfather’s work with Clark curator-at-large Richard Kendall. Picasso’s sculpture will be the focus of this conversation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Picasso Looks at Degas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;June 13, 2010 - September 12, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Focusing on two of the great artists of the modern period, this exhibition explores Pablo Picasso’s lifelong fascination with the life and work of Edgar Degas. This ground-breaking exhibition examines Degas through Picasso’s eyes and the ways his response varied over time from emulation to confrontation and parody to homage. The Clark is the exclusive North American venue for this exhibition which explores the depth of the Spanish artist’s fixation through dramatic pairings and groupings that have never been brought together in this ambitious way. Degas’s In a Café (L’Absinthe) (1875–76, Musée d’Orsay) is placed alongside Picasso’s Portrait of Sebastià Junyer i Vidal (1903, Los Angeles County Museum of Art); Picasso’s oil on canvas The Blue Room (Le Tub) (1901, Phillips Collection, Washington, DC) is paired with The Tub, (c. 1876–77. Bibliothèque de l’Institut national d’histoire de l’art, Paris), a monotype by Degas that may have served as a prototype; and Picasso’s 1905 Portrait of Benedetta Canals (1905, Museu Picasso, Barcelona) is hung beside Degas’s Woman with an Umbrella (Berthe Jeantaud) (c. 1876, National Gallery of Canada, Ottawa).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;The two artists shared a lifelong obsession with women that is seen in portraits of friends and images of singers, laundresses, ballet dancers, bathers, and prostitutes. While it is widely acknowledged that these are Degas’s signature themes, all are echoed in Picasso’s work. Usually identified as painters, both Degas and Picasso were innovative sculptors, printmakers, and extraordinary draftsmen, and the exhibition uses the full range of media to examine Picasso’s reaction to the challenge of Degas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the lobby </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279208228000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271261452000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Picasso Looks at Degas - Clark Museum, Williamstown,MA</name><id>13181128</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278864000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13181128/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/2/7/global_14373111.jpeg</photo_url></item>