<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hilldale Lane</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03070</zip><lat>42.982900</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Hillsborough County 4-H Youth Center (Fairgrounds)</name><city>New Boston</city><id>1339916</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.681630</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This should be an easy hike for most people unless walking 6 miles is an issue for you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Piscataqua River Rail Trail in New Boston is a flat, wide trail most of the way.   As this is a line hike (you come back the exact same way) on a easy to follow mostly straight trail any one getting  tired before we reach the turn around point can easily find their way back to the parking lot. We will be crossing a road so if your dog is not easily controlled by your voice you will want to have a leash on hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water dogs will like this one as there are various places along the hike where dogs will have access to the river.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robin Homsey-Blaine</member_name><member_id>2500267</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367234441000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365336930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy 6 mile walk along the rail trail</name><id>113105802</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367071200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/113105802/</event_url></item>