<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Boston chapter of Wokai, a global microfinance organization dedicated to alleviate poverty in China, is hosting an event on Tuesday July 27th featuring two guest speakers. Come for a drink and beat the heat, learn about microfinance and meet new friends!  Hor D'Oeuvres will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time&lt;/b&gt;: Tuesday, July 27th, 6:30- 8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt; Lir Restaurant Downstairs, 903 Boylston Street, Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: Tickets - $10 ($8 goes Wokai &amp;amp; $2 goes to food coverage)&lt;br /&gt;                    * You can purchase tix in advance or pay at the door. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purchase at  &lt;a href="http://wokai.org/Events.action" target="_blank"&gt;http://wokai.org/Even...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30-7:00 Reception&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00-7:30 Presentation by Kim Wilson and Ben Clark&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30-8: 30 Happy Hour&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kim Wilson is a lecturer of international business at Tufts Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy.  She is also a consultant to US Agency for International Development, Accion International, Save the Children US and ADRA International and other organizations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ben Clark is a project management officer for the Innovations and Integrated Solutions unit of Accion International, a U.S.-based nonprofit organization operating globally. He has also worked with FINCA International, a charitable microfinance organization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT IS WOKAI&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wokai (&amp;#25105;&amp;#24320; - “I start” in Mandarin) is an 501(c)(3) nonprofit founded in 2007 dedicated to helping individuals in rural China lift themselves out of poverty through microloans.  Wokai's platform connects you and other contributors around the world directly with individual farmers and microentrepreneurs in rural China in need of small loans.  To date, Wokai has raised over $335K in microloan capital, been featured on CNBC, MSNBC and Newsweek and has garnered the support of organizations like Google and the Salesforce.com Foundation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW WOKAI WORKS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A unique model, powered by the web.  Wokai.org is a platform that allows anyone to fund microloans to rural Chinese individuals through a credit card, and contributions can be made for as little as $10.  Contributors are able to track the borrower's progress and will be able to redistribute their contributions after the borrower repays.  Due to China's financial sector regulations, your contribution will be recycled as loan capital year after year.  Our sustainable model greatly amplifies the impact of any single contribution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info on Wokai:   &lt;a href="http://wokai.org/Events.action" target="_blank"&gt;http://wokai.org/Even...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wokai Boston is also on FB. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?pid=32680555&amp;amp;id=50201592#!/group.php?gid=290057067194&amp;amp;ref=ts" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve </member_name><member_id>5132502</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280531327000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279672053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wokai Boston - Drink for a Better World!</name><id>14163771</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280269800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/14163771/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/c/global_13817612.jpeg</photo_url></item>