<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*** Weather update 3/28/09 7:30 AM: &lt;b&gt;35% chance of rain just at start of hike between 9 and 10 AM -bring rain gear in case!&lt;/b&gt; Very good chance we may not see any rain or only brief rain. Cloudy with some sun! by 11 AM and later, temperatures start out at 44 F and go up to 53 F by end of hike. Winds low at 4 - 9 mph. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A 4 hr. loop hike of lower to moderate difficulty near the south-central shore area in this 1,200 acre sanctuary with 39 miles of very interesting trails. Exact trails to be cover will be determined depending on conditions. We will attempt to explore areas we haven't seen on past hikes here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trails have a unique blaze system (&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/reading_trailblazes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt; ). North-south trails are marked with a circle shaped blaze. Square or triangular trails weave back and forth connecting circle trails. Crossover trails that connect two circle trails of different colors are marked with an X of the color of the circle they lead to. Complicated?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a good chance of mud on the trail given the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go should have: &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots (sneakers not advised!) &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 9:30 AM at the parking area. &lt;b&gt;Parking may be limited so RSVP's are limited.&lt;/b&gt; We would finish up at about 1:30 PM and have lunch out if the group feels like socializing more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General directions (from a trail source):&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 58 off I-95&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 77 south (toward Guilford) about 0.5 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right (west) onto Route 1 and go 0.7 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Bear left onto Peddlers Rd. and drive 1.1 miles&lt;br /&gt;* Parking area on left just past Denison Dr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aproximate location/directions via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=540+Peddlers+Rd&amp;amp;city=guilford&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westwoods Reserve website (with trail maps):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westwoods interactive trail map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/inter_map.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guilford Land Trust (maintains Westwoods):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guilfordlandtrust.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guilfordla...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238873930000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237762785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Westwoods Reserve Trails in Guilford CT</name><id>10011314</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238247000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10011314/</event_url></item>