<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>East Foxboro Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02067</zip><lat>42.096439</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sharon Dog Park</name><city>Sharon</city><id>916696</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188057</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us for a playful free-for-all at Sharon Dog Park!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your friendly dog for a play date with some of his own kind at Sharon Dog Park, a beautiful location set back from the street and seperated by a half-mile or so of beautiful trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, this is an enclosed dog park, so your dog should be friendly and socialized, and, as a responsible owner, you should be paying attention, not just chit-chatting on the side-line :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That being said, this park is beautiful, fun, clean and full of great people who generally seem committed to keeping it that way!  Join us for some fun, and a tiring, well-exercized afternoon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Note* not every dog does well in this setting (and I'm not necessarily saying OURS), and not every person who brings their dog to the park is responsible (this is true of anywhere); it just means you should always pay attention and be responisble for your pooch while at the dog park, and be honest with yourself if this isn't the place for you (the NEBBC hosts many, many other meet-ups and events where the dogs are trail walking, leashed, or not confined by a fence).  Remember as well, that while many of today's bullies are very social and perfect playmates, IF there was an instance, and you're a bully owner, the finger is always pointing at you.  Let's just remind everyone to keep an eye, be responsible and represent as the responsible owners with wonderful dogs that we are :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, email me at justcassie101@comcast.net.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did I mention the NEBBC got a letter from Animal Planet?!  Check it out on our discussion board, or visit &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Bully-Breed-Club/pages/www.newenglandbullybreedclub.com"&gt;NEBBC&lt;/a&gt; to read it in full.  Can't wait to meet you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Punish the Deed, Not the Breed.&lt;br /&gt;Cassie-Leigh Stock&lt;br /&gt;President&lt;br /&gt;NEBBC&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The w</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272380762000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269412247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sharon Dog Park Play-Date!</name><id>cmwgnyngbhc</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272207600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/12976646/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/8/global_6966856.jpeg</photo_url></item>