<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Rogers Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.611411</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>866-BEER-MEN </phone><name>Cape Ann Brewing Co</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1479186</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.665247</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's go down to the Brewery in Gloucester, go for a tour then check out their menu for Linner (lunch early Dinner).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.5.11 UPDATE&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;span style="color : #263469"&gt;We would like to get a count of who will be joining us  for lunch/very early dinner after the tour.&amp;nbsp; If you do plan on staying for  lunch please update your RSVP on the site.&amp;nbsp;  Check out their menu at: www.capeannbrewing.com.&amp;nbsp; Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little information about the Cape Ann Brewing company:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Visit our brew house, enjoy a pint, and take a &lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt; tour! Taste our specialty craft beers on draft and brewed on premise. Growlers and growler refills are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beer whose bold flavor and character reflects the spirit and courage of the sailors of the North Atlantic fishing fleet, Fisherman's is a tribute to hard work and a salute to friendships that endure. Cape Ann Brewing Co. is an award-winning, family-owned, microbrewery in the heart of downtown Gloucester on Cape Ann, Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in the heart of Gloucester, the pub at The Cape Ann Brewing Company is the ideal place to have a beer with friends or make new ones.  At Cape Ann Brewing Co they use only the finest 2-Row Barley imported from throughout Europe.  This ensures that they are always putting out a consistently superior product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brewing award winning beer in the brewery in the back, it's served in a comfortable family friendly environment. Large German beer hall style tables, a bar shaped like the port side of a boat, rocking chairs and an array of games including Risk, Chess, Darts, and Biminy Ring Toss add to the welcoming atmosphere you'll always find at the brewery. We're a family owned and run business established in 2004. Hope to see you here. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, non-alcoholic drink options are:  &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Brown's Soda's - Rootbeer, Cream, Black Cherry, Cel-Ray, Diet Black Cherry, and Diet Cream Coke, Diet Coke, Iced Tea, Bottled Water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will update what time the tour will start remember to check back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hate to say it in April.  IF we get snow it may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you!  &lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302477262000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295814050000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brewery Tour in Gloucester</name><id>16155448</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302368400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/16155448/</event_url></item>