<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ski House</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03812</zip><lat>44.081680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>872006</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.231277</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets get a Summer event on the Somerville Snowboard Meetup. &amp;nbsp;I have been running an annual day trip on the Saco River for over 10 year. &amp;nbsp;This event typically gets 80 to 100 people and it is an absolute blast. &amp;nbsp;We stay overnight at the Wedeln Ski Club and take a school bus (20 min ride) to the river on Saturday morning. &amp;nbsp;We put in at Canal Bridge in Fryeburg Main and take out at Walkers Bridge. The total trip is just under seven miles but our mellow pace means we enjoy a full day (about 5 hours) on the river. Please feel free to RSVP on this site BUT to reserve your spot you MUST mail in the Registration form. This Meetup site is ONLY to show interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year we will have a pirate theme - imgine 50 canoes going down a river with pirate hats, plastic swords and water guns, yes that will be us. Cost includes canoe rental(including paddle, pfd), dinner(including Tuckerman beer on keg), lunch, breakfast, and a bus to and from the river. We also host a bonfire party at night with beer/wine cost included. Cost for the weekend ($85) does not include guest fees so please add $20 dollar a night for guests staying at the Wedeln House. I recommend guests stay both Friday and Saturday. Friday night is the best time to meet people. If you have your own canoe or kayak then cost for the weekend is only $55(no bus), there are no other substitutions or savings even if you plan to skip meals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mail checks and form by JUNE 12th to: Jennifer Vecchi {email tom_lane@harvard.edu to get full address} 3 important things:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Check should be made out to "Wedeln" - not me, not Jen, not Wedlens :).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Please use the Registration form (I will send if you respond "yes")&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. No LATE people Guest fees should be pay ahead of time (include $40 added to check): IMPORTANT - This is a huge weekend for the canoe outfitters on the Saco. If your check/letter is not postmarked by 6/10 it is highly likely that we will not have a spot for you. If you are late please do not show up with your own canoe and hope to "tag along", This trip is difficult to organize and supervise and having people who are "kind of with us but not really" can lead to problems. Thank You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE Here is the basic schedule - All times are aprox. and everything usually runs a bit late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FRIDAY July 8th - 7PM BYOB Social at the Wedeln Ski Club House&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SATURDAY July 9th 8 am to 9am Full breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:45am Buses arrive at Wedeln. 1pm - Lunch on the river: sandwiches and snackfood&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4pm Takeout: be patient it can take a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30pm - BBQ - steak tips, chicken lots of vegi and sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30pm - Bonfire, beer and wine included.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SUNDAY July 10th - optional day at Diana Bath Waterfall&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you or your friends do not have a canoe partner we will find you a paddle buddy. We pair several people up that morning and it can actually be more fun to be put in a canoe with people you do not know. No guest will get stuck alone (unless you want a single kayak). If we have an odd number of paddlers I will paddle solo.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come up Friday night, I will be at the house bar.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310264092000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Snowboarders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>snowboard-46</urlname><id>389975</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Somerville Snowboarding Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307123933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saco River Canoe weekend!</name><id>20850651</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310259600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/snowboard-46/events/20850651/</event_url></item>