<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;One hope with this meeting is to provide a safe space for nonreligious people who may not yet have had a chance to express their feelings in a supportive environment. We trust that all who attend will help us create an atmosphere of respect and dignity. Licensed psychologists will be available to support members of our community in case of extreme distress during the event. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We will meet at the Humanist Community at Harvard's offices at 12 Eliot Street in Harvard Square, before moving to the nearby John F. &lt;/span&gt;Kennedy Park. There, representatives of the Secular Coalition for Massachusetts, the Boston Atheists, the Humanist Community at Harvard, and other community and civic groups will speak briefly; after which, those in attendance will be invited to share their own responses to the events of the past few days. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

All are welcome to join us afterwards for dinner at Pizzeria Uno in Harvard Square. For more information about this program, please email community@bostonatheists.org. RSVP (appreciated but not required) at &lt;a href="http://bostonatheists.org/vigil" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonatheists.org/vigil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm a little worried that we could overwhelm the 12 Eliot Street location, so if you see a lot of people RSVP you might want to consider the chance that we'll have to meet at the park.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Josiah</member_name><member_id>3504482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366635691000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366466148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Humanist/Secular Community Memorial for Boston Marathon Bombings</name><id>115288192</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366578000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/115288192/</event_url></item>