<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>***Short notice*** Exploring more of this nice park &amp;amp; having free ice cream! Hiking about 3 miles of forest and ledge starting at the pond and going up a hillside to the Hop River Linear Trail (i.e. Rails-To-Trails in Vernon area) and on up into the hillside with some more hillside climbing to find a hidden soccer field in the woods. Then we loop back and eventually get to the very nice ledge over the Hop River Linear Trail for some very good views. We decend onto the Linear Trail and follow it until we eventually find the turnoff back into the park down by the stream. We'll expore some more trail at a leasurly pace until we end up back at the start. Generally, we'll hike portions major of the Blue/Yellow blazed trail that loops around the park &amp;amp; other blazed portions within the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot at 6:30 PM and head out to hike the trail. The hike should take about 1.5 hrs. and we should be done by 8:00 PM. ***I'll bring some ice cream and cups/cones we can have after at the pavillion!***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 8.5 miles of blazed trails in the park, as well as a playground, picnic pavilion, toilet facilities and a swimming beach. Portions of the park contain riuns of textile mills and an early trout hatchery and have been declared a national historic site. The park is heavily used for swimming, picnicking, hiking, x-country skiing, fishing, wild flower &amp;amp; wildlife observation and a scenic vista.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S. is leading on this one so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A park map can be found in the document link. Look at page 13.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.munic.state.ct.us/vernon/VRTT.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.munic.state.ct.us/vernon/VRTT.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.munic.stat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1148328013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Valley Falls Park in Vernon CT</name><id>4947041</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1148423400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4947041/</event_url></item>