<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>206 Thames Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02840</zip><lat>41.487916</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-845-9300</phone><name>The Gas Lamp Grille</name><city>Newport</city><id>1036457</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.315025</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The trivia is run differently here ... each round is 10 questions and all are answered on one sheet of paper at the same time - interesting, and it moves faster. We ruled! We took all 4 rounds and of course the grand total!&lt;br /&gt;As Adam said, we even beet the reigning champs by 6 points! 35 out of 41 possible points ... Not too shabby!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our prizes? 2 free appetizers, a pitcher of beer, and a free dessert. We will be using these this coming Monday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each and every one of us is filled with countless bits of useless knowledge - With our group being so diverse in ages, backgrounds, and tastes we really had it covered! Let's continue put them to good use! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gas Lamp has Pub Trivia every Monday, with drinks and gift certificates as prizes. Anything we win will be put toward drinks the next meetup there. Teams can be any size, so we can have one or more teams depending on the turnout. There's also 25 cent wings ... Yummmmmm! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can respond 'maybe' if you must, but it's good to have an accurate count of attendees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come have fun and meet some great people!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at 8:30 - just ask the hostess for the Newport Friends Meetup Group. I you have any trouble, call Mark at 631-433-5223.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>10739343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281478462000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newportfriends</urlname><id>429443</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>Newport Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280932487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>No Trivial Matter - We are the Champions!!!</name><id>14316314</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281402000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newportfriends/events/14316314/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/e/global_11672510.jpeg</photo_url></item>