<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Pearl St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.202263</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-843-0883</phone><name>Cafe Asiana</name><city>Braintree</city><id>359773</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.004460</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for a midweek dinner @ Cafe Asiana in South Braintree Square.  Your Event Organizers have been wanting to try eating here for awhile and would like to do so with the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group.  Co-workers and family members enjoy the cuisine.  With appetizers ranging from $4-$8 with entrees ranging from $7-$14 this makes this reasonably priced restaurant one worth trying new cuisine.  Please join us for a Mid-Week Asian and Thai Dinner at this cozy restaurant!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, September 26th @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Cafe Asiana&lt;br /&gt;25 Pearl Street&lt;br /&gt;South Braintree Square&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;781-843-0883&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp &lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Max of 10 people.&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Sorry, no guests due to the size of the restaurant.  &lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 12noon on Wednesday, September 26th &lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer: Angela and Maureen&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: In front of Cafe Asiana.  (This restaurant and entryway is small so please meet outside.  If it's raining then we will meet at our table and the Organizers will send out an email stating such that day.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WAIT LIST PROCEDURE FOR FULL EVENTS:&lt;br /&gt;**If the event fills up and you want to attend please:&lt;br /&gt;1. RSVP &amp;quot;No&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;2. State in your Comments &amp;quot;Please put me on the waitlist.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;3. When there is a cancellation the Event Organizer will change your RSVP from &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; in the order in which people RSVPed.  Since the RSVP list goes in order of most recent RSVP to earliest RSVP, the further down the list you are the better.  You will receive an email if/when a spot opens up and you are confirmed.  &lt;br /&gt;4. If, after being moved to the Active/&amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; RSVP list you are no longer able to attend you are asked to please update your RSVP w/in 72 hours if there are more people on the waitlist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please Note: You may change your RSVP from &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; up until the deadline (which is listed above).  If there is a waitlist we ask that you change your RSVP as early as possible to allow others the opportunity to attend.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  (Angela can pretty much get you from anywhere.  If you feel directions are needed from another direction please email her directly and she will update directions accordingly.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Cafe Asiana is located @ 25 Pearl Street directly across the street from McDonald's and directly in front of Rite Aid (formerly Brooks Pharmacy).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 17/Union Street.  Exit out of the Rotary heading towards South Braintree keeping the construction site on your right and the Motel 6 on your left.  Take a left at the first light onto Ivory Street, keeping the T on your right.  Go straight thru the 1st light.  Take a right at the 2nd light onto Pearl Street.  Go straight through the first light.  Go under the overpass and up the hill.  Once you get to the top of the hill Cafe Asiana will be on your left across from McDonald's.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: They have a tiny parking lot and limited on-street parking in front of the restaurant.  The good news is there is plenty of on-street parking in South Braintree Square as well as a Municipal Parking lot diagonally across the street to the left (when looking at) of The Farragut House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may also want to try maps.google.com or mapquest.com for an aerial map and/or door-to-door directions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191078318000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188523082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Asian and Thai Midweek Dinner</name><id>6272779</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190845800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/6272779/</event_url></item>