<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Folks-&lt;br /&gt;Happy New Year!&lt;br /&gt;I'm pleased to kick off the year with Mark McCurdy as our guest presenter.  See below for the summary of his talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  NEW NIGHT and NEW LOCATION!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark motivates the audience with his three principles for creating a successful future:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Volunteer strategically and consistently &lt;br /&gt;2. Make the lives of others better through your passion and your dreams will come true &lt;br /&gt;3. Ask for help, find a mentor and pursue your dreams &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional Topics Covered During Talk:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to leverage your volunteer or pro-bono experience into a job reality &lt;br /&gt;Six key strategies to find your dream job for a social impact &lt;br /&gt;Number one mistake people make when interviewing with nonprofits &lt;br /&gt;What are the hot careers in the nonprofit sector &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mark McCurdy is President of the Nonprofit Career Coach and founder of Jobs In Nonprofits, a boutique company helping job-seekers and nonprofit organizations fulfill their missions. As an inspiring leader, in-demand speaker, trainer and strategic nonprofit career coach, Mark has helped over 4000 professionals accelerate their nonprofit careers and has also assisted nonprofit organizations in unearthing skilled human capital. In the past 2 years, Mark has been a featured speaker at Brandeis University, Amnesty International USA, the University of Massachusetts, the Global Fund for Children, the World Resource Institute, Net Impact Boston, AmeriCorps, WINDS Networking, and the Jericho Road Project. Mark gives presentations on careers in nonprofits, career transitions, and key strategies for finding a dream job that will maximize one’s “social impact” in the nonprofit world. Lean more at www.thenonprofitcareercoach.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; NEW LOCATION: &lt;br /&gt;(Thanks, Hardeep!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Project Place&lt;br /&gt;1145 Washington Street&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02118&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A 6 story brick building across from Dunkin Donuts.  First floor has a restaurant  (Meyers + Chang).  There is a Silver Line stop (Washington Street) right in front and New England medical center is down the street, about a 5 minute walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monique Morimoto Flaherty</member_name><member_id>8025083</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264118859000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262810592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How Mission-Focused Volunteer Work Can Advance Your Career</name><id>12243385</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263945600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/12243385/</event_url></item>