<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Okay, its not officially a lake, but the Chestnut Hill Reservoir still very pretty at sunset. Meet in front of the Dunkin Donuts in Cleveland Circle at 6:30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Considered a nineteenth-century masterpiece of engineering, urban planning and landscape design, the Chestnut Hill Reservation is listed on the National Register of Historic Places and is a City of Boston Landmark.  Today, visitors can jog, walk their dog (please keep on leash and remove waste), or just stroll around the historic reservoir.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The history of the Chestnut Hill Reservation, which includes the Chestnut Hill Reservoir and surrounding public land, is closely tied to the development of Boston's water supply system. As the city's population grew over the course of the nineteenth century, so did its need for a steady supply of safe drinking water and an effective means of fighting fires. What would eventually become an extensive network of reservoirs, gatehouses, pumping stations, distribution pipes and other infrastructure traces its origins to the 1820s, when a committee was appointed to study the City's water supply needs and recommend solutions. It was not until the 1840s, however, that construction on the system began, with the erection of a 14.5 mile-long aqueduct linking Long Pond (now Lake Cochituate) in Natick with the Brookline Reservoir. This project was completed in 1848.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238858700000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237548557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset on the lake walk</name><id>9995027</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238625000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9995027/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/5/global_7752725.jpeg</photo_url></item>