<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Londonderry Commons</address_2><address_1>44 Nashua Road (rte 102)</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03053</zip><lat>42.800994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-434-2660</phone><name>Whippersnappers</name><city>Londonderry</city><id>524780</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.432482</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mama Kicks has been around for quite a while and she gets the place hopping, this restuarant has excellant food, great service and there is also a lounge with a few huge TV's for viewing. The parking lot is huge so plenty of space. All we need is people to come out and join in a fun filled night out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ginette I am throwing this gathering cause you are such a sweety, save room for dessert!!! Yes a Birthday cake and ballons!!! Its your celebration, I know I cannot keep things a secret cause you are a member of every group,LOL...So come out and join us all you fun folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mama Kicks is New Hampshire's # 1 Party Band. Four talented musicians performing a diverse mix of classic rock, blues and simply great dance tunes. Featuring Lisa Guyer, arguably the most talented female vocalist around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be another Meet Up group joining us, I will be hosting for them as well, the more the merrier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Party will start at 7pm for dinner and the band starts at 9 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please put in your RSVP if you plan to have dinner by 1/22/11- 5 pm, there are no more Maybe options but you can always include it in your reply, but be firm about dinner because I am making reservations.&lt;br /&gt;I will have Meet Up signs posted on the tables when you enter the dining area, and I will inform the hostess where you can find us just mention Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also ask that you be responsible for your own service checks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>978-857-6626(eva) </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>eva</member_name><member_id>4457040</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Natalie</member_name><member_id>5909042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295811785000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293778118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>   Rock  on to "Mama Kicks" Dinner/Dancing/Happy Birthday Ginette!</name><id>15866807</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295740800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/15866807/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/2/global_20529442.jpeg</photo_url></item>