<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well, it was bound to happen sooner or later, folks...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You voted and the Org Team, working with Jaime (Dudley's Mom), who suggested it, went to work to put together an event at the &amp;quot;F&amp;quot; restaurant of your choice: Fifty-Three South. Only problem was, Jaime couldn't reach an actual person there, and they weren't returning her phone calls. Finally, Mike stopped by in person, only to be greeted by a huge &amp;quot;For Lease&amp;quot; sign in the parking lot of an empty restaurant!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, you read right! &amp;quot;Fifty-Three&amp;quot; has gone South!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On to plan &amp;quot;B&amp;quot;! (For the detail-oriented among us, that is technically plan &amp;quot;F(b)&amp;quot;.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;a href="http://www.firesidegrille.com/index" target="_blank"&gt;Fireside Grille&lt;/a&gt; in Middleboro came up just one vote shy of first place in our poll. Based on that and the uniformly good reviews of our members who have eaten there, we are happy to make the Fireside our &amp;quot;F&amp;quot; venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open as the Fireside Grille since 1983, the Fireside is an established favorite located just off the Middleboro Rotary on Route 18. The spacious dining room features the warm tones of wood and stone, while the menu offers classic New England comfort food, with the usual smattering of Italian influences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the kind of evening that our members typically enjoy: a time for good food and relaxed conversation. We are looking forward to our visit to the Fireside and hope you'll join us there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fireside Grille&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;30 Bedford St., Middleboro&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, July 30 @ 7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; S2.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Tuesday, July 29 @ 5:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions: (Credit to the &lt;a href="http://www.firesidegrille.com/directions" target="_blank"&gt;Fireside website&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/b&gt; The fireside Grille is located on Route 18, just south of the Middleboro Rotary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drivers coming from the Quincy/Braintree/Weymouth area can simply take Route 18 South, but will probably prefer to take Route 24 South to Exit 14A (495 South), then take Exit 5 to Route 18 North. Look for the Fireside on your left just before the rotary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drivers coming from the Plymouth area can simply take Route 44 West to the Middleboro Rotary, then take the third right (Route 18 South) off the Rotary and look for the Fireside on their right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drivers coming from Cape Cod or Wareham may take Route 495 North to Exit 5, taking a right off the ramp onto Route 18 North. Look for the Fireside on your left just before the Rotary.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation notes the names 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217908247000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216735280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at the Fireside!</name><id>8388419</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217460600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8388419/</event_url></item>