<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Ash St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>42.997272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-669-6144</phone><name>Currier Museum of Art</name><city>Manchester</city><id>761744</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.455039</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It been over two years since we've been to the Currier Museum, so time to go again.  On Saturdays, admission is free until noon, so we are planning to meet there at 11:00 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Currier Museum:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Currier Museum of Art is an internationally renowned art museum located in Manchester, New Hampshire. The Currier features European and American paintings, decorative arts, photographs and sculpture, including works by Picasso, Monet, O'Keeffe, Wyeth, and LeWitt with exhibitions, tours, and programs year-round. The museum also offers tours of the Frank Lloyd Wright-designed Zimmerman House -- reservations required. The Currier Museum Art Center offers studio workshops and classes for children and adults.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Currier Museum of Art is accredited by the American Association of Museums.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.currier.org/history.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.currier.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Now on View:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Homer to Hopper: American Watercolor Masterworks from the Currier Museum of Art&lt;br /&gt;Organized by the Currier Museum of Art&lt;br /&gt;March 6, 2010 - June 7, 2010  (11:30-12:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This exhibition features extraordinary works by such nationally known masters as Winslow Homer, Maurice Prendergast, Childe Hassam, Rockwell Kent, Edward Hopper, Charles Burchfield, John Marin, Charles Sheeler, Stuart Davis, and Andrew Wyeth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drawn from the impressive collection the Currier has built over its 80-year history, these watercolors have not been exhibited as a group for two decades because of the fragile nature of the medium. The exhibition includes about seventy five works that trace the history of watercolor over the last 175 years. A strong representation of work by important New Hampshire artists ranges from portraits by nineteenth-century itinerant painter Joseph H. Davis to landscapes by New Hampshire Living Treasure award winner John Hatch and abstract compositions by contemporary painter and sculptor Varujan Boghosian.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Hampshire Art and Artists&lt;br /&gt;Organized by the Currier Museum of Art&lt;br /&gt;February 11, 2010 - June 7, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since its founding 80 years ago the Currier has been committed to exhibiting and acquiring the work of New Hampshire artists. The collections are rich in examples of art that depicts the people and places of New Hampshire, many created by artists, of national and international reputations. Selected from the 1,000 art works in the collection that were created by 156 New Hampshire artists this exhibit will celebrate the state’s vibrant arts community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The presentation will include works by painters like James Aponovich and John Hatch, furniture makers&lt;br /&gt;Jon Brooks, Terry Moore, and Jere Osgood, ceramic artists Mary and Ed Scheier and Viveka and Otto&lt;br /&gt;Heino. Explore the state’s cultural heritage through the Currier’s New Hampshire collections!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.currier.org/nowonview.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.currier.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Car Pool From Nashua:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the tennis courts parking lot at the corner of Candlewood Park and Westgate Crossing in Nashua no later than 10:15 AM.  To get to Westgate Crossing, from Rout 3 take Exit 5W and stay on Route 111 (Hollis Street).  Westgate Crossing is about 1.5 miles west of route 3 on the left, right after you pass a nursing home.  Candlewood Park is the first exit on the right.  Note, if you want to carpool, please indicate it in the RSVP.  I don't plan to come back to Nashua until after the dinner at 5:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in front of the Currier Museum.  Wearing a MEET-UP Badge.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274743718000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273028494000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Currier Museum of Art </name><id>13389203</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274540400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/13389203/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/b/global_3433051.jpeg</photo_url></item>