<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Bruegger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>972928</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121038</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I want to give everyone time to read this month's selection, as it is a little longer than what we normally read. &amp;nbsp;However, it has gotten great reviews and I'm hoping everyone will enjoy it. &amp;nbsp;The book is 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Unbroken: A World War II Story of Survival, Resilience, and Redemption&lt;/span&gt; by Laura Hillenbrand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;"From Laura Hillenbrand, the bestselling author of&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0345465083/"&gt;Seabiscuit&lt;/a&gt;, comes&amp;nbsp;Unbroken, the inspiring true story of a man who lived through a series of catastrophes almost too incredible to be believed. In evocative, immediate descriptions, Hillenbrand unfurls the story of Louie Zamperini--a juvenile delinquent-turned-Olympic runner-turned-Army hero. During a routine search mission over the Pacific, Louie&amp;rsquo;s plane crashed into the ocean, and what happened to him over the next three years of his life is a story that will keep you glued to the pages, eagerly awaiting the next turn in the story and fearing it at the same time. You&amp;rsquo;ll cheer for the man who somehow maintained his selfhood and humanity despite the monumental degradations he suffered, and you&amp;rsquo;ll want to share this book with everyone you know."&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you all in August!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachel Greene</member_name><member_id>11862196</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314566399000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310604556000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August Book Club</name><id>25670441</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314561600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/25670441/</event_url></item>