<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>You heard right.. nothing but variations and varieties of vegan cheesecakes! I'd love for everyone to post what kind they plan on bringing so we don't have too many duplicates.. although there is never too much of any kind :) Feel free to bring your favorite wine too.. and we'll have juices for the kiddies and age challenged of course. As of now this will have to happen at my place unless anyone else has a better space for it (if so let me know ASAP!). Hope no one is allergic to animals!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm also considering a meet up just for adults so we don't have to censor our game answers lol Let me know what you think..  We also need to get back out to the farm and I can schedule a visit for any weekend. Also don't forget to add your awesome recipes to the message board folder for them.  Feed back and suggestions are always welcome!!! Thanks for a great time and I hope to have a repeat next time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions you can reach me at 508-459-1074 or you can email me as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all soon!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dreads, glasses and a whole lot of veganess ;)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309486802000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231095971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Cheese"cake and wine (or grape juice) party!!</name><id>9441456</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233511200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/9441456/</event_url></item>