<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>840 West Middle Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.780023</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurel Marsh Trail</name><city>Manchester</city><id>227925</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.567810</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well, discretion is the better part of valor, so I'm going to change the hike.  Forecast for today is for rain all day -- may be some breaks around the time we were going to start hiking, but then heavy rain is supposed to return.  This trail is already a wet one, we don't want to be out there in the rain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, I'm rescheduling the hike for tomorrow -- Sunday, October 28 at 2:00 PM.  Same place.  Please update your RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that parking is limited to maybe a dozen cars at this trailhead, so if we get the number of people who RSVP'd for Saturday, some will need to park on the street or across the street at Cheney Tech.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the hike details again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll hike the 3-mile or so Laurel Marsh Trail in Manchester.  Meet in the parking lot, which is just off from Exit 60 from I-84, turn toward Manchester and lot is on the right.  This is a good hike for this time of year because it's too buggy in the summer!  Meet at 1:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is an event for the Hartford Heights Tall Club, and we are extending the invitation for our hiking meetup friends to join us.  Gloria will be leading this hike and questions should be addressed to her.  Cell phone is 371-7125.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please don't RSVP &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; and take up a spot unless you really expect to be able to attend!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the town website's description of the trail:&lt;br /&gt;Laurel Marsh Trail (3.52 mile loop) Park at Laurel Marsh lot on south side of Middle Turnpike West (Route 44) just east of I-84, Exit 60, follow trail to right toward river, cross bridge over river, along boardwalk, turn left on trail along marsh near I-84, up along hillside, downstream under three I-84 bridges, up onto paved bikeway, cross river on third highway bridge, under three bridges upstream, leave bikeway and take trail upstream through woods, along I-384 path, then left into woods over two long boardwalks, upstream along river, up brook path, left across brook on road toward sewer plant, left downstream along Hop Brook, around stonedust loop path either way to starting point. Long, mostly easy walk, many wet areas, a few hills, great marsh views, water birds, mature forest, giant white pines, beautiful mountain laurel, need boots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193767811000</updated><rating><average>4.36000013351</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191755124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Laurel Marsh Trail - change of date and time!</name><id>6504430</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193594400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6504430/</event_url></item>