<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey guys and gals! We are going out to Springfield for a Friday night adventure again! Last time we took that city by storm and we all had an awesome time! The guys and girls met a bunch of new people and basically had a blast. We are definitely ready to do it again. We will probably meet up at Springfield at 10:00p.m. The Salty Dog in Springfield is where we will be meeting up at and then probably bouncing to other venues nearby afterwards. We are trying to get some awesome deals from the nightlife establishments down there and it all depends on the participation of our members.&lt;br /&gt; Like before, when we had a tremendous participation we got in for free! The complimentary alcohol just made it soooo much better! But yours truly will make something happen. Just remember we are not a dating meetup where we promote only dating inside of the group. We are wingmen and wingwomen, and the name should explain it all. Any questions feel free to hit me up via email. For all our new members, realize that our group takes partying to a whole new level of fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. Bring your friends, girlfriends, sisters, and cousins. It is always more fun to be a part of a huge party than one person of a two man/woman team.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email me (Ace) at russian1985@yahoo.com or call/text Red Man 860-919-9782.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249870378000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249065488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Adventure in Springfield!</name><id>11002757</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249696800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/11002757/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/4/global_9957156.jpeg</photo_url></item>