<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you were not able to go when Aime hosted, here is another chance. I like going on Fridays at Cinestudio because they have an optional after-movie discussion led by one of the professors. From the Cinestudio website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(UK, 2012) Directed by Lasse Hallström. Screenplay by Simon Beaufoy, based on the novel by Paul Torday. Cast: Emily Blunt, Ewan McGregor, Amr Waked, Kristen Scott Thomas. 107 min.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The screenwriter of Slumdog Millionaire (Simon Beaufoy) and the director of Chocolat (Lasse Hallström) have collaborated on a romantic comedy for grownups with a taste for the winningly absurd. A Yemeni sheikh (Amr Waked) who’s fallen under the spell of fly-fishing in Scotland dreams up a crazy plan: to stock his own (very dry) country with 10,000 North Atlantic salmon. Hoping for a diplomatic coup, the British government gives the green light, but it falls to a skeptical civil servant (Ewan McGregor) and the sheikh’s optimistic assistant (Emily Blunt) to make the impossible a reality. “Makes use of pink-fleshed vertebrates as the inspiration for musings on love and life, faith and patience - and the courage to go against the flow.” - Amy Biancolli, San Francisco Chronicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fish​ingintheyemen.c​om/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.fish​ingintheyemen.c​om/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336866703000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335150018000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Salmon Fishing in the Yemen" @ Cinestudio</name><id>61710972</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336778100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/61710972/</event_url></item>