<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mount Auburn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>3900472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From the Facebook event page (&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/259661027493389/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/events/259661027493389/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Puerto Rico’s Mijo de la Palma has extended their Northeast Tour and will present two encore performances in Cambridge, MA and Hartford, CT as well as presentations in New Jersey and Washington DC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, Dec. 28 • 8pm • $10 sliding scale • Democracy Center, Harvard Square&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Far from being an ensemble, Mijo is more about a metamorphous crossing of people. Looking back at years of musical encounters with diverse people, Mijo resembles a Socratic circle that refuses a definition. Fusión Jíbara has been the tagline adopted by many but it seems to be more complex than that. Fusión Jíbara resembles one of the many aspects that has characterized Mijo, for their ability to merge creative energies as a whole. Not surprisingly, what seems to endure is the Jíbaro vibe. As Mijo embarks on their US tour, Canto E’ Jíbaro, they hope to find new ways to feed their soul as they try to bring the same to those who experience it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melvin Lopez Rivera: guitar / main vocals &lt;br /&gt;

 Adaliz Ortiz Toro: harmonies &lt;br /&gt;

 Surprise Guest Artists&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mijo De La Palma did it with style tonight. How did they make that look so easy? …and to a packed house! ” – Mission Cultural Center for the Latino Arts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Por fin pude ver a Mijo De La Palma. Ellos te agarra por los pies y te arrastran a un monte que sólo ellos conocen. Antes del primer acorde menor, te quitan los zapatos y te llevan de la mano. Pero cuando se van, te dejan pa que bajes por tu cuenta y descalzo.” – Joshua Cortes, Río Piedras, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nada sabía yo de este jíbaro de Puerto Rico que canta como si hubiese nacido en el Puerto de Santa María, crecido en el delta del Mississippi y abrevado en los pantanos del África negra.” - Jose Ángel González&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show starts at 8pm, and if people are up to it, afterward we can go somewhere nearby in Harvard Sq. for food/drinks/extra conversation. I attended the last show in November, the music was great, and very passionate. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kenny Hyde</member_name><member_id>11634784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356792656000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355288995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mijo de La Palma Encore Performance in Cambridge, MA</name><id>95043982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356739200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/95043982/</event_url></item>