<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our next meeting will be on Tuesday, September 25th from 7-9 in the Senior Center Lounge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come with your advice, triumphs, challenges, and testimonials for certain treatments and health care providers. This group has a wealth of knowledge that can help all of us in our recovery from Fibromyalgia. Try to make it even if you don't feel like it, you'll be glad you did. Sharing your pain with those that understand can give you the push you need to take the next step in your recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always donations are needed to defray my meetup and meeting costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to you in a few weeks and remember you can call me at anytime with questions at 623-251-7547 or 617-943-5570.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betsy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS As always I am happy to set up appointments with anyone interested in trying the LaserTouch One for their Fibromyalgia or any pain condition.  A demo takes less than 10 minutes and you'll know right away if it's an option for your pain.  I use the laser on a daily basis for my feet and neck and low back pain and it helps more than I can express here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still have samples of Lifewave Pain Patches as well. They are powerful photon based patches that stimulate pain relief without any medication or substance entering the body.  I no longer sell them but they are such a miracle product you owe it to yourself to try them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can come early to the meeting to demonstrate either product or you can come to my office by appointment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Upstairs in the Senior Center Lounge, elevator to right on first floor through double doors</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Timmerman</member_name><member_id>3507700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348698399000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People With Fibromyalgia</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fibromyalgia-301</urlname><id>586410</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>The Reading Fibromyalgia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346273405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Have a meeting</name><id>79959632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348614000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fibromyalgia-301/events/79959632/</event_url></item>