<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;Just in time for the holidays, The Brattle Theater presents Divorce, Italian Style and Seduced and Abandoned, two Italian  comedies from the 1960's from director Pietro Germi. We'll meet and discuss after Divorce. Since this is a double-feature, you may be interested in catching the 5:00 PM screening of  Seduced as well. Please indicate so when you RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIVORCE ITALIAN STYLE (screens at 7:15) , starring Marcello Mastroianni, won the Oscar for best screenwriting and  best comedy at Cannes. It has some of the richest, most beautiful black and white photography ever put on film. [It's] very inventive, it really moves as few films do, with a deftness and the driest, most cutting wit.&amp;quot; - Martin Scorsese &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Germi gave a new impetus to Italian comedy: he nudged the genre from farce to satire, from the comedy of hysterical overplaying to the wit of underreaction. It remains a terrific entertainment, a European corollary to Preston Sturges.&amp;quot; - Dave Kehr &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1960's Catholic Italy, divorce is illegal, but a crime of passion, ahh... that's another story: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the funniest pictures the Italians have sent along.  &lt;br /&gt;This nifty frolic about a bored Sicilian baron who plots to force his wife to compromise herself with another man so he can honorably shoot her and then marry a 16-year-old girl, the director and star have accomplished that very difficult and delicate thing of making murder seem an admirable ambition and the would-be murderer seem a sympathetic gent, all without violating reason or causing really serious moral offense. To be sure, the assumption is outrageous, at least, to a non-Latin it is, that the &amp;quot;code of honor&amp;quot; might be craftily manipulated in order to &amp;quot;divorce&amp;quot; one's spouse. But Mr. Germi has managed to establish his thesis so well, with a wonderfully droll illumination of the slippery characters of the community, and he has worked out his plot so deftly, with his tongue obviously in his cheek, that the whole arrangement seems not only respectable but also devilishly ingenious.   NY Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEDUCED AND ABANDONED  (screens at 5:00)&lt;br /&gt;again features the beautiful Stefania Sandrelli, this time as Agnese, a young woman who loses her virginity to her sister's lascivious fiancé. With his family's reputation hanging by a thread, Agnese's father sets out on an increasingly desperate campaign to restore his honor, resorting to shotgun weddings, kidnapping, attempted murder, and emergency dental work in the process.  Brattle Description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Germis' Seduced and Abandoned was the follow-up to his international sensation Divorce Italian Style, and in many ways it's even more audacious - a rollicking yet raw series of escalating comic calamities ... Merciless and mirthful, Seduced and Abandoned skewers Sicilian social customs and pompous patriarchies with a sly, devilish grin.&amp;quot; - The Criterion Collection &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone know of a good Italian restaurant in Harvard Sq where we could quietly discuss these films? Probably not, and so as is our custom, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after Divorce, Italian style and then its off to a local non-paesano restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;br /&gt;Tom &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198542106000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196467916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Divorce Italian Style +1 at The Brattle</name><id>6833072</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198368900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6833072/</event_url></item>