<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Day St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02145</zip><lat>42.395584</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.0552</phone><name>Sacco's Bowl Haven</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669347</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>First off, sorry for the late notice on this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next long story short, we do not have the classroom at Lesley/The Porter Exchange this week.  So in lieu of our usual, your organizers have a planned some alternate excitement.  An Incubator Social!!!  Complete with ice cream!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at 7:30 right out side Davis Square T station in the open area in front of J.P. Licks.  Then we'll grab some ice cream, chillax, and even do some improv in the fresh air!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Around 8:30 we'll walk the whopping two minutes over to Sacco's Bowl Haven: a quaint, family owned old school candlepin bowling alley!!!  No worries if you have never been candlepin bowling before, it's not like regular bowling, you'll learn, and get the swing of things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll play a couple of games and with this weeks donation money, we'll order some pizzas for you all to munch down on! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to a coupon for a free shoe rental on the their website.  Print it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.saccosbowlhaven.com/specials.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.saccosbowl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And it's a mere $3 a game which is petty cash compared to most the bowling alleys in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you all there.  And def come out even if you don't want to go bowling.  This night's all about relaxing and having a good time.  And feel free to meet us over at Sacco's too.  Day street is right across the street from JP Licks, a block or two left of Somerville theater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember it's your leader extraordinaire, Barbara's, last few days in Boston, so come out and give her a good send off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No worries though, she'll be back to visit.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock on!  and out everyone!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the goofy looking bloke.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217720465000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217428150000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>!!! Incubator Social !!! Candelpin Bowling at Sacco's Bowl Haven in Davis Square</name><id>8440886</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217547000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/8440886/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>