<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today: A chance of showers, mainly before 10am. Cloudy, then gradually becoming mostly sunny, with a high near 62. Calm wind becoming southeast between 6 and 9 mph. Chance of precipitation is 30%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But bring some Pot Luck food &amp;amp; something for the Boil Up and wood for the after party fire. Leave it in you car till we have chosen a place (depends on the conditions outside and options). SO FAR IT'S LOOKING LIKE A PRIVATE RESIDENCE IN WINDSOR.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Reference to concerns on parking:&lt;br /&gt;Hi  Everyone&lt;br /&gt;Parking isnt a problem there..but you will not be very close like in the summer events......in general at the scantic for this event&lt;br /&gt;as you go down rte 190 to the intersection of 192/ South maple enfield,&lt;br /&gt;Follow the south maple to either Southview rd or Powder Ridge or Dust House Rd, most of the time there are people that direct you to park in some place nearby, its just a short walk from there..&lt;br /&gt;When i went a few years ago i parked on Powder Ridge rd.&lt;br /&gt;All total i guessed maybe 150 people maybe more but its not like its a Rock concert..most of the people were kids and familys so maybe only 100 cars on all the streets nearby.&lt;br /&gt;Or i think if that many people are there,  just park at South View or on South maple closer to rte 190.. from rte 190 its only a quarter mile, and any other location its closer..Pretty simple..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im not sure how long we will stay at the Scantic and then go to the after party somewhere else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok lemme send this out to the group.&lt;br /&gt;see ya soon..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Location that is prime for so many things, last summer it was a place for us to play in the water, tubing,  and have a barbie -q a few times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This time of year only the brave will go in the water, and we are only just going to watch them and cheer the racers on... They will go in the water for us..but valiantly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scantic River Water Temp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 10 th, 39.2 degrees F&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 15th - 39.3 degrees F&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 26th - 42.1 degrees F&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is also listed on my other site(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CT-Recreational-Sea-Kayakers/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Forever-Young/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The actual race starts about 11:30 to 12:00 pm and it takes a while to go the 5 miles, but with a good current and their paddle speed, its not long before some start to finish, while waiting its good to check out the area and just converse..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So closer to the date the event will be updated on weather, water conditions and if the event is canceled by the promoters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im thinking we MAY stay after the people leave and make this the Pot Luck area..but again..its dependent on the weather..an Alternate site will be available if it doesn't seem good enough here..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check back closer to the event day.. Too soon now to predict..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The site to check for the promoters updated info also is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check the site since there are some good pics...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.scanticspringsplash.com/"&gt;http://www.scanticspr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2009 Race Date:   Saturday, March 28 2009 for the 18th annual race&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt; WE will be UPSTREAM from the Finish line near the South Maple Street Bridge ON THE RAPIDS AREA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Be a Fan, Donate a Can, &lt;br /&gt;Let's Fill Up the Canoe for The Enfield Food Shelf!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Be a part of giving a canoe load of food to the Enfield Food Shelf.&lt;br /&gt;Point Series:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * The New England Canoe Racing Association and&lt;br /&gt;      The New England Downriver Championship Series&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      American Canoe Association (ACA)&lt;br /&gt;      New England Regional Down River Championship Races&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The river racers will be paddling &lt;br /&gt; 5 Miles with 1 mandatory Portage from Somersville, CT to Powder Hollow Barn in Hazardville. 3 Class II Rapids, including the popular finish area. Lots of spectators.&lt;br /&gt;THAT WILL BE SOME OF US..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thats where we will meet, near the bridge or where we have had all our summer events in this great location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving and parking directions DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 91 to Parking lot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 47 East. Go eastbound 2.7 miles on RT-190 (Hazard Avenue) from Enfield to Hazardville.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At intersection of RT-190 and North/South Maple (RT 192)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~&amp;gt; turn right (South) onto South Maple.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 84 via RT-190 to Parking and HQ: 1: Take the RT-190 West Exit and follow RT-190 West through Stafford Springs and Somers to Hazardville (Intersection R-190 and RT-192).&lt;br /&gt;2: At stoplight, turn left on to South Maple.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS apx 1 - 100 South Maple, Hazardville (Enfield) ct 06082 for a GPS (Just follow the directions above).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may have to park on a street near the finish instead of the parking lot since the kayaker's have those spaces near the barn.. There will be traffic directors in the area, just follow their instructions and walk a little ways.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Flourecent Orange Hat&amp; 6 foot Orange Pole near Rapids Upstream from Finish Line</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240767735000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235668770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RIVER RATS-Cheer em on  (Racers) @ Scantic River SPLASH Event &amp; Barbie-Q Nearby </name><id>9830087</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238256000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/9830087/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/7/global_4907255.jpeg</photo_url></item>