<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Lexington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.412483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 547-5655</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739900</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.233269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jacob Jankowski says: "I am ninety.  Or ninety-three.  One or the other."  At the beginning of &lt;em&gt;Water for Elephants&lt;/em&gt;,  he is living out his days in a nursing home, hating every second of it.   His life wasn't always like this, however, because Jacob ran away and  joined the circus when he was twenty-one.  It wasn't a romantic,  carefree decision, to be sure.  His parents were killed in an auto  accident one week before he was to sit for his veterinary medicine exams  at Cornell.  He buried his parents, learned that they left him nothing  because they had mortgaged everything to pay his tuition, returned to  school, went to the exams, and didn't write a single word.  He walked  out without completing the test and wound up on a circus train.  The  circus he joins, in Depression-era America, is second-rate at best.   With Ringling Brothers as the standard, Benzini Brothers is far down the  scale and pale by comparison.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Water for Elephants&lt;/em&gt; is the  story of Jacob's life with this circus.  Sara Gruen spares no detail in  chronicling the squalid, filthy, brutish circumstances in which he  finds himself.  The animals are mangy, underfed or fed rotten food, and  abused.  Jacob, once it becomes known that he has veterinary skills, is  put in charge of the "menagerie" and all its ills.  Uncle Al, the circus  impresario, is a self-serving, venal creep who slaps people around  because he can.  August, the animal trainer, is a certified paranoid  schizophrenic whose occasional flights into madness and brutality often  have Jacob as their object.  Jacob is the only person in the book who  has a handle on a moral compass and as his reward he spends most of the  novel beaten, broken, concussed, bleeding, swollen and hungover.  He is  the self-appointed Protector of the Downtrodden, and... he falls in love  with Marlena, crazy August's wife.  Not his best idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  most interesting aspect of the book is all the circus lore that Gruen  has so carefully researched.  She has all the right vocabulary:   grifters, roustabouts, workers, cooch tent, rubes, First of May, what  the band plays when there's trouble, Jamaican ginger paralysis, life on a  circus train, set-up and take-down, being run out of town by the  "revenooers" or the cops, and losing all your hooch. There is one  glorious passage about Marlena and Rosie, the bull elephant, that truly  evokes the magic a circus can create.  It is easy to see Marlena's and  Rosie's pink sequins under the Big Top and to imagine their perfect  choreography as they perform unbelievable stunts.  The crowd loves  it--and so will the reader. The ending is absolutely ludicrous and  really quite lovely.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be the group of people talking at the same time and enjoying it!!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303433278000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>We should read the book before the movie comes out!!</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301019637000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Water for Elephants</name><id>17048719</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303428600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/17048719/</event_url></item>