<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you sometimes find it hard to communicate your best qualities to someone you're attracted to, even though you know deep down that you really are an interesting person?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;When you go out to social gatherings (such as a meetup event), do you find yourself wishing that people would see through your shyness and take the time to discover the &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;real&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; you that's hiding inside?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you answered &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to either of these questions, then you're going to love this.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;In this unique event, you'll gain a critical skill that will help you become more interesting and attractive to others.  When you have this skill, you'll be able to experience the kind of effortless connections that you've been hoping for when you go out to socialize.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;******************************************************&lt;br /&gt;THE SECRET IS IN THE PERSONAL STORIES YOU SHARE WITH OTHERS&lt;br /&gt;******************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;It's not enough to say to people, &amp;quot;I have this quality and that quality.&amp;quot;  Listing facts about yourself in a conversation is boring and usually compels people to find someone else to talk to.  The way to convey your personality to others is through the stories you tell, and not by merely communicating data.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;But you and I know it's not that simple.  The trouble with telling our personal stories is that:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We sometimes don't know what to say, where to start, or how to even say it.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don't know how to tell them in a concise and interesting manner.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don't know if people are even interested in hearing our stories.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's what this special workshop is all about.  You'll discover how to talk to people in a way that lets them get to know the real you, while also being interesting and attractive in a social environment.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;******************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;******************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The single most important thing you must say before you tell a story that will instantly capture people's attention and make them want to listen to what comes next.  Once you master this technique, your conversations will become effortless and natural.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We'll do a simple exercise that will mine your brain for the gold that's trapped within, and help you discover how many interesting personal stories you really do have.  These are stories that will bring people closer and make them want to spend more time with you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The secret structure of a good conversational story, and how to use it to instantly make your stories more interesting.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We'll do a fun drill from improv comedy that will train your mind to effortlessly keep a conversation going.  Your stories will flow smoothly and naturally in every conversation as a result.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;By the end of this workshop, you will have at least one story that is ready to use in any social environment, and that will help people get to know the real you.  Plus, you'll also possess a proven formula for coming up with an unlimited number of stories on your own.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  We will start the seminar promptly at 3:30 and run until 5:30.  Please plan on arriving at 3:00pm so you have time to settle in and network with the other students.  You never know who you'll meet that can become a new friend and add a lot of value to your life.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to the first 40 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings often sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, September 27th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:00pm for registration and personal networking.  We will start promptly at 3:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256499609000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253300795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conversational Storytelling - Help Others Get To Know The Real You</name><id>11407548</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254079800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/11407548/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/7/global_10766055.jpeg</photo_url></item>