<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45-55 Union Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.361576</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Bell In Hand Tavern</name><city>Boston</city><id>1964861</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057068</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So, the Bell in Hand has started a new trivia night on Wednesdays.&amp;nbsp; :D WHOOO HOO!! Here is a recent description sent to us from the Boston Event Guide folks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span&gt;We are starting a weekly trivia night on Wednesdays at Bell in Hand. The winning team or individual gets their bar tab taken care of up to $50 and a gift certificate to Bell in Hand. We are working on building the night up and creating a grand prize contest. The event is free with chips &amp;amp; salsa, low cost drinks and low cost food."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 A lover of all things trivia related, I figure I'll give it a whirl this next Wednesday, October 5th.&amp;nbsp; Trivia starts @ 8pm but I'll be there sooner than that to get myself situated.&amp;nbsp; I'll try to save seats/spots but NO GUARANTEE!! If you show up at 7:59pm don't complain that there's nowhere to sit, no tables, etc. I'm not putting an attendee limit on this as we'll just break up into teams if needed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bell in Hand offers great menu items, and as seen above, free chips and salsa! I'll post more deets as the date nears.&amp;nbsp; I hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: Everyone is responsible for their own food and drink.&amp;nbsp; MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is cross-listed with Social Fun.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UPDATE 10/5/2011 4:45pm:&amp;nbsp; Trivia will be held on the side of the bar/restaurant with the STAGE so please look for me there.&amp;nbsp; I look like my pic so you should be able to find me.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Thanks! Hope to see you soon!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll try to post what I'm wearing that day so people can find our group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317911160000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317050193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivia Nite at the Bell in Hand</name><id>34995892</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317855600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/34995892/</event_url></item>