<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-325</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>447074</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Boston Investors Main Meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;PHIL ERLANGER ON THE SQUEEZE PLAY AND TRADING SEASONALITY and FRED SEARS ON THE MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Feature Talk: The Art of the Squeeze Play and Trading Seasonality by Phil Erlanger, CMT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Phil Erlanger describes:&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;li&gt;The process of tracking short and long squeezes in stocks, groups and sectors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using short interest and options data to measure the majority at risk, he applies specific price action indicators to measure the squeezes that the market inflicts on bets made by a mistaken majority.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Phil shows:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to judge the validity and consistency of seasonal cycles and &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to use seasonality as a setup for a trade.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Philip B. Erlanger, CMT, is the President of Phil Erlanger Research and has been providing research to institutions since the early 1990s. Prior to starting Phil Erlanger Research, Phil was the Senior Technical Analyst for Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research. Phil came to Fidelity from Advest where he was the Chief Technical Analyst through most of the 1980s.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Phil has developed Erlanger Chart Room, a technical analysis platform that focuses on advanced technical indicators that include in depth sentiment and seasonal studies. This platform runs on eSignal, Bloomberg and MB Trading. Phil has also developed the free www.goodmorningwallst.com educational video series that offers videos that teach how to use technical analysis in the real world.&lt;li&gt;Mr. Erlanger is a two-time past president of the Market Technicians Association. In 1997, Mr. Erlanger won the MTA Best of the Best Award for Computer Assisted Analysis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Erlanger has lectured at Universities such as Rutgers, MIT, Boston University, Howard University, Emory and as an adjunct Professor at Bentley College where he taught a course in Technical Analysis. He is a graduate of Boston University with a degree in Economics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Market Talk by Fred Sears&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker. The speaker then makes a short case for the prediction - about 10 minutes.  The audience participation of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. The discussion is lively; insights come from around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Long time members of Boston IBD know and love Fred Sears. He started attending meetings back at Buddha's Delite and delivered a regular talk every month until October 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred Sears is a 4 Star (AFTER 5.75% load, 1.5% management fee) Morningstar rated Mutual Fund Manager. FYI stars are earned after 3 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has made more than 75 worldwide television appearances – CNBC – interviewed by Maria Bartiromo, Tyler Matheson, Dylan Ratigan, Bloomberg Television, TechTv, Fox Television – interviewed twice by Neil Cavuto, Reuters Televison, quoted and or interviewed in the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, Investor’s Business Daily, The Street.com, New York Post, Kiplingers, plus frequent radio appearances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Doug&lt;br /&gt;7:15 Market Talk by Fred Sears&lt;br /&gt;7:45 Open Discussion by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;8:00 Break&lt;br /&gt;8:10 Feature Talk: The Art of the Squeeze Play and Trading Seasonality by Phil Erlanger, CMT&lt;br /&gt;9:15 Stockpicks by Chris&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to join our online discussion!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are open to the public, there is no admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244677758000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241402727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors Main Meeting</name><id>10330023</id><headcount>77</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243551600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/10330023/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/e/global_8476366.jpeg</photo_url></item>