<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>How the Common Law courts, which grew out of English and Scottish anarchy, embodied Rand's&lt;br /&gt;ideal state. Galt's Gulch needed no constitution -- all it needed was Judge Narragansett, but neither Rand&lt;br /&gt;nor Judge Narragansett realized it when at the end of Atlas Shrugged he set out to write a new constitution&lt;br /&gt;for the Gulch. The Founding Fathers' vision of a constitutional republic, although vastly different in&lt;br /&gt;practice from its current embodiment, directly led to the current statist quagmire. Because the Founding&lt;br /&gt;Fathers' vision is more appealing than the current modern state, Rand and libertarians tend to uphold&lt;br /&gt;the Founding Fathers' vision with an uncritical eye -- it is, in theory, better than the modern state,&lt;br /&gt;and so has achieved a sometimes undeserved place of reverence. But Rand and libertarians overlook a much&lt;br /&gt;better, third alternative: the Common Law courts in an otherwise anarchic state. Early English Common Law&lt;br /&gt;courts did exactly what Rand required: created a rational government limited to defending life, liberty, and property,&lt;br /&gt;without venturing into paternalist policymaking.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gavin Pitt</member_name><member_id>4194885</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249844997000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246892625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Uncommon Praise for the Common Law</name><id>10812354</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248620400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/10812354/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/f/global_9524479.jpeg</photo_url></item>