<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a very different topic for our philosophy discussion group.&lt;/span&gt; One of our own members, Ilie Ruby, has just had her second novel, &lt;em&gt;The Salt God's Daughter&lt;/em&gt;, released on September 4&lt;span&gt;th&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;and she will participate in our discussion of the book.&lt;/span&gt; Ilie's talk will focus on the major themes of the book and what inspired her to write it, its socio-cultural influences "and the reality of those caught in the riptide of feminism. I'll discuss why I placed the story in the crucible of a Celtic myth and the role of mythology in modern-day storytelling." &lt;span&gt;Ilie's website is&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.ilieruby.com"&gt;http://&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/8/c/event_170536012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;www.ilieruby.com&lt;/a&gt;. And if you'd like to read the book before the meeting you can find it here on &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Salt-Gods-Daughter-Ilie-Ruby/dp/1619020025/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1350740951&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=the+salt+god%27s+daughter"&gt;Amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the book: “&lt;em&gt;The Salt God's Daughter&lt;/em&gt; is a metaphysical literary work that weaves Celtic folklore and mythology with Jewish mysticism in a rich and compelling tapestry of one family's struggle to survive, illuminating the shadows and watershed moments of the female experience across generations, ultimately invoking our notion of what it means to love and begging the question of how far we must go to feel at home in the world.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;REVIEWS: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The book “invites comparison to visual art... I suspect &lt;em&gt;The Salt God’s Daughter&lt;/em&gt; will be recognized for its homage to Scottish sea lore and for its relationship to mystic Jewish traditions. Surely it can be discussed as modern-day myth or legend. But first it finds its success as a caring observation of the devotion between women, the complex but enduring bonds between daughter and mother."—Stacy Bierlein, &lt;em&gt;The Rumpus&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"A breathtaking, fiercely feminine take on American magical realism. Ruby spins sweeping mythologies without straying far from the story of a young woman just trying to survive." —&lt;em&gt;Interview Magazine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This dinner discussion is being co-sponsored with the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Social-Philosophizers/"&gt;Social Philosophizers&lt;/a&gt; group. For those of you who belong to both groups, please RSVP on one or the other but not both (any double booking will be removed to keep the RSVP count accurate). It should be a great evening and I hope that you can join us!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For this meeting, please add $1.00 to your food and beverage costs (see below) to help defray the group's expense for Ilie's meal. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!  While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).  Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353128820000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350611200000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Salt God's Daughter" A discussion with the book's author, Ilie Ruby</name><id>87626872</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353110400000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/87626872/</event_url></item>