<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is another German film that is part of the Goethe Institute series, which this year features first time directors.  All films in the series are $5 (what a deal!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for a discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Finnisher Tango:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alex has no girlfriend, no investments, and no parents who are willing to lend a hand. But he does have his accordion, which he plays with his buddies in a band. Their tour isn’t going well, and one evening he finds himself pulling his accordion out of their wrecked van and walking away from all that was. Penniless and alone, while seeking a job Alex comes to find out that if he were to get a hold of an identification pass that proves he is disabled, certain life necessities would be taken care of—he could move into a group home for the disabled, for instance. Living in a community requires some care and responsibility, however, and he eventually rises to the occasion. A warm-hearted tragicomedy, FINNISH TANGO's range spans melancholy, laughter, warm-heartedness, world-weariness, and friendship. It won the German Film Festival Ludwigshafen’s 2008 Audience Award.&lt;br /&gt;(2008, Germany) dir. Buket Alakus, DVD, 90 min &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the movie I'll be near the exit holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241486465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Finnish Tango</name><id>10339163</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242572400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10339163/</event_url></item>