<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will hike the awesome loop through Peoples Forest.  Part two will be a potluck cookout to recognize our leader Kevin's birthday.   We are hoping that the Mountain Laurel will be blooming.&lt;br /&gt;Peoples State Forest has beautiful trails and a terrific picnic pavillion below the Stone Museum.  The park is due to be open that day so there may be a parking fee for the lot ($10).  If there is a fee we can try to park creatively.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets meet at 10:00 a.m. for those who want to hike.  This is a roughly 6.2 mile looping hike in Peoples State Forest. Some portions will be steep but do-able. Established in 1924, the forest includes over 11 miles of trails as well as the west branch of the Farmington River which was designated as a Wild and Scenic River by the National Park Service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet by 10:00 AM at the state forest main parking area on the west side of East River Rd. This paved parking area will be roughly across the street from the main entrance.  They have done some renovations so this first entrance is the one you want to be at. We'll start the hike at 10:15 AM.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll hike a short distance to the Nature Center and pick up the blue blazed trail on the west side of Greenwoods Rd. We'll follow the Robert Ross Trail north and then get onto the blue w/yellow dot Jesse Gerard Trail and eventually intersect with Greenwoods Rd. again at the northernmost point of this hike. Then hike a little south on the road and then pick up the yellow blaze Charles Pack Trail on the left and head generally south-east. We'll then finish up the hike on the eastern half of the orange blaze Agnes Brown Trail where we'll end near the Nature Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike should end at 2:00 at a decent pace.  &lt;br /&gt;The birthday cookout will start at 2:00.&lt;br /&gt;After we will meet for the picnic at the pavillion/picnic tables.  I ask folks to bring your own main course and an item to share.  If people have portable grills they can bring please drop me a note.  I will provide all the paper goods, condiments and a jug of lemonade.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come for the hike and the picnic or just come to picnic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Water is a must on the hike -1 Qt. at least, bug spray is strongly advised, food (e.g. trail mix) is optional but we do have a beautiful vista to take a break upon, sunscreen, hiking boots, non-cotton clothes, a day pack. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please no dogs or children.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The strong response to our events had led to putting caps on attendance.  If you take a spot and then do not show to the event, I reserve the right to make you wait on another event until all others have been let in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/peoples.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford (about 45 min.):&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 44 west&lt;br /&gt;* Take right onto Route 181, RIVER RD., about 1 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Go across the steel bridge&lt;br /&gt;* Take an immediate left onto East River Road&lt;br /&gt;* The parking area is approximately 1 mile up on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the parking area can be found via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=%5b100%2d109%5d%20E%20River%20Rd&amp;amp;city=Barkhamsted&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06063&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=1SQnVj2M956m56ubJXeg%2bk04z0uUP2laFE%2fs9mMspX1Jrkjs6AS7Ztl0svM2v1uchjVHWLTFQABAF6C24B8CygUeQ%2bZUxhenrkv9QiF0aNpO8DEqHlnlbOn3czLRyMDVvFh6m%2fseyi2KmSy17Qbe9ALHotoU15N%2b&amp;amp;ambiguity=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the state park, see:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325054&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1276748060000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272843355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike People's Forest, Barkhamsted CT and B.Day Cookout </name><id>13360835</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276351200000</time><rsvp_limit>38</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13360835/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>