<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The11th French Film Festival in Providence held at the Cable Car Cinema &amp;amp; Cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi everyone we will be meeting at Rue De L'espoire at 6:30 PM.  The restaurant is located at 99 Hope Street, Providence East Side, near the Brown Campus. If you RSVP'd for the cinema can you update your RSVP to let us know if you will be going to the restaurant too? You can edit your RSVP and make a comment too, stating if you are going to the dinner or just the cinema or both. &lt;a href="http://www.therue.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.therue.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liz has offered to buy the tickets in advance for the cinema, so we can get a discounted price, but we will need an accurate count of who is going. We need all of the RSVPs no later than February 19 at 12 noon. If you RSVP yes, please attend so that Liz can be reimbursed for each ticket purchased.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday night, 20 February, at 9.30 pm.  The movie scheduled for that time slot in the festival is &amp;quot;Peindre ou faire l'amour&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring Sabine Azema, Daniel Auteuil, Amira Casar, Sergi Lopez &amp;amp; Jacques Nolot.  The festival's site describes the plot as &amp;quot;An affluent, middle-aged couple’s uneventful lives are forever changed when they move into an isolated house in the country and befriend an odd, younger couple.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet Up Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Hill</member_name><member_id>1489154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236297331000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234428919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 11th French Film Festival in Providence</name><id>9726990</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235181600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/9726990/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/5/global_4089333.jpeg</photo_url></item>