<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>72 Commercial St.</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.657610</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Flatbread Pizza Company</name><city>Portland</city><id>130102</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.250145</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us on Tuesday, May 20 from 5 to 9 p.m. at &lt;a href="http://www.flatbreadcompany.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Flatbread Pizza Co.&lt;/a&gt; on Portland's waterfront for an evening of great food and fun benefiting the Bicycle Coalition of Maine's Safety and Education Programs. The evening's events will include a silent auction featuring bike gear, clothing, gift certificates, bike art and more. Check out some of the great &lt;a href="http://www.bikemaine.org/flatbread_auction.htm" target="_blank"&gt;SILENT AUCTION&lt;/a&gt; items. You also can participate in the fundraiser by buying takeout orders at Flatbread on May 20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flatbread will donate $3.50 for every large pizza sold and $1.75 for every small pizza sold (takeout orders included) to the Bicycle Coalition of Maine (BCM). In addition, Shipyard Brewing Co. will donate $1 for every beer sold at Flatbread that evening to BCM. The money will be used for safety and education programs that teach bike safety to thousands of Maine children, adults and motorists annually.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This annual fundraiser offers a chance to socialize with other bicycling enthusiasts and eat some delicious pizza while supporting a good cause. You also can purchase tickets for BCM's &lt;a href="http://www.bikemaine.org/press/press2008_5.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Aegis Super Raffle&lt;/a&gt;. The $50 tickets (only 300 will be sold) give you a chance to win a Maine-made Aegis bicycle worth $4,500. The second-place prize is a week-long bicycle tour in Tuscany, Italy provided by VBT Bicycling Vacations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to donate an item for the silent auction, please write to Nancy at ngrant@bowdoin.edu or call 837-1567.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have our Green Streets/Bike Commuting A-frame sign near our table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Brooking</member_name><member_id>2040136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211490223000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><why>This annual fundraiser offers a chance to socialize with other bicycling and green commuting enthusiasts and eat some delicious pizza while supporting a good cause.</why><group><who>Bike Commuters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Bike-Commuting</urlname><id>225788</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Bicycle Commuting</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210609378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike Coalition Benefit at Flatbread</name><id>7922553</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211317200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Bike-Commuting/events/7922553/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/4/global_4104852.jpeg</photo_url></item>