<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Every great ride should start with a big breakfast! This tour starts in Enfield, CT at the Country Diner. The ride is 218 miles of twisting, rolling roads with some lakes and rivers of beautiful Litchfield and Fairfield counties thrown in. After leaving civilization behind, the road climbs for 4 miles followed by rollers that drop us at Barkhamsted Reservoir in New Hartford; stop at Saville Dam for a photo op, then by Mcdonough Reservoir, more uphill through Minetto State Park and off to Cornwall- home of the landmark Cornwall covered bridge (1841) which we actually pass on the return. From there we ride down Route 7 following the Housatonic river and the Appalachian Trail to Candlewood Lake, passing POIs that include the Town of Kent, Kent Falls, Bulls Bridge, Candlewood lookout tower and a few great vistas. We follow Candlewood Lake nearly to its end before getting on the twisty roads of CT37 and CR66/67 over to NY. Ride hard or stop for pictures- tough choice here. Up NY22 with a stop for lunch, coffee and dessert (every ride should have a coffee stop without the initials &amp;quot;DD&amp;quot;); a brief detour onto CR6 to follow Tenmile River; then back to the main road and return to CT via NY SR343 and CT4. But wait, there's more- more twisting tarmac; more rollercoaster hills as we carve from West Cornwall, CT up to Route 57 in New Marlborough and Granville, MA. The ride ends at the MA Pike in Westfield, MA. Link to map: &lt;a href="http://mapshare.delorme.com/Consumer/V.aspx?p=5555djxz" target="_blank"&gt;http://mapshare.delor...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Red Suzuki Burgman 400.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272892387000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271680653000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tri-State Rural Ramble</name><id>13223009</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272718800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/13223009/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/8/global_14492824.jpeg</photo_url></item>