<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Transition Towns is a fast-growing, community program to increase local resilience and economic vitality. Thousands of communities around the world are exploring and using this positive, solutions-focused approach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Communities are coming together to build community resilience and to transition to a cleaner, safer, renewable energy sources. Energy costs will go back up in the coming years, increasing the costs of food, home heating, transportation and almost everything in our lives. Energy problems, combined with economic instability and climate change, pose a “Triple Challenge” that requires bigger, more creative solutions. Change is unfolding quickly, and local action is essential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Transition approach is a fast-growing, community-based response that increases local resilience and economic vitality. Thousands of communities around the world are exploring and using this positive, solutions-focused approach.&lt;br /&gt;This free evening presentation will describe the Transition approach, the growing global network of resources, and some of the practical solutions at the heart of this successful model. Tina Clarke, a certified Transition Towns trainer, will describe the Transition model and share some of the reasons why the model is proving so useful to communities around the world. &lt;br /&gt;For more information, visit: www.transitiontowns.org and www.transitionus.org.&lt;br /&gt;Contact Tina at: tinaclarke@transitionnetwork.org, 413-658-8165&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tina Clarke has over 25 years experience as a professional trainer, consultant, and director of nonprofit community leadership and advocacy programs. She has consulted with over 400 NGOs, most recently working with Bill McKibben's global 350.org initiative, the Massachusetts Municipal Association, and the Sustainability Institute. In Washington, D.C. she directed national citizen 350.org initiative, the Massachusetts Municipal Association, and the Sustainability Institute. In Washington, D.C. she directed national citizen advocacy training programs for faith communities, and directed Greenpeace USA's citizen activist network. Tina directed a regional nonprofit assistance center and organized coalitions on environmental justice, toxins and energy for New England Clean Water Action. Tina has an M.A. in Public Policy from the University of Chicago. Her passive solar, Platinum LEED, low-toxic &amp;quot;Power House&amp;quot; won the Massachusetts utility company-sponsored competition, the Zero Energy Challenge, and the 2010 Northeast Sustainable Energy Association’s 2010 Zero Net Energy Award (www.nesea.org/inspirationawards/zeroenergy/2010applicants). The house is free of all fossil fuels and wood-burning, and generated 2.5 times more energy than needed in 2009 (www.zeroenergypowerhouse.com). &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Transition Towns&amp;quot; is a fast-growing, community-based response to economic instability, oil dependence, climate change, and resource depletion. Thousands of communities around the world are exploring and using this positive, solutions-focused process. Begun in the U.K., Transition &amp;quot;Initiatives&amp;quot; have popped up in cities, rural areas, neighborhoods and universities -- geographical communities where people are working together to increase local resilience, while doing their part to address the global challenges of our time. &lt;br /&gt;The Transition process helps people face the enormous challenges of rising energy costs of energy, food, home heating, transportation and virtually everything in our lives, yet catalyzes practical, positive responses that enhance the quality of life. By &amp;quot;unleashing the collective genius&amp;quot; we not only develop positive responses to the energy and economic challenges; we can create more fulfilling lives, and a more just and stable world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276733927000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276660841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TRANSITION TOWN PUBLIC PUBLIC FORUM</name><id>13816018</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276729200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/13816018/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/e/global_10735486.jpeg</photo_url></item>