<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Action: Hand out Free Talk Live flyers, FSP tax flyers, and FSP bookmarks plus talk to people about what is happening in NH to End the Fed and reduce government on all levels&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: email keithcarlsen at gmail dot com or call 997-1446&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston End the Fed Rally on April 25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There were End the Fed Rallies at all of the Federal Reserve Buildings in the nation shortly after the November elections.  A new round of rallies was setup and they will happen on April 25th.  People will be&lt;br /&gt;there with signs, handing out flyers, spreading the word about freedom and listening to speakers - including Mark Edge of Free Talk Live.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come and help Mark spread the word about the New Hampshire freedom movement - we need more folks in NH.  I need help with passing out FTL flyers, FSP tax flyers, and FSP bookmarks.  Please wear FTL, FSP, pro-freedom NH clothes or whatever you think is best.  Let’s reach out to folks in the Boston area and tell them what we are up to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may want to carpool as parking in Boston isn’t the easiest thing in the world.  Contact me or post here if you are interested in carpooling and I may be able to help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your help in building the NH liberty movement!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241400842000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239900724000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston End the Fed Rally</name><id>10199228</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240668000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/10199228/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>