<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join the NBMAA from 5:30-8 p.m. Friday, Jan. 2, 2009 for First Friday featuring the Ben Billelio Trio, a classic jazz ensemble of piano, bass, and drums. Ben has forged a career as a noted performer and as a much sought after private instructor. As one of the most in demand freelance jazz drummers in New England, Ben can be seen at numerous clubs, concert halls and festivals with a wide variety of artists. At this time, Ben can be seen performing with his own trio, with Dezron Douglas on bass and Roy Dunlop on piano.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Friday features live jazz music performed by local and nationally-known musicians, an opportunity to view the Museum's premier permanent collection of 300 years of American art, gallery talks, art activities, a chance to mix and mingle with other art and jazz lovers, a selection of light hors d'oeuvres, wine, beer and soda. The cost is $5 for Museum members and $10 for non-members, $3 for beer and wine, soda is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is so hard to find people here some times plan to com and have a good time and if we connect then great.  If not enjoy the music and the Art.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It is so dificult to meet at a certain spot.  On Jan1 I will e-mail yeses My #</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231108668000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230678027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Friday at New Britain Museum of Art</name><id>9410021</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230935400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/9410021/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/0/global_2892656.jpeg</photo_url></item>