<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>300.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Spiritual Awakening/Psychic Development Class&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This &lt;b&gt;10 week class&lt;/b&gt; is geared to assist you in opening up to your life path, why you are here and how to get to where you really want to be.  Combining science and spirituality, pragmatic and alternative knowledge, this class will provide you with valuable tools that will help you to create an amazing and purposeful life!  A three tiered approach to psychic awareness, this class empowers you to awaken to your current life, make decisions based on your inner knowledge, hone your natural psychic abilities and begin living in abundance and spiritual flow.  If you find yourself presented with difficulties, are wishing to open up intuitively and psychically or if you are simply ready to make a change in your life, this class will provide you with what you need to do just that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;I love teaching this class.  It’s an honor and it’s amazing to see the outstanding growth each student experiences! - Isabeau Esby&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dates: &lt;u&gt;10 Wednesdays from 7 PM to 8:30 PM&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jan 6th, Jan 13th, Jan 20th, Jan 27th, Feb 3rd, Feb 10th, Feb 17th, Feb 24th, Mar 3rd, Mar 10th&lt;br /&gt;Cost - $300.00   Location - Dover, New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;**Space is limited to 10 students, pre-registration required **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Testimonial from a previous student:&lt;br /&gt;A person can find many workshops or multi-week programs offering life renewal or change. But rarely does a person have the opportunity to study with someone who can bring so much 'to the table'.  How to explain the talents of Isabeau Esby. To the point, she is both out of this world and very much of this world.  A person of enormous spiritual gifts, experience and education, she has be ability to connect a person to metaphysical energies that allude most human beings. She is a successful medium, after all; it is her job to bridge both worlds. Yet she is a grounded mother of two who fully lives in everyday America and understands the challenges in melding spiritual exploration and practices with the pressures and practical demands of our lives. As with all good teachers, she is both an excellent listener and communicator. And her classes are fun! - those who expect discussions on spirituality to be ponderous and dreary will be disappointed with Isabeau's classes. &lt;br /&gt;Her 10 week class has given me much to ponder and has allowed me to creatively explore the important life questions facing me now.  Quite frankly, I can hardly wait to get to class. Every time I go, I have one of those 'aha' moments that we hear Oprah  talk about. It is quite addicting!  I believe anyone willing to make the time and the commitment will benefit greatly from Isabeau's class.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A. Webber&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be given upon completion of registration</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262995611000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255221194000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic Development/Spiritual Awakening Class</name><id>11598176</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262822400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/11598176/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/3/global_6795651.jpeg</photo_url></item>