<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Providence Place Mall</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826747</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Providence WaterFire</name><city>Providence</city><id>1089680</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416949</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The plan is to meet at a private home at 5:00pm.  Then we can carpool to Providence Waterfire at 7pm to see the Philharmonic on Fire.  &lt;br /&gt;When you rsvp yes further details will be sent.&lt;br /&gt;BYOB&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you prefer to head directly to waterfire paste this address into your browser for directions -  &lt;a href="http://www.waterfire.org/plan-your-trip/parking-and-directions" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waterfire....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; July 31st - Philharmonic on Fire9:00pm @ Turk’s Head Plaza, ProvidenceFrancisco Noya conducts   Free Concert         &lt;br /&gt; The Philharmonic on Fire: Rhode Island Philharmonic Orchestra LIVE at WaterFire Providence Saturday July 31, 9PM Turk’s Head Plaza On Saturday, July 31, the Rhode Island Philharmonic Orchestra, conducted by Resident Conductor Francisco Noya joins WaterFire Providence to present a spectacular evening of live orchestral music performed in the heart of downtown Providence. This first-of-its-kind event will allow tens of thousands of people to experience the Rhode Island Philharmonic Orchestra live at the Turk’s Head Plaza and also all along the three rivers of WaterFire and in Waterplace Park. This will be an evening of music inspired by WaterFire and carefully selected by the Philharmonic’s Francisco Noya in collaboration with WaterFire creator Barnaby Evans. The Orchestra will perform at the Turk’s Head Plaza, beginning at 9pm. Approximately 2,500 chairs will be placed in the Plaza for audience members. Tens of thousands more people can listen to the performance while enjoying the flames of WaterFire from anywhere along the WaterFire rivers. The program includes Smetana’s The Moldau, Mahler’s Adagietto from Symphony No. 5 and Pärt’s Fratres. Choreographed by Mark Harootian, dancers from Festival Ballet Providence will join the Philharmonic performing to Barber’s Adagio for Strings and de Falla’s Ritual Fire Dance from El Amor Brujo. Misha Djuric is Festival Ballet’s artistic director. Soprano Diana McVey will sing music by Puccini and others. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet beforehand at a private house</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Germaine</member_name><member_id>10481143</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280695109000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280440191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waterfire &amp; Philharmonic in Providence</name><id>14256745</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280610000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/14256745/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/3/global_13367603.jpeg</photo_url></item>