<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hartford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02052</zip><lat>42.204330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-784-0567</phone><name>Rocky Woods Park</name><city>Medfield</city><id>821026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.277432</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We think it’s the rich history of Rocky Woods’ 491 acres, laced by footpaths and former logging roads that meander through woods and wetlands and to the top of 435-foot Cedar Hill. At adjacent Fork Factory Brook, a trail network traces hay fields and climbs wooded uplands across a 135-acre landscape that once supported both farms and mills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 6.5 miles of trails winding through varied terrain, Rocky Woods is a year-round destination for outdoors lovers of all abilities. The 0.75-mile loop around Chickering Pond, the largest of the reservation’s five man-made ponds, is a family favorite. The Bridle Trail and Loop Trail are short, flat options that tour wetlands, while the half-mile Echo Pond Trail, with its long, narrow footbridge, loops around this large pond. Or, if you’re looking to stretch your legs on a longer trek, you can take on the Mine Hill Loop, which links together the Wilson Swamp, Ridge, and Cheney Pond trails and circles 420-foot high Mine Hill ridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The reservation is situated with one foot within the Charles River watershed and the other foot within the drainage of the Neponset. Mill Brook, which flows through the Fork Factory wetlands, meanders southeast to the Neponset River, while Vine Brook, on the Rocky Woods side, flows southwest into the Charles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The area’s high water table forms wetlands throughout the reservation and these varied habitats attract songbirds, particularly the towhee, with its “drink-your-tea” call. Bullfrogs and painted turtles live in the Reservation’s four man-made ponds where visitors can enjoy catch-and-release fishing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails&lt;br /&gt;6.5 miles of trails. Moderate hiking, strenuous in places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When to Visit&lt;br /&gt;Year-round, daily, sunrise to sunset. Allow a minimum of 2 hours, 3 hours if also visiting adjacent Fork Factory Brook. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facilities&lt;br /&gt;Restrooms, handicapped-accessible fishing platform, picnic tables, terrace, picnic &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regulations &amp;amp; Advisories&lt;br /&gt;Dog walking by Green Dogs permit only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mountain biking permitted only on designated trails. Trails are closed to mountain biking March 1 to April 30, during muddy season. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Swimming and ice skating are not permitted. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camping is not permitted. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservation closes at sunset. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;Hartford Street&lt;br /&gt;Medfield, MA&lt;br /&gt;Telephone: 508.785.0339&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: charlesrivervalley@ttor.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258474194000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258040301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ROCKY WOODS MEDFIELD WALKING MEETUP</name><id>11858688</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258300800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/11858688/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>