<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.360067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Suites</name><city>Boston</city><id>968618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;D.E.N. - Deals Exchange Network&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: 1st Tuesday of Every Month 6:30 PM - Next D.E.N. January 5, 2010 - Enjoy Networking, Deals, Prizes and Fun!!! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Doubletree Suites, 400 Soldiers Field Road, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHAT:  Networking, Deals Exchange, Featuring: &lt;br /&gt;               **Deal or NO DEAL** - Get your deals analyzed by a panel of local real estate experts!  To be a candidate to submit your deals - email Bernadette (Bernadette@bostonareia.com) today!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cost: $25 for visitors, FREE for Members of Boston AREIA  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;***SAVE THE DATE - BRING YOUR DEALS - BRING LOTS OF BUSINESS CARDS AND COME PREPARED TO NETWORK!***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLUS . . .&lt;br /&gt;Attorney, Matthew Desrochers!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our featured speaker Attorney Matthew Desrochers.  He'll point you in the right direction and keep you and your deals on track.  He'll will give you the inside track to avoid legal issues that spring on any and all types of real estate deals!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matthew T. Desrochers is a real estate and bankruptcy attorney with offices is Stoneham and Reading, MA.  He holds a mortgage broker license and real estate broker’s license.  Practicing law for ten years, he has conducted over 10000 closing representing buyers, sellers, banks, developers and investor just like you.  Matthew has seen it all as an attorney related to issues that you face every day.  Personally as an investor he also owns property in Peabody, Worcester and Charlestown, MA.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;US Bank v. Ibanez the Seminole foreclosure case in Massachusetts is analyzed.  This will save you time, and time is money &lt;br /&gt;Current bankruptcy law and how it affects your real estate investing... &lt;br /&gt;Legal issues with Short Sales and Short Sale Flips &lt;br /&gt;How to avoid litigation; go from getting sued to be suing; CYA… &lt;br /&gt;LLC’s how to set them up in Massachusetts/advantages/disadvantages etc… &lt;br /&gt;Loan modification - how to modify an existing mortgage&lt;br /&gt;Short Refinances - how the work and how to get one for you or a client.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;D.E.N. Meeting&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Doubletree Guest Suites, 400 Soldier's Field Road, Boston &lt;br /&gt;Free to members, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263846804000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260755278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>D.E.N. - Deals, Exchange Network, PLUS Attorney Matthew Desrochers!</name><id>12078816</id><headcount>76</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262734200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/12078816/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/b/global_1787963.jpeg</photo_url></item>