<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>132 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01984</zip><lat>42.603954</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 468-2377</phone><name>Wenham Museum</name><city>Wenham</city><id>669413</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a first for the Salem Board Games Meetup...a field trip.  New England winters can be pretty boring, so let's mix it up a bit.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wenham Museum is comprised of the treasures of childhood and explores how New Englanders have lived, worked, dressed and played from the 17th century to today.  They boast a world-famous 19th- and 20th-century doll, toy, and game collection.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They are currently hosting the special exhibit &lt;b&gt;Look What I Got!: 100 Years of Timeless Toys&lt;/b&gt;,  where kids, parents, and grandparents rediscover the joy of favorite childhood pastimes in a colorful exhibition of classic games and toys from the last 100 years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've never been to the museum, but hopefully it will be a lot of fun.  Let's plan to meet there at noon.  Admission is $7.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free parking at the museum is available including limited handicap parking next to the museum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, visit: &lt;a href="http://www.wenhammuseum.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wenhammuse...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The phone number listed is mine and not that of the museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*******************&lt;br /&gt;Marica lives very close to the museum and has so kindly offered to host a luncheon for the group after our tour.  She will provide soup, salad, coffee, and soda.  Should you want anything sweet, feel free to bring it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her address is 34 Crescent Road Hamilton, MA and it is a brown house.  She does have dogs, but they will be crated while we are there.  Her phone number is 978-239-3392.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should you only be able to attend the museum portion of the day, please indicate that in your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203368075000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201588966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Game Group Takes a Field Trip and Lunch</name><id>7219243</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203181200000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/7219243/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/6/7/global_3094455.jpeg</photo_url></item>