<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Shepard St, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA 02138</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381058</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>59 Shepard St, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA 02138</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10326162</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.124931</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This November, the Humanist Community at Harvard, through its Values in Action program, is partnering with the Boston Interfaith Campus Coalition and Kids Care to package meals for the food insecure in Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be sorting, weighing, and packaging food from noon-6 PM at 59 Shepard Street in Cambridge; stay for as little or as long as you'd like -- help is needed all day. This is a great all-ages event (bring kids!) and a wonderful way to put your/humanistic values into action with the whole family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Status Report on Hunger in Massachusetts notes that in 2010, 10.8 percent of households were food insecure. This is the highest rate recorded in the Commonwealth since this data was first collected in 1995, according to the Project Bread website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, we'll be joining members of the HCH and other secular community groups in coming together around our shared value of service, to package more meals than ever -- 40,000 -- in time for Thanksgiving. In order for the project to succeed, a total of $10,000 (that's 25 cents per meal!) needs to be raised. Please consider making a donation to this important cause. If you choose to send in a donation, please write "VIA event" in the "special instructions" box when you send your contribution in via PayPal. Donate via www.harvardhumanist.org. Checks can be written to "Outreach, Inc. - Kids Care" and given to any member of the HCH staff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the money goes to Kids Care for the cost of food.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353295265000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352928481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Values in Action: Thanksgiving Meal-packing</name><id>91416312</id><duration>21600000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353258000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/91416312/</event_url></item>