<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Patriot Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02035</zip><lat>42.093693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Renaissance Boston Patriot Place Hotel &amp; Spa</name><city>Foxboro</city><id>9692572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.263123</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A Standout Evening of Standup with the Goddesses of Laughter. The new all female comedy tour featuring We are rolling out the pink carpet to have fun going Passionately Pink for the Cure. Join us for a great girls’ night out, wear pink and have fun at the upcoming Goddesses Of Laughter comedy show at the Renaissance Hotel Patriot Place. Enjoy five hysterical women who sit on top of comedy as they perform a dinner show for one night only to benefit the Susan G. Komen Passionately Pink for The Cure foundation .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Goddesses of Laughter will donate 10% of the proceeds of ticket sales to the Susan G. Komen Passionately Pink for The Cure foundation. The dinner starts at 5:30 pm and reservations for dinner are required. The show starts at 8:30 pm. A cash bar is available. The Renaissance Hotel and Spa is located at 28 Patriot Place in Foxboro, MA. Tickets are general admission and cost $49 Per Person for the Dinner Show. Dinner Show includes 3 course prix menu . Show Only tickets are also available at $25. Large groups of 10 or more will enjoy complimentary flatbread pizzas. Tickets can be purchased online at www.drinkwaterproductions.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Claudette</member_name><member_id>14230550</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350089051000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349830243000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Dinner Show with the Goddesses of Laughter</name><id>86287692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350077400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/86287692/</event_url></item>