<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 Pequot Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06890</zip><lat>41.136570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 292-6124</phone><name>Southport Galleries</name><city>Southport</city><id>1211138</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.283801</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;You are invited to a very special event on&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday, March 20, 2011, from 4:30 to 6:30 PM&lt;/strong&gt;!&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;We are hosting an artists&amp;rsquo; reception to honor the youth who participated in this year&amp;rsquo;s Discovered Spirit Project.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;This is a rare opportunity for you to meet youth representative of those whom we serve through our programs at Covenant to Care for Children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;The participants created masks guided by professional Connecticut artists, who volunteered their time and talents to the project, Katrina Franzen of Southport; and Marta Cunha and Julie Nearing of Middletown. &lt;br /&gt;The masks are part of a juried show displayed at&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Southport Galleries&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in Fairfield County. Sarah Biggers, Gallery Manager, has again generously allowed use of this beautiful Southport gallery located in the renovation of the village&amp;rsquo;s historic hardware store. Our Discovered Spirit Exhibit will share gallery space with acclaimed graffiti artist CRASH!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Celebrity judges include&lt;/strong&gt;: Diann Cook, Artist and last year&amp;rsquo;s Discovered Spirit Project Committee Chair, Representative Tony Hwang, and First Selectman Ken Flatto of Fairfield who will present awards for the masks showing the greatest originality, presentation, and representation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beverages and hors d'ourves&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Girl Admiral&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;will guarantee this to be an afternoon to remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;This is a free event&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Southport Galleries is located at 330 Pequot Ave, Southport&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.southportgalleries.com/"&gt;southportgalleries.com&lt;/a&gt;. For more information, please contact Covenant to Care for Children or visit our website at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.covenanttocare.org/"&gt;covenanttocare.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;We hope to see you there, and please invite your friends and neighbors!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000090 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;Covenant to Care for Children (CCC) is pleased to announce our Discovered Spirit Project. This project is for children and youth with any experience in Connecticut&amp;rsquo;s Department of Children and Families, the Foster Care system or the CCC Mentoring Program. The project is intended to give them a voice by encouraging self-expression through art.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;Words alone are not enough to express what children feel. This is especially true when they are faced with the complex issues of divorce, grief, violence, abuse, neglect or coping with poverty. We are giving a voice to these children to express a wide range of emotions and help them work through conflicts and traumas. We expect to see an array of outcomes with our masks from the whimsical to the evocative. While expressing themselves in this visual way, the children gain a sense of empowerment that can help them develop a positive self-image and improve their selfesteem. Children will create masks guided by professional Connecticut artists, Donna Frustere, Karen Wright of Hartford, Katrina Franzen of Southport, Marta Cunha, and Julie Nearing of Middletown, who are volunteering their time and talents to the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;Southport Galleries in Fairfield County will display the masks created by the children, along with examples of the professional artists&amp;rsquo; work. Sarah Biggers, gallery manager, has generously allowed use of this beautiful new Southport gallery located in the renovation of the village&amp;rsquo;s historic hardware store. At the Discovered Spirit Project gallery opening reception on Sunday, March 20, 2011, the masks will be available for sale with all proceeds supporting the programs CCC. Celebrity judges will present awards for the masks showing the greatest originality, presentation, and representation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 12px"&gt;After the gallery opening event, the masks will be available for viewing and purchase at the gallery through April 1, 2011. After this period, the masks will travel to faith-based volunteering sites throughout Connecticut as a traveling display during the following ten months. Our goal is to bring broader awareness of Covenant to Care for Children and the children we serve, offer an opportunity at recognition and accomplishment to the children participating, and build support of our programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301627102000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>This is an extraordinary project and the reception brings the project and the youth artists together with you! Additionally, showing at the gallery along with our kids amazing masks is renowned pop graffiti artist CRASH!</why><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299865354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Support for Covenant to Care for Children &amp; a cool way to spend Sunday afternoon</name><id>16885999</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300653000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/16885999/</event_url></item>