<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 491 9400</phone><name>Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>730460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trading deadline is causing great anxiety among Red Sox Natives as many feel the Red Sox need to acquire some outfield, infield, bullpen and catching help to replace some of their injured players before they fall out of the pennant race. How far can they go with all of these AAA and released player call ups?    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is our Annual Trading Deadline Round Table Event. The trading deadline takes place the following day and we will be sorting out all of the moves made and to be made by the Red Sox and the competition. Where will Roy Oswalt end up? Who will be the biggest name moved at the deadline? Who will the Yankees acquire?  Will the Red Sox acquire any bullpen help?  At last years event we debated the Victor Martinez trade and anticipated August waiver deals for Alex Gonzales and Billy Wagner. Two years ago the event was quite lively as we celebrated the departure of Manny and the arrival of Jason Bay with a shot of Johnny Walker Red!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Natives Team Weatherman Scott says it will probably be a hazy, hot and humid night so we will venture outside to watch the Sox game at Legal Seafoods out door bar and patio at the Charles Hotel in Harvard Square. This is the raw bar at street level visible from the street, not the patio dining area in the courtyard. There are several Televisions at the bar. The bar menu is sufficient for most people.  The Red Sox play the Tigers at Fenway at 7:10pm and we will watch the game.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be either at or around the bar and then move to a round table. Ask the bartenders if you can not find us or are a newbie. All members should wear Red Sox Baseball hats.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attendance at this is unlimited. Please RSVP and bring guests and other Sox fans. Come meet other members who share your interest, provide feedback on desired events and cheer on our Sox.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay cash for your beverage and food and tip your server/bartender when paying your separate food and drink check before leaving.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go Sox   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fenway Frank and Jon&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the bartenders, look for Natives wearing Red Sox Hats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280615446000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279510914000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Trading Deadline Roundtable/Watch Sox Game at Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar </name><id>14142554</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280530800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/14142554/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/1/global_4236993.jpeg</photo_url></item>