<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/d/4/event_85192692.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Important! &amp;nbsp;Since this second Tuesday happens to fall upon Valentine's day, we are having this Month's Meeting the week before on Tuesday, February 7th. &amp;nbsp;Our new venue is The Rusty Hammer in Portsmouth.**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The February book club selection is Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children by Ransom Riggs. &amp;nbsp;Here is a brief synopsis of the book from the editor:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A mysterious island. An abandoned orphanage. A strange collection of very curious photographs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It all waits to be discovered in&amp;nbsp;Miss Peregrine&amp;rsquo;s Home for Peculiar Children, an unforgettable novel that mixes fiction and photography in a thrilling reading experience. As our story opens, a horrific family tragedy sets sixteen-year-old Jacob journeying to a remote island off the coast of Wales, where he discovers the crumbling ruins of Miss Peregrine&amp;rsquo;s Home for Peculiar Children. As Jacob explores its abandoned bedrooms and hallways, it becomes clear that the children were more than just peculiar. They may have been dangerous. They may have been quarantined on a deserted island for good reason. And somehow&amp;mdash;impossible though it seems&amp;mdash;they may still be alive.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A spine-tingling fantasy illustrated with haunting vintage photography,&amp;nbsp;Miss Peregrine&amp;rsquo;s Home for Peculiar Children&amp;nbsp;will delight adults, teens, and anyone who relishes an adventure in the shadows.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And from Amazon.com:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a kid, Jacob formed a special bond with his grandfather over his bizarre tales and photos of levitating girls and invisible boys. Now at 16, he is reeling from the old man's unexpected death. Then Jacob is given a mysterious letter that propels him on a journey to the remote Welsh island where his grandfather grew up. There, he finds the children from the photographs--alive and well--despite the islanders&amp;rsquo; assertion that all were killed decades ago. As Jacob begins to unravel more about his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s childhood, he suspects he is being trailed by a monster only he can see. A haunting and out-of-the-ordinary read, debut author Ransom Rigg&amp;rsquo;s first-person narration is convincing and absorbing, and every detail he draws our eye to is deftly woven into an unforgettable whole. Interspersed with photos throughout,&amp;nbsp;Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children&amp;nbsp;is a truly atmospheric novel with plot twists, turns, and surprises that will delight readers of any age.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a special guest this evening! &amp;nbsp;Local author T.J. Waters will begin the evening with a discussion on his newest novel &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Secret-Signs-T-J-Waters/dp/156368473X/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1328630194&amp;amp;sr=1-1"&gt;Secret Signs&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Autographed copies will be available for all who attend! &amp;nbsp;Visit his &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/TJ-Waters/132262233478349?sk=wall"&gt;fan page&lt;/a&gt; and please thank him for coming this evening!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/c/4/event_91905252.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331680953000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326253433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club February - Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children</name><id>djdpkcyqdbsb</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328659200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/47607002/</event_url></item>