<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>799 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363407</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-8356</phone><name>Bertucci's </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>754675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097389</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll explore Social Media measurement with the AMA Boston Social Media Team and Cesar Brea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the importance of Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn continue to grow, you're including social media more and more in your marketing mix. But now, how do you prove that social is really delivering the ROI you need? And how do you measure social media's impact on your brand, on customer loyalty, on retention? Is social media measurable? Join us for a conversation with Cesar Brea of Force Five Partners to answer these questions, and point to ways you can identify the ROI of social media marketing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A social marketer's greatest nightmare is a campaign that fails to attract any attention -- much less ROI. What principles can we apply to social campaign design that will hedge this risk and produce both buzz for the brand and data to direct other marketing efforts? Cesar Brea of Force Five Partners will suggest some lessons from his experiences, and looks forward to learning from yours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cesar is a partner at Force Five Partners, a Boston-based marketing company that works with brands, retailers, media firms, and emerging technology vendors to design, run, and optimize multi-channel marketing campaigns that fully leverage the range of digital options available today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your questions answered and share great conversations and networking over dinner at a tweetup for everyone in Boston's digital marketing community and beyond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosted by the AMA Boston Social Media team.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://connect.amaboston.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://connect.amabos...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at the Bertucci's near Central Square, next to Toscanni's. &lt;br /&gt;Bertucci's&lt;br /&gt;799 Main St&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $5 (includes one drink) plus pay-your-own way meal, if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://measuresocial.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://measuresocial....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Boston Internet Marketing Meetup sign - we should be in a private room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lew</member_name><member_id>10673992</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288837526000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286641361000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Is Social Media Measurable? Prove it!</name><id>15055296</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288648800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/15055296/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/1/global_10196385.jpeg</photo_url></item>