<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Monmouth Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.344881</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 566-5715</phone><name>Brookline Arts Center</name><city>Brookline</city><id>893321</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107525</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Brookline photographer Istvan Akos Morocz will lead a discussion on photography techniques and ideas during a free photo salon on Friday, October 23 from 6:30 – 8:30pm at the Brookline Arts Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Istvan Akos Morocz's Dialogues is currently on view at the Brookline Arts Center, 86 Monmouth St., Brookline through Friday, November 10, 2009. Now a Brookline resident and a researcher at the Brigham and Women's Hospital, Istvan Akos Morocz was born in Hungary, where he was exposed to a rich tradition of mid-20th century photography. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pisti (his Hungarian nickname) was given a Yashica twin-lens reflex camera when he was 12 years old. He continues to use film for image capture. Now, he digitizes the images that result, and prints them on cotton canvas, for a warm tone and matte texture that recalls 20th century print techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more at: &lt;a href="http://www.brooklineartscenter.com/events/exhibitions/morocz.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brooklinea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The photo salon is open to all photographers and anyone interested in learning more about photography. Photographers are invited to bring their photographs and discuss composition and techniques with the artist. The event is free, but donations will be accepted. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brookline Arts Center is located at 86 Monmouth St., at the corner of St. Mary's Street, and is convenient to public transportation. For more information, please call 617-566-5715 or visit www.brooklineartscenter.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256510571000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256142258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free photo salon - discussion on photography techniques with Istvan Akos Morocz </name><id>11678336</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256337000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11678336/</event_url></item>