<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/2/c/event_169177932.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Intro....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I know this may be hard to believe with today's horrible weather;-( but tomorrow is supposed be a gorgeous sunny day in the 50's so I'd like to get out for a nice hike which my puppy can enjoy too and we would love some company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Description....&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This is a 4 1/2 mile loop hike at the beautiful Tully Lake in Royalston which includes the scenic Doane's Falls at about the halfway point.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The pace will be moderate, approximately 2 MPH. The length of this hike is 4 1/2 miles so it will probably take us more than two hours plus our stop time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;We will stop at Doane's Falls for maybe 15-20 minutes, at approximately the halfway point for photo ops, rest, snack break, etc. There is a gradual ascend with some steep areas near the falls but most of this hike is fairly easy to moderate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beautiful photo of Doane's Falls above is compliments of Doug M on a previous hike&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please be prepared....&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Muddy conditions still exist so please make sure you wear waterproof footwear and even gators if you have some to keep mud off your legs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Please do bring adequate water and snacks and dress appropriately in layers. We do stop for anyone who needs to so please don't be shy about speaking up and saying, "hey need to shed a layer, find a tree, get a shot of this hot chick";-), etc.... Okay, so I got a good laugh anyway;-).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where we are meeting....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Thanks to a heads up from Terry about an area of the trail that was flooded a few days ago near the Tully Recreational Area, I am changing our starting point to the campground. If we loop around and find it still flooded we can turn around or detour back over to the campground so&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;we are now meeting at Tully Lake Campground on 25 Doane Hill Road.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This is the first right north of the Tully Recreational Area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I drive a 2003 maroon Chevy Monte Carlo &amp;amp; am not known for being early generally so if you don't see my car there when you arrive, please don't panic;-).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please read before you RSVP....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;By RSVPing "yes" for this hike, you assume responsibility for yourself and your own well being. If you have a medical condition, ie: diabetes, heart condition, convulsions, allergic reactions to bees, etc... which I should be aware of even if you are capable of this hike, please do let me know and also fill me in on an appropriate plan if you should need emergency care. Thank you!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Here's a description of Tully Lake from the North Quabbin Woods guide....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/168"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/168&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 North Quabbin Woods Logo: Forestry, Wood Products, Recreation &lt;br /&gt;

 Area Guide – Tully Lake Recreation Area&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paddle among dozens of islands on this spectacular lake. To the northeast follow the narrow Tully River to Long Pond for excellent wildlife viewing. Cartop boat access also available on Doane Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;

 Description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tully Lake Recreation Area protects about four miles of the Tully River, including Long Pond, where the river widens, and the 200-acre Tully Lake, created by a flood-control dam. The wetlands and the forest support a wide variety of flora and fauna, lists of which are available online. The land and the lake offer numerous recreational opportunities, including camping, picnicking, boating, fishing, and hiking. A one-mile interpretive trail introduces visitors to both natural and cultural history; another trail loops around the lake and connects to scenic vistas and waterfalls. Part of this loop constitutes one leg of the Tully Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;From Rte. 2 take Exit 17 (Rte. 32N) and follow Rte 32 signs closely for about 6 miles to entrance, just past dam, on right(heading north on rt 32). You will also be on rt 2a (which is Main St). As a landmark, you'll see Athol Hospital on your left. Continue on Main Street past the hospital to the intersection of Main Street and School Street, which bears left. Stay on Main Street which will go down a hill near the river and take the next right which will take you over the river then bear left after you cross the river(via bridge, nothing adventurous;-) to the top of the hill. Oncoming traffic strangely has the right of way here so be careful. You have a stop sign and they don't. Proceed left(or straight) onto Chestnut Hill Road and then take an immediate right onto Silver Lake Street (rt 32N) for approximately 3+ miles. Go past the Tully Lake headquarters building and the dam and Tully Lake Recreational area is just past the dam on the right side. Now that we changed our location to meet at the campground keep going past the Tully Lake Recreational Area to the next right which will be Doane Hill Road. The Campground will be on the right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;My phone in case you are running late or lost.....413.559.0192 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Here are google map directions from the Athol Hospital to the campground where we are now going to park...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://goo.gl/maps/sgNXV"&gt;http://goo.gl/maps/sgNXV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tully Lake Campground&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25 Doane Hill Road &lt;br /&gt;

 Royalston, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Latitude: 42.6517 &lt;br /&gt;

 Longitude: -72.2123&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another alternative From Rt. 2, is to take Exit 18 and turn left onto Rt. 2A West toward Athol. From the intersection of Rts. 2A and 32 North in Athol, cross the Millers River Bridge and bear left following the signs on Rt. 32 North. Proceed about 4 mi., passing the Tully Dam, and take a right onto Doane Hill Rd. Proceed for 1 mi. Tully Lake Campground is on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Just FYI....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Tomorrow is the 50th River Rat Race starting in Athol at 1pm and ending in our neighboring town of Orange. The two towns will be bustling all day with events surrounding this race so avoid being caught up in traffic, parade, etc..., please use rt 2 rather than rt 2a if you can(or rt 68 from the east or 119 from the north). Rt2a is also Main Street for both towns. Other side roads will also be rather busy but most of this will wind down before our hike hopefully.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tully Lake Campground parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cheryl M</member_name><member_id>84314272</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366118924000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365785099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Loop Hike Around Tully lake, 4 1/2 miles</name><id>114024302</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365877800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/114024302/</event_url></item>