<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What to expect... Complete a Lyme's Questionnaire indicating signs and symptoms you may be showing or experiencing. Participate in a preliminary screening using Computerized Electro Dermal (EDS) Analysis to show imbalances in the body. Learn the identifiers and symptoms. Explore and understand ways of tick and Lyme prevention. Listen and share with others personal experiences with Lyme and how to deal with and overcome obstacles that you are facing with this disease. Find out about treatment options and how to combat Lyme from every angle. The questionnaire takes about 20 minutes to complete and the EDS testing will take about 15 minutes to complete. Those identified as a Lyme's candidate will be given a referral to see Dr. Marie Dam at a fee to be diagnosed and to take the next steps toward removing Lyme from the body. Appointments for Dr. Dam will be begin scheduling for Friday, July 20th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first step to education many people who are out there that need help. Please tell your friends that might suspect that this may be in their system or even those that have been sick and are getting no anwers elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.thehsccenter.com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342570484000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342192479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Lyme Clinic for identifying and educationing</name><id>73194092</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342558800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/73194092/</event_url></item>