<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;November's meeting will have a few items on the agenda. Election of Officers for Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 for year&amp;nbsp;2012. (Yes, I'm stepping aside to help change and improve the FPA). Please contact Ed Murphy, Jim Bisson or Larry McGee ASAP if interested in a leadership role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, on the list is FAA FAASTEAM Jim Adams will present &lt;strong&gt;The Wright Brothers Master Pilot Award to our own Vinny Manduca&lt;/strong&gt;. Vinny has been a safe flying pilot for over 50 years!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wright Brothers Master Pilot Award&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I am convinced that human flight is both possible and practical." &lt;br /&gt;

Wilbur Wright, 1899&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Wright Brothers Master Pilot Award recognizes pilots who have demonstrated professionalism, skill and aviation expertise by maintaining safe operations for 50 or more years. Recipients are awarded a certificate and a lapel pin and are recognized in our Wright Brothers Master Pilot Award - Roll of Honor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also&amp;nbsp;have a guest speaker. From 1941, Joe Poshefko worked as an AVG (American Volunteer Group) in China. a Chief Armorer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/d/c/2/event_64604482.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joseph Poshefko never aimed to become one of World War II's enduring legends as an original member of the famed "Flying Tigers."&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;After completing his first year of college, Joe entered the U.S. Army Air Corps and was stationed at Langley Field, Virginia, in 1937.&amp;nbsp; He later was assigned to the 65th Squadron of the 57th Fighter Group.&amp;nbsp; He was recruited by Skip Adair, along with 19 others, and left the 57th to join the AVG in 1941. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1941, the Chinese brought together a group of Americans to help them train in aeirel combat. With President Roosevelts permission, 87 pilots and 165 ground personnel headed to meet up with 100 P-40 Fighter planes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were three squadrons, Adam and Eve, Panda Bears and the Hell's Angels. With only three months of training, between Christmas and New Years, the squads shot down 75 enemy planes and lost only 2 pilots and 6 planes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the next 7 months of war, the 85 surviving pilots and their tiger-toothed P-40's, shot down 299 enemy planes and destroyed another 240 Japenese aircraft! With another 153 "probable" kills while losing only 16 American airmen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outnumbered by as many as 8 to 1, using devoted ground crews and pure will and determination, the Flying Tigers checked the Japenese invasion of China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to our member Bob Hanlon for his contact with Joe Poshefko.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $25 bucks a year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fly Often and Fly Safe, &lt;br /&gt;

Charley&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320958794000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 Monthly Meetup</name><id>lrkdnyppblb</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320793200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/34716592/</event_url></item>