<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ACROSS STREET from 261 Union St. (Crepes Tea House), Ground Floor; Park &amp; enter on the opposite side of the st. from Tea House</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.099113</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>A to Z Moving Company</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>698661</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.617401</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;How about this – the world needs you.&lt;/b&gt; Not a washed out, pale, shadowy version of who you are. Not a stuck, quiet, frustrated, depressed, angry and asleep version of yourself. The world needs the BIG YOU. The fully awake you. The you that is willing to take some risks to make the world, your relationships, and your dreams, shine the way you want them to.  Everything going pretty good these days? Awesome. Then the world needs the you that is ready to be even MORE alive, awake and empowered. The you that knows that growth is a never-ending journey. Are you ready to take the next step in your journey?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have been meeting weekly for over two years.&lt;/b&gt; We help one another through mentoring, exploration, truth telling and building safe spaces to share our lives. This is the continuing work of our circle; to heal, to empower, to trust, to connect, to continue our personal evolution as men and as human beings. You are invited to participate in this evolution - and continue on YOUR path. This open men's group is for all men.  This open men's group is FREE. This group is not affiliated with any one spiritual practice, your beliefs are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be holding Open Men's Circles for the next 3 weeks in a row - October 14th, October 21st, October 28th - from 7pm  to 9pm at 380 Union Street, West Springfield - (at A to Z Movers, look for the big trucks - enter the building on the ground floor under the &amp;quot;Auction Preview Sign&amp;quot;) - more info? Call Boysen 413 883 2462.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the cars near the AtoZ Moving Trucks.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256169285000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255489511000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Extra Extra - Open Men's Groups this Month</name><id>11622626</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255561200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/11622626/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/d/global_4591725.jpeg</photo_url></item>