<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first picnic! Come and spend all afternoon in the park. It's okay... go ahead and take your shoes off and walk barefoot in the grass. Come and spend the afternoon hanging out in the sun and in the grass. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While I was living in Manhattan, instead of brunch, sometimes my friends and I would have a huge picnic in the park and hangout all afternoon eating and lounging on blankets or in the grass and playing wiffle ball and touch football all afternoon. Afterward... sometimes we'd all head over someones apt for wine and cheese and then gather at our favorite neighborhood hangout. And, sometimes we'd continue the evening at our favorite 24hr diner, talking with Pete, the old man and our friend behind the counter until 4a.m. Pete always remembered our names and what we liked. It was the coolest thing - all of us sitting there together talking; and talking with Pete.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doesn't this sound like a lot of fun :O) Needless to say, here I am trying to get some of this back here in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When and where?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: May 3rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Place: Boston Common &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 12PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not your typical picnic! It is going to be big! There will be tons of food/drinks and all kind of activities/games (i.e. twister, frisbee, wiffle ball, kick ball, football, etc...) Let's get creative :] It will be a lot of fun! Please send me your ideas, thoughts and suggestions... Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you at our first ever picnic! It's going to be a ton of fun!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservation will be under Mike/Meet up</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241540564000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234003827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Co-Event w/Girls with Moxie Picnic: Spend All Afternnoon Hanging Out in The Park</name><id>9692197</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241366400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9692197/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/5/global_7605045.jpeg</photo_url></item>