<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hiking about 2.5 miles of very pleasent forest and ledge starting at the pond and going up a hillside to the Hop River Linear Trail (i.e. Rails-To-Trails in Vernon area). Depending on the whim of the group we can visit the ledge of the cliffs over the park, explore the deeper reaches of the park and see the &amp;quot;hidden&amp;quot; soccer field, or continue in forested trail. We could even stick to the Hop River linear Trail and make it to the railroad cut and pass between the cliffs in Bolton. Generally, we'll hike major portions of the Blue/Yellow blazed trail that loops around the park &amp;amp; possibly other blazed portions within the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot at 5:30 PM and head out to hike the trail. The hike should take about 1.25 hrs. and we should be done by 6:45 PM. There is no meal planned after this hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 8.5 miles of blazed trails in the park, as well as a playground, picnic pavilion, toilet facilities and a swimming beach. Portions of the park contain riuns of textile mills and an early trout hatchery and have been declared a national historic site. The park is heavily used for swimming, picnicking, hiking, x-country skiing, fishing, wild flower &amp;amp; wildlife observation and a scenic vista.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;)  is leading on this one so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A park map can be found in the document link. Look at page 13.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.munic.state.ct.us/vernon/VRTT.pdf"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.munic.state.ct.us/vernon/VRTT.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.munic.stat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1151944058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Valley Falls Park in Vernon CT</name><id>5006527</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1152567000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5006527/</event_url></item>