<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/a/6/event_149533222.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Please read the liabilty waiver at the end of the hike description.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to begin your quest to complete the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weber 40&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; this is a great place to begin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barden Reservoir is a pond in Foster and is part of the Scituate Reservoir system.  This hike is more of a scenic walk on mainly dirt roads rather than a strenuous hike.  It is approximately four miles and we'll be doing it at a slow to moderate pace so it should take us about two hours to complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll see the remnants of some old mills and a historic cemetary or two along with an earthen damn that turns into a large waterfall when the water levels are high.  This land is well protected and with any luck we'll see some wildlife, so bring your cameras.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd rank this hike as easy to slightly moderate because of some climbing.  Proper footware is required  because there are rocks and it only takes one to sprain an ankle (yes, that's experience speaking).  The weather is starting to warm up so remember to hydrate and bring snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn west onto Central Pike off Route 102 in Scituate.  In just over 1 1/2 miles you'll enter Foster and reach a bridge.  Cross the bridge where you'll find more room to park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Safety First!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Ed after you cross the bridge (intersection of Central Pike and Rams Tails Rd)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ed</member_name><member_id>51524592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367770603000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366830859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Barden Reservoir-Ken Weber's Hike #23</name><id>115992862</id><headcount>13</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367672400000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/115992862/</event_url></item>