<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Exchange Street</address_1><state>Rh</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.827023</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jacky's Waterplace &amp; Sushi Bar</name><city>Providence</city><id>7147822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.412300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurants and events in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Jacky's Waterplace &amp;amp; Sushi Bar overlooking Waterplace Park downtown!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacky's (part of the infamous and RI-only Jacky's Galaxie restaurants) opened this upscale restaurant last year. The interior is definitely razzle dazzle and offers spectacular views of Waterplace Park and the PVD skyline from the bar, lounge, dining room AND (the best part) OUTDOOR BALCONY!!!! They have something for everyone on the menu, and as we discerning, if not a little spoiled RI diners already know, the food is pretty great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've already been here for music, apps and drinks on a Saturday night. It has a HUGE central bar with comfortable lounge seating all around and music on the weekends, so its a great place to catch a bite before a show or just to hang out on a weekend (or weeknight) evening! It was a great time when I went before and now we're making it an official MNM!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is FREE VALET PARKING after 5pm!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://jackyswaterplace.com/"&gt;http://jackyswaterplace.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one has been on the "go to" list for awhile, so let's check it out! (and you thought I might have forgotten this week........ ;-))&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Meetup. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a bright blue, gradated-dyed scarf, but we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337125609000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336713433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Jacky's Waterplace!!!!!</name><id>64350942</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337032800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/64350942/</event_url></item>