<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The sap is running, which means it’s maple syrup season here in Connecticut, so I thought it might be fun to visit a traditional sugarhouse. Did you know although Connecticut is the third smallest state in the nation it is one of the nation’s leaders in producing 100% Pure Maple Syrup? The traditional maple sugaring season in Connecticut extends from early February until late March, depending greatly on the weather.  Freezing nights and warm, sunny days are necessary for the maple tree to yield sap, a colorless liquid with a light, sweet taste.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a field trip to a family run sugarhouse where we will have a private “class” which will include a presentation on the sugaring process, a history of sugaring and other fascinating facts about maple, viewing tapped trees, a guided tour of the sugarhouse facility and equipment, and possibly watching them boil sap. The class lasts approximately 1 1/2 hours, and costs &lt;b&gt;$5 per person&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The farm is located in East Hartland, so I thought we could set up car pooling – meeting at Caryl’s house in West Hartford in time to depart for the farm at 12:30 pm. If you plan to come, let me know if you want to car pool, and if you want to be one of the drivers. Those who live closer to East Hartland (Avon for example) may want to set up another designated meeting spot. Once we know who is attending, we’ll get a better idea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also – dress appropriately – it could be snowy or muddy out by the sap trees – boots are recommended!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer</member_name><member_id>3917688</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268073176000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267203013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Field Trip to a Sugarhouse</name><id>12716540</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267900200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/12716540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/4/8/global_13330424.jpeg</photo_url></item>