<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Car camp Saturday night- Call Scott or Diane for location $5 to join us&lt;/b&gt; and We'll hit the trail at 5:30am.  No source for water filtering for 7 miles until Rocky Branch trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancels this swampy rock hopping hike. Bug spray and zip off hiking pants in case of black flies. Sounds like fun, right? Actually on nice day this trail can be fun and does have its personality. On a bad day it has been ugly though so that is why its is fair weather only with strong hikers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/8/highres_2223640.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There can only be 10 hikers in this group as we are in a wilderness designated area. U.S.F.S. rules. This round trip traverse up Glen Boulder Trail to Mount Isolation (4003') and out Rocky Branch is 13.3 miles, an elevation gain of 3,800' in a book time of 9 hours that will likely take 10-11 hours. All, as usual, are welcome to join in the fun, share good fellowship &amp;amp; the awesome views!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SINCE SPACE IS LIMITED, PLEASE KEEP YOUR RSVP UP TO DATE. WE'RE LOOKING FORWARD TO A GREAT HIKE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Isolation  route: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spot cars at Rocky Branch (end), then drive a few cars to  &lt;br /&gt;Glen Boulder where we will hike Glen Boulder trail 3.2 miles&amp;gt;, &lt;br /&gt;Davis path to summit isolation on the Mt Isolation Spur .7 miles, retrace to Isolation path&amp;gt;, 7.04 mi. &lt;br /&gt;after Shelter # 2 Rest break at shelter, filter water, and descend rocky branch trail for the final 2-3 hours/3.70 miles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total 13.45 mi  average book time 10 hr 45 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must be a seasoned hiker for this hike. For this summer hike Don't forget sunscreen, trekking poles, a hat, leg gaitors, sock change, rain poncho, bug spray, extra food and drink powders/water filter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book time will vary with the condition of the hikers and elements. Sweep (end team) will insure that all hikers have finished&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Cars will be at the end of hike at Rocky Branch. and Cars will be at the start</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215890472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Experienced hikers needed for trail support on this advanced level hike. Those n</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210806664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Isolation/or Glen Boulder Sunrise Hike</name><id>7940019</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215336600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7940019/</event_url></item>