<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Photo Plus</address_2><address_1>655 West 34th Street</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10001</zip><lat>40.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>774-239-0214</phone><name>Jacob K. Javits Convention Center</name><city>New York</city><id>199356</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.989998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dramatic Landscapes:&lt;br /&gt;A Lecture By Ron Rosenstock&lt;br /&gt;Friday, Feb 9, 2007 6-8pm&lt;br /&gt;AutumnColor Digital Imaging, 70 Webster Street, Worcester, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Join Us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Outdoor lovers and photographers alike! Join us for an evening of dramatic landscapes and images from abroad, including Iceland, Italy, Morocco, and Peru! All will be on view in the AutumnColor Gallery starting promptly at 6:00pm on the evening of February 9th. This lecture is FREE to all those interested in attending!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RON ROSENSTOCK, known for his photographic work in black and white for over 40 years, will be giving a lecture on some of his latest works?in COLOR!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A student of Minor White, Ron?s images are in the permanent collections of the Fogg Art Museum at Harvard University, The International Center of Photography in NYC, and The Worcester Art Museum in Worcester, MA. Ron is a former Instructor of Photography at Clark University in Worcester, MA and a founding member of the Worcester Center for Crafts. He presently conducts photo tours to Ireland, Italy, Peru, Morocco, New Zealand, and within the United States.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book Signing! After the lecture Ron Rosenstock will be making his books available for sale and signing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171299044000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169504976000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dramatic Landscapes: A Lecture By Ron Rosenstock</name><id>5416031</id><headcount>47</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171062000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/5416031/</event_url></item>