<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I know some of you already know about this, but the Friends of Cavaliers group is having their Annual Holiday Party.  I was waiting to make sure it was okay with Karen (party hostess) to post this info on the Meetup website, and she emailed me to say she'd love to meet us all and our doggies!  (I think some of you have already been to a Pawty.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's not really necessary to RSVP on Meetup, but I'd like to know who is going so I can look out for you and we can finally meet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5th Annual FOC Xmas Pawty&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's the Pawty of the season you won't want to miss it!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come with the fur kids and enjoy good food, titillating conversation, a game or two for the guys.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring one special little present for our shelter baskets!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to wear your party hats, bring your cameras and come prepared to have lots of fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Grinches or bah-humbugging allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: December 15, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1:00- 5:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Place: The Pawty House of Karen &amp;amp; Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Menu is whatever is brought.  There will be a couple of raffles and they will also collect treats, etc. for animal shelters.  And if you wish to donate anything for soldiers in Iraq, they are taking collections for that as well.  :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress your little furry people up if you wish!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, they are also going to have photos with &amp;quot;Santa Claus&amp;quot; for your pooches!  One of the people who is going will take the photos and download them onto a CD for you.  Bring a CD if you'd like to take advantage of this generous offer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>790021</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197915141000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196181633000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friends of Cavaliers Holiday Pawty!</name><id>6811942</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197741600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/6811942/</event_url></item>