<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The new film by Majid Majidi (&lt;i&gt;The Color of Paradise, Children of Heaven&lt;/i&gt;) tells the gently humorous story of ordinary guy Karim (Reza Naji, winner Best Actor at the Berlin Film Festival) as he struggles to support his family. He loses his well-paid job at an ostrich farm when a particularly ornery bird escapes and cannot be recaptured. Driving his moped in to Tehran to try to fix his deaf daughter's hearing aid, Karim accidentally finds himself embarking on a profitable new career when a harried businessman jumps on and demands a ride. But exposure to heavy traffic and big city values starts to corrupt Karim's once generous and honest nature, much to the concern of his family, who want the old Karim back. Majidi's lyrical storytelling shines in this simple but affecting tale. Grammy-nominated composer and musician Hossein Alizadeh, a master tar and setar player, provides the haunting score. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thesongofsparrowsmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Song of Sparrows Web Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the NYT Critic's Pick review:  Iran’s submission for the foreign-language Oscar in 2008, it may be the most religious movie released in the United States by Mr. Majidi, whose best-known films, “Children of Heaven,” “The Color of Paradise” and “Baran,” helped put Iranian cinema on the world map. In “The Willow Tree” (2005), his most recent film to be seen here, a blind professor of literature miraculously regains his sight but quickly sinks into despair, disgusted by the world he discovers outside his imagination and by his own image in the mirror. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've never seen &lt;i&gt;Children of Heaven,&lt;/i&gt; I highly recommend you netflix the film, even if you cannot attend &lt;i&gt;Song of Sparrows&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we'll attempt to get a table at &lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;The Friendly Toast&lt;/span&gt;. Those who've been to the Telluride By the Sea Film Festival in Portsmouth, New Hampshire are familiar with the original &lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;Friendly Toast&lt;/span&gt;, a family friendly restaurant. Great food and a great place for a group discussion - provided there is space for us on a Saturday night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time approximate. Specific start time to be posted later in the week.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing in front of spare rows holding a Meetup Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243115013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Song of Sparrows</name><id>10478948</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243725300000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10478948/</event_url></item>