<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We were unable to hold an actual Pow Wow, this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its place, I'll post reviews of films that we would have discussed at the Pow Wow in order to help everyone make choices.  Those with high rating in bold.  Please feel free to add comments so that it will feel like we held a Virtual Pow Wow, and use this space to hook up with other members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12:00 - The Land of Eb - IMDB: 7.5 - Jacob, a humble, hardworking refugee of the Marshall Islands, heroically struggles to support his family in his adopted home on the Big Island of Hawaii after he is diagnosed with stomach cancer. &lt;br /&gt;

 "&lt;span&gt;A rare, extraordinary film that celebrates the dignity of hard work, as well as the tenuous connections of cultural legacy in a fragmented community....&lt;/span&gt; Don't miss this one if it comes to a film festival by you."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;12:15 - The Defector - Escape from North Korea - IMDB: 4.5 - Dragon smuggles North Korean defectors across borders for a living, and his latest undercover trip with Sook-Ja and Yong-hee takes an unexpected turn when they are left stranded in China. This is just the start of an extraordinary 5,000 km journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;12:30 - &lt;strong&gt;(BRATTLE)&lt;/strong&gt; The Garden of Eden - No Reviews - Israel’s idyllic Gan HaShlosha National Park, better known as the &lt;em&gt;Sakhne&lt;/em&gt;, serves as the picturesque backdrop for a portrait of the multilayered Israeli national character.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;12:45 - The Elders - No Reviews - A feature-length documentary, The Elders uses stylized interview portraits of elderly individuals to tell a universal story about life's most important lessons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;2:00 - Laurence Anyways - IMDB: 7.2&lt;/span&gt;/&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RT: 78% &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;The 10-year relationship of a male-to-female transsexual with her lover. "A sumptuously orchestrated love story about a transsexual man's decade-long struggle to maintain a passionate romance with his female soulmate in the face of creeping hostility from friends, family and society."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;2:30 - Here One Day - No Reviews - A longing daughter discovers intimate, dramatic audiotapes left behind by her bipolar mother, who committed suicide. The film follows her family through life, devastation, tragedy, and rebirth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;2:45 - Remote Area Medical - No Reviews - A pop-up medical clinic for the rural poor in Tennessee illuminates the failures of modern medical care in America.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3:00 - Future My Love - IMDB:  6.3 -&lt;/span&gt; An experimental documentary that explores our dual fascination with destruction and relentless optimism about the future.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;3:00 - &lt;strong&gt;(BRATTLE)&lt;/strong&gt; - Gideon's Army - IMDB: 4.0 - Follows three young, committed Public Defenders who are dedicated to working for the people society would rather forget. Long hours, low pay and staggering caseloads are so common that even the most committed often give up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;3:30 - Twenty Feet From Stardom -IMDB: 6.9 - Filmmaker Morgan Neville pays homage to some of the greatest vocalists you've never heard of in this documentary. While the lead singers in rock, pop, and R&amp;amp;B are the ones who get the glory, knowledgeable music fans will tell you the backing vocalists often add the touches that make a performance truly memorable, and though many backup singers have the respect of their peers in the music business, they're all but unknown to the average listener. "REASONS TO GO: Amazing music and spiritually uplifting. Everything a documentary should be."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please feel free to add a comment to meetup with other members, or to add information for any film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367176857000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366574604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Afternoon Films at the BFF</name><id>115461362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367164800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/115461362/</event_url></item>