<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>[b]"With "WALL-E," Pixar at last takes the great leap forward many of us knew the company had in it. A "family movie" in name and MPAA rating only, it's a major visionary work, a sci-fi parable of astonishing scope and depth that is anchored by an adorable bucket of bolts and yoked to a sensibility that is - there's no other word for it - furious. It's also, by a substantial margin, the best American film of the year to date."[/b]

[b]Review:[/b]
&lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/ae/movies/articles/2008/06/26/out_of_this_world/?page=full" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.boston.com/ae/movies/articles/2008/06/26/out_of_this_world/?page=full&lt;/a&gt;

I now know the movie time. The movie is at 7:05. And it will be upstairs in theater 14. 

[b]How to find me[/b]

I will be at the movie theater at 6:35. I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. The movie is upstairs, at theater 14. I'll be at the tables near the huge front window on the second floor. We'll head in to the theater ten minutes before showtime. a.k.a 6:55.

After the movie, we gather just outside the theater doors (the theater where the movie is showing that is, not outside.) and talk about where we're going for food and drinks. Sometimes I lose people at that point - and I'm not sure if it's because I just lost someone or they didn't want to come to dinner. So, if you are coming to dinner, please find me after the show. I will be wearing that red hat. 'Cause that's my job - to wear the hat!

[b]Synopsis[/b]

What if mankind had to leave Earth, and somebody forgot to turn the last robot off?

Academy Award®-winning writer-director Andrew Stanton ("Finding Nemo") and the inventive storytellers and technical geniuses at Pixar Animation Studios ("The Incredibles," "Cars," "Ratatouille") transport moviegoers to a galaxy not so very far away for a new computer-animated cosmic comedy about a determined robot named WALL?E.

After hundreds of lonely years of doing what he was built for, WALL?E (short for Waste Allocation Load Lifter Earth-Class) discovers a new purpose in life (besides collecting knick-knacks) when he meets a sleek search robot named EVE. EVE comes to realize that WALL?E has inadvertently stumbled upon the key to the planet's future, and races back to space to report her findings to the humans (who have been eagerly awaiting word that it is safe to return home). Meanwhile, WALL?E chases EVE across the galaxy and sets into motion one of the most exciting and imaginative comedy adventures ever brought to the big screen.

Joining WALL?E on his fantastic journey across a universe of never-before-imagined visions of the future, is a hilarious cast of characters including a pet cockroach, and a heroic team of malfunctioning misfit robots.

Filled with surprises, action, humor and heart, "WALL?E" was written and directed by Andrew Stanton, produced by Jim Morris, co-produced by Lindsey Collins and features original and innovative sound design by Academy Award®-winner Ben Burtt ("Star Wars," "Indiana Jones," "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial").

[b]Trailer 1[/b]
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/Y2yBXGMWRGw&amp;hl=en" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

[b]Trailer 2[/b]
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/mC86heBo0d4&amp;hl=en" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See description for how to find me...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214918265000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210511235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wall-E</name><id>7916727</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214607600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7916727/</event_url></item>