<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>555 Asylum Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767876</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-978-2622</phone><name>ArtSpace</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1045061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.682486</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Wish you were making more progress toward achieving your health goals and New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions? &amp;nbsp;Want to get rid of what's blocking you? &amp;nbsp;Looking for support?&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If so, join our discussion!&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Amy LaBossiere, a holistic health coach, will be facilitating a dialogue where we&amp;rsquo;ll address these questions:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;bull; What have you done in the last year to Upgrade Your Life?&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;bull; What are the obstacles to an Upgrade? &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;bull; What areas of your life do you need to Upgrade:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Diet?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Exercise?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Self-Care? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about our efforts to get healthy and boost our lifestyles toward greater wellness, vibrancy, and authentic body weight. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about our efforts to boost our energy, achieve greater mental clarity, get better sleep, and achieve authentic body weight, and we'll discuss any other health goals people have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy will present recommendations for how you can create your unique path to wellness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the end of the night, you will possess greater self-awareness and feel more confident and inspired about what steps to take next. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please bring an open mind, questions, success stories, and ideas to share with the group!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Amy LaBossiere: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Amy has been working professionally in communications for more than 20 years, including stints in various small to mid-size advertising agencies and an alternative magazine as editor. She currently works from home as a consultant in marketing and holistic health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy found a passion for health while pursuing her Master&amp;rsquo;s in Conscious Evolution, and after she earned her masters, she enrolled at the Institute for Integrative Nutrition. She is a certified holistic health coach who helps individuals achieve greater health and happiness. &amp;nbsp;She is certified by the American Association of Drugless Practitioners as a board-certified Holistic Health Practitioner.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amy is also a mixed media artist and co-owner at Still Waters, a seasonal retreat center in Eastern Connecticut where she plans, schedules and facilitates retreats and cooks nourishing, plant-based meals for groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***************************************&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Schedule for the evening: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 pm: Potluck Dinner begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:45 - 8:30 pm: Discussion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 pm -&amp;nbsp; 9:30 on: &amp;nbsp;Hanging out and clean up&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through the backdoor by the murals.  Walk down the long corridor.  At the end of the corridor is the art gallery where we meet.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>13105264</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336699189000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332983644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion about "Upgrading Your Life For Optimal Wellness!" &amp; Potluck Dinner</name><id>58311292</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336518000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/58311292/</event_url></item>