<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;yes....this is way last minute, but what the hell...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;!!Welcome to the return of $5 movie night at showcase north haven!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I checked the movie listings for this week and found it so chock full of delicious schlock that I just can't resist, rarely does this much b-movie dreck appear at one time and under one roof outside of an X-rated theatre in mexico.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's so much choice rancid meat that I truly can't decide what to dine on, so here is my (admittedly half ass) plan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be at Barnes and noble reading magazines, if anyone wants to attend please stop in by 6:30 and we will vote on a movie (most films start at 7).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The choices are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FRACTURE : Anthony Hopkins finally accepts that he will have &amp;quot;Hannibal Lecter&amp;quot; carved on his tombstone and decides he may as well continue to get payed for it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE CONDEMNED:  Hell yeah!  This bad boy stars non other than the WWF bionic redneck himself Stone Cold Steve Austin a full 5 years after anyone remembers who the heck Stone Cold Steve Austin is....I'm glad I don't own stock in this film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEXT : Nope, not the film of the MTV dating show (although that would probably be better).  Basically Nic Cage travels through time and tries to prevent himself from making Ghost Rider.  Here is what one reviewer has to say : &amp;quot;Jessica Biel puts in an Oscar worthy performance to make us believe a hot babe like her would be interested in a balding, creepy guy twice her age like Nic Cage, so give her some props&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IN THE LAND OF WOMEN: Meg Ryan proves that CGI digital effects are not nearly as scary as bad plastic surgery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARE WE DONE YET: Ice Cube continues to sell out, as far as I can tell he basically plays a white guy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;KICKIN IT OLD SKOOL : In contrast to the Ice Cube movie Jamie Kennedy plays a black guy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PERFECT STRANGER: This movie is on the brink of receiving a single digit rotten tomatoes rating.  Hopefully it will result in Bruce Willis giving up his movie career to revive &amp;quot;Moonlighting&amp;quot; on TV and Halle Berry descending into porn films.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE INVISIBLE : I'm sure it makes some type of metaphorical commentary on being a teenager and how we should pay attention to them....whatever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VACANCY: Two attractive people are videotaped in a motel room...so what else is new?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IN ADDITION TO THESE FINE CHOICES I MAY PURCHASE SPIDERMAN 3 TICKETS FOR THE THURSDAY MIDNIGHT SHOW SO IF ANYONE IS INTERESTED PLEASE LET ME KNOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave 203-499-7777&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;......and that's the bottom line cause Stone Cold says so&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541364000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178028275000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Got 5 bucks and 2 hours to throw away??</name><id>5728354</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178058600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5728354/</event_url></item>