<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bay State Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.349949</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bay State Underground at BU</name><city>Boston</city><id>777983</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095289</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our very own Zachary Bos is reading at Boston University's Bay State Underground series this Friday, along with Janet Ruth Young and Christen Enos. Zachary is a wonderful poet and reader; this event is one not to miss!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, October 3rd, 7:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The return of The Bay State Underground! &lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by Boston University &lt;br /&gt;and AGNI Magazine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;236 Bay State Road &lt;br /&gt;(BU East T-stop on the Green Line) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zachary Bos : Zachary, former deputy editor of News from the Republic of Letters , is a founding member of the Boston Poetry Union and the Union 's literary imprint, The Pen &amp;amp; Anvil Press. His poetry has most recently appeared in FULCRUM: a journal of poetry and aesthetics. His current projects include a secular English-language redaction of the Koran; a redacted Bible edition entitled 'HOLY'; and a translation of Vicente Huidobro's 1939 novel, Sátiro; o, El poder de las palabras.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Janet Ruth Young: Janet graduated from Salem State College, and from the creative writing program at Boston University . Her last novel, The Opposite of Music (2007, Atheneum/Simon &amp;amp; Schuster), garnered enthusiastic reviews from Booklist, School Library Journal, Publishers Weekly, The Denver Post, and The Boston Globe. It won the PEN NewEngland Discovery Award and was a Book Sense Pick, a Borders Original Voices selection, and an American Library Association Best Books forYoung Adults nominee. She is currently at work on her third young adult novel as well as a breakup memoir, Leaving Leonard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christen Enos: Christen lives and teaches in Boston . Raised in Massachusetts , she studied film as an undergraduate at New York University and received her MFA in creative writing from Emerson College . She has work forthcoming from The Portland Review and The New Orleans Review.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223418875000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222877058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zachary Bos at the Bay State Underground</name><id>8872437</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223074800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/8872437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/5/global_187765.jpeg</photo_url></item>