<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This will be the start of our Online Photoshop series. This Workshop will focus on the basics of Photoshop. Explaining the basic tools of photoshop and working with layers. Layers were first introduced to Photoshop with version 3.0 so any version after that will be ok for this workshop. There are some added features with some of the newer creative suite versions but for this workshop most of the tools and features of 3.0 and beyond will work for this workshop. We will be using Photophlow for our online plateform. We will provide a link to those who sign in including instructions on how to sign in to photophlow. A basic Flickr account is required to log into this Workshop and Photophlow. A basic Flickr membership and access to Photophlow is free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To sign up for a new flickr acct please follow this link&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.flickr.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All our workshops will include tips and tricks on enhancing your photos. For this workshop it will be : Creating a Soft Focus and Glow effect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost for this Workshop is $10.00 and the workshop will run approx 1 hour.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258766100000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256668876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photoshop Online Workshop - Learning the Basics and Layers</name><id>11724972</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258592400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/11724972/</event_url></item>