<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Salut a tout le monde!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A la dernière réunion, il faisait si beau qu'on a pu s'asseoir sur la terrasse.  Et c'était magnifique de s'imaginer à un café en France.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pour le mois de juillet, je vais me servir d'une suggestion d'un de nos membres, alors, je propose qu'on parle de quelque chose qui:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- est français (de France ou de Québec ou de Haïti ou n'importe quel pays francophone), et qui&lt;br /&gt;-- nous rend heureux.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C'est peut-être un verre de vin sur la terrasse d'un café près du Jardin du Luxembourg, ou bien une soirée dansante à la vieille ville de Québec, ou regarder un match de football avec Zédine.  Il y a pas mal de choix, pas vrai?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A bientot,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ &lt;br /&gt;Hi, everybody!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our last meeting, the weather was so nice that we could sit outside on the sidewalk at Starbucks.  It was magnificent to imagine that we were at a French cafe, well, at least that's what I was thinking.  It sure *sounded* that way to me, anyway! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For July, I am going to use a suggestion from one of our members and propose that we each talk about something that:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- is French (from France or Quebec or Haiti or any Francophone country), and that&lt;br /&gt;-- makes us happy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe it's a glass of wine at a cafe near the Luxembourg Garden, or a dance party in the old town of Quebec City, or watching a soccer game with Zedine!  There are quite a few choices, aren't there?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann</member_name><member_id>1968241</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184974909000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>french-584</urlname><id>376538</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Dis-moi French Conversation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183841795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Qu'il fait chaud!</name><id>5988877</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184801400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/french-584/events/5988877/</event_url></item>