<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Riverside Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06880</zip><lat>41.138935</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-222-7070</phone><name>Westport Arts Center</name><city>Westport</city><id>718564</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.363793</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/2/a/event_73040522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Note this date has been changed from 1-6 to 1-13, by the Westport Art Center&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Think if we meet at 6:45 for the show it should be sufficient.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This film is meant to compliment the exhibit on display:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;On Duty: Odermatt, Metinides and Weegee &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the Andrew and Christine Hall Collection&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

For details on the exhibit see below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;THE PUBLIC EYE&amp;rdquo; FILM SCREENING&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join the Westport Arts Center for an evening of wine, discussion, and film, presented by Weegee expert, Miles Barth.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Public Eye&lt;/em&gt; This film is rated "R."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/f/b/event_38459131.jpeg" width="57" height="48" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7-9pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$10.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Order your ticket online from Westport Art Center -&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;see link below&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2&lt;a href="http://www.westportartscenter.org/ev.php?genre=third_thursday#10vapublic"&gt;http://www.westportartscenter.org/ev.php?genre=third_thursday#10vapublic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets go fast for their events, you may want to order ahead, no guarantee at the door!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Miles Barth&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Miles Barth is the founding curator of the Permanent Collection at the International Center of Photography (1979). He has written and/or edited over 12 books on photographers and various aspects of photography and organized numerous exhibitions in the U.S., Europe, Africa and Asia. His book Weegee&amp;rsquo;s World (1997) won several major awards including the best book and exhibition from the International Association of Art Critics, and Best Photography Book of 1998 from the American Photographic Historical Society. Mr. Barth was also the Curator of Photography at the Rubin Museum of Art (2007-2009) and is currently a writer, independent curator and advisor to public, private and corporate photography collections&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Public Eye&amp;rdquo; Plot Summary&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Leon Bernstein is New York's best news photographer in 1942, equally at home with cops or crooks. The pictures are often of death and pain, but they are the ones the others wish they had got. Then glamorous Kay Levitz turns to him when the Mob seem to be muscling in on the club she owns due to some arrangement with her late husband. Bernstein, none too successful with women, agrees to help, saying there may be some good photos in it for him. In fact, he is falling in love with Kay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On view in the gallery:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Duty: Odermatt, Metinides and Weegee &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the Andrew and Christine Hall Collection&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

through Sunday, 1/15/12 &lt;br /&gt;

This exhibition will feature 45 photographs by three important historic photographers &amp;ndash; a Swiss policeman, Arnold Odermatt; a Mexican photojournalist, Enrique Metinides; and New York&amp;rsquo;s Arthur Fellig, known as &amp;ldquo;Weegee.&amp;rdquo; All three, while on duty in their respective &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/1/8/event_74477432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;professions, crossed the line of simply documenting accidents and day-to-day mayhem. The content of the imagery, often tragic, transcends the rawness of the event and moves into the realm of a modernist aesthetic that is both profound and thought provoking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Weegee, Metinides, and Odermatt can be thought of as examples of outsider artists who, like other outsider artists, wittingly or not, presaged ideas and concepts that were developed more willfully by later practitioners working in their medium, in this instance photography. Because of the nature of their creation, one needs have no special knowledge to appreciate these works: what you see is what you see. They are eminently approachable to even the casual viewer &amp;ndash; a refreshing counterpoint to the insider obscurity that shrouds so much contemporary art produced today.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Andrew Hall, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the entry way 6:45 or so.  Will wear the bw scarf with Piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326647539000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321393703000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>“THE PUBLIC EYE” FILM SCREENING</name><id>41300582</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326498300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/41300582/</event_url></item>