<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 West St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 587-1011</phone><name>NORTHAMPTON MA_ FORBES LIBRARY </name><city>Northampton </city><id>832342</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sir-Laugh-a-lot (aka Mark Sherry) will be your laughter guide to an evening of fun and laughter. Meet new friends in a fun non-threatening atmosphere. Just bring with you some child-like playfulness and an openness to laugh and connect with other people!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt; Other people will be joining us who are not coming through Meetup.com so our numbers will be greater than only those signed up here&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughter has many proven physical benefits: It boosts the immune system's production of disease-fighting T-cells, releases endorphins that serve as natural pain killers and make us feel good, helps reduce stress, anxiety &amp;amp; blood pressure by lowering the level of the stress hormone cortisol, provides aerobic exercise &amp;amp; promotes muscle tone, increases blood flow thereby bringing more oxygen to body cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our evening will be based on activities used in Laughter Yoga, a branch of Yoga developed in India by Dr Madan Kataria. There are now over 6,000 Laughter Yoga clubs all around the world. 
&lt;em&gt;If you never done any yoga before don't worry--NO physical yoga postures or poses will be used.&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Laughter Yoga&amp;trade; is not recommended for people suffering from uncontrolled high blood pressure, heart disease, epilepsy, any kind of hernia , severe backache and major psychiatric disorders. If in doubt about your medical condition consult a medical professional for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Donations are gratefully accepted (Suggested donation $3-$5)&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Come and join us !
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt; Other people will be joining us who are not coming through Meetup.com so our numbers will be greater than only those signed up here.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Route 91 Exit 18 left turn, slight left at Conz St, left at Main St, left at Route 66 20 yards to Library on left</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Sherry</member_name><member_id>5650811</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311824962000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Partners in Laughter</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup</urlname><id>1384386</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Laughter is the Best Medicine and Fun Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309925863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Laugh for Your Health with Sir-Laugh-a-lot!</name><id>24710781</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311634800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup/events/24710781/</event_url></item>