<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>in front of Yale Art Gallery</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.330000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Corner of York and Chapel</name><city>New Haven</city><id>240813</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.940000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>some of you have no doubt been asking yourselves, &amp;quot;where can I go to see men in skirts AND get sloshed in public?&amp;quot; well here's your answer: New Haven's 51st annual St. Patrick's Day Parade!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;not sure why it ever became illegal to drink on the streets in most towns, but good old New Haven makes an exception for the St. Patty's parade. so strap a quarter-keg to your back and come on out for a raucous good time. after all, it's what St. Patrick would have wanted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;starting at 12:15 we will be staking out the corner of York and Chapel streets in front of the Yale Art Gallery, and the word is that YAG is generously allowing parade-watchers to use their facilities (maybe they figure it's easier to clean the restrooms than the Gallery's outside walls...though that didn't seem to be much of a deterrent last year).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the parade starts at 1pm this year, and don't forget, daylight savings starts on parade day this year! (that's spring forward). those driving should be able to find parking in the York Street garage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for more info on the parade, &lt;a href="http://www.stpatricksdayparade.org/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;click here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i, ben, will be your contact for this event. if you have trouble finding me, give me a call: 203-554-5144&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;post-parade-party tbd. maybe liffey's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177474858000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173203866000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sun. 3/11 - St. Patty's Parade - Get a little Irish in you!</name><id>5542354</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1173629700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5542354/</event_url></item>