<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E. Pleasant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01002</zip><lat>42.378838</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>413-549-0077</phone><name>The Pub Amherst</name><city>Amherst</city><id>629193</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.519950</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come Celebrate Summer Solstice with us at the U-Mass Amherst Sunwheel ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this meet-up we will be going out to dinner, in Amherst at 5:00 pm at the: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pub Amherst&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We checked it out, and this place has a very nice atmosphere, and all kinds of reasonably priced food, &lt;br /&gt;that will satisfy everyone. They have appetizers, soups, salads, steaks, prime rib, chicken dishes,&lt;br /&gt; B-b-que ribs and chicken, fish, and pasta dishes- $8.95- $18.95. &lt;br /&gt;For the menu and more details&lt;br /&gt;you can them out at the following website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.virtual-valley.com/thepub/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.virtual-va...&lt;/a&gt; - 3k&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(please note, they do not have an official website-this is someone else's website, and DOES NOT&lt;br /&gt;have the full menu on it- it does not list even half of the things....what they do have is listed above)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE: I MUST have your DEFINATE RSVP by Sunday, June 15th for numbers to give the restaurant!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We will then be celebrating the Solstice at the standing stones, as the sun sets &lt;br /&gt;over the stones at 7:30 pm. There will be a woman there, Dr. Judith Young, who will give us a special&lt;br /&gt;presentation. (more details to come on this!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is a SUNWHEEL?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNWHEEL is a SOLAR CALENDAR and OBSERVATORY; perhaps the best known example of a Sunwheel is Stonehenge. A Sunwheel is an outdoor stone circle whose standing stones line up with the locations on the horizon of the rising and setting Sun at the times of the solstices and equinoxes. A Sunwheel on our University campus will provide an EXPERIENTIAL basis for University students, for school children, and for the general public to learn about and understand the cycles exhibited by the Sun throughout the year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT IS THE PURPOSE OF A SUNWHEEL?&lt;br /&gt; For thousands of years, human beings have been intrigued by the cycles in nature. Astronomically, these cycles include the daily rising and setting of the Sun, Moon and stars, the monthly cycle of phases of the Moon, and the yearly cycle of the seasons. The long-term repeatability of these cycles provided an indication to human beings throughout time of the presence of order in the Universe. Cultures which depended upon farming learned how to use the Sun as a calendar, and in particular, to mark the seasons through observations of the location of sunrise and sunset along the horizon (cf. Hawkins 1965; Willimason 1984). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some cultures also used these observations of the Sun to indicate the proper times for ceremonies. Indeed, circles of standing stones with solar alignments, and occasionally lunar alignments, are found throughout the world (Zink 1979). These stone circles were constructed with a detailed knowledge of astronomy, and they represented the importance of the Sun and Moon for peoples of a wide variety of cultures on Earth, dating as far back as 4,800 B.C. (Zink 1979). Even in the technologically advanced age in which we live, and whether we pay attention or not, the pattern in the locations and times of the rising and setting of the Sun and Moon continue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THROUGH THE SUNWHEEL, which concretely illustrates the variations in the Sun's position on the horizon during the year, VISITORS WILL GAIN A GREATER AWARENESS AND UNDERSTANDING OF ASTRONOMY. Furthermore, the Sunwheel provides not only a scientific learning experience, but also a cultural, historical, and social one as well. It is a compelling symbol of the connection between our modern society and our past. At the same time, the Sunwheel represents the present-day connection between our planet Earth and the expansive Universe which we see around us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the UMass Sunwheel standing stones, go to the following link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.umass.edu/sunwheel/index2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.umass.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, they also sell:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; T-shirts: $17.95&lt;br /&gt;Sweatshirts: $25.95&lt;br /&gt;Hooded-Sweatshirts: $35.00&lt;br /&gt;Tote Bags: $18.95&lt;br /&gt;Note Cards: $2.00 ea&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not sure if you will be able to buy them there, or if you will have to order them.&lt;br /&gt;There are (2) designs, the picture on this site &lt;br /&gt;(Day of the Winter Solstice)&lt;br /&gt;and one that is the Summer Solstice Sunset. (not shown)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be writing the director, so more information will be posted on this site before the meet-up&lt;br /&gt;so check back for more details! :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions to the restaurant will be up a week before the meet-up- Say you are with the Meet-up at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214430058000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Because you will be with a great bunch of people, celebrating Mid-Summer Solstice, and it will be an educational experience! :)</why><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210027341000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Solstice Celebration at Amherst Sunwheel</name><id>7879267</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214082000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/7879267/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/b/global_4320379.jpeg</photo_url></item>