<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Still Walking&lt;/b&gt; Japan 2008 114 min.  written and directed by Hirokazu Koreeda  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Note&lt;/b&gt; The film will start at 1:10 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transcendent...Completely Absorbing, so sure of its own scale and scope that while you’re watching it, the rest of the world fades into irrelevance. NY Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Writer/director Hirokazu Kore-eda's characters come sharply to life, exchanging dialogue that both delight and tug at your heart. As the film unfolds, brimming with compelling realism, it reveals the modest joys and gentle sorrows that accompany the realization that life must inevitably move on. The Yokoyamas are a typical dysfunctional family, bonded by love as well as resentments and secrets. With a subtle balance of gentle humor and wistful sorrow, Kore-eda (Nobody Knows, After Life, Maborosi) portrays just how difficult, and exactly how precious, family can be. Kendall Description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This small gem of a movie always feels true and real as it gently reveals the quiet moments that define our lives. L.A. Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An usually insightful rendering of an ordinary family, Hirokazu Kore-eda's contemplative Japanese drama is the sort of movie that makes its greatest impact long after you've seen it. Several films have recently tackled the themes found here, but few with Kore-eda's subtle grace. Unemployed Ryota  has returned home to mark the 15th anniversary of his brother's death, a tragedy that remains the central focus of his parents' lives. Nothing goes right, but how could it? Everyone is firmly encased in their own emotions. Kore-eda has an extraordinary grasp on his characters, modest people who clearly mean a great deal to him. They will to you, as well. NY Daily News &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the more accomplished and beautiful films released thus far this year. Washington Post &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of us had the opportunity to see &lt;b&gt;Still Walking&lt;/b&gt; at the Boston Independent Film Festival this year as it won the Fan's Favorite Award with only about 30 people in attendance (everyone must have given it more than 5 stars!). We had an engaging and lively conversation afterward and I anticipate yet another as we discuss this new film from one of the world's most underrated  directors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And yes, after the film we will go to a nearby restaurant for our post-film discussion. &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there-&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252455854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Still Walking at Kendall</name><id>11323245</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253466000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11323245/</event_url></item>