<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>730 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 868-8800</phone><name>Tavern in the Square - Central Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>680367</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105103</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come and meet other Boston area Sci-Fi and Fantasy fans in a comfortable setting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is our regular social meetup, which always happens on the First Tuesday of every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Holiday season is in full swing, if you're interested in doing an inexpensive gift swap at this meetup (no more than $20), please email me! If there is enough interest, I'll set it up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, we will have LOTS of giveaways this month including:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Star Trek Movie pins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Star Trek Movie Posters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Star Trek Movie DVD (1)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Autographed Star Trek Movie Prequel Comics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Thanks to Blockbuster Video for providing the freebies!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, we're going back to Tavern in the Square in Central Square (NOTE: NOT THE ONE IN PORTER SQUARE). This will be our regular meeting space, barring conflicts, because we effectively have a private room to ourselves! Just ask at the entrance for the SciFi meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're taking the T, Central Square is on the Red Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll probably talk about the books, television, movies, comics and games that we like (and those we don't like, and even those we may be ashamed to admit that we like), but there is no set agenda!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're can't come on time, that's fine, there is usually still a critical mass of people until 10:30 PM (or later). If you want to come early, that is fine too, I usually get there around 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have SciFi/Fantasy Books or DVDs that you don't want anymore? Feel free to bring them to the meetup and give them away (please, no sales here), but be sure that you take home anything that is left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom "spot" Callaway</member_name><member_id>2590946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259885503000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257196198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Social Meetup</name><id>11774052</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259712000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/11774052/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/global_8154265.jpeg</photo_url></item>