<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>66 Maple St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.567062</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-777-1879</phone><name>Toys N Things</name><city>Danvers</city><id>1079316</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.937019</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The newest Toys N Things meetup is to give players a chance to check out the Players Handbook III while trying to prevent a rift to the Far Realms from expanding further on the mortal world. Thanks to events like the &lt;i&gt;Dawn War&lt;/i&gt; the wards which protect the mortal world from the effects of the Far Realms have been weakened. So strange beings are now being seen near the town of &lt;i&gt;Beorunna’s Well&lt;/i&gt; and a place called &lt;i&gt;The Lonely Tower&lt;/i&gt;. The locals have sent two expeditions to the tower to find out what is happening, but both did not return.&lt;br /&gt;So the locals are now putting out calls for powerful adventurers to investigate what is going on at the tower and stop it if they can. &lt;i&gt;Beneath the Lonely Tower&lt;/i&gt; is a scenario for 6th level characters and characters will be provided for those players who who don't have a character of their own.&lt;br /&gt;In addition to running &lt;i&gt;Beneath the Lonely Tower&lt;/i&gt;, we will also be demoing the D&amp;amp;D Encounters: Undermountain. D&amp;amp;D Encounters is WotC's new program of weekly scenarios designed for those who want to play D&amp;amp;D, but can't devote the time to play a full four to six hour game. WotC designed D&amp;amp;D:Encounters for both new and experienced players who want to play in as series of short adventures, but might not be able to attend every session.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan J</member_name><member_id>10199663</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269273798000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266109509000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>D&amp;D Game Day and Meetup</name><id>12598986</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269100800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/12598986/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/c/global_13082060.jpeg</photo_url></item>