<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>19 King Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.320000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Calvin Theatre</name><city>Northampton</city><id>196050</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.660004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us for an excursion to see one of the most talented, soulful singer/songwriters to arrive on the music scene in recent years! In celebration of Michelle's Birthday (12/15/06) we'll be travelling the relatively short distance to Northampton, Mass to support the creative and inspiring sounds of Ray!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a Sunday night but the show is set to go off at 8PM and I'm confident we'll all be home at a very reasonable hour in order to prepare for work or school the next day! Take a break from all the holiday-related craziness to enjoy some fine music! You deserve it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be dining at Siam Square Thai Restaurant at 6PM! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attached is the website for the Calvin Theatre for tickets and information. The site is really cool, it gives you a seating chart so you can see what's still available and you can select your seat from the seating chart!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, please find Ray's website so you can get a sense of what you're getting into - hope to see you there - we'll make a really enjoyable day out of it - you might even forget you have to work or study the next day! Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From what I'm told - there's not a bad seat in the house!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.iheg.com/calvin_theater_main.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.iheg.com/c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.raylamontagne.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.raylamonta...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.siamsquarenorthampton.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.siamsquare...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166566258000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163191392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at Siam Square (Thai) and Ray Lamontagne at the Calvin Theatre!</name><id>5258371</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1166378400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5258371/</event_url></item>