<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to Rosemary Fortin for attending our meet yesterday, on Nov. 6th and photographing our Maltese in costumes!  As soon as Rosemary sends me photos, I'll get them out to all of you and post them on our meetup site, so that you can order copies from her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Maltese Meet for the coming month will take place on Sunday, November 27th.  We will meet again from 1pm to 4pm at Especially for Pets in Sudbury.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS IS AN EXCEPTION TO OUR USUAL PATTERN OF MEETING THE FIRST SUNDAY OF EACH MONTH.  Especially for Pets couldn't accommodate us in December, because they have reserved the dog class ring each Sunday for holiday photographers or Santa Claus appearances &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are presently contacting dog trainers to see if one of them would like to do a presentation about obedience/agility at our next Meet, possibly doing demos with our dogs.  If you know of a good candidate for this, please write me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regarding the Boston Maltese Meet that usually takes place in downtown Boston --- we are presently searching for a bigger space, and will announce another Meet when we locate one.  The staff at Doggie Day has been very helpful, going way out of their way to make us feel welcome there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on November 27th at our holiday party!&lt;br /&gt;Maltese best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1134936469000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1131303947000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Maltese December Meetup</name><id>4795601</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1133114400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/4795601/</event_url></item>