<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come Join us for Buddhist Movie Night&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring the film: Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter and Spring&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 11th at 7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;At the First Parish Unitarian Church, 425 Congress St. in Portland.&lt;br /&gt;Admission is Free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This eveing brings together Buddhist meditation groups and individuals who practice in the Buddhist tradition to meet and support each other. Come share this film, drink tea, eat dessert, and connect with people from many different Sanghas and traditions throughout Southern and Mid-Coast Maine. Those who are unaffiliated with a group or a center, and who have an interest in Buddhist practice are warmly welocme to attend. So whether you have practiced for a while or are new to practice please come join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The exquisitely beautiful and very human drama Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter . . . and Spring, staring director Kim Ki-duk, is entirely set on and around a tree lined lake where a tiny Buddhist monastery floats on a raft amidst a breath thaking landscape. The film is divided into five segments with each season representing a stage in a man's life. With an extraordinary attention to visual details, Kim Ki-duk has crafted a totally original, yet universal story about the human spirit, moving from innocence, through love and evil, to enlightenment and finally rebirth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional information, please contact&lt;br /&gt;Maggie Miller at 207-671-7714 or buddhistmovienight@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;James Prentice at 207-837-8431 or lowlandbear@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandbuddhist.org" target="_blank"&gt;Nichiren Buddhist New England Sangha Web Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryuoh Faulconer Shonin</member_name><member_id>7835520</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292273133000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Maine-Nichiren-Shu-Fellowship</urlname><id>1419413</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Maine Nichiren Shu Fellowship</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290091699000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhist Gathering and Movie Night</name><id>15488569</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292113800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Maine-Nichiren-Shu-Fellowship/events/15488569/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/e/global_7854846.jpeg</photo_url></item>