<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Middle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810561</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 465 8008</phone><name>The Grog</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>689907</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.869301</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>OK..here's the update as of today Friday, July 11:&lt;br /&gt;The manager said they do not take reservations for downstairs however people can meet upstairs at the bar for a drink around 7:30. They open downstairs at 8 and there is plenty of room, including a very large booth that fits 20-25 people and they serve food there as well. He indicated there should not be a problem getting seating at that time and the band doesn't start until 9-9:15. I personally would recommend gathering tables rather than the booth so it is easier to get up to dance should the spirit move you later on....so...get tables...because you will want to dance! LOL :-) I am not sure exactly what time I will get there but some of the regulars know the routine. Just check out the photos and look for each other, everyone is very friendly.&lt;br /&gt;Please remember,bring cash to pay your own expenses i&lt;b&gt;ncluding tax and tip&lt;/b&gt;...&lt;br /&gt;and do not forget to leave your share before leaving. The servers work hard in these crowds, please do not forget them. Thanks, thoughtfulness is what makes our group the BEST.&lt;br /&gt;:-)&lt;br /&gt;Sandy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Craig's coming back for this gig at the Grog...those of you who follow this band know he is the fabulous keyboard player, Mr. Personality and lot's of fun, who left the group... he will be back just for this evening...bring a doorag or a scarf to wear! The band and dancing goes from 9-12:30...let me know if you want to go earlier to get some good seats and a bite to eat. Maybe Blackie will make a special appearance too..no voodoo spears please.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet downstairs near the dance floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216180777000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214071340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Four on the Floor at the Grog</name><id>8185870</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215819000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/8185870/</event_url></item>