<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>47 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380584</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Marran Theater, Lesley University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1235475</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116506</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Nobel Prize-winning poet and playwright Derek Walcott will read from his new book of poetry, White Egrets, at 7:30 p.m. Tuesday, April 6, 2010 at Lesley University’s Marran Theater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public, the reading is funded by the Strauch-Mosse Endowed Fund for Visiting Artists. The fund was established through a gift from Hans Strauch, President of the Mosse Foundation and Lesley University Trustee, to advance artistic and cultural literacy by bringing artists to Lesley to share their work through lectures, exhibitions and workshops. This event is part of Lesley University’s Centennial Year celebration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: In 1992 Walcott won the Nobel Prize in literature. The awards committee wrote at the time that “West Indian culture has found its great poet,” and commended Walcott as well for his work as a playwright.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walcott’s best-known work includes 1990’s Omeros, an epic poem modeled on Homer’s The Odyssey, but based on St. Lucia. He has published twenty-one collections of poetry, as well as essays and plays, Dream on Monkey Mountain among the most celebrated. His new collection, White Egrets, continues his examination of Caribbean life, while exploring themes of age and ageing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nobel Prize-winning poet Derek Walcott&lt;br /&gt;7:30 p.m., Tuesday, April 6&lt;br /&gt;Marran Theater, 47 Oxford St., Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;Book signing and reception to follow&lt;br /&gt;More information: 617.349.8666 or centennial@lesley.edu&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270769539000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270267346000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Derek Walcott reading new poems at Lesley University</name><id>13074023</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270596600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/13074023/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/4/global_8983348.jpeg</photo_url></item>