<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>24 South Main Street</address_2><address_1>Concord Cooperative Market</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.208634</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 225-6840</phone><name>Celery Stick Cafe</name><city>Concord</city><id>1034067</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.548656</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately most of the packaged survivalist foods available are anything BUT healthy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since these are overpriced as well, it is important to take the time to be selective.  It's not enough to simply SURVIVE by the survivalist foods you stock up on!!!  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to remain healthy, it is important to understand your body's basic nutritional needs and begin making changes now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll explore differences in individual needs and how to be mindful about stocking up on the essentials... while also using what we save to eat and replace right away... especially if you want to enjoy significant health improvements NOW! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best strategy is to keep a supply of the basics on hand... while simultaneously taking what you use from the front of each shelf and adding new purchases to the back. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Switching to this new way of eating can provides the opportunity to notice what we at first forgot... so that we can continuously add to our store of the basics for a new self-sufficient way of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When items are no longer available for purchase...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully that won't affect us much... because we are prepared.. and already accustomed to living on what we previously stock up on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;                                    ******&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extremely challenging times will soon be upon us, due to several situations which have reached a critical threshold. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To better understand why our very survival depends upon personal preparedness steps we  take now, please view the following links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eidQTDjQ5gw"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eidQTDjQ5gw&lt;/a&gt;   (Crash Course - The Three E's)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nI-BIVWlc7A"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nI-BIVWlc7A&lt;/a&gt;    (Resources &amp;amp; Monetary Systems)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm"&gt;http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm&lt;/a&gt; (2012 Cosmic Energy Changes)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details about each monthly topic will be added a month before the Meetup date. Please feel free to make suggestions for future topics. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The quickest way to contact the group organizer is by sending an e-mail to &lt;a href="mailto:info@ulcsclinic.com"&gt;info@ulcsclinic.com&lt;/a&gt;.  Please enter "Meetup Member" in subj. line. &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign on one of the tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342141453000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Co-Creative Planetary Stewards</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Back-to-Basics</urlname><id>1438479</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Back to Basics: Sustainable Self-Sufficient Healthy Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336578027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stocking up on Balanced Healthy Food Essentials</name><id>dpfpncyqkbqb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342130400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Back-to-Basics/events/64080942/</event_url></item>