<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Lot next to Drunken Donuts)</address_2><address_1>24 Shunpike Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.599295</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mettabassette River Put in area, Cromwell</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>785624</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.676995</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This river has a lot of interesting features,&lt;br /&gt;Its a start and return to the same place kind of trip&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info from Tina,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle the Mattabassett River - 12 Noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that still have kayaks, I'm organizing an afternoon paddle down the Mattabassett River and back (same put in and take out point).  Maybe explore the Coginchaug or go out to the CT River and back.  Depends on what folks want to do but since there's no car shuffling, you can basically call it a day whenever you want.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;17 Shunpike Road (behind Dunkin Donuts)&lt;br /&gt;Cromwell, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Probably won't stop to picnic anywhere re &amp;quot;Al-R style,&amp;quot; but bring something to drink and a snack.  Plan to be off the river by 3:30 or 4:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tina Manley&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi  Everyone,&lt;br /&gt; Tina has been on this river for a bunch of trips and is familiar with the launch area also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I cant go since i put away all my equipment for the year and wont have the hitch and trailer ready until spring of next year.&lt;br /&gt;I wish you all a good Kayak Trip..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE, from Hartford, &lt;br /&gt;Look at your map first if you haven't been here before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I 91 south, go past Wethersfield and Rocky Hill&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get onto Rte 9 south, (its a left exit off of 91 south ) then head to (Cromwell/Middletown) go to exit 19 &lt;br /&gt;Turn (right) off the exit, =west toward Kmart and Stop and Shop &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the first light you see (intersection of rte 372 and rte 3) take the left (south toward stop n shop) onto rte 3= Shunpike rd &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a KFC, MackDonalds, and a Drunkon Doonuts while heading to the next traffic light. Use Drunkin Donuts (driveway) there is an empty lot right off to the right which is ok to park in, if there is no parking, park down in the far back of the Drunken Donuts lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a water trail sign showing the most dangerous animals ...including the banjo boys... watch out for their floating house boat...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Tina's Car or other way to find her, she will indicate in her comments</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226858141000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223611450000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Event on the Mettabassett River Cromwell/Middletown CT</name><id>8935234</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223740800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8935234/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>