<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me for a film with great Oscar buzz – Doubt.  Please note that the film screens at 1:50, not 1:45 as shown above.  As this film is in its first weekend, I recommend you buy your tickets ahead of time by visiting &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" target="_blank"&gt;the Kendall's site&lt;/a&gt; and arrive to the theatre early to get a good seat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Writer/director John Patrick Shanley brings his Pulitzer Prize- and Tony Award-winning play to the screen as a gripping story about the quest for truth, the forces of change and the devastating consequences of blind justice in an age defined by moral conviction. It's 1964, St. Nicholas in the Bronx. A vibrant, charismatic priest, Father Flynn (Philip Seymour Hoffman), is trying to upend the school's strict customs, which have long been fiercely guarded by Sister Aloysius Beauvier (Meryl Streep), the iron-gloved Principal who believes in the power of fear and discipline. The winds of political change are sweeping through the community, and indeed, the school has just accepted its first black student, Donald Muller. But when Sister James (Amy Adams), a hopeful innocent, shares with Sister Aloysius her guilt-inducing suspicion that Father Flynn is paying too much personal attention to Donald, Sister Aloysius sets off on a personal crusade to unearth the truth and to expunge Flynn from the school. Now, without a shard of proof besides her moral certainty, Sister Aloysius locks into a battle of wills with Father Flynn which threatens to tear apart the community with irrevocable consequence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the middle of the theatre after the film and then it’s off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a Meetup sign near the middle of the theatre after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228007827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Doubt</name><id>9248681</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229280300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9248681/</event_url></item>