<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>La prochaine Boston French Party aura lieu&lt;b&gt; le Jeudi 26 Février à Foundation Lounge à partir de 19h30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Une Boston French Party un Jeudi dans un nouveau bar !!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Situé en bas de l’Hotel Commonwealth sur Commonwealth Avenue (Kenmore T stop), le Foundation Lounge est un bar moderne et innovant qui se prête parfaitement à l’ambiance d’une Boston French Party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;La soirée débutera comme la précédente à 19H30 avec un apéritif Français offert par notre partenaire : le Petit Robert Bistro !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venez vous joindre à nous pour rencontrer des Français, des francophones, des francophiles, déguster des plats Français du Petit Robert, revoir vos amis ou vous déhancher sur le meilleur de la musique Française !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next Boston French Party will be held at Foundation Lounge, on &lt;b&gt;Thursday, February 26, 2009, from 7:30 PM on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Boston French Party held on a Thursday in a new bar!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Foundation Lounge (Kenmore T stop) is a true lounge experience with Champagne and martinis, in modern and innovative atmosphere, perfect for a French Party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the previous one, this party will start at 7:30 with French appetizers, courtesy of our partner Petit Robert Bistro!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and join us to meet French people, French speakers and French culture lovers, enjoy great French appetizers, see your friends or dance on the best French music!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t forget to join the guest list before 4:30 PM the day of the event to get the reduced admission price of $5 !!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julien</member_name><member_id>1573841</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238630765000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>voulezvous</urlname><id>541017</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Voulez-vous français Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235698990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Party March Meetup</name><id>9834082</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237939200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/voulezvous/events/9834082/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/f/global_7101247.jpeg</photo_url></item>