<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01001</zip><lat>42.056824</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413 789-1917</phone><name>Michaels Pasta In The Pan</name><city>Agawam</city><id>988061</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.605049</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This month we again have two choices...Here they are&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Ayatollah Begs to Differ&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;by Hooman Majd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Publishers Weekly:&lt;br /&gt;In this critical but affectionate portrait of Iranian politics and culture, Majd, the Western-educated grandson of an ayatollah, delves into the very core of Iranian society, closely examining social mores and Farsi phrases to identify the Persian sensibility, which, Majd determines, cherishes privacy, praise and poetry. Nothing is too small or too sweeping for Majd to consider, and although he announces his allegiance to the former president Khatami, he remains scrupulously even-handed in assessing his successor Ahmadinejad, shedding light on the Iranian president's obsession with the Holocaust and penchant for windbreakers and why the two are (surprisingly) intertwined. The author's brisk, conversational prose is appealing; his book reads as if he is chatting with a smart friend, while strolling around Tehran, engaged in ta'arouf (an exaggerated form of self-deprecation key to understanding Persian society). Although Majd seems to gloss too quickly over realities that don't engage his interest—women's voices are only intermittently included—this failing scarcely mars this remarkable ride through what is often uncharted territory. (Oct.) &lt;br /&gt;Copyright © Reed Business Information, a division of Reed Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved. --This text refers to the Hardcover edition. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Twelve Angry Men&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reginald Rose&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first play for our meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Penguin Classics debut that inspired a classic film and a current Broadway revival.  Reginald Rose's landmark American drama was a critically acclaimed teleplay, and went on to become a cinematic masterpiece in 1957 starring Henry Fonda, for which Rose wrote the adaptation. A blistering character study and an examination of the American melting pot and the judicial system that keeps it in check, Twelve Angry Men holds at its core a deeply patriotic belief in the U.S. legal system. The story's focal point, known only as Juror Eight, is at first the sole holdout in an 11-1 guilty vote. Eight sets his sights not on proving the other jurors wrong but rather on getting them to look at the situation in a clear-eyed way not affected by their personal biases. Rose deliberately and carefully peels away the layers of artifice from the men and allows a fuller picture of America, at its best and worst, to form.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>8272134</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253753319000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245868443000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August's Book Discussion - 12 Angry Men and The Ayatollah Begs to Differ!</name><id>10726721</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251153000000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/10726721/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/0/global_10046560.jpeg</photo_url></item>