<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>237 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.402649</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 440-7387</phone><name>Istanbul'lu </name><city>Somerville</city><id>1343915</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.126799</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hostelling International’s Cultural Café series of fundraising dinners is visiting Turkey through Turkish food at the exquisite Instanbul'lu. Join us for a night full of lively conversation and unique food and beverages – all while supporting a great cause!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: Tuesday, December 7th, 6-8 PM (Note: time is earlier than usual) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Place: Instanbul'lu - 237 Holland Street (Teele Square), Somerville, MA 02144   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: $30 includes meal, gratuity, and a donation to Cultural Kitchen   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You MUST pre-register for this event: &lt;a href="http://culturalcafeturkey-autohome.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://culturalcafetu...&lt;/a&gt; – Cultural Cafe events have sold out every time, so don’t miss out! You may also buy tickets offline by contacting Laurine at admin@usahostels.org or at 617-718-7990 ext 10.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turkish Cuisine is the result of time-honored recipes of unexpected combinations that intrigue and delight the palate. Enjoy a unique dining experience unlike any you have had before. Instanbul'lu stands alone in serving sumptuous Turkish Home Cooking. Matt Schaffer from the Boston Herald was quoted saying, &amp;quot;one bite of Mucver or Adana Kabap and you'll break into a smile - yes, Akgun's cooking is as good as ever.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More about Cultural Café and Cultural Kitchen:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For over a year, Hostelling International USA’s Cultural Café has been exploring the diverse cultures and cuisines Boston-area restaurants have to offer. Cultural Café is an enjoyable meal shared among fellow members of the community, and also raises funds for Cultural Kitchen, Hostelling International’s program for inner-city youth, as well as other educational and outreach programs and initiatives. For all the latest updates, consider joining the Facebook group New Boston Hostel.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an afterschool activity, Cultural Kitchen teaches Boston area youth about culture and diversity using cooking as the primary vehicle - just like travelers at our hostels learn about one another while cooking together in the hostel kitchen.  For more information, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.culturalkitchenboston.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.culturalkitchenboston.org&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:admin@usahostels.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hostelling International Boston</member_name><member_id>12811800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302045038000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Culturalcafe</urlname><id>1554280</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Cultural Café - Dine Out for a Cause</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288893215000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cultural Cafe Turkish Cuisine!</name><id>15339589</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291762800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Culturalcafe/events/15339589/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/global_11736302.jpeg</photo_url></item>