<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>661 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02124</zip><lat>42.288437</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Codman Square  </name><city>Dorchester</city><id>3369802</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071152</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A spectacular day of Live Entertainment for ALL to ENJOY! This will be a great event for members from the world meet up group to come out and enjoy a great day of vending, food, and music. It is from 10 - 6 and a Free community event. The Fifth Annual One Heart Festival will take place on Saturday, September 10th at 661 Washington Street in Codman Square (Dorchester). A FREE &amp;amp; FUN DAY FOR THE FAMILY. The mission of this festival is to bring together Bostons diverse communities for a day of live entertainment, food, and specialty shopping in hopes that all can enjoy a full day of PEACE &amp;amp; UNITY. Come Listen to the great Multi-Cultrural Sounds of R&amp;amp;B, African Drums, Reggae, Dancehall and more from the Commonwealth and beyond. Featuring live music performances by: Anguile, Dis-N-Dat Band, Ezemdi Chikwendu, Fiyah Binghi, Garrisun Famally, I-Medz, Iron Zion, Jahriffe, Jah Jah Drummers, Janey David, King-I, Livalect, Mamado, Raymon Jamez, Super Adonai, Tiggana / Lance Gordon and Truthful. Additional music by 105.3FM, DJ Wreckage and more. Please visit our website for more info: www.oneheartfestival.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315751356000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315341193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>This Saturday is the 5th Annual One Heart Festival in Codman Sq in Dorchester. </name><id>32495392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315663200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/32495392/</event_url></item>