<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>310 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357006</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 482-6439</phone><name>Old South Meeting House</name><city>Boston</city><id>669048</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us at this lunchtime lecture at the Old South Meeting House. Price: $5.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Old South Meeting House Site&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://oldsouthmeetinghouse.org/osmh123456789_1773L/Calendar/DispForm.aspx?ID=250" target="_blank"&gt;http://oldsouthmeetin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Title&lt;/b&gt;: Stimulating Beverages: A Brief History of Tea, Coffee and Chocolate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Before 1650, a New England breakfast often included a mug of ale, beer or hard wine, but with the introduction of tea, coffee, and chocolate the tastes of the Western world were forever changed. Originally prescribed as cures for ailments ranging from headaches to depression, tea, coffee, and chocolate were soon counted  among the necessities of daily live. Hear Amanda Lange, curator at Historic Deerfield, explain how these three beverages emerged as the popular drinks we know today&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Begins&lt;/b&gt;: 12/10/2009 12:15 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Ends&lt;/b&gt;: 12/10/2009 1:00 PM &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price&lt;/b&gt;: $5; Free for members &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will get there a bit before noon to save half a pew or so for the group up near the podium, placing a red MEETUP sign on the aisle. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, and a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag. The Old South Meeting House is in Downtown Crossing across from the large Borders Bookstore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Historic Deerfield Site&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.historic-deerfield.org/files/hd/docs/Amanda_Lange_Featured_in_New_Chocolate_Anthology.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.historic-d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Amanda Lange Featured in New Chocolate Anthology&lt;/u&gt;:  Loved by many cultures for centuries, chocolate is still today perhaps the world's most adored confection. But how did this sweet treat become so revered? A new 1,000 page book titled 'Chocolate: History, Culture and Heritage' explores the topic in depth, including an article from &lt;b&gt;Amanda Lange&lt;/b&gt;, Curatorial Department Chair and Curator of Historic Interiors at Historic Deerfield. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The book first sprouted roots in 1998 when the Chocolate History Group was formed by the University of California, Davis, and Mars, Incorporated. It was the research and contributions from more than 100 members of this group that led to this new encyclopedia of chocolate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'It really covers, in-depth, the current scholarship on chocolate,&amp;quot; Lange said. 'There are items about the economic and regional aspects of chocolate, down to the associations between chocolate and crime.' Lange's chapter in the anthology, 'Chocolate Preparation and Serving Vessels in Early North America,' focuses on how Americans were preparing their chocolate in the 17th and 18th centuries. Included in the chapter are descriptions and images of artifacts from Historic Deerfield's collection, including a 1760 chocolate pot made by Zachariah Brigden of Boston, MA&amp;quot;. ( &lt;b&gt;MORE&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.historic-deerfield.org/files/hd/docs/Amanda_Lange_Featured_in_New_Chocolate_Anthology.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.historic-d...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Old South Meeting House, Wikipedia&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Old_South_Meeting_House" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Old South Meeting House, in the Downtown Crossing area of Boston, Massachusetts, gained fame as the organizing point for the Boston Tea Party on December 16, 1773. 5,000 colonists gathered at the Meeting House, the largest building in Boston at the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] After the Boston Massacre in 1770, yearly anniversary meetings were held at the church until 1775 featuring speakers such as John Hancock and Dr. Joseph Warren. In 1773 5,000 people met in the Meeting House to debate British taxation, and after the meeting a group raided a nearby tea ship in what became known as the Boston Tea Party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Old South Meeting House was almost destroyed in the Great Boston Fire of 1872, and the congregation then built a new church (the 'New' Old South Church at Copley Square) which remains its home to this day. Once twice a year, on the Sunday before Thanksgiving, the Old South congregation returns to Old South Meeting House for services in its ancestral home&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263057888000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262370784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introducing Tea, Coffee, and Chocolate to the Colonies @ Old South Meeting House</name><id>12190660</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262884500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12190660/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/7/global_12440663.jpeg</photo_url></item>