<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Deerfield Ln</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06401</zip><lat>41.344260</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203)736-1053</phone><name>Ansonia Nature Center</name><city>Ansonia</city><id>664225</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.054640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for an evening with Mark Morey as he describes his vision of creating regenerative communities that draw from the wisdom of the natural world and life ways of ancestral cultures. Learn how to create community resilience through building deep interconnected relationships. And how to respond to an uncertain future in local ways that create rich life-affirming communities and a healthy, abundant natural world. It takes a village to raise a child, learn how to rebuild the village. Time: 6:30-9:00 Location: Ansonia Nature Center, Ansonia 10 Deerfield Road Ansonia, CT Cost: Donations appreciated Childcare and Refreshments provided To Register email info@twocoyotes.org. Mark Morey is the founder of Vermont Wilderness School, and the Institute for Natural Learning, His work has sparked a nature and community awareness movement in the Northeast impacting over 7,000 people. For the past 14 years, Mark has led wilderness survival and spiritual passages for teens and adults, including the transformational Art of Mentoring Workshop. To learn more about Mark's work visit his website: &lt;a href="http://www.ifnaturallearning.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ifnaturall...&lt;/a&gt; To see a video of Mark speaking visit: &lt;a href="http://markmorey.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://markmorey.com...&lt;/a&gt; To Register email info@twocoyotes.org.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317339797000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314905564000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creating Regenerative Communities with Mark Morey</name><id>31899132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317335400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/31899132/</event_url></item>