<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hartford CT</address_2><address_1>100 Trumbull St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.766030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dulce</name><city>Hartford</city><id>623750</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.676090</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mass-Conn-Fusion Big Band, will be performing at  Hartford's Hottest new club &amp;quot;Dulce&amp;quot;, Music starts at 9:PM. Dulce is located at 100 Trumbull Street, Hartford.  For more information, please call 860.727.9997&lt;br /&gt;Looking for a sound to shake up your club, festival or private function? Try a little Mass-Conn Fusion - from Boston's Faneuil Hall to Hartford's First Night, from the ski slopes of Vermont to the beach front of Nantucket, this energetic band has been keeping New England joints jumping for 20 years.. &lt;br /&gt;As its name suggests, Mass-Conn Fusion draws its talent fro both sides of the Massachusetts-Connecticut border. The group has an extensive repertoire featuring Motown, R&amp;amp;B, Jazz and Blues hits of the 60's through 00's. This versatility allows the band to tailor sets for every occasion, focusing on a single style or fusing them into a lively mix that offers something for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winners of the Hartford Advocate's Grand Slam Band R&amp;amp;B for SEVEN years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Playing over 250 dates a year, Mass-Conn Fusion is a pleasing professional act with musical credentials to match its charisma. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether lending its talent to a nightclub, a wedding, a corporate banquet or an outdoor celebration, Mass-Conn Fusion keeps the dance floor in motion by not only singing and playing, but whole-heartedly performing for listeners. It's more than just a band. It's an audio-visual experience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massconnfusion.com/calendar1.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massconnfu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be dancing to Mass Conn Fussion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221959345000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220502308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mass-Conn- Fusion at Hartford's Hottest new Club "Dulce</name><id>8685295</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221786000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8685295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>