<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>robbinslibrary.org</address_2><address_1>700 Massachusetts Avenue Arlington, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.416168</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-316-3200 </phone><name>Robbins Library</name><city>Arlington</city><id>490314</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.155983</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Boston/Cambridge SEO Networking Group &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite local Boston seo, affiliate marketing and search engine marketing professionals in New England area to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robbins Library Arlington, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm to 7pm: Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Card Buffet: drop you card on the networking buffet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm to 7:30: 2 Min Elevator Pitch:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Tell us about you and your business or website interest&lt;br /&gt;* Any networking goal your trying to achieve out of this meeting?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - 8:00 Guest Speaker &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic: &lt;br /&gt;Using analytic tools for SEO &amp;amp; how to identify the right long-tail keywords that will help you identify and get more of your most valuable traffic. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christina Inge is a marketing consultant with over 10 years'&lt;br /&gt;experience in content creation, web technologies, and project&lt;br /&gt;management. She is adept at finding creative ways to maximize the&lt;br /&gt;small marketing budgets of startups and nonprofits. Her articles on&lt;br /&gt;marketing have appeared in trade publications, and she is a speaker on&lt;br /&gt;cutting-edge marketing practices. Her areas of expertise include&lt;br /&gt;boosting clickthrough and conversion rates for paid search campaigns,&lt;br /&gt;as well as best practices in organic search. She also consults for&lt;br /&gt;companies on product go-to-market plans, email marketing strategy and&lt;br /&gt;implementation, online lead conversion and lead generation analysis&lt;br /&gt;and optimization, and product positioning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christina has led workshops on wireless energy management systems at&lt;br /&gt;the UMass Sustainable Energy Summit, on cause marketing at the Center&lt;br /&gt;for Nonprofit Success' Boston Fundraising Summit, on Web 2.0&lt;br /&gt;technologies and event marketing at PodCampNH, and on boosting&lt;br /&gt;conversion at eMetrics Toronto.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to her work in marketing, Christina was a journalist for many&lt;br /&gt;years, writing for MSN.com, Succeed, and a variety of general and&lt;br /&gt;special-interest magazines. A Summa Cum Laude graduate of the&lt;br /&gt;University of Maryland with a Bachelor's in English, Christina also&lt;br /&gt;hold a Master's in Instructional Technology, focusing on designing&lt;br /&gt;optimal, user-friendly online learning experiences for adult students,&lt;br /&gt;from the University of Wyoming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Her: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/christinainge" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://connect.amaboston.org/profile/ChristinaInge" target="_blank"&gt;AMA Boston Profile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Twitter &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/christinainge" target="_blank"&gt;@christinainge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:15: Additional Q &amp;amp; A, What's Working, &amp;amp; Challenge Questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:45pm The End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all at this informal Boston search engine round table discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge SEO MeetUp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker's Wanted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been working hard to find industry experts and to develop a formal agenda to keep it interesting for all those that attend at this new big meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food Event Sponsors:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEO Pro's, will work for food! Contact us about sponsoring the event with goodies and drinks in exchange for publicity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Matson</member_name><member_id>1490252</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Hawkins</member_name><member_id>2319452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275953610000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in SEO/SEM</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSEO</urlname><id>219718</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>69</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268252283000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Search Engine Optimization SEO Networking Meetup</name><id>12841237</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274740200000</time><rsvp_limit>106</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSEO/events/12841237/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/7/global_3054519.jpeg</photo_url></item>