<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*** 5/18, Event still going on :-) Weather prediction 52 F, 40% chance of rain, winds 9 mph. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A 5 mile hike through the beautiful Bigelow Hollow State Park in the southwestern section. This is a bit of a &amp;quot;workout&amp;quot; hike with low-moderate to moderate difficulty overall (rolling trail and a couple good uphill stints). Bring water (a must!), snacks, and bug spray (or else you WILL be eaten!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bigelow Hollow State Park and the adjoining Nipmuck State Forest offer over 9,000 acres of recreation opportunities, including miles of hiking trails and 3 large ponds (Bigelow, Mashapaug, and Breakneck Ponds) in Northeastern Connecticut. This park is beautiful!.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For carpooling, meet at 12:45 PM - 1 PM at the I-84 exit 67 &amp;quot;Park &amp;amp; Ride&amp;quot; lot to save gas and to minimize the entrance fee (if any). The lot is located to the right off of Exit 67 if you are eastbound and to the left if you are westbound. Please indicate on your RSVP if you will use the carpool or meet at the park (so we know where to find you). We will leave the carpool location at 1 PM sharp!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll get to the park entrance and parking by 1:30 PM. There may be a $7 CT resident/$10 non-resident per car entrance fee to the park but as we are getting there so late the fee may be waved. We'll park in the 3rd parking lot (per park map) from the entrance which is a picnic area. If you reach the boat launch and the end of the accessible road you've gone one parking area too far. In the event the 3rd parking area is full, we will still meet at that location as the trailhead is there. Please allow some extra time in case you need to walk to this area from available parking. Note that there is virtually NO CELL reception at the park! If you'd like to drive to the park yourself, please meet at the 3rd parking area as mentioned at 1:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike should start at about 1:30 PM. We'll be hiking the Blue/White Bar (BWB) Mushapaug Pond View Trail in the southwestern part of the park in a clockwise direction. The hike takes no more than 2.5 hours and will complete before 4 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will return to the carpool location by 4:30 PM. If there is a desire by those in attendance, we can go somewhere in the Vernon area after for dinner and conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs are permitted on the hike as long as they are on a leash.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/big_nipm.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325174&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate meetup location/directions for carpool at Park &amp;amp; Ride lot at I-84, Exit 67 in Vernon, CT via Mapquest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=%5b95%2d128%5d%20Reservoir%20Rd&amp;amp;city=Vernon%20Rockville&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06066&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=1oLffePGBZudscNQewpQ6Q5M6uDbP5GuDNn8bVHfvM%2bA64GeIBoY6ZVGyWW2dYLglUucuUgGgCKmz3YWuaZKOc9Deu3gJnFtZZi0KOi%2fsnVaavDD32H9PWblJhukTikXvdr29pR46rcMRE6bZAfELqWS1FNEJTgC&amp;amp;ambiguity=1"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/directions for entrance to Bigelow Hollow State Park off of Rte. 171 in Union, CT via Mapquest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?latlongtype=internal&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;latitude=QQWkby9wPM7%2bn4MKPogaHA%3d%3d&amp;amp;longitude=sDlWYDFHNsTZsodliIrNcA%3d%3d&amp;amp;name=Bigelow%20Hollow%20State%20Park&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;address=Ct%2d171&amp;amp;city=Stafford%20Springs&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06076&amp;amp;phone=860%2d684%2d3430&amp;amp;spurl=0&amp;amp;&amp;amp;q=bigelowhollow%20state%20park&amp;amp;qc=Parks"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions from the carpool location to the park entrance (22 min./19.5 mi.) via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/directions/main.adp?do=nw&amp;amp;go=1&amp;amp;r=&amp;amp;aoh=&amp;amp;aot=&amp;amp;aof=&amp;amp;1a=%5b95%2d128%5d%20Reservoir%20Rd&amp;amp;1c=Vernon%20Rockville&amp;amp;1s=CT&amp;amp;1z=06066&amp;amp;1y=US&amp;amp;1l=1oLffePGBZvp3DgK1a99jw%3d%3d&amp;amp;1g=cYZxCqQlnPxtXj%2bUlAZteg%3d%3d&amp;amp;1pn=&amp;amp;1pl=&amp;amp;1v=STREET&amp;amp;1ffi=&amp;amp;1n=&amp;amp;1qn=&amp;amp;2a=&amp;amp;2c=Union&amp;amp;2s=CT&amp;amp;2z=&amp;amp;2y=US&amp;amp;2l=3705vmLVkIQl%2b9tMCyPkyg%3d%3d&amp;amp;2g=kCCvqHDAV8xlIbJMAtIr%2fw%3d%3d&amp;amp;2pl=&amp;amp;2v=CITY&amp;amp;2ffi=&amp;amp;2n=Tolland%20County&amp;amp;2qn=bigelow%20hollow%20state%20park&amp;amp;panelbtn=2&amp;amp;1qc=&amp;amp;q=bigelow%20hollow%20state%20park&amp;amp;2pn=bigelow%20hollow%20state%20park&amp;amp;2sb=Bigelow%20Hollow%20State%20Park%7cCt%2d171%7cStafford%20Springs%7cCT%7c06076%7c41991600%7c%2d72134841%7c860%2d684%2d3430%7cUS&amp;amp;2qc=Parks"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179767155000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179143738000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Bigelow Hollow SP and Nipmuck SF in Union CT</name><id>5775708</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179594000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5775708/</event_url></item>