<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Members of the Friends of Myles Standish Hiking and Birding Group are invited to join the AMC at their summer picnic 9-4 at Charge Pond Pavillion. &lt;br /&gt;Activities include nature walks, hikes, biking and an afternoon family walk around the East head Resevoir.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activities will be followed by LOTS of good food beginning around 1:00pm with our partial-pot-luck lunch and our Fourth Annual Cherry Pit Spitting Contest . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Chapter will provide hamburgers, veggie burgers, soft drinks, watermelon (and cherries). Participants should supply the side dishes and salad. (If your last name begins with A-I, please bring side dishes; if J-R, please bring salad; if S-Z, please bring dessert.) Please be sure to bring a cooler with sufficient ice for items that must be kept cold. Alcohol is not allowed in the State Forest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charge Pond is an 18 acre pond open to swimming, fishing and paddling, but has no life guard. Overnight campsites in Area A are available. Reservations for the best sites should be made through Reserve America. And don’t forget the sun, fun, and camaraderie of getting together with your friendly, like-minded fellow SEMers and Friends of MSSF! All this for just $5 pp for individual adults, or $10 per family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre registration is required. To register, please contact: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joanne Jarzobski  508-212-4427 &lt;br /&gt;Claire Goode         508-759-7362 &lt;br /&gt;Don't forget your camp chairs. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Vickstrom</member_name><member_id>11406046</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280670766000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278383302000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Appalachian Mountain Club Summer Picnic</name><id>14011898</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279371600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/14011898/</event_url></item>