<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 York St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03909</zip><lat>43.144084</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nubble Lighthouse</name><city>York</city><id>797990</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.651759</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Due to demand from so many of you regarding the Super Moon (largest moon in almost two decades) that will rise tonight at 7:15PM, I put together exact locations from where you can shoot this spectacular moon rising behind lighthouses in Maine, New Hampshire, and Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can you tell the exact spot to set up?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We've used the excellent Photographer's Ephemeris (TPE) to do this in the past, and it's highly accurate. Links to screenshots from TPE are included for each location below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find maps, directions, and more on an interactive map I set up for this purpose &lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/maps/?v=2&amp;amp;cp=42.927508605208864~-70.29174168032179&amp;amp;lvl=10&amp;amp;dir=0&amp;amp;sty=u&amp;amp;cid=15D7434C480DC34!510"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/b/1/highres_22101681.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/b/1/global_22101681.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Maine - Nubble Lighthouse in York&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I'll be leading a trip to the Nubble Lighthouse in nearby York because, well, I've never seen the Nubble and it's the closest to shore of all the three lighthouses mentioned here. It's also so very easy to park and walk to the final set-up spot here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click the TPE image on the left to zoom in on the details, or &lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/maps/?v=2&amp;amp;cp=42.927508605208864~-70.29174168032179&amp;amp;lvl=10&amp;amp;dir=0&amp;amp;sty=u&amp;amp;cid=15D7434C480DC34!510"&gt;visit the interactive map&lt;/a&gt; to get more info and directions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;Note &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;that this lighthouse is raised quite a bit above the nearest shore from where we'll shoot, and by the time the moon rises so you can see it behind the lighthouse, it (the moon, not the lighthouse, silly) will have moved quite a bit south. If you plan on shooting from below the lighthouse base, you will want to be a bit north of where TPE indicates, as that is the moon position at 7:15PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/a/f/highres_22101679.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/a/f/global_22101679.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;New Hampshire - Isles of Shoals (White Island) Lighthouse from Jenness Beach in Hampton&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/maps/?v=2&amp;amp;cp=42.927508605208864~-70.29174168032179&amp;amp;lvl=10&amp;amp;dir=0&amp;amp;sty=u&amp;amp;cid=15D7434C480DC34!510"&gt;Look at the map&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/a/e/highres_22101678.jpeg"&gt;check this shot&lt;/a&gt; from TPE to find the exact location on Jenness Beach to set up, and make sure you're in front of the sixth house (counting north from the southernmost house).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're looking for someone to lead a trip to this spot tonight. If you're interested, let me know and we'll set up a separate meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/b/3/highres_22101683.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/b/3/global_22101683.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Massachusetts - Thatcher Island lighthouse in Rockport&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Beth from the CAPE group has already set up a meetup just a bit farther south in Gloucester. Look for the meetup today titled &lt;a href="http://meetup.rumdoodle.com/events/16972378/"&gt;Super Moon Shoot&lt;/a&gt; to sign up for that one. If you're interested in shooting the moon rising behind the Thatcher Island lighthouse, then&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/maps/?v=2&amp;amp;cp=42.927508605208864~-70.29174168032179&amp;amp;lvl=10&amp;amp;dir=0&amp;amp;sty=u&amp;amp;cid=15D7434C480DC34!510"&gt;check the map&lt;/a&gt; or look at this &lt;a href="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/b/2/highres_22101682.jpeg"&gt;shot from TPE&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;to see where to set up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How should I prepare?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are attending this evening, but who did not make the &lt;a href="http://meetup.rumdoodle.com/events/14914875/"&gt;previous full moon shot&lt;/a&gt;, here are some tips:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wear warm clothing. Temps drop as the sun goes down, and we're by the ocean where breezes are stronger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the longest lens you have to get a good shot of the moon. A 200mm lens on a digital crop sensor (most anything except a full-frame professional camera) is fine. Longer is better. If you're shooting at the Nubble, a shorter lens will allow you to incorporate the lighthouse and its island. Come early with a few lenses to test things out. For the other two lighthouses, use the longest lens you have.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring a sturdy tripod. The moon travels fast, and you'll want to shoot at 1/60 of a second or faster to minimize motion blur, at 1/125 or faster to get texture in the moon. The moon will rise 22 minutes after sunset, so there will still be some ambient light, but not much. If you want to capture the lighthouses in ambient light, you'll want to use a much slower shutter speed while on a tripod, then shoot the moon itself at daylight speeds, and marry the two in post-processing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wear comportable and supportive hiking boots. While you're clamoring on the beach and rocks, you don't want to twist an ankle. Everyone else will be intensely concentrating on shooting the quickly rising moon and may not pay attention to you before the high tide laps at your feet. Not really, but wear sensible footwear anyway.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare to come early and stay late. Coming early means you set up properly while it's still light out. Well after moonrise there will be great shots of the moon reflecting on the water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See details below for the exact spots to meet and setup in ME, NH, and MA</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300800693000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><why>The largest full moon in almost two decades will rise on a clear night, and we have the exact spots to capture the moon rising behind three lighthouses in ME, NH, and MA.</why><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300541757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moon-a-Palooza</name><id>16975811</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300573800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/16975811/</event_url></item>