<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>263 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02180</zip><lat>42.484222</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-279-1400 </phone><name>Body Mind Systems</name><city>Stoneham</city><id>422006</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100174</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Stoneham Human Harmonies Health Center presents a free seminar on &amp;ldquo;Creating The Life You Want,&amp;rdquo; focusing on creating a healthy, physical body, Thursday, Sept. 22, from 7:30 to 9 PM, located inside the Body Mind Systems Training Center, 263 Main St., Stoneham, Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you want your life to change, you have to change things in your life. This seminar will address how to make changes that will positively affect your physical health. Participants will learn to recognize habits and behaviors that positively and negatively influence health. The lecture will cover the four areas that most affect people&amp;rsquo;s health and energy: breathing, water, food and movement. Breathing techniques and gentle movements will be covered. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The seminar will be presented by Tim Bielby, LMT, CST, a National Director of Human Harmonies Health Centers and a 7th Degree Black Belt with Body Mind Systems. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Human Harmonies is a combination of Eastern and Western health methods that promotes the body&amp;rsquo;s natural healing capabilities and helps to create life balance. Through the program, participants can understand the different systems in the body and how the body works. Programs are personal and tailored to the individual. Movements taught through the program include breathing and meditation, stretching and strengthening movements and tai chi. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For more information about the seminar or about Human Harmonies, call 781-279-1400 or visit &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #336699 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;www.humanharmonies.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert</member_name><member_id>5472488</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316817778000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Martial Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>martial-257</urlname><id>800996</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston/North Shore Martial Arts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316173258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE LECTURE “CREATING THE LIFE YOU WANT” (THURSDAY SEPTEMBER 22, 2011 7:30 PM)</name><id>dvghccypmbdc</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316734200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/martial-257/events/34218762/</event_url></item>