<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Dundee Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.655712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yang's Martial Arts</name><city>Andover</city><id>10413882</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.145569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For more info contact Brian @ 617.290.4512 or&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="mailto:chentaichiboston@gmail.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;chentaichiboston@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spaces still open, register now. Early Registration Date: November 26, 2012, get your payment in early and save on the tuition cost. Please see flyer and registration attached to this email for more info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn the twisting, winding, spiraling body motions; that thread through the body frame in Chen Tai Chi, as well as other exercises for regulating the body and energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Friday 12/7: (6:00PM-8:30PM) Qigong/Silk Reeling/Chen Style Fundamental Training&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sword practice will greatly enhance the practitioner's sense of body connection, coiling, and intent, as they extend their focus out to the tip of the sword.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday 12/8: (11:30AM-6:00PM) Traditional Chen Style Straight Sword&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Sunday 12/9: (10:00AM-4:30PM) Traditional Chen Style Straight Sword&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The straight sword, or "Jian" is considered the king of short range weapons in Chinese Martial Arts. Usually, the length of this weapon is 3 feet or more including the grip and has 1.5 to 2 inches wide straight double edge blade. Wooden practice swords are perfectly acceptable to learn the form as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those not as familiar with swords, please note that the material taught in this seminar will be based on the "straight sword", and NOT "broadsword".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**The YMAA Andover facility is tucked back, at Dundee Office Park, which is adjacent to the Andover Commuter Rail T Station. Once you drive into the office park area, you will see old, red brick, mill style buildings. You will need to drive all the way down to the end of the office park to arrive at the YMAA Andover studio; approximately a 1/4 mile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, we are very fortunate to have access to Grandmaster Chen in the Boston area, don't miss out on this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erik Squires</member_name><member_id>10287351</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355089051000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Chen-Tai-Chi</urlname><id>1515290</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Chen Tai Chi</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353446938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GM Chen Zhenglei Sword and Silk Reeling</name><id>92216482</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>167400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354921200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Chen-Tai-Chi/events/92216482/</event_url></item>