<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ayer, Groton, Pepperall and Dunstable</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01432</zip><lat>42.561203</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-597-8802</phone><name>Nashua Rail Trail</name><city>Ayer</city><id>1564612</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.589790</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let's Ride the Nashua Rail Trail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;22 Miles Ride&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAIN WILL CANCEL THIS EVENT!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a joint meet up with Boston Ski&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ayer Center&lt;/strong&gt; parking lot (60 paved spaces)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;Take Rte. 2 east or west to exit 38B, then follow Route 111 north to Ayer Rotary. Go halfway around rotary to Rte. 2A. On Rte. 2A turn right after Ayer Center, take first right on Groton Street to trail parking lot on the right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/images/nashCampMap.gif"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/images/nashCampMap.gif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Nashua River Rail Trail is a former railroad right of way that travels 11 miles through the towns of Ayer, Groton, Pepperell and Dunstable. The trail offers a 10-foot wide paved surface for the entire length, and a five-foot wide gravel equestrian path for seven miles of the trail from Groton Center to the New Hampshire border in Dunstable. The entire trail is open to pedestrians, bicyclists, inline skaters, wheelchairs, and cross-country skiers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Nashua River Rail Trail travels along a varied landscape, offers numerous scenic overlooks, opportunities to see wildlife and has several resting stops. The trail is particularly attractive during fall foliage season. The Ayer trailhead offers access to commuter rail service between Boston and Fitchburg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;The average speed of this ride should be between 13 &amp;amp; 15 mph. I recommend Road bikes or hybrids. Please make sure you have a helmet or I cannot allow you to ride with our group. The total mileage is about 22 miles so plan your schedule accordingly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Please bring spare tire, water, snacks, bike pump, jacket.......&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; The leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Ayer Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathy B</member_name><member_id>2614440</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368290802000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364786775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike the Nashua Rail Trail</name><id>112013092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368279000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/112013092/</event_url></item>