<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358156</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>708011</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063692</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>An international general strike will be held in Europe on 29 September. Such militant action by the working class of Europe is without precedent and deserves our attention and solidarity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here in Boston, we are calling for our allies and friends to join us in a protest outside the statehouse with a similar message: No to budget cuts! No austerity! Global capitalism is not working!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So far the struggle against budget cuts in defense of jobs and social services has been set in the context of Massachusetts politics. It is time to expand this perspective internationally and unite with our brothers and sisters in Europe!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite you to unite with millions of workers, students, the unemployed, underemployed, the elderly, and people living with disabilities and say NO to budget cuts and austerity measures in Massachusetts, the US, and in Europe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know that the same people – working people – in Spain, Greece, Portugal, Italy and other parts of Europe are suffering the same exact budget cuts?  This shows us that globalization is more powerful than government policies – it proves that capitalism is bent on destroying the wages, education, health care, mass transit, natural environment, and social services that keep working people alive. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What began as a call from Spanish labor unions has snowballed into an international day of action in response to the injustices which our governments ask us to bear.  Politicians ask us to accept budget cuts in the face of multi-billion dollar bail-outs for big banks; more than a trillion-dollar series of wars, and continued attacks on our basic rights to education, social services and public safety.  We are joining with our European sisters and brothers to say NO MORE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On September 29 let’s demand – not ask – for our right to fair wages, education, health care, affordable housing, child care, elder care, public transportation, social services and sustainable jobs for the unemployed and underemployed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come together with working people from Barcelona to Boston, and show “the powers that be” that we stand united with all working people, no matter where we live.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We stand for real democracy: democratic ownership of our economy under worker control. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285862945000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283063170000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International General Strike Solidarity</name><id>14577577</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285776000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/14577577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/c/global_17658940.jpeg</photo_url></item>