<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In the last several years, we have seen an Integral community that is increasingly fragmented, and yet yearning to be a movement that can impact culture.  Healing this fragmentation and unifying around a shared vision is crucial, or else we risk diminishing our potential impact upon a world that’s increasingly in need of Integral perspectives, insights, and solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tonight we are excited to hold a panel discussion between Managing Director of EnlightenNext Boston Kenzo An, Mahamudra meditation teacher and Samadhi co-owner John Churchill, Integral scholar Dr. Tom Murray, and Social Change consultant Gibrán Rivera to cover this fascinating and far reaching topic!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this panel discussion, we will confront “the We” in our space of the world, and explore many of the challenges and opportunities we are seeing the respective communities to find shared agreement.  We will hone our ideas about the current state of the Integral movement and to explore how together we can have a far greater impact on the Boston area cultural conversation in 2013. What is working? What do we need to communicate better? How are we treating each other? Does the Integral community maintain a consistent reputation of integrity in the larger culture? What resistances and obstacles do we see in trying to bring the Integral vision to a larger audience? And what sorts of behaviors and ethical underpinnings are we currently modeling for the culture at-large?  Bring your questions, ideas, and vision so we can take this exploration further and go somewhere we have not been before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bios&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kenzo An&lt;/strong&gt; currently serves as Managing Director of EnlightenNext Boston. Beginning in 1999, Kenzo began intensive spiritual and philosophical study under direct guidance from EnlightenNext founder Andrew Cohen, whose contemporary path of Evolutionary Enlightenment has been widely recognized as redefining mysticism for a rapidly changing world. In 2008, after years of organizing public dialogues and growing EnlightenNext’s community in Boston, Kenzo was promoted to Managing Director. In his role, Kenzo designs EnlightenNext Boston’s engagement strategy across Greater Boston and much of New England, creating innovative event programming and working with a growing movement of individuals interested in creating a new culture based on the principles of Evolutionary Enlightenment. In addition to mentoring groups of practitioners learning how to apply Evolutionary Enlightenment to their lives, Kenzo actively builds alliances with local leaders who share a commitment to growing Boston’s progressive spiritual community. While not overseeing EnlightenNext Boston, Kenzo maintains a full-time career as an accomplished sales executive, having worked for the world’s top technology research and advisory firms in the automotive, oil and gas, and financial services industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Churchill&lt;/strong&gt; has been practicing meditation since 1990. After leaving high school he joined Samye Ling Kagyu Monastery in Scotland where he began his studies in the Mahayana and Mahamudra. He came to the United States to study at Naropa University where he majored in Contemplative psychology with a specialization in mind/body health. During his time at Naropa he studied with American philosopher, Ken Wilber, and was a founding member of Integral Institute.  John has taught meditative and somatic approaches to awakening for the last decade. He co-founded, with his wife Nicole, Samadhi Integral, a center dedicated to the contemporary development of body, mind and spirit. He practices acupuncture and specializes in energetic psychosomatics. Since 2005 John has been a Mahamudra student of Daniel Brown, and began to study Dzogchen with Rahob Rinpoche in 2007. He was authorized in January 2012 as a teacher in the Pointing Out Way. He is deeply interested in the relationship between psychological and contemplative development, the ‘awakened sangha’, technology and dharma, and the integral evolution of humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Tom Murray&lt;/strong&gt; is a Senior Research Fellow in the Computer Science Department at the University of Massachusetts Amherst. Currently his primary research is in supporting social deliberative skills in online contexts. He has published papers on integral theory as it relates to education, dialog, leadership, ethics, knowledge building communities, and epistemology. He is on the editorial review boards of two international journals, the International Journal of Artificial Intelligence in Education, and at Integral Review as an Associate Editor.  Tom's non-academic interests include contact improvisation, aerial fabric dance, Vipassana meditation, NVC, dispute mediation, and grandparenting.  He knows that somehow all this ties into spiritual growth, if ever so gradually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gibrán Rivera&lt;/strong&gt; has devoted his life to the idea of democracy and to the work of emancipatory politics. He is a graduate of the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, and has been recognized for his scholarship as well as his grassroots work for social transformation. Gibrán is currently a senior consultant at the Interaction Institute for Social Change. He has led community engagement work at Roxbury’s La Alianza Hispana and served as Executive Director of Iniciativa – the Massachusetts Education Initiative for Latino Students. Gibrán was a candidate for the Boston City Council in what was widely recognized as a movement building campaign and a new approach to politics. He served as the founding board chair of MassVOTE and as a director on the Board of the Schott Foundation for Public Education. His approach to his work is particularly influenced by the work of Robert Gass, founder of the Rockwood Leadership Institute; C. Otto Scharmer and his peers at the Presencing Institute; the work and writings of Grace Lee Boggs at the Boggs Center in Detroit; and the forward thinking work of John Powell and the Kirwan Institute.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356197609000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351871918000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The State of the "We" (in the Greater Boston Area)</name><id>89646022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354925700000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/89646022/</event_url></item>