<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 South Quinsigamond Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01545</zip><lat>42.270437</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-774-262-0075</phone><name>Maironis Park</name><city>Shrewsbury</city><id>834635</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.750818</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Don't want to miss this one!!!  $12.00 advanced.  $15.00 at the door&lt;br /&gt;www.danceworcester.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston's Best Tribute to the Early Days of Rock-n-Roll! This 5 piece band pays homage to the golden- throated, guitar slinging pioneers of rock-n-roll, focusing on much of the pre-Vegas Elvis era, as well as many of The King's compatriots, like Carl Perkins, Bill Hayley, and Jerry Lee Lewis, to name a few. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever thumb through the Want-Advertiser looking for a used automobile and stumble upon those ads with the side note - &amp;quot;great for parts?&amp;quot; Velvet Elvis is just that - the sum of extremely salvageable parts from classic Boston area bands, welded together to create one finely tuned, well oiled Roots Rock/Rockabill Rock. Rich Bartlett, of The Fools fame, provides the V-6string engine that gets the audience rockin' from 0-60 in seemingly zero time. &lt;br /&gt;Jimmy Rogers is the aftermarket flare that customizes the style and energy of what is known as Velvet Elvis - Boston's Best Tribute to Elvis and the Pioneers of Rock and Roll.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Mass. Pike: Take exit 10 (Auburn).  Follow signs to Route 290 East, then continue as follows...&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Route 290 East: (from Auburn): Take exit 22 - at end of ramp, take a LEFT.  Go about .2 of a mile to a light. Take a LEFT onto N. Quinsigamond Ave, and proceed 1.9 miles to MAIRONIS PARK – it will be on your right, set back from the road.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Route 290 West (from Hudson/Marlboro): Take exit 22 - at end of ramp take a RIGHT.  Go .1 of a mile&lt;br /&gt;to a light. Take a LEFT onto N. Quinsigamond Avenue, and proceed 1.9 miles to MAIRONIS PARK - it will be on your right, set back from the road.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Maironis Park is next to White City Shopping Plaza (south of Route 9).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for tables with meetup signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacki</member_name><member_id>6777705</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256250075000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254873309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Velvet Elvis Band </name><id>11566808</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255822200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/11566808/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/9/global_11105225.jpeg</photo_url></item>