<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lots of things going on Saturday night it seems. But if you are up for something more low-key then meet up at the Avery on the West Side for a drink and conversation. This bar is a lovely little neighborhood lounge and hidden gem. Due to neighborhood restrictions they close at midnight. If anyone wants to stay out a little bit later, we'll head over to Lily Marlene's at the end of Atwells Ave in Federal Hill. This is also a hidden gem and you probably drive by it all the time without realizing it's there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Direction Tips: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.averyprovidence.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.averyprovidence.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

If you can find Julian's on Broadway, there's a gas station just east of that restaurant towards the city. The street there will take you almost directly to the Avery. Go all the way to the stop and when you look to the left, The Avery sits at the center of a fork on the downstairs of a 2-story building. Park in front or on the adjacent streets. &lt;br /&gt;

If you know where the bakery is on Broadway, there's a lighted intersection. That street cuts between Broadway and Westminster. At the stop sign in between those streets, is the street where Avery is going east towards the city. You will also see another great local jaunt at that stop sign - called E&amp;amp;O.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find Lily Marlene's at 422 Atwells Ave, Providence, RI 02909, it's on the west side of Atwells going away from the city. It's in a free standing building adjacent to an empty lot and the next building down is a big church. So across the street is a tattoo place, the Bistro is across from the empty lot, and before you get to it, if coming from downtown, on the right hand side is a cigar bar. The name of the place is etched on the door so at night you have to be standing in front to see it. The windows have beautiful red velvet curtains but from the outside it just looks dark. &lt;br /&gt;

Note that Lily's has a kitchen so they do have a late night menu if you have the munchies.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337578908000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337202429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Low-key Saturday Eve on West Side</name><id>65087352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337479200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/65087352/</event_url></item>