<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 North Great Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.448772</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Minuteman national park</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>12605012</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.273712</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, It's that time of year....Spring is here!!!   I don't know about the rest of you but I'm out of shape and I need to start my riding  season slow... So let's start the season with a fun and fairly easy ride.   My favorite beginning of the season bike ride is the Battle Road that runs from Lincoln to Concord.  If you have never been on it, you will LOVE it!!  It's both beautiful and historical&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Battle Road is the actual path that the Redcoats marched on between Concord &amp;amp; Lexington...you will need a Hybrid or a Mountain Bike to do this ride..&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire ride will be somewhere between 16 to 20 miles because once off the dirt Battle Road Trail we will ride over to the Old North Bridge take a look around head back to Concord to grab a snack and then head back to follow the Battle Road again back to our cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This five mile trail connects historic sites from Meriam’s Corner in Concord to the eastern boundary of the park in Lexington. The main theme of the trail is the Battle of April 19, 1775, that launched the American Revolution. More over, the trail interprets the broader human story of the people whose lives were altered by the events that took place here. Much of the trail follows original remnants of the Battle Road; other sections leave the historic road to follow the route of the Minute Men, traversing farming fields, wetlands, and forests. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If you are interested we can stop at two key points, the Paul Revere Capture Site and the Hartwell Tavern Historical Area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the ride we will go to one of the local "watering holes" for a bite to eat, and some libations..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bike helmets and hybrids or mountain bikes in good repair (we will be riding on packed dirt for the majority of the ride)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;minimum 1 full water bottles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bring snacks and money for refreshments or ice cream in Concord when we take a break&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;A GREAT ATTITUDE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;For more information go to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/mima/planyourvisit/placestogo.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/mima/planyourvisit/placestogo.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's recommended:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ------------------------------------ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Spare tire, repair kit, sun screen, snacks, energy bars, rain gear, an extra layer, a bike lock, and a cell phone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are participating in this ride with members of the 4 Seasons Hiking Meetup Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; The leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We shall meet in the parking lot at the visitor center.  Bring your bikes over to the beginning of the Bike Trail.  My # is 781-856-2933 text for questions of problems.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368594412000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364934710000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>In Honor of Patriots Day let's Ride the Battle Road</name><id>112318642</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368282600000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/112318642/</event_url></item>