<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Who would betray by telling the truth? Who would you lie for? Who can you trust? What do you do when the one you trusted for years may have betrayed your trust? Is it a lie if you don't tell everything you know? Principles before love? Principles before family?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for this new dramatic thriller staring Richard Gere: &lt;em&gt;"Arbitrage&lt;/em&gt;, the feature directorial debut of writer Nicholas Jarecki, is a taut and alluring suspense thriller about love, loyalty, and high finance. On the eve of his 60th birthday, New York hedge-fund magnate Robert Miller (Richard Gere) appears the very portrait of success in American business and family life. But behind the gilded walls of his mansion, Miller is in over his head, desperately trying to complete the sale of his trading empire to a major bank before the depths of his fraud are revealed. Struggling to conceal his duplicity from loyal wife Ellen (Susan Sarandon) and brilliant daughter and heir-apparent Brooke (Brit Marling), Miller's also balancing an affair with French art-dealer Julie Côte (Laetitia Casta). Just as he's about to unload his troubled empire, an unexpected bloody error forces him to juggle family, business, and crime with the aid of Jimmy Grant (Nate Parker), a face from Miller's past. Running on borrowed time, Miller is forced to confront the limits of even his own moral duplicity. Will he make it out before the bubble bursts? Also starring Tim Roth."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at 6:30pm in the Kendall cinema lobby, next to the staircase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will attend the 6:50pm show and head over to Tommy Doyle's or CBC afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Exact date and time subject to change</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348246514000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345935449000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Arbitrage (movie)</name><id>79354622</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348180200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/79354622/</event_url></item>