<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*** &lt;b&gt;Weather update 10/15/09 8:40 PM&lt;/b&gt;: Fri. night cloudy and down to 30F. At meetup time Sat. it will be mostly cloudy and 31F (wind chill feels 27F) so there could be some ice but I don't expect much at all. Day gets more cloudy, winds 8 mph, and high around 3 PM of 43F. By about 7 PM reach low of 33F for the night. Sun. has 40% chance for rain/snow showers with a high of 41F and winds of 12 mph. &lt;b&gt;This has become a winter hike (just no snow).&lt;/b&gt; ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A lovely Fall &lt;b&gt;2-day&lt;/b&gt;, approximately 20.8 mile hike in Vermont on the Appalachian Trail (AT) starting on Mad Tom Notch Rd. (USFS 21) in Mad Tom Notch and heading northbound to Rt. 140.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet 10/17/09 at 8:30 AM at the ending point AT parking area on Rt. 140 a couple miles east of Wallingford, VT. We'll shuttle to the starting trailhead on Mad Tom Notch Rd. (USFS 21) and start hiking by 9:30 AM. We'll hike with rest stops the roughly 9.4 miles to the shelter for the night. We start off in the Peru Peak Wilderness of the Green Mountains and will ascend from 2446 ft. to the twin peaks of Styles and Peru (alt. 3394 and 3429 ft., at miles 1.6 and 3.3). We should have great views of the fall colors from these peaks. We'll have a generally descending trend after that and stop at the Peru Peak Shelter (alt. 2550 ft., at mile 4.6) for lunch and water. We then enter the Big Branch Wilderness of the Green Mountains. We'll hit Baker Peak (alt. 2850 ft., at mile 7.3) for more views and then we'll stop at the Lost Pond Shelter (alt. 2150 ft., at mile 9.4) by about 6 PM at the latest (sunset at 6:06 PM). We'll get water, have dinner, and set up for the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll get up and ready somewhat early the second day given the approximate 11.4 miles we need to cover. We should be hiking by 8:00 AM (sunrise 7:09 AM) and reach the endpoint by about 6:00 PM at the latest (sunset 6:05 PM). The second day has us decending, with a stop at Big Branch Shelter (alt. 1470 ft., at mile 1.7 for the day) for water, to Danby-Landgrove Rd. (USFS 10) with two AT parking areas at mile 3.1. We'll start an upward trend for White Rocks Mtn. We stop near Little Rock Pond to resupply water at about 5.2 miles for the day. A little further on we stop at Little Rock Pond Shelter for lunch (alt. 1820 ft., at mile 5.3 for the day). We continue upward toward the peak of White Rocks Mtn. (don't actually summit) and start a downward trend to reach White Rocks Cliff (alt. 2680, at mile 9.4 for the day). If time permits, we will check out the cliffs which adds about .2 mile to the hike. We then hike the remaining 2 miles to the end on Rte. 140.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll then shuttle back to the beginning to recover vehicle left there. After that we head home!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we could come in earlier than I estimated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Nights should be cold so watch the weather and pack accordingly!&lt;br /&gt;* Backpack -suitable to hold sleeping bag and all other gear and food, overall weight should be no more than about 40 lbs &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable &amp;amp; broken in  &lt;br /&gt;* 2 pair wool socks &lt;br /&gt;* Hat -something good in the rain and/or sun &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold mornings &amp;amp; possibly hot afternoons, avoid cotton as it stays wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Comfortable underwear -no chaffing! &lt;br /&gt;* Rain poncho/jacket -essential! -Gators or rain pants optional &lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag -3 season&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Headlamp -or flashlight, fresh batteries -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;2 quart water min.&lt;/b&gt; -strongly suggest bringing a water filter to restock on water &lt;br /&gt;* Trail meals -2 lunches, 1 dinner, 1 breakfast. High energy meals should be planned. Only meal time to cook are dinner &amp;amp; breakfast. &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks &amp;amp; electrolytes -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, GU energy gel, Gatoraide drink powder, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Toilet paper -in plastic bag to keep dry -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Hand soap/hand sanitizer -in plastic bag &lt;br /&gt;* Personal backpack First Aid kit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries &lt;br /&gt;* Bug spay -not too many bugs now, good for ticks at least&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking cookstove -if cooking &lt;br /&gt;* Matches -for cookstove &lt;br /&gt;* Something to sleep in -PJ's or shorts and T, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* Games or reading for night activity &lt;br /&gt;* Head net -keep bugs out &lt;br /&gt;* Tent &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to the meetup location and endpoint&lt;/b&gt; AT parking area on the &lt;b&gt;north side&lt;/b&gt; of Rt. 140 near Wallingford, VT and 1 - 2 miles to the east (another parking area is on the south side):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/l=43.4568;g=-72.9324" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=43.4568, Lon.=-72.9324]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to the starting point&lt;/b&gt; (we shuttle to this) AT parking area on Mad Tom Notch Rd. (USFS 21) near Peru, VT (note, road is dirt and somewhat rough): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Peru&amp;amp;state=VT&amp;amp;address=2200+Mad+Tom+Notch+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions from Rt. 140 meetup/endpoint to Mad Tom Notch Rd. starting point&lt;/b&gt; (about 50 min.):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?1c=Peru&amp;amp;1s=VT&amp;amp;1a=2200+Mad+Tom+Notch+Rd&amp;amp;1z=05152&amp;amp;1y=US&amp;amp;1l=43.257993&amp;amp;1g=-72.940034&amp;amp;1v=ADDRESS&amp;amp;2qn=Latitude%3A+43.4568%2C+Longitude%3A+-72.9324&amp;amp;2c=East+Wallingford&amp;amp;2s=VT&amp;amp;2z=05742&amp;amp;2y=US&amp;amp;2l=43.4568&amp;amp;2g=-72.9324&amp;amp;2v=LATLNG" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure what vehicle I'll have at the starting point. Look for 6'2" guy &amp; you have my picture on the hiking site.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256071781000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251525444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT from Mad Tom Notch Rd to Rt. 140 VT</name><id>11230061</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255782600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11230061/</event_url></item>