<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;Organizer: Alex Nedzel @ (617) 461-7823&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;*** ALTERNATE HIKE - SOUTH AND MIDDLE CARTER ***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been monitoring the Mt. Washington weather forecast carefully, and thus far the forecast conditions for Tuesday are a bit too angry for us to be comfortable leading you straight into their maw:  90mph wind gusts, -40 degree wind chill. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, I’ve chosen an alternate, more sheltered hike of slightly longer but roughly comparable magnitude that is fully worthy of our attention.  For the extra effort of having to rise out of our warm beds almost an hour sooner, it will deliver us the benefit of nailing two exciting but less frequently visited NH 4000 footers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Alternate Plan:  South and Middle Carter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We’ll hike the Nineteen Mile Brook and Carter Dome trails up to the Carter ridge.  From there, we’ll traverse the Carter-Moriah Trail north, over to South Carter and Middle Carter, where we’ll then turn around and retrace our snowshoe tracks to the cars.  The stats for this route are roughly comparable to those of our originally planned  Mt. Washington hike, though three miles longer:  11.8 miles, 3850’ of elevation gain.  If we find ourselves pressed for time, we will have the option of foregoing Middle Carter, which trims the stats to 9.2 miles, 2950’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should the forecast take a drastic, last-minute turn for the better on Tuesday morning, our group will have the option of driving a few miles south to Pinkham Notch, and attacking Mt. Washington from its eastern side. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gear:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  Please come armed with all the required winter gear we’ve been talking about, including snowshoes and crampons.  If you own an ice axe, feel free also to bring that -- we will take a little time on our hike to go over some basic ice axe technique, and we’ll share as needed.  Lastly, remember to save 1-2L of space in your pack to carry a piece of group gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll meet at &lt;strong&gt;8:30am&lt;/strong&gt;, at the &lt;strong&gt;Nineteen Mile Brook Trailhead&lt;/strong&gt; approximately 7 miles south of Gorham, NH on the east side of Route 16.  GPS coordinates: 44.302138,-71.220889.  This trailhead is approximately 3:30 from Boston and 2:30 from Concord, NH, not counting time for gas, coffee, poor road conditions, and readying gear.  Carpooling continues to be encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*** A NOTE ON THE COLD ***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The forecast keeps getting colder, and we're currently looking at temps in the zero-degree range, combined wiith wind.  It's really important that all of us are dressed for this: Warm (-30 rated or better) boots that do not fit tightly (good circulation is key; similarly, sox and boot uppers should not be tight around your ankle and calf).  In addition to base and mid layers, come with TWO good insulating layers (heavy fleece and/or down) PLUS a windproof shell layer, top and bottom.  You'll most likely start the trip wearing one of the insulating layers, with the other packed.  Bring two pairs of warm mitts/gloves, in addition to liner gloves that you can wear under them -- these are great for when you need to take your mitts off to manipulate something (food, pack adjustment, etc).  You need a workable balaclava/facemask/goggle combo that leaves no facial skin exposed.  Forget about trying to use a camelback/bladder setup for hydration -- it will freeze no mater what you try.  Bring 2-3L of water in bottles., and be sure that this water is close to boiling hot when you leave home.  One bottle should be at your hip in an insulated 'cozy' so that you can drink easily and frequently.  The other water bottles should also be insulated, but can be stored in your pack.  And of course, you want to make sure that whatever food you bring (be generous with yourself, you'll need the energy for heat generation) won't assume the texture of a brick in these temps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVPs for this event will close two days before it is scheduled to occur.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;After celebrating the night before, join us on the #1 day of 2013 on the Northeast's #1 peak - far more fulfilling and healthy than the alternative course of couch potoato-dom!  And because you did celebrate, we're going easy on the start time, relatively speaking -- you just need to get yourself to the meetup point by 9am.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is to climb Mt. Washington (6288') via the beautiful and breathtaking Ammonusuc Ravine Trail and Crawford Path, and return via the more moderate Jewell Trail.  Through almost all of this hike, the views are splendid. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;It could be cold and windy, it could snow, or it could be warm with blue skies, and this is a fully exposed, above treeline hike. Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need warm layers, wind protection, and full crampons among other things. I will update everyone on the weather and conditions as our trip date approaches.  If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip so that it will be ready to go when needed.  Also, please save 1-2L of space in your pack to carry a piece of group emergency gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must register individually.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is NOT a dog friendly hike,&lt;/strong&gt; due to the likelihood of steep ice on our route.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/span&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (1.5-2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; loop, we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 8.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,600 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. It should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 6 hours to complete this trip in favorable conditions&lt;/strong&gt;, not including time for rest/food breaks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE-ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, elevation gain, and likley winter conditions.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/conditions-map.php?find=mt+washington"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?CityName=Mount+Washington&amp;amp;state=NH&amp;amp;site=GYX&amp;amp;textField1=44.2706&amp;amp;textField2=-71.3047"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(weather.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;We will meet in the hiker parking area just below the Mt. Washington Cog Railway station in Bretton Woods, NH.  Via Rts. 93, 3, and 302, and turning L onto Base Station Rd at Fabyans, the driving time to this location is 1:50 from Concord, NH, 3:00 from Boston. As you near the top of Base Station Road, the parking area will on your right approximately 200 yards before you get to the station proper. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;GPS coordinates: &lt;/span&gt; 44.268090, &lt;span&gt;-71.353467.  Note that this is NOT the official trailhead parking lot for the Ammonusuc and Jewell trails, which will be a few tenths of a mile behind you; we will be joining the trails a little farther up the mountain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://mapq.st/VcgezU"&gt;customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(mapquest.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMC Trip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I am running this is an official AMC trip.  Once you add yourself here on Random, I'll be in touch to finalize your sign-up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The AMC's participant waiver/release is pretty similar in spirit to Random's, except that you sign a hardcopy at the trailhead. You can preview it &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease.pdf"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Any questions, don't hesitate to be in touch via e-mail, or via phone at my number above.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Toyota Yaris 4-door with MA Plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1357074901000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356033100000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Mt. Washington on New Year's Day (INTERMEDIATE-ADVANCED)</name><id>96056482</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357047000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/96056482/</event_url></item>