<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>robbinslibrary.org</address_2><address_1>700 Massachusetts Avenue Arlington, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.416168</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-316-3200 </phone><name>Robbins Library</name><city>Arlington</city><id>490314</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.155983</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boston / Cambridge SEO Internet Marketing Networking Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite local Boston seo, affiliate marketing and search engine marketing professionals in New England area to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robbins Library&lt;br /&gt;Mass Ave&lt;br /&gt;Arlington, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm to 7pm: Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Card Buffet: drop you card on the networking buffet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Food Sponsor WANTED*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm to 7:30: 2 Min Elevator Pitch:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Tell us about you and your business or website interest&lt;br /&gt;* Any networking goal your trying to achieve out of this meeting?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - 7:45 1st Guest Speaker &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Selig&lt;br /&gt;Director of Media and Analytics&lt;br /&gt;Overdrive Interactive &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/SEOSEM" target="_blank"&gt;@SeoSem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blended Search: SEO for Social, Video, Images, PDFs and News&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bio:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Director of Media and Analytics, Jeff has over 20 years of media experience from the studios of Electric Lady, working with Hall and Oates, AC/DC and Brian Adams to building video productions facilities for FEDEX TV. Jeff is a veteran media executive who has been in the online space since 1995, designing, building and optimizing sites for a wide variety of clients, including his own domain portfolio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His depth of experience has Jeff consulting to the likes of Bain &amp;amp; Company, McKinsey &amp;amp; Company and many other institutions looking to gain insight in today's fast paced and dynamic online space. Most recently as Vice President of Marketing for Prospectiv Direct, he ran Search marketing SEO, PPC and Social Media online lead generation programs for some of the biggest brands in the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A proven results-driven Executive with a strong track record of building new businesses, growing existing businesses and creating value. Developing strategic alliances, partnerships and the marketing plans, Jeff's skills and experience in business planning and analysis are reflected in the growth of the companies he has worked with and for. You get a strategic thinker who works &amp;quot;hands-on&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:45pm The End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all at this informal Boston search engine round table discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge SEO MeetUp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker's Wanted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been working hard to find industry experts and to develop a formal agenda to keep it interesting for all those that attend at this new big meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food Event Sponsors:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEO Pro's, will work for food! Contact us about sponsoring the event with goodies and drinks in exchange for publicity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Matson</member_name><member_id>1490252</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Hawkins</member_name><member_id>2319452</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter T. Davis</member_name><member_id>2771541</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294772444000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in SEO/SEM</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSEO</urlname><id>219718</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>64</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287764475000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Internet Marketing SEO Networking Event </name><id>15194779</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294702200000</time><rsvp_limit>125</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSEO/events/15194779/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/7/global_3054519.jpeg</photo_url></item>