<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>materials fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Eben Metevier from Kindled (Northern New England Bioneers) and learn to make herbal tinctures with Katherine Korniotes.  Katherine studied herbs and plant energies at the North Carolina School Of Holistic Herbalism.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is another in a series of lead-up events to the October Bioneers Conference in Portland.  There is room for 10 of our meetup members in this workshop!&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the workshop we will be learning about using herbs and extracting their medicinal properties in order to nurture our bodies through a practice that has been around for centuries. The workshop will be hands-on in Dave Homa's beautiful organic garden. We will be collecting the herbs, cutting, straining and applying them. You will walk away from this experience with a freshly-made tincture, a jar with the herb and menstrum that you can tincture at home, and most importantly, the knowledge of how to make your own medicine.  Katherine is planning on using lemon balm, native willow bark, and kava kava.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intro and lite potluck (snacks) from 12:00 to 12:30 followed by the session itself.  Will wrap up around 2pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information email eben(a)kindledinme.com or dave at mainepermaculture(a)gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you are unable to attend, we will be offering additional herb workshops in August and September of this year (focusing on hebs for the immune system as well as tonic herbs for general health).&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216656595000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216130448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Making Herbal Tinctures Hands-On Workshop</name><id>8344479</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216483200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/8344479/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/1/global_4670289.jpeg</photo_url></item>