<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>285 Water Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02885</zip><lat>41.729671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trafford Restaurant</name><city>Warren</city><id>10883572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.285149</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In a crazy fluke of the calendar, this week's Monday Night Meetup falls on New Year's Eve! In light of the fact that many of us have other events to attend that evening, I am officially breaking tradition, and &lt;strong&gt;we will hold the MNM instead THIS SUNDAY (yes, that's tomorrow folks) at Trafford Restaurant in Warren!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trafford is not open on Mondays, and I have been meaning to hold a Sunday gathering here for several months, so here we go and the timing couldn't be better! The snow will have passed and we can pass the afternoon chatting about the storm and raising a glass to the new year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trafford Restaurant is located on Water Street in Warren, on the Warren River. It offers a very updated, clean nautical theme and two bars. One downstairs and smaller, which overlooks the river and  is open to the breezes in the summer and enclosed in the winter with heat lamps, and a larger upstairs bar and dining area that also overlooks the river. It's really quite nice and the food I've had there is very good! The whole atmosphere is updated and fresh, which I love!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come on down to Warren, celebrate the new year a day early, and appropriately, in RI, on the water! &lt;span&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AND as always, in the Monday Night Meetup tradition:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy and NYE 2012!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the UPSTAIRS bar. The views of the water are great from the second floor! I'll be wearing the scarf or hat int the picture, but we're not hard to find!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356905708000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356804140000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre- New Year's Gathering - THIS SUNDAY AFTERNOON at Trafford!</name><id>96960142</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356894000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/96960142/</event_url></item>