<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>351 Boylston Street</address_2><address_1>Arlington Street Church</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352021</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Friday Night Supper Program (FNSP)</name><city>Boston</city><id>1021154</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071292</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We provide nutritious, home-cooked meals to the homeless and hungry people of Boston in a safe and dignified environment/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FNSP serves approximately 130 meals every Friday to some of Boston’s most vulnerable citizens, many of whom face a constant struggle not only for food but for understanding and friendship as well. We pride ourselves on providing both nourishment for the body through food and for the soul through dignity and respect. We also seek and value the opinions of the people we serve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FNSP is committed to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Serving as much fresh food as possible with an emphasis on nutritional value &lt;br /&gt;* Providing basic needs such as clothing and toiletries for our guests &lt;br /&gt;* Offering a sense of security, abundance, and choice to those who have limited or no access to these very basic essentials. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been serving 13,000 meals a year to those in need every Friday night since 1984. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. It is important that you RSVP here: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/calendar/13730173/?from=list&amp;amp;offset=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonvolu...&lt;/a&gt; (Very popular celebration. Few spots left!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been volunteering at FSNP for over a year, it's an amazing operation. It runs like clockwork. Between 5 and 7 we serve approximately 130 meals, clean up, and leave the place like we were never there. And it's been happening since 1984. It's busy and it's fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP yes only if you can definitely make it for the entire shift 5-7pm. FNSP schedules the number of volunteers it uses each week, so if anyone doesn't show up it really impacts the program. If your plans change, please change your reply ASAP so I can try to fill the spot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: FNSP is located in the basement of the Arlington Street Church at the intersection of Arlington and Boylston Streets in the Back Bay section of Boston. The program entrance is just off Arlington Street in Public Alley 438 (between Boylston and Newbury Streets). Go down the stairs, ring the bell if the doors are not open yet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Trans: The church is right to next the Arlington St. station (Green Line)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dress code is very simple: volunteers should tie up long hair and wear closed toe shoes with no heels. That's it. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. It is important that you RSVP here: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/calendar/13730173/?from=list&amp;amp;offset=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonvolu...&lt;/a&gt; (Very popular celebration. Few spots left!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helping your community. Meeting good new people who share your values. Feeling great about yourself! :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"The program entrance is just off Arlington Street in Public Alley 438 (between Boylston and Newbury Streets). Go down the stairs, ring the bell if the doors are not open yet." </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346122165000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285026512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Helping hungry Bostonians. Very popular celebration. Few spots left!  </name><id>14838636</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290819600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/14838636/</event_url></item>