<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bearsden Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01331</zip><lat>42.604852</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bearsden Conservation Area</name><city>Athol</city><id>985992</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.191981</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;This is a very cool place to explore. I've recently hiked a few of the trails here and would love to explore more of them and share some that I have hiked.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;Tomorrow, I'd like to hike Round Top Trail (which is absolutely beautiful!) to Bearsden Road to Duck Pond to Fire Road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;These are not paved roads. They are older roads now used as part of the trail system. Fire Road is along the Miller's River.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;This hike is approximately 5 miles in length and approximately 2 1/2 hours in hiking time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;This hike is moderate in difficulty with a moderately short in length yet  partially steep climb to Round Top. You must be healthy and somewhat fit to do this hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : large"&gt;Please bring adequate cold water (most people need at least 16 ounces)and lunch or snacks if you need them too).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : large"&gt;Also prior to the hike (or via email) please privately let me know if you have any medical conditions I should be aware of in case of emergency, ie: asthma, seizures, heart disease, diabetes, allergies, hypo or hyperglycemia, blood pressure problems, etc...&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : large"&gt;any health conditions that could likely pose a threat to you during a hike and provide me with knowledge of a proper treatment plan in case of emergency. Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/219"&gt;http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/219&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Activities Prohibited &lt;br /&gt;

 ATV's/ORV's &lt;br /&gt;

 Available Information &lt;br /&gt;

 Brochure &lt;br /&gt;

 Information Kiosk &lt;br /&gt;

 Facilities &lt;br /&gt;

 Picnic Area &lt;br /&gt;

 Fees &lt;br /&gt;

 No fee &lt;br /&gt;

 Land Owner &lt;br /&gt;

 Town &lt;br /&gt;

 Parking &lt;br /&gt;

 Yes &lt;br /&gt;

 Pets &lt;br /&gt;

 Pets OK &lt;br /&gt;

 Recreation Activities &lt;br /&gt;

 Fishing &lt;br /&gt;

 Hiking &lt;br /&gt;

 Hunting &lt;br /&gt;

 Mountain biking &lt;br /&gt;

 Rock climbing &lt;br /&gt;

 Road biking &lt;br /&gt;

 Snowmobiling &lt;br /&gt;

 x-country Skiing &lt;br /&gt;

 Season &lt;br /&gt;

 All Seasons &lt;br /&gt;

 Signage &lt;br /&gt;

 Off-site sign &lt;br /&gt;

 Trailhead sign&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearsden Conservation Area&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearsden Rd., Athol, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miles of forested trails among steep hills, stone walls, &amp;amp; views of the Millers River - beautiful all year round. &lt;br /&gt;

 Description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ten miles of trails crisscrossing 1,000 acres of forest, some climbing hills with wonderful views of the Millers River and of mountains near and far; some leading down to the river itself; some, like those that parallel stone walls and traverse a cut through rock ledge, revealing human history - all of this and more await visitors to the premier conservation area of the town of Athol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A strenuous climb takes visitors to Round Top, at 1,278 feet Athol’s second highest hill, and to Warren’s Vista, each with panoramic views of the valleys around. Other trails lead to the Newton Reservoir, no longer a water supply but still a lovely pond; to Duck Pond, a haven for waterfowl; to the Ox Bow, a curve in the river and a popular picnic spot; and to a magnificent wetland known as Thousand-Acre Swamp. Visitors can listen to the songs of myriad birds and find evidence of other wildlife that frequents Bearsden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A map board at the parking area outlines the many possibilities for exploration, and a log cabin, built of local hemlock, is available for overnight use. Call Conservation Constable Elwin Bacon (978-249-2004) to reserve the cabin; limited camping is also permitted by prior arrangement with the constable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;From downtown Athol, go east on Main St. (Rte. 2A) approx. 1.5 mi. Take left onto Bearsden Rd. Go 1 mi., bear right to stay on Bearsden Rd and continue 0.5 mi. to entrance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;Bearsden Road has a big conservation area sign at the base of it from Main Street(rt 2A) in Athol. It may say Athol Conservation Area as it is referred to by both names. Bearsden Road is located across the street from Larry's Variety Meat and Produce market which is next to the Athol Hospital. There are signs to the hospital from rt 2 at the Athol exits to get you to that vicinity. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/MqXWx"&gt;http://goo.gl/maps/MqXWx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345463243000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345337428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Explore Beautiful Bearsden Conservation Area Trails</name><id>78345322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345388400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/78345322/</event_url></item>