<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join us at the upcoming Providence Latin American Film Festival!  The festival runs from September 30th through October 3rd.  There are numerous films at various venues in Providence and all movies are $6!  Please check out the film listings - if folks can let me know which films they are interesting in seeing we can coordinate  specific meetup times and places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the press release:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;PROVIDENCE, RI (August 9, 2010) – The Providence Latin American Film Festival (PLAFF) is pleased to announce its 18th annual festival, September 30 – October 3, 2010 at the RISD Auditorium, RISD’s Metcalf Theater and Bryant University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since it’s founding in 1992, this unique event has shown more than 650 feature films, shorts, documentaries and animations from Latin America, Portugal and Spain.  Many have gone on to receive international awards. In addition to the festival, the organization presents filmmakers’ workshops, art exhibits, panel discussion and free screenings.  PLAFF believes in teaching understanding and appreciation of the Latin American experience through film and culture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As one of the most exciting film festivals of its kind in New England, PLAFF has been recognized nationally and internationally for its rich history and the quality of its films and programs. It is the first Latin American film festival to present juried awards.&lt;br /&gt;Program and schedule of events will be announced at a later date and will be posted on the festival website: &lt;a href="http://www.plaff.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.plaff.org...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: The Providence Latin American Film Festival (PLAFF) will celebrate its 18th anniversary with first-class films from Latin America, Portugal and Spain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Thursday, September 30 through Sunday, October 3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: RISD Auditorium, RISD Museum’s Metcalf Auditorium and Bryant University.  A free community screening is scheduled for the International Institute of Rhode Island (date: TBD). General admission is $6.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more specifics please check out the website: www.plaff.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285884659000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist</urlname><id>12929</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284401959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society - Providence Latin American Film Festival!</name><id>14755149</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285880400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist/events/14755149/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/0/global_13237216.jpeg</photo_url></item>