<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Al --&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I'd really like to go see this movie on Monday or Tuesday evening if you'd like to post it for the group and see if anyone wants to join me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;I see the show is on Monday and Tuesday.. I just chose tuesday,,well since its already monday now..well&lt;br /&gt;just about now here...&lt;br /&gt;anyway...let Gloria know if you are going..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;as much as i like seeing things...my eyes need a rest..besides i have to wear sunglasses for a few days more.....cant see a movie well thta way...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look at Gloria's comment section on how to find her at the place..its actually a pretty good place...art stuff..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The INFO :&lt;br /&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;Disappearances&lt;br /&gt;Q&amp;amp;A w/ Director Jay Craven Tuesday, July 10 following the 7:30pm screening &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This picaresque ?western? set in Kingdom County Vermont has a great cast that includes a grizzled Kris Kristofferson, a spooky Genevieve Bujold, a wily Gary Farmer and a loathsome Lothaire Bluteau. Visually the film exposes a hard-scrabble universe of gut-wrenching hard work and ruined dreams, but set against breath-takingly beautiful scenery with virgin woods and clear streams. One who?s not willing to ruin a dream, Quebec Bill (Kristofferson) leads a little army out of northern Vermont in 1932 to steal a notorious smuggler?s cache of whiskey and return it to the US?for Bill?s own profit of course. Enlisting his brother-in-law?s white Cadillac for speed and durability and taking his young teen son Wild Bill (a misnomer) along for the experience. Quebec Bill?s adventures are often punctuated by magical realism and Wild Bill?s by many firsts?first time drunk and first kill among them. Chasing them for his liquor is Carcajou, a French Canadian bandit played by Bluteau, dressed in a civil war uniform that looks more like a costume than clothes. It?s all a wonderful time, often sweet and comical. Vermont director Jay Craven made the film for $1.7 million but the money went far in the obvious places. The look and feel of the film is as rich as its characters. (US, 2006) 103 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hartford Courant review can be found here:   &lt;a href="http://www.courant.com/entertainment/movies/hc-disappearancesrev0706.artjul06,0,1583503.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.courant.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;Real Art Ways Members: $5&lt;br /&gt;Seniors &amp;amp; Students Members: $4.50&lt;br /&gt;Non-members: Regular Admission: $9.00 &lt;br /&gt;Seniors (62+): $6.25&lt;br /&gt;Full-time Students with ID: $6.25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shows are at 5:30 and 7:30 either Monday or Tuesday, with Tuesday's 7:30 show including a talk by the director.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many casual places to grab a bite to eat in that neighborhood before or after the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184282310000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183952886000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gloria's Movie suggestion.</name><id>5994359</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184109300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5994359/</event_url></item>