<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Walnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02460</zip><lat>42.346506</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>United Methodist Church</name><city>Newtonville</city><id>1280079</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.206274</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A live auction to help to stop obesity in Children. Karen Ranzi author of Creating Healthy Children will be hosting a workshop at 7:15. Potluck Dinner at 6:00 PM. Registration Begins at 5:30PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this workshop, Karen Ranzi will guide you on the path  to creating happy and healthy children, confident of their disease-free future. Rather than medicate your child's asthma, ear infections, chronic allergies and learning problems, Karen's holistic approach simply eliminates the causes of health problems through a healthful raw food lifestyle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She will share the value of understanding the biological and emotional needs of children. You will learn the importance of obtaining the best possible nourishment for your family, and how to implement healthy choices successfully during pregnancy and raising children. She shares delicious kid-tested recipes and reveals terrific tips for children of all ages in how to improve their diet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Author, lecturer, and raw food consultant, Karen Ranzi, has recently authored her much-anticipated new book, Creating Healthy Children: Through Attachment Parenting and Raw Foods. She has been interviewed on TV and radio on the topics of vegetarian and raw food parenting. Karen has presented her class “Creating Healthy Children” at numerous seminars, festivals and health institutes throughout the United States. In addition to her work in raw vegan nutrition, Karen holds a Masters degree in speech pathology from New York University, and is a speech therapist working with children of all ages for over 30 years, specializing with autistic children for the past 8 years. By means of her education, life-changing personal experiences, and sincere desire to share her message, Karen has been able to guide thousands toward developing excellent health.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to bid on our fantastic items before our live auction begins you can bid on our silent portion at &lt;a href="http://www.biddingforgood.com/optimumhealth" target="_blank"&gt;www.biddingforgood.com/optimumhealth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To help eliminate obesity in children:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Donate services or items at &lt;a href="http://www.biddingforgood.com/optimumhealth" target="_blank"&gt;www.biddingforgood.com/optimumhealth&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;    * Bid for items on  &lt;a href="http://www.biddingforgood.com/optimumhealth" target="_blank"&gt;www.biddingforgood.com/optimumhealth&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;    * Come Tuesday July 20th to this fun event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceeds go to scholarships and CSA shares for low-income families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost $18 if bought online at &lt;a href="http://optimumhealth.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;optimumhealth.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt; and $20 at the door  with an organic, unprocessed, raw/vegan/unprocessed dish to feed 8 or $10 extra without food.  Questions, call Betsy Bragg 781-899-6664 or email betsy@optimumhealthsolution.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Betsy Bragg,  Executive Director&lt;br /&gt;Optimum Health Solution&lt;br /&gt;337 Newton  St. #4&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA 02453&lt;br /&gt;781-899-6664&lt;br /&gt;cell 617-835-2913&lt;br /&gt;Fax 617-663-6868&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.OptimumHealthSolution.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.OptimumHealthSolution.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;posted by &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.com" target="_blank"&gt;essenic.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please wear Meetup button (click Promote on left), introduce yourself, &amp; enjoy!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 11398866</member_name><member_id>11398866</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279723932000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277567126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS Potluck/Auction/Talk: Karen Ranzi</name><id>13917640</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279661400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/13917640/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/5/global_8815349.jpeg</photo_url></item>