<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Soldiers Field Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.361426</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-454-1444</phone><name>Publick Theatre</name><city>Brighton</city><id>693524</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.146548</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>7:30 Performance of Checkhov's The Seagul under the stars at The Publick Theatre in Christian Herter Park.  Directed by Diego Arciniegas. On a fading country estate in rural Russia, a mix of celebrated artists, their family and servants weigh their lives. Some hope to defy the obstacles between reality and their dreams, while the others seek comfort by consigning themselves to the inevitable. A delicate balance of levity and drama reveals a surprising kinship to more contemporary dark comedies of stage and screen, demonstrating Chekhov’s ability to transcend time, place and layers of historic interpretation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy your ticket ($32/ $27 student or 62+) at the event when the box office opens at  at 6:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a large parking lot across from WBZ.  Head into the park, follow signs for Publick Theatre and you will spot the picnic area, where we will gather at 6:00-7:15 for a BYO picnic supper.  (Wine and beer should be brought in disguises like a Thermos.)  BRING A SEAT CUSHION not only for comfort, but also to allow me to claim an area for us in the open-seating ampitheater at 6:30 when gates open (but I will return right away to the picnic).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions? Call Thurman at 781-388-9386. Cell phone 617-571-3740&lt;br /&gt;wil be on from 5:00 to 7:30 that evening.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Gather at the picnic table with Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>THURMAN SMITH</member_name><member_id>1416920</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219442934000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218771053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Theater under the stars: Checkov's The Seagull</name><id>8548770</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219269600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/8548770/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/d/3/global_5159075.jpeg</photo_url></item>