<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373271</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)876-2700</phone><name>Crema Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>693403</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120426</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>More than 150 years and many cultural upheavals later, Emily Brontë’s only novel remains almost blindingly original, undimmed in its power to convey the destructive potential of thwarted passion as expressed through the unappeasable fury of a rejected lover. To paraphrase Shakespeare, age cannot wither it, nor custom stale its infinite variety. Every aspect of the novel—whether it be the writer’s expert grasp of the laws pertaining to land and personal property, her meticulous rendering of local dialect, or her use of multiple narrators—has been put under microscopic study. And yet, despite the shelf after shelf of books that have been written in the attempt to understand the frail yet flinty-willed young woman—&amp;quot;the sphinx of literature,&amp;quot; as she was called by Angus M. Mackay in The Brontës: Fact and Fiction (1897)—who wrote it, as well as the tragedy-struck, remarkably talented family from which she came, Wuthering Heights still presents a dark and fierce view of the world that is seemingly without precedent.&lt;br /&gt;--from Daphne Merkin’s Introduction to Wuthering Heights &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274720334000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273510205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brontë: Wuthering Heights</name><id>13438163</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274652000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/13438163/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/a/7/global_5819031.jpeg</photo_url></item>