<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;The Tree of Life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; directed by Terrence Malick 2011 USA 138 min.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Screening time is 5 pm.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;The Tree of Life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; opens this weekend but I will not be able to host this film&amp;nbsp;until the end of June. Hopefully&amp;nbsp;there will be multiple postings&amp;nbsp; for our group for the (&amp;nbsp;somewhat surprising) winner of the&amp;nbsp;2011 Palme d&amp;rsquo;Or prize at Cannes&amp;nbsp;. This event&amp;nbsp;will be limited to 10&amp;nbsp;and will use&amp;nbsp;a waiting list. Members on a manual waiting list receive an email whenever a spot opens up. Whoever responds first gets in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Terrence Malick, the acclaimed director of &lt;em&gt;Badlands, Days of Heaven&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Thin Red Line&lt;/em&gt;, comes &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Tree of Life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/em&gt;an impressionistic story of a Midwestern family in the 1950s. The film follows the life journey of the eldest son, Jack, through the innocence of childhood to his disillusioned adult years as he tries to reconcile a complicated relationship with his father (Brad Pitt). Jack (played as an adult by Sean Penn) finds himself a lost soul in the modern world, seeking answers to the origins and meaning of life while questioning the existence of faith. Through Malick's signature imagery, we see how both brute nature and spiritual grace shape not only our lives as individuals and families, but all life. Kendall Description&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/film/video/2011/may/16/finding-terrence-malick-cannes-2011-video"&gt;Terrence Malick's mad and magnificent film&lt;/a&gt; descends slowly, like some sort of prototypical spaceship: it's a cosmic-interior epic of vainglorious proportions, a rebuke to realism, a disavowal of irony and comedy, a meditation on memory, and a gasp of horror and awe at the mysterious inevitability of loving, and losing those we love. Guardian UK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Terry had been collecting footage for decades, since Badlands," Jack Fisk, the director's longtime production designer and collaborator, told the LA Times. "Things like eclipses and other natural wonders, just for this film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;The Tree of Life's&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; fetching images are like glowing shards of glass, and together they form a grandiose mirror that reflects Malick's impassioned philosophical outlook. It's unquestionably this great filmmaker's most personal work, a revelation of how he came to be, why he creates, and where he feels he's going. And though it's also a highly self-absorbed vision, emotionally aloof by aesthetic design, in connecting his elliptical depiction of his own spiritual making with a customarily quizzical regard for the shape of all things, from the veins of a plant to the wrinkles of the human face, Malick is sincerely asking us to scrutinize the meaning of our own creation. Slant Magazine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully it will be a warm early summer eve where we can discuss &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;The Tree of Life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #003300"&gt;al fresco at either Doyle's or CBC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film and then we will dine al fresco at either Doyle's or CBC</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1309405870000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306279873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Terrence Malick's The Tree of Life</name><id>19604721</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309122000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/19604721/</event_url></item>