<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>141 Standish Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02908</zip><lat>41.836881</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-521-6133</phone><name>Pia's Place</name><city>Providence</city><id>834034</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.452666</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our Third Vegetarian/Organic Meetup will be on January 17th at 6:00p.m at Pia’s house in Providence (direction below).  We have had two great meetings so far, the first at the Garden Grille Café and the second was a potluck at Kevin’s house in Coventry. Each time we had more members attending so let’s keep the momentum going!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the food was so incredible at our last meeting we decided to have another potluck, if you would like to bring a dish (optional) please make sure that it is Vegan.  I look forward to seeing everyone on January 17th!  Please remember to RSVP and feel free to bring a friend or two.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Ward Residence&lt;/b&gt; (141 Standish Avenue):&lt;br /&gt;95 (North or South) to exit 22, follow signs to “Providence Place Mall”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At end of exit ramp can only turn Right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drive to end of street. Straight ahead will be entrance to parking for Providence Place Mall. Make a U turn at traffic light to the Left. Travel down road (parallel to road you just drove down after exiting 95)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just before next set of lights, and right after passing Red Cross Blood Center, take a right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pass Coca cola plant on Right. At second set of lights turn Left onto Chalkstone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pass Shell gas station (on left, first set of lights). Pass Walgreen (on right at second set of lights). At third set of lights turn Right onto Mount Pleasant Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fourth block on Left is Rialto Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Left onto Rialto (there will be a soccer field on your right). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take first left. Ward household is only house on this block. &lt;br /&gt;White with black shutters, 141 on front screen door, 2 large pines on either side. It is located across from Mt Pleasant high school football stadium (with medium sized island just in front of house).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pia’s telephone number in case anyone gets lost is 401-521-6133.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kerrie Amatelli</member_name><member_id>2732003</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin</member_name><member_id>7947968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234910965000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229437391000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our Third Vegetarian/Organic Meetup is Schedule for January 17th at 6:00p.m!</name><id>9346833</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232233200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/9346833/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/8/global_6156808.jpeg</photo_url></item>