<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color : #0a0000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Life Science Innovation &amp;amp; Technology Forum (IGNITE): Announcing the Nominated Companies To Speak at Our Exciting Event!&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt; When: Tuesday, September 27, 2011, 5:30 PM &amp;ndash; 9:00 PM Where: 100 Technology Square Atrium (Novartis Building), Cambridge, MA 02140 Website &amp;amp; Registration: 
&lt;a href="http://www.bvsweb.com/php/register.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bvsweb.com/php/register.php&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;(Select Event Details for a Full Itinerary. Mass Life Science Center Subscribers Enjoy a Special Discount of 25% Off of the $45.00 Attendee Fee through September 9, 2011 &amp;ndash; Enter IGNITE25 when registering)&lt;/strong&gt; Please join us for an exciting evening of presentations from companies, which have been nominated to highlight their cutting edge technologies comprising areas such as: sequencing, imaging, lab automation, bioinformatics, and bio-processing. Attendees will be life science researchers and professionals from industry, academia, as well as from the investment community, service providers, and state and local government among others. Complimentary Wine and Hors D&amp;rsquo; Oeuvres will be served during our reception. Light Refreshments along with Cash Bar will be available throughout the night. 
&lt;strong&gt;Keynote Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Winston Patrick Kuo,&lt;/strong&gt; Director, Harvard Catalyst Laboratory for Innovative Translational Technologies 
&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Susan Windham-Bannister&lt;/strong&gt;, President and CEO, Massachusetts Life Sciences Center Advanced design and construction of innovative robotic systems and laboratory devices used by pharmaceutical, biotech companies, and academic research laboratories to accelerate drug discovery and biorepository science 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Presenter: Chris Pacheco, Ph.D., Director of Life Sciences&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Innovative technology enabling easy and rapid isolation and access to Circulating Rare Cells in peripheral blood enabling the biopharma and academia research and discovery 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Presenter: Mich&amp;egrave;le Arnoe, VP Marketing &amp;amp; Business Development&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Evaluation and identification of emerging biomedical technologies through unbiased analytics approach to the complex process of technology evaluation focused on the biopharma industry with tested expertise across biologic and chemical science 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Presenter: David Greenwald, Ph.D., Co-Founder/Chief Executive Officer&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Novel high-throughput cellular microenvironment screening technology, coupled with cancer genomics capabilities, resulting in a powerful strategy toward drug discovery and development 
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Presenter: Douglas W. McMillin, Ph.D., Founder/Chief Executive Officer&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; Speaker Information: 
&lt;a href="mailto:inquire@munevarassociates.com" target="_blank"&gt;inquire@munevarassociates.com&lt;/a&gt; Event Information: 
&lt;a href="mailto:info@bvsweb.com" target="_blank"&gt;info@bvsweb.com&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;em&gt;Brought to You By: Biotech Vendor Services, Inc. and Munevar &amp;amp; Associates, Inc., with space kindly provided by Alexandria Real Estate Equities, Inc.&lt;/em&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317163784000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315358034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Announcing the Nominated Companies To Speak at Our Exciting Event!</name><id>32532902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317159000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/32532902/</event_url></item>