<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;latest prediction: NOTE : as i guessed and hoped the weather is looking better closer to the event day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: A chance of showers, mainly before 10am. Cloudy through mid morning, then gradual clearing, with a high near 65. Northwest wind between 10 and 18 mph. Chance of precipitation is 30%. New rainfall amounts of less than a tenth of an inch possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if we decide to not do the Q- Bugg for some reason, the East Brookfield River is right near the boat launch and ok for us up to about 2 or so miles,&lt;br /&gt;Then we just head to the after party at Roberts a bit earlier,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;since the days are getting shorter i set the start time to 12.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Q-Bugg River looks like a interesting trip through many different kinds of wilderness areas while going along with the current all the way to the take out point at Lucy Park in Warren MA making for a nice 10 mile down stream excursion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its actually a long travel distance for an event but i have not done this streach of river yet and want to know if its worth listing it officially this year or next year, &lt;br /&gt;and besides i move the events around, some closer for some some further, it all avrages out in the end...So:&lt;br /&gt;It starts at apx 126 Quaboag Street in Brookfield MA and goes to Lucy Stone Park at px 171 Old West Brookfield Road in Warren MA,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The put in has a nice large parking area,&lt;br /&gt;The take out area has 2 points, one before the bridge and one after.&lt;br /&gt;It depends on water level/flow which is better on the day of.&lt;br /&gt;We will most likely take out before the bridge and carry our yaks a few hundred feet so bring your transport wheels or we just simply help each other also since its a small groop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Destination: 126 Quaboag Street, Brookfield, MA boat ramp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford: 50 miles.&lt;br /&gt;Take I 84 East for 42 miles to exit # 3 A  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the Rte 20 East exit and follow rte 20 East for 2 miles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto Rte 49 North&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take 49 North for 4 miles to the intersection of Flagg Road,&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto Flagg Road and an immediate right onto Podunk Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Podunk Road for 1.5 miles then take a left onto Shore Rd,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boat launch is apx three quarter miles further on the left.&lt;br /&gt;see ya there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting from the boat launch to Lucy Stone Park:&lt;br /&gt;Take a left out of the boat launch, follow Quaboag St to the intersection of rte 9.&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto rte 9 heading west,&lt;br /&gt;Follow rte 9 for 4.75 miles to the split of rte 67 / 9&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the left onto rte 67 follow that for 2.5 miles to Warren Center then take a RIGHT onto  Old West Brookfield Rd, go apx 1/4 mile and the park is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRING SOME POTLUCK FOOD, STUFF TO BURN, AND YOUr PREFERRED BEVERAGE(S)&lt;br /&gt;for the after party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details forthcoming on location, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have driving directions and a map for those that need it to Roberts home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 15 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this RIVER trip with WERNER Fiberglass and Carbon paddles with paddle leaches..Now All Kayaks come with &amp;quot;Yakpads&amp;quot; brand Gel High Back Seats also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ya wont get that from your local Rent-A-Yak places..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;since we will stop along the way everynow and then..ya can switch yaks and paddles or whatever..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lady, Short Sea Kayak Necky Eliza Fiberglass Version 16 ' @ 40 lbs with Fibergalss Werner paddle= ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Short Sea Kayak Riot Tourlite 15', with Fiberglass Werner Camano or Greenland wood paddle= ?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Long SOT Sea Kayak, Cobra Expidition SOT 18', with Werner Carbon Kaliste Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner Wind Dancer 18', Long sea Kayak with Werner Carbon Kaliste Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red NDK Greenlander Pro 18', Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Werner Fiberglass Camano Paddle  paddle= = &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CT-Recreational-Sea-Kayakers/calendar/11536083/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see ya soon..al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I WILL BE WEARING AN ORANGE HUNTING HAT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256229566000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254578889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*KAYAKING  TRIP - FALL FOLIAGE  EXPLORATION down current*@  Q-BUGG RIVER </name><id>11536083</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255190400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11536083/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_5044665.jpeg</photo_url></item>