<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>321 Main Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04609</zip><lat>44.384259</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207 288-5587</phone><name>Bar Harbor Hostel</name><city>Bar Harbor</city><id>1358586</id><country>us</country><lon>-68.203455</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi! Everyone,  One more last call for Bar Harbor.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.barharborhostel.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.barharborh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is $25 per night.. They have 22 beds available. Currently there are only 16 of us signed up so there is still room to add on.  If you still wish to come, please indicate it here but call the Hostel direct to let them know, I have given them our final count.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone who cancels at this point will be charged for their space. &lt;b&gt;If you need to reach the Hostel their phone # is:207-288-5587&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tell them you are with the Greater Boston Cycling Group, or give them my name Cyndi Pariseau&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;On Friday at 7:30 we will have a gathering in the Lobby at the Hostel.  If you could each bring an appetizer with you and a bottle of wine/beer or beverage of your choice... We can order pizza's for the group.. Since people will be arriving at different times, we can just hang out in the Hostel that night, socialize and get to know one another.  Some may want to go for a stroll around town.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday we will bike the Carriage road around Acadia National Park and stop at the Jordan Pond House for Scones and snacks... If you have never been there it's beautiful....  Mountain Bikes and Hybrids are  more appropriate for this, because if I recall it's packed dirt road... If you don't have one, there are a ton of bike shops up there that rent them&lt;/b&gt;...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday Night we will all go out for a Group Dinner... I will try to make a reservation at a reasonably priced location...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, we won't make a plan right now... everone may want to do different things, of course the hiking is great, there are Adorable shops and restaurants, and they happen to be having the Mt Desert Island Marathon on Sunday the 17th...  So if you are a runner perhaps you might want to sign up.  It also could be a fun event to watch...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the website for that:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mdimarathon.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mdimarathon.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have already sent out a note with more details to the trip participants! Check the message more on the meetup sight for these details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you book this and are not going to make it you are obligated to cancel 48 hours in advance.. Otherwise you will be charged for the spot... Please do not book it unless you know for sure you can go otherwise you are preventing others from attending that know they can..&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a great weekend.  If you have never been to Bar Harbor it's like a little peice of Heaven up there!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Greater Boston Cycling group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287764174000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282859563000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FALL BAR HARBOR WEEKEND OCT 15-17</name><id>14554666</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287183600000</time><rsvp_limit>23</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/14554666/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/2/7/global_17483415.jpeg</photo_url></item>