<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>246 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.395358</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 629-4963</phone><name>Diva India Bistro Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1347820</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122204</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The sequel to "Sister of My Heart."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Publisher's Weekly review, found on Amazon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This exquisitely rendered tale of passion, jealousy and redemption  continues the extraordinary relationship between Anjou and Sudha, the  two exceptional women at the heart of Divakaruni's praised Sister of My  Heart. The two cousins have traveled a lifetime away from their home  city of Calcutta to California, a place so foreign to their native  culture and traditions that they must constantly reevaluate their  bearings and values. Anjou, miserable after a miscarriage and its  unhappy effect on her marriage, and Sudha, fleeing both a husband whose  family urged her to abort her daughter, and a first love who wants to  take care of her and her child, hope to find solace in their sisterlike  relationship. Divakaruni expertly juxtaposes the challenges, freedoms  and crassness of modern-day America with the issues, both personal and  cultural, each woman faces. Anjou uses Sudha to help her cope with a  growing restlessness as well as with dissatisfaction with her husband,  Sunil. Sudha is both comforted and suffocated by her life as an escapee  from her past, becoming a servant in her cousin's household. At the same  time, each woman must eventually acknowledge Anjou's husband's unspoken  but obvious attraction to Sudha. Divakaruni combines a gift for  absorbing narrative with the artistry of a painter. Her lyrical  descriptions of the characters' inner and outer worlds bring a rich  emotional chiaroscuro to an uplifting story about two women who learn to  make peace with the difficult choices circumstances have forced upon  them. Agent, Sandra Dijkstra. National author tour. (Feb. 1)Forecast:  Already a reading group favorite, and consistently hailed by critics,  Divakaruni can expect excitement for this book to build quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Books on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313356067000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303324859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August 2011 - Vine of Desire</name><id>17374804</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313251200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/17374804/</event_url></item>