<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302 &amp; George Street</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.078011</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>837242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.283012</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come on up for a weekend of thrills more fun than a barrel of monkeys!  Top on the agenda for the weekend will be the Monkey Trunks ropes course.  There are 2 available courses:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discovery Course&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dare&lt;br /&gt;yourself or challenge your friends to do the 27 exciting elements set&lt;br /&gt;on 3 different levels up to 65' with 500' dual zip lines and giant&lt;br /&gt;swing. Try the tension traverse or crazy ladder, jumping platforms,&lt;br /&gt;swinging beams and even skateboarding on a tightrope. As you progress up&lt;br /&gt;the course, things get even more difficult! Will the gauntlet defeat&lt;br /&gt;you? Have you got the strength for the net climb? Our adrenaline fueled&lt;br /&gt;challenges will push you to the limit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jungle Course&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For real adrenaline junkies we have the King Kong of all courses - 15&lt;br /&gt;of the toughest challenges traversing through the forest of the White&lt;br /&gt;Mountains. You will begin with a 90 foot zip line into the forest and&lt;br /&gt;end with a giant swing into one of the world's largest spider webs.&lt;br /&gt;You'll be crossing rolling logs, walking on hanging tires and even&lt;br /&gt;jumping the leopard's leap all at 65' above the forest floor. There's no&lt;br /&gt;lower level here for wimps! And no way back!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.monkeytrunks.com/index.php?page=new-hampshire" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.monkeytrun...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After monkeying around in the trees join us for a Monk(ey) fish dinner &lt;br /&gt;and a wine tasting. We will be celebrating the wines from the monkey &lt;br /&gt;country of South Africa: Pinotage and Chenin Blanc, just to name two. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chenin Blanc is most famous for its dominant role in many of the sweet &lt;br /&gt;dessert wines of the Loire Valley in France. But when it found a home in&lt;br /&gt;South Africa's vineyards it was reborn as a delicious dry wine. There &lt;br /&gt;are plenty of dry Chenin Blanc wines in France, too, but it was the &lt;br /&gt;South African vintners that brought this grape to new heights of &lt;br /&gt;appreciation as a dry wine grape to the R.O.W. (Rest Of World). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pinotage&lt;br /&gt;is all South Africa, a cross between Pinot Noir and Cinsault (AKA &lt;br /&gt;Hermitage in S.A.) that was first bred there in 1925. While there are a &lt;br /&gt;few acres of this grape planted in New Zealand, USA, Canada, Brazil, &lt;br /&gt;Israel, Zimbabwe and most recently, Germany, it remains a totally South &lt;br /&gt;African varietal. Deep and earthy wines come from this grape and its &lt;br /&gt;blends with Cabernet and Merlot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Banana splits to follow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A portion of the proceeds will be donated to Monkeybiz South Africa &lt;a href="http://www.monkeybiz.co.za/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.monkeybiz....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costs:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The&lt;br /&gt;ropes course will be no more than $45. There will be a discount, &lt;br /&gt;depending on the number of people who sign-up, and we'll pay the &lt;br /&gt;discounted rate the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dinner and wine tasting will be $25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please send a check payable to &amp;quot;BHSC&amp;quot; for this amount to reserve your spot to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brettle-Hupfers Ski Club&lt;br /&gt;c/o John Raeder&lt;br /&gt;31 Linden Rd&lt;br /&gt;West Roxbury, MA 02132&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who are not full members will also need to pay the $15/night lodging fees on arrival at the lodge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sara Hickson</member_name><member_id>7424991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285600438000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282054846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come Monkey Around with us!</name><id>14449002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/14449002/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/4/global_17268516.jpeg</photo_url></item>