<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Kyureo in Wayland Square is going out of business!  &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/660856251752819977145734/img/smileys/crying.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Final Chocolate Martini Party &amp;amp; Sale - Thursday, April 26th, 5:30-8:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of you know I never do this, but I wanted to share this one with you before its gone:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides having great and VERY eclectic home decor items, Jay, the owner is a really great guy and wonderful interior designer. Browsing through his shop, talking to him and being introduced to vintage Hollywood designer Tony Duquette was a huge inspiration for me. Sadly he is leaving Little Rhody for bigger things in Miami. If you've never been to this little gem next to UPS Store in Wayland Square (kind of across from L'Artisan and next to Angell Nails), here's your chance to check it out before the doors close forever. There really is something for everyone and it is truly a store which is a visual pleasure to browse. Jay is bringing out some of his personal collection for sale and the discounts are deep, so bring your wallets! He has some of the most unusual things in PVD!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As is his style, all this will be coupled with complimentary chocolate martinis and light bites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a link to his website: &lt;a href="http://www.kyureo.com/kyureo_index.html"&gt;http://www.kyureo.com/kyureo_index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I won't be able to make it, but hope that some of you will!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is posted as an FYI - if you want to go, please RSVP so other members know who to look for!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335480076000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334878848000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Final Chocolate Martini Party &amp; Sale at Kyureo in Wayland Square!</name><id>61323912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335475800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/61323912/</event_url></item>