<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2056 Mohawk Trail</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01370</zip><lat>42.622330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crab Apple White Water</name><city>Charlemont</city><id>1592007</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.788666</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/2/3/event_25653571.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Ok those of you who want to go &lt;strong&gt;RAFTING&lt;/strong&gt;, Crab Apple White Water is offering a "friends of rafting guides" special for Memorial weekend.&amp;nbsp; It will be the Monroe Bridge section of the Deerfield with a full day of rafting and then food afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The usual price for this trip is $95.&amp;nbsp; If come on Saturday, May 28, the price is $60 per person.&amp;nbsp; Are you kidding me?&amp;nbsp; This is an amazing price for a super duper event.&amp;nbsp; I know its Memorial Day weekend but how much lawn jarts and hot dogs can you do?&amp;nbsp; Aunt Edith would scream with joy to be out on the river.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must register and buy your ticket before going.&amp;nbsp; Here are the steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.&amp;nbsp; Call Crab Apple White Water 1-800-553-7238.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.&amp;nbsp; Tell them you want on the Mass. Monroe Bridge trip for May 28 with the friends of a guide special.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.&amp;nbsp; You want to be on Janice May's boat and your guide friend is Timo (photo above).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.&amp;nbsp; Pay them the $60 for the trip via credit card and you will get a confirmation email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are good to go.&amp;nbsp; We can discuss carpool needs when we see who decides to tackle this cool adventure.&amp;nbsp; I have attached the page from Crab Apple that gives you info for times and what you need to bring and what will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Don't miss the boat on this one!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (Kelli's quote, not mine).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crabapplewhitewater.com/massachusetts/deerfield-monroe_bridge.shtml"&gt;http://www.crabapplewhitewater.com/massachusetts/deerfield-monroe_bridge.shtml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307024795000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305807869000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPECIAL WHITE WATER RAFTING EVENT AND PRICING, Crab Apple in MA</name><id>18954401</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306589400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/18954401/</event_url></item>