<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am running a 2-4 session kind of &amp;quot;Indiana Jones'y&amp;quot; scenario.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Stoneham, my place although other places are possible if more central location is needed.&lt;br /&gt;When: Weekends. We start on October 4, Saturday, noon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who should come: People for whom role-playing is &amp;quot;role&amp;quot; playing. This is a game for people who can roleplay anything that DM throws at them. Anyone who can play good and evil as well as Anthony Hopkins, Glenn Close, Johnny Depp and Helena Bonham Carter. ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. DM or organizer's name and preferred contact info: I will DM. &lt;br /&gt;2. City/Location of the most common place you will be playing: Stoneham.&lt;br /&gt;3. Campaign world for the game: Our world 1930s with some changes. This is a fictional scenario and character actions do not in any way represent or reflect on any real people living or dead. :) Couple of Europeans are starting an expedition into Mayan ruins. Oh well... :) &lt;br /&gt;4. What you really need to know and think about: It is darker than typical Indiana Jones adventure. There are people who are evil in this world. Individual character goals may not be the same as party goals.&lt;br /&gt;5. System: GURPS will be used, but the game is mostly not dependent on Gurps, although some player knowledge about the system is preferred. We will be &amp;quot;rule-lite&amp;quot; so if you don't know GURPS, don't worry. There is a free GURPS lite PDF available, maybe we will use mostly it. :) Game will be ROLE PLAY biased. You can always discuss with DM what ability X does and DMs word is final rule independent of the book's version. Don't expect leveling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this module the style is:&lt;br /&gt;Roleplaying: 9&lt;br /&gt;Action: 4&lt;br /&gt;Story: 7&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a preset module for 5 players. &lt;br /&gt;Players cannot select character race, background, etc, since characters are preplanned with existing backgrounds. Some things are open for personalization based on GMs discretion. The game has both social interactions and combat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the short list of the characters. Every character will receive a much longer background story for your role playing. When signing up, please select the character you want to play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expedition organizers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Serge Bordot&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;i&gt;Chuck&lt;/i&gt; - European archeologist. In his thirties. Looks like a French archeologist. If you know how French archeologists look like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maxina Pruet&lt;/b&gt; - Rich lady financing the expedition. Similar age to Serge. Looks tougher than your typical English ladies spending money on exotic expeditions. Not that she looks English or lady in any way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local adventurers, who act as guides and bodyguards for Europeans. Common knowledge: reputation of all of the adventurers is mostly OK, none are outside the law as law can be understood in largely wild country. They all are mercenaries and whole Yucatan knows them. They are legendary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pancho&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;i&gt;Justin&lt;/i&gt; - one of the biggest scoundrels in Mexico, brawls and bloodshed seems to follow him. His skin looks darker than a native mayan, but claims to have been raised by Mayans. Always carries with him a strange obsidian mayan sword. And overall he behaves like mayan. Served in couple armies, so knows how to command. Cold blooded cynic, but nobody can call him a traitor. Maybe the ones who could are already dead...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ivan Hairy&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;i&gt;Douglas&lt;/i&gt;- Mike Tyson of Yucatan. Hairy Russian, the champion of all Yucatan boxing rings. Anyone who takes him as bodyguard can be totally sure that they'll be safe. Closed guy, everybody knows him, but no one really knows who he is.  To drink with him is a huge honor though no one has done it twice. His appetite is bigger than his strength, people say that he has eaten two pigs in one sitting and asked for more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mapuche&lt;/b&gt; -  Integrity is another name for Mapuche. He has great reputation and iron character. He helps everyone who needs it most. The government does not like him, since he is well known for hatred of oppression and love of freedom. Is he really from South America, like all mapuche? Who knows...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raimondas</member_name><member_id>3008243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225678174000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221445519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Golden coffin" - Indiana Jones'y GURPS 2-4 session game</name><id>8758665</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223136000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/8758665/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/f/global_3081279.jpeg</photo_url></item>