<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bostwick Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06605</zip><lat>41.158321</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-335-1433</phone><name>Captain's Cove Seaport</name><city>Bridgeport</city><id>709960</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.212502</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey guys and gals! Come join us at Captain's Cove, our tiny slice of summertime heaven, as we dance the afternoon away to the awesome sounds of &amp;quot;SHORT BUS&amp;quot;! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's right, SHORT BUS! This band is amazing! VOTED THREE TIME WINNER &amp;quot;BEST COVER BAND&amp;quot; BY THE READERS OF FAIRFIELD WEEKLY MAGAZINE AND BY GREENWICH, DARIEN, NEW CANAAN &amp;amp; WESTPORT MAGAZINES! THE FIRST BAND THAT HAS EVER WON BOTH AWARDS!!! I guarantee they will get you off you off your seat and on the deck! The boardwalk will feel like a trampoline with all the energy they generate &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The SHORT BUS is Chris Goane, Mark Zelenz, Ernie Albert, Kenny Muller, and some guy named Chuck! - Their goal is to get you up and dancing to Maximum Rock &amp;amp; Roll! That's why they're Fairfield County's most rippin' rock dance band! Click on the links to see photos, listen to their demos and watch their videos, THEY WILL MAKE YOU HAPPY! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a peek at the SHORT BUS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE GET THERE EARLY TO HELP US HOLD DOWN THE PICNIC TABLES (you can also bring a lawn chair)! THIS IS A POPULAR BAND SO THE JOINT WILL BE JUMPING! ALSO IF YOU GET THERE EARLY IT'S A GREAT WAY TO MEET &amp;amp; MINGLE WITH EVERYONE BEFORE THE MUSIC STARTS BECAUSE ONCE THAT HAPPENS, MOST OF US WILL BE ON THE DECK, DANCING!!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a look at CAPTAIN'S COVE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Multi-Group Meetup with 4 other single groups so get ready to mix and mingle with other singles! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a small fee of $1 for this event which we will collect using an honor system at the event. We love your company so please come and have a great time with us!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Margaret</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250895989000</updated><rating><average>4.30999994278</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243446094000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come Party with ShortBus @ Captian's Cove</name><id>10505119</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250445600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/10505119/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/0/global_8204688.jpeg</photo_url></item>