<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The first nationally televised Republican presidential debate in the 2012 election cycle will be held on May 5, 2011 on Fox News. Because of this, it is imperative to showcase Ron Paul as the leading frontrunner in the race. On May 5, 2011, we will hold an online money bomb in support of Ron Paul for President 2012. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For those of you who haven't participated in a "moneybomb" before, it is a 24-hour online fundraising event, pioneered by Dr. Paul's grassroots support in 2007, aimed at dramatically increasing funds for a specific candidate.&amp;nbsp; In November 2007, we raised $4.2 million for Dr. Paul in a single day; In December 2007, we raised in excess of $6 million in a single day, from thousands upon thousands of small donations - setting a record that has yet to be matched. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can see some great new videos, as well as pledge to make a donation at &lt;a href="http://debateday.com/"&gt;http://debateday.com/&lt;/a&gt; .&amp;nbsp; Donations themselves, no matter how small, are ONLY to be made at &lt;a href="http://ronpaul2012.com/"&gt;http://ronpaul2012.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It's time again for us to make a statement.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://debateday.com/ and http://ronpaul2012.com/</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304572639000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Now that Ron Paul has announced the formation of his 2012 Presidential exploratory committee, we need to make a statement to show that our ideals are embodied in Dr. Paul!</why><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303996668000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Paul Moneybomb, May 5th!</name><id>17465777</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304568000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/17465777/</event_url></item>