<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>THIS IS AN ALL DAY EVENT! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PICNICING - BEACH - CONCERT AND MORE....... &lt;br /&gt;I am inviting several meetup groups. Hoping  for a good turnout! &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;UPDATE 6/7: MEETUP IN FRONT OF THE INDIAN RANCH OFFICE BEFORE&lt;br /&gt; ENTERING THE GATE TO THE VENUE AT 10:30 AM. Being ealry ensures us a good &lt;br /&gt;spot. I will get there as early as possible. I will have the MEETUP sign with me &lt;br /&gt;at the gate. I will also use it to mark our table(s) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* For anyone who wants to? There are several picnic tables and grills&lt;br /&gt;   for  another one of our famous pot lucks. So, if you wish to participate,&lt;br /&gt;   please bring a food item to share and your own water/beverage. I will&lt;br /&gt;   supply the paper, plastic utensils, trsh bags... etc This will be a FUn&lt;br /&gt;   time. ***** Charcoal anyone??????? &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* WHAT IS NOT ALLOWED:  glass containers and alcohol. &lt;br /&gt;                                          (check the website for more info)&lt;br /&gt;* There is a tour boat (20 -25 min) available if anyone&lt;br /&gt;   decides to take a tour of the lake area. There is an extra&lt;br /&gt;   charge for this. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* The beach is open for the season. Anyone for some beach &lt;br /&gt;  games?  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;    &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKETS: $15.00 (advance)&lt;br /&gt;             $20.00 ( 2 wks prior to show) &lt;br /&gt;         ***If not sold out tickets are sold until right before the show&lt;br /&gt;TO PURCHASE YOUR TICKET: www.indianranch.com (online)&lt;br /&gt;                                            508-943-3871 (by phone) &lt;br /&gt;                              &lt;br /&gt;About: Indian Ranch: &lt;/b&gt; more to folow &lt;br /&gt;Website: www.indianranch.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The band's webiste: &lt;a href="http://www.changesinlatitudes.biz/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.changesinl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About : Changes In Latitudes&amp;quot; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aloha!!!  We're glad you stopped by.  &lt;br /&gt;In case you haven't seen us yet, Changes In Latitudes is one of America's premier tribute shows to singer-songwriter Jimmy Buffett, the master of the tropical lifestyle. We are a nine-piece band with a singular plan, to take you to Margaritaville. Our show is good clean fun; we aim to offend no one, and entertain everyone. Every set is a party, with beach balls flying, dancing conga lines, and leis galore. It's one exciting show. Oh yes, and the music. You know more Jimmy Buffett songs than you think you do, and we'll prove it. Let us bring our rolling beach party to you.For the true Parrot Heads out there, we are an authentic tribute show.  We've captured the look, feel, and sound of a real Buffett concert.  We are to Buffett what &amp;quot;Beatlemania&amp;quot; is to the Beatles.  The only thing we don't provide is the tailgate party before the show. (Of course, you can always have your own).&lt;br /&gt;So, if you're ready for a &amp;quot;Latitude Adjustment&amp;quot;, break out your grass skirts and Hawaiian shirts, kick off your shoes, and join the beach party.&lt;br /&gt;It's all about da beach, mon!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the Indian Ranch Office - before the gate into the venue@ 10:30 am</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245195902000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236106126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHANGES IN LATITUDES: Jimmy Buffet Beach Bash </name><id>9871050</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244993400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/9871050/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/0/global_7745776.jpeg</photo_url></item>