<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>286 Franklin St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.326660</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-945-2212</phone><name>Cafe Andala</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669158</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122250</lon></venue><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>+ $9 food minimum</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Need a break from the stress of work, the economy, and everyday life? Looking for something to do that is fun, cheap, and progressive? Join us for &lt;strong&gt;Games for Justice at Andala Cafe&lt;/strong&gt;! Arrive by yourself or bring a friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scrabble, Boggle, Apples to Apples, Scattegories - what's your favorite board game? Bring it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look no further if you're seeking like-minded folks to game with, want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while you Boggle, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. If you want to build a strong cross-issue social justice movement, SoJust is for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Haven't been to Andala Cafe? The food is delicious! Check out &lt;a href="http://www.andalacafe.com/menu.php"&gt;their menu&lt;/a&gt; filled with vegetarian and vegan options. &lt;strong&gt;Each attendee is asked to purchase a minimum of $9 in yummy food - or SoJust will have to pay the difference to the venue.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andala Cafe is located in Central Square - here's a &lt;a href="http://www.andalacafe.com/map.php"&gt;map&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us if you want to &lt;em&gt;cross-promote your events and campaigns&lt;/em&gt; while enjoying great cocktails, are &lt;em&gt;new to the area&lt;/em&gt; and looking for groups to get involved in, or you've been looking for &lt;em&gt;like-minded progressive&lt;/em&gt; to hang with in Boston. &lt;strong&gt;Newcomers always welcomed!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 SoJust is all about building a cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston based on the philosophy of abundance. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SoJust isn't a non-profit 501(c)(3).&lt;/strong&gt; We're a grassroots, volunteer-run, member-supported, cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have 2000 members, hosted 115+ events and manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network, please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/dues/" target="_blank"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335891705000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331695249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Games for Justice</name><id>56278592</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335391200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/56278592/</event_url></item>