<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>108 Newbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 927-0400</phone><name>Tealuxe</name><city>Boston</city><id>669022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Bookcrossers!  This month, for our Saturday meetup we will do something different.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Saturday, the 24th of October, is the day of the first Boston Book Festival. This is a free event featuring authors, presenters, book signings, outdoor exhibits, a street fair with music -- lots of great book-oriented activities.  Check out the website and see what's going on: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbookfest.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonbookfest.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonbook...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;   It looks like great fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Boston Bookcrossers for tea or an early lunch at Tealuxe on Newbury Street at 11:30 a.m. for our usual book-themed chatting and book sharing.  Look for the group with books on the table and a sign with the bookcrossing logo.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, join us as we attend this Boston Book Festival event: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Future of Reading: Books without Pages?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonbookfest.org/index.php/bookfest/schedule_detail/schedule_the_future_of_reading_books_without_pages/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonbookfest.org/index.php/bookfest/schedule_detail/schedule_the_future_of_reading_books_without_pages/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonbook...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation will showcase the ways in which digitization of books may change everything about the way we read in the future.  I thought this presentation would be of particular interest to bookcrossers, because bookcrossing depends on, and celebrates, books as physical objects with individual histories, while at the same time using technology to enhance reading.  What do we stand to gain, and what do we stand to lose, if books are stripped of their physical presence in the world and become disembodied content?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to join us at Tealuxe so we know how big a table to get.  If you would like to meet us for the presentation only, please include this in your RSVP comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the group with books on the table and a sign with the bookcrossing logo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liz</member_name><member_id>220016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256571360000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>BookCrossers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookcrossing-195</urlname><id>23495</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Bookcrossing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255889867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tea and Technology</name><id>11654445</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256398200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookcrossing-195/events/11654445/</event_url></item>