<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 94B Middlebridge Road </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02882</zip><lat>41.457645</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>narrow river kayak</name><city>Narragansett</city><id>2597501</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449608</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;UPDATE - it looks like the the outfitter has been busier this year so I have reserved some boats ahead of time. &amp;nbsp;If you can commit to coming please let me know what boat you want. &amp;nbsp;Choices are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. single kayak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. tandem kayak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Tandem open canoe (can hold 2 or 3 plus lots of cooler space)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. paddle board (single. &amp;nbsp;can be diffcult to go straight but a great core workout)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. flexible - can take any option&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;please update your comment or add a note.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_____________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever asked yourself - "How does Tom do the beach?".&amp;nbsp; Well come on this trip and find out the best way to experience a great beach day. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start at Narrow River Kayaks &lt;a href="http://www.narrowriverkayaks.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.narrowriverkayaks.com/&lt;/a&gt; where we can rent kayaks, canoes and paddles boards.&amp;nbsp; Then we start the 1 mile journey down the Narrow River to Naraganesett Beach.&amp;nbsp; The Narrow River is famous for warm shallow water, salt marsh and&amp;nbsp; a variety of nesting birds.&amp;nbsp; On the beach we will set up&amp;nbsp; on the back side of a sand bar near the mouth of the Narrow River and enjoy the day.&amp;nbsp; The river side has warmer, more calm water, which is perfect for practicing kayak techniques and goofing around. The ocean side provides an opportunity to play in the surf with surf boards or even white water kayaks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If all the the paddling is too much for you just chill on the beach, you have several hours to relax before the return journey.&amp;nbsp; We will return to the outfitter around 3pm but may stay a bit later if the weather is good.&amp;nbsp; Narrow River Kayak has outdoor showers and hoses to wash gear and bodies. We may hit a local restaurant for a seafood dinner on the way back north but that is purely optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a cooler with drinks and lunch. also any beach/water games you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have your own boat?&amp;nbsp; Just meet us at the outfitter an park your car in their lot.&amp;nbsp; I have done this trip several times and they have always let me park for free as long as others in the group are renting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To Lazy to paddle?&amp;nbsp; You can meet us on the beach, look for us where the river meets the ocean at the far end of the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost? free with your own boat or about $55 rental for a whole day kayak (save $15 if you bring back within 4 hours). If you want to save $ you can put 3 or 4 people in an open canoe. I will probably get a paddleboard so feel free to try it out if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the weather is raining or windy we will cancel. &amp;nbsp; I will try to reserve a bunch of boats but if we do not have enough we can head straight straight to the beach. &amp;nbsp;I have advanced ordered several different boats, we can swap boats during the day so you all get some variety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's try to carpool! If you can drive please list the town you are coming from.&amp;nbsp; Need a ride? just ask - Wedelns are always happy to help out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a dark blue Mazda</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314067843000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310763949000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak to Narraganset Beach</name><id>25886741</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313935200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/25886741/</event_url></item>