<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #241a13"&gt;Another last minute event, but I hope you can join us if you missed the last meetup for this film like I did. (Here's hoping Gary Oldman gets his long-deserved first Oscar nomination!)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #241a13"&gt;About the film:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Spy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;is the long-awaited feature film version of John le Carr&amp;eacute;'s classic bestselling thriller. The time is 1973. The Cold War of the mid-20th century continues to threaten international relations. Britain's Secret Intelligence Service (SIS), code-named the Circus, is striving to keep pace with other countries' espionage efforts and to keep the U.K. secure. The head of the Circus, known as Control (John Hurt), personally sends dedicated operative Jim Prideaux (Mark Strong) into Hungary. But Jim's mission goes bloodily awry, and Control is forced out of the Circus&amp;mdash;as is his top lieutenant, George Smiley (Gary Oldman), a career spy with razor-sharp senses. Estranged from his absent wife, Smiley is soon called in to see Undersecretary Oliver Lacon (Simon McBurney), who tells him that he is to be rehired in secret. There is a gnawing fear that the Circus has long been compromised by a double agent working for the Soviets, jeopardizing England. Supported by younger agent Peter Guillam (Benedict Cumberbatch), Smiley pores over Circus activities past and present, trying to find the mole. Also starring Colin Firth, Tom Hardy, Toby Jones, Kathy Burke and Ciar&amp;aacute;n Hinds. Directed by Tomas Alfredson &lt;em&gt;(Let the Right One In)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We'll go to an area restaurant afterwards for a discussion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Lisa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be inside the theater near the front holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327105167000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326310546000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy (2nd meetup)</name><id>47694412</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326574800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/47694412/</event_url></item>