<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Safety is No Accident&lt;/b&gt; and ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure. With that in mind, the &lt;b&gt;GBSC, Twist &amp;amp; Go Scooter Club and Twisted Touring Scooter Club&lt;/b&gt; in conjunction with our sponsor, &lt;b&gt;Danny's Scooter Shop&lt;/b&gt; have decided to host a &lt;b&gt;Pre-season Safety Check Event and Ride&lt;/b&gt; to help insure a safe &lt;b&gt;2009 Riding Season&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;When:&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Saturday May 3, 12 Noon at Danny's Scooter Shop in Avon, MA  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Meeting Locations:&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Main Group will leave from South Bay Shopping Plaza, Mass Ave. Dorchester,MA. 11:00 am  &lt;br /&gt;Rendezvous:  &lt;br /&gt;Star Market, Beacon St. Somerville, MA 10:00 am  &lt;br /&gt;MIT near the Fire Station on Mass. Ave. in Cambridge, MA 10:00 am  &lt;br /&gt;Everyone will meet at South Bay and we will ride together to Danny's approx. 13 miles south on RT 28.  &lt;br /&gt;This event will be mostly focused on &lt;b&gt;Safety&lt;/b&gt; issues, and any &lt;b&gt;Equipment Tune-ups&lt;/b&gt; you may need, it is a good way to start the season off by knowing, learning and refreshing ourselves with the do's and don'ts of the road as well as keeping your scooter and gear in good shape.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Remember this is your club, if there is anything you want to add, or suggest your comments and input is not only welcome an encouraged, but necessary for our continued success.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a link to the MSF site so you can download a free PDF of the Scooter Saftey Handbook:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://msf-usa.org/downloads/Scooter_tips-screen.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://msf-usa.org/do...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for smiling happy people riding scooters</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241876142000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236944558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Safety is No accident</name><id>9945865</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241366400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/9945865/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/f/global_7670831.jpeg</photo_url></item>