<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-1667</phone><name>Harvest Co-Op Market/Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>428348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yay!  We can do three weeks!  Tonight we'll be reading Survival of the Sickest by Dr. Sharon Moalem, Jonathan Prince.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comments from: &lt;a href="http://www.harpercollins.com/books/9780060889654/Survival_of_the_Sickest/index.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harpercoll...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Was diabetes evolution's response to the last Ice Age? Did a deadly genetic disease help our ancestors survive the bubonic plagues of Europe? Will a visit to the tanning salon help lower your cholesterol? Why do we age? Why are some people immune to HIV? Can your genes be turned on -- or off?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;J&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;oining the ranks of modern myth busters, Dr. Sharon Moalem turns our current understanding of illness on its head and challenges us to fundamentally change the way we think about our bodies, our health, and our relationship to just about every other living thing on earth, from plants and animals to insects and bacteria.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Through a fresh and engaging examination of our evolutionary history, Dr. Moalem reveals how many of the conditions that are diseases today actually gave our ancestors a leg up in the survival sweepstakes. When the option is a long life with a disease or a short one without it, evolution opts for disease almost every time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everything from the climate our ancestors lived in to the crops they planted and ate to their beverage of choice can be seen in our genetic inheritance. But Survival of the Sickest doesn't stop there. It goes on to demonstrate just how little modern medicine really understands about human health, and offers a new way of thinking that can help all of us live longer, healthier lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Survival of the Sickest is filled with fascinating insights and cutting-edge research, presented in a way that is both accessible and utterly absorbing. This is a book about the interconnectedness of all life on earth -- and, especially, what that means for us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, by popular request, we'll tack on Horton Hears a Who, so we can hit the theaters the following Monday (it comes out March 14th....let's hope it sticks around that long!!  If not, adjustments will be made:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to the Clear Conscience Cafe for their tasty sandwiches and comfy couches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Lisa with any questions!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll try to snag the couches</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207177642000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205200126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Meetup:  Survival of the Sickest/Horton Hears a Who</name><id>7507297</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207004400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/7507297/</event_url></item>