<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I’m posting this on behalf of the Boston Vegetarian Society&lt;br /&gt;Please try to RSVP by Monday the 29th. &lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you'd like to car pool and I’ll coordinate. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's PICNIC TIME!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us on the 4th of July!  There will be lots of good people to meet, great vegan food to eat, beautiful views, and activities from lounging in the back yard, to kayaking, to beach walks, and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY, JULY 4, 2009, starting at 1 PM&lt;br /&gt;(arrive whenever you can)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN DATE is Sunday, July 5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A generous member is opening her home and yard to us, located just 500 feet from the beach at charming Broad Cove on Onset Bay.  We'll also be an easy stroll (6/10 mile) from beautiful Onset Harbor, and Onset Village Center.  Here we have the flavor and charm of Cape Cod, but are NORTH of the Cape Cod canal, so there is no bridge to cross and travel is easier.  Oncet is a village of East Wareham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.onsetvillage.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.onsetvilla...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD:  &lt;br /&gt;Bring a generous potluck dish to share that is vegan (no meat, fowl, fish, dairy, eggs, or honey).  This event is a chance to display how amazing pure plant cuisine is.  Attaching a card with ingredients or your recipe is appreciated.  We'll have a vegan grill, so if you can't prepare a dish, you could bring vegan burgers or not-dogs and buns.  (Please check ingredients labels.)  No alcoholic beverages, please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comments from attendees:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The food at the July 4 picnic is stupendous and I personally would love to have recipes for many dishes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We went to your event last year and have a suggestion: can you ask everyone to bring the recipe for what they made?  There was some incredible stuff there I wish I knew how to make.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEATING: &lt;br /&gt;If you have a lawn chair, bring that, too!  (We'll have some, but will need more.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THINGS TO DO:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Share a delicious vegan picnic meal and meet others in BVS!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Stroll to nearby Cove beach just 500 ft. away. (Bring a beach towel or chair). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Swim at the Cove and three kayaks are available **at your own risk**.  There are no lifeguards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Take a beach walk.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Walk 6/10 mile into charming Onset Village and view the beautiful Harbor with its little verdant island.  There will be a free concert at the Band shell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Watch a video indoors at the house. Chose from a wide selection of veg-themed educational videos.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* Play horse shoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have a group game that you could bring?    Let us know! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL ARE WELCOME - kid friendly event!  Your friends are welcome, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DONATION:  &lt;br /&gt;FREE to BVS current members.&lt;br /&gt;$2 for non-members - kids are free. (Please bring exact change.)      &lt;br /&gt;           &lt;br /&gt;Join now and save!  Details at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonveg.org/membership/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonveg.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS to picnic:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;49 Main Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Onset, MA (north of the canal - no bridge to cross)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oncet is a village of East Wareham.  Use 49 Main Avenue, East Wareham, MA for Internet directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Boston area, take Rt. 93 South.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At fork, go to RIGHT, continuing on Rt. 93S/128.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 4 onto Rt. 24 South (a left side exit)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Rt. 24 South to Rt. 495 South (Exit 14A) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Rt. 495 East to end, when it becomes Rt. 25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rt. 25, and take Exit 2 (Rt. 6 &amp;amp; 28, Onset/Wareham).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear right at exit, and go to the sixth traffic light. (Benny's is on the&lt;br /&gt;left side just before the intersection.) Turn right onto Main Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go 3/10 mile, and #49 Main Ave. is on your right, at the red fire&lt;br /&gt;hydrant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:  &lt;br /&gt;Free street parking on both sides of Main Ave.    If you plan to stay for the fireworks, park on the opposite side of the street from the house so you can get out easily when there is traffic after the fireworks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the BVS Picnic by the Sea!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247331562000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245904082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Vegetarian Society - 4th of July Picnic by the Sea</name><id>10731668</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246726800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/10731668/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>