<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>155 Seaport Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.349870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-832-1000</phone><name>Foley Hoag</name><city>Boston</city><id>1727931</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043043</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello BIMM'rs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have to make a &lt;strong&gt;time change&lt;/strong&gt; to Wednesday's final Ebook event.&amp;nbsp; Our case study presenter cannot get to us for a 4 pm start, so we will push back to &lt;strong&gt;6 pm&lt;/strong&gt; which is closer to our normal evening start time.&amp;nbsp; We are also at our Foley Hoag location down at the Seaport so don't head over to Cambridge for this session!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the last minute update - we surveyed our sign-ups and most folks could do the 6 pm start - my apologies to anyone who has a conflict with the later schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been a great learning process on our part figuring out how to best communicate this info.&amp;nbsp; As this program has pulled together and we actually got a number of people to create their own eBooks, we now begin the testing phase to see if our Ebooks can drive email sign-ups and build a database you can use to market your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who participated in the meetups.&amp;nbsp; We'll have some special announcements as to the next steps of this program on Wednesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the third and final meetup in this series. We will review everyone's progress and share conclusions and successes. You do not need to have attended prior sessions to join us here, but you should sign up for &lt;a href="http://rapidebookpublishing.com"&gt;our free online companion program&lt;/a&gt; self paced; so you can get more out of the Meetup event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Keith</member_name><member_id>12427891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319290162000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309441875000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ebooks, Lead Generation and building Power Email Lists - part 3 the Conclusions</name><id>24087651</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316037600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/24087651/</event_url></item>