<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>111 Cummington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.349228</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 353-2000</phone><name>Boston University</name><city>Boston</city><id>280142</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The meeting will in a conference room on the basement level of 111 Cummington Street.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this meeting we will get presentations on System Requirements for CMS and Portal systems.  There will also be time for general discussion and news on CMS systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be two presentations at the May meeting:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a) Trade and Professional Association Requirements for CMS and Collaborative Intranets (CENSA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;b) University Requirements for CMS and Portal Systems (Boston University)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are doing requirements reviews first, because that is where all good CMS projects should start.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every other month we will have requirements reviews followed by evaluations and discussions of CMS products.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group is still gathering momentum.  Please come and discuss your goals with the group, what you want to see covered, and when you want to them covered (or want to cover them yourself!)  There are as many CMS applications as people implementing them.  There are also many technologies involved, and many ways to use them.  So please come to learn and have your voice heard.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come prepared with your questions and answers ....this meeting will be a lot of fun!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;N.B. THE DATE MOVED TO MAY 23rd AND PLACE MOVED TO BOSTON UNIVERSITY.  BECAUSE THE LOCATION IS SO CLOSE TO FENWAY PARK, PARKING IS IMPOSSIBLE ON THE NIGHTS OF BALL GAMES, SO WE MOVED IT ONE WEEK LATER BECAUSE OF THE RED SOX GAME ON MAY 16th.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>RichKin</member_name><member_id>3557763</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180809868000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People interested in CMS</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newengland-webcms</urlname><id>422397</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Web Content Management Systems Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176942118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Web Content Management Systems May Meetup</name><id>5685047</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179962100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newengland-webcms/events/5685047/</event_url></item>