<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Media Education Foundation's Community Room</address_2><address_1>60 Masonic St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01063</zip><lat>42.318775</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Woodstar Cafe building</name><city>Northampton</city><id>604654</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I don't typically advertise for fee events but this one seems to have specific, useful information and this duo typically charges a lot more for their presentations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 to 7:00 p.m. Networking&lt;br /&gt;7:00 to 9:00 p.m. Program&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $10 at the door. Open to the public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participants will learn:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) What audio and video podcasts are, including their history and the latest trends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) How to create your own podcasts and, most important, where and how to distribute them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) The benefits of video and audio in online marketing with demonstrations, including one way to integrate video into your Web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) About using video streaming as a marketing and training tool through a company (a client of ours) case study.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) About online social networks and how they can be used for your business (an introduction).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6) About the new fad of online virtual worlds and how marketing, entertainment, social networking, video streaming and audio streaming can all be integrated (an introduction).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7) About a new virtual world/social network that will be launched around the time of the presentation, through a case study of PlanetCazmo.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the presenters:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Hake has worked as a multimedia producer for over six years, producing interactive CDs, advanced Flash applications and DVDs for a variety of clients. After launching paul hake productions in 2004, he moved to a manager role and has since set up a new studio in downtown Greenfield, Massachusetts. He works with some of the most talented programmers, artists, sound engineers and animators in New England and his business has seen rapid growth during its first two years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat King began his career in the music industry promoting concerts for various musical projects, tour management, self performance, composition and audio and video recording. After a year abroad working as tour and orchestral manager with the Irish Chamber Orchestra, he met Paul Hake in Greenfield, MA and soon established a working relationship with Paul as Audio engineer and Producer for Paul Hake Productions. In September of 2007,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pat and Paul began the Pioneer Media Group to specialize in audio and video editing, CD/DVD duplication, podcasting and applying audio/video to the World Wide Web, sound effects, commercial jingles, Non-linear editing, Motion graphics and post effects. Pat King is a current resident of Greenfield, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212100599000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Paul Hake (Paul Hake Productions, LLC) &amp; Pat King (Pioneer Media Group) present/ explain some of the latest trends in online marketing/ communications. Incl. Case studies &amp; discussion.</why><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210333958000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WEB 2.Whatever </name><id>7905015</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211927400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/7905015/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_1616503.jpeg</photo_url></item>