<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Littleton Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.553112</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-486-3891</phone><name>Kimball Farm</name><city>Westford</city><id>669421</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.452760</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What more could you ask for??? :-)&lt;br /&gt;Let's go to Cruise Night at Kimball's  Farm in Westford! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like good weather and a great turn out for this event.&lt;br /&gt;The plan is to meet around 6:30. I am going to try to get there around 6:20 and will find a place to sit in the area where the band will be playing. It is held in a large grassy field so bring your own chair or blanket to sit on, you might want to bring a bug spray just in case. Let's try to all meet and chat between 6:30 and 7 to get to know each other a bit to help our new members get comfortable and then we can decide how we want to move around...or even if we do want to move around at all! ;-)&lt;br /&gt;Kimball's provides a grill area with food and I'm sure we will find the ice cream and music with no trouble at all. To find the group look for &amp;quot;THE MYLAR BALLOON&amp;quot; I'll have tied to my chair! :-)&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you then!&lt;br /&gt;Sandy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kimball's hosts Cruise Night, with as many as 350 cars ranging from Corvettes to Model A's. The now famous &amp;quot;Ultimate Cruise Night&amp;quot; offers the additional excitement of live local band entertainment, the delicious Kimball Farm BBQ grill, and the Legendary Ice Cream Buffet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On this evening the John Penny Band will be playing from 5-9 PM.&lt;br /&gt;Voted Best Country Band by MA Country Music Association in 1995, 1996, 1997 and  1998.&lt;br /&gt;The John Penny Band is a five piece country band with two guitars, bass, keyboards, and drums. All five members sing lead and backup vocals. Their repertoire consists of contemporary and traditional country music plus some pop standards and some oldies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on...dust off your cowboy hat, bring a beach chair, (maybe some bug spray) and let's just laugh and have some fun together! What better way is there to spend a Summer evening. Admission for the general public is $3.00 for adults. &lt;br /&gt;;0)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185852014000</updated><rating><average>4.63000011444</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184709645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BBQ, Ice Cream, Old Cars, Country Music and Great Company!!!</name><id>6037874</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185489000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/6037874/</event_url></item>