<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>877 Broadway </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02914</zip><lat>41.817280</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Positive New Beginnings</name><city>East Providence</city><id>4989542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369522</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come play the game of Life by understanding the Universal Law of Attraction, which states that whatever we think about we bring about. Nicole will start this new LOA group in the East Providence area at Positive New Beginnings Are you ready to embrace a new you, a new year, one filled with unssibilities? Do you want to tap into the non-physical spiritual world to access a powerful Source that will help you co-create with the Divine&amp;hellip; When we use the law of attraction to the fullest we become a Dliberate creator, we attract from an allowing perspective as opposed to forcing life to happen and living in a place that doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel good Life transformed into something we&amp;rsquo;ve dreamed of&amp;hellip;relationships manifest, career opportunities manifest, money manifests, friendships manifests, trips manifest, our dreams and our passions manifest, life becomes magical!!! Come see how life can get really good...bring your ideas on what you want to change or manifest this year!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>8953582</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332011993000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Magnificent Manifestors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors</urlname><id>1552727</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>South Shore Law of Attraction  Manifestors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329689059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connect and Discuss Law of Attraction in Action</name><id>dcpsmcyqfbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331938800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Magnificent-Manifestors/events/52961682/</event_url></item>