<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Queer Women of Color and Friends (QWOC+ Boston) is ONCE AGAIN collaborating with MadFemmePride to bring you....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OPTIONZ: a WOMEN's Pride party for the diversity-conscious queer; a celebration of the entire SPECTRUM of the rainbow. Come out and FLAUNT your style, pimp out your gender, DEFY your age, and be prepared to WORK IT on the dancefloor! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LIMITED NUMBER OF DISCOUNTED TICKETS AVAILABLE ONLINE! &lt;br /&gt;***NO SERVICE FEES! Going.com has teamed up as a sponsor so the price you see is the price you pay! Get your discounted ticket now cause I only made 100 available!***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you missed it last year, you don't want to miss it again this year! It's gonna be bigger and better! We've secured a larger, swankier space that can hold even more people - no lines! - and is closer to the T. Ah yes, we can hear the buzzzzz about these new optionz already! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all love and enjoy the madfemmepride/QWOC+ synergy, and just couldn't WAIT to bring you THE inclusive, diversity-conscious dance party during pride week. We had to tell you about it NOW - in March! Please join us in making sure that this event sustains its reputation as being one of the richest and most diverse social event during Boston pride and get your tickets NOW, ONLINE! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets will go fast so gets yours today! Avoid the lines and kickoff your pride season mfp/qwoc+ style!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday June 12th. Doors open at 10PM. &lt;br /&gt;$15 Cover b4 midnight at the door! Limited number of discounted tickets available &lt;a href="http://boston.going.com/optionz" target="_blank"&gt;ONLINE&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;*GET YOUR TICKETS NOW AND GET THERE EARLY to avoid the already-forming line. It's pride, people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Underbar &lt;br /&gt;275 Tremont Street &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02116 &lt;br /&gt;This is a 21+ Event &lt;br /&gt;T: Green to Boylston / Orange to New England Medical Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring DJ Sun One &lt;br /&gt;spinning hiphop, reggae, reggaeton, house and Top 40&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you ALL there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a downtown takeover, at the heart of the theater district. We'll be reppin' our groups in full effect. (NOT at Wonder Bar in Allston. NOT at Breezeway like last year.) Downtown!!! T: Green to Boylston / Orange to New England Medical Center.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>2859082</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>jo</member_name><member_id>3137718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213495556000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>The Boston Dyke March likes to support our friends from Queer Women of Color and Friends (QWOC+ Boston) and MadFemmePride.</why><group><who>Friends of the Boston Dyke March</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostondykemarch</urlname><id>997856</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Dyke March</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213065632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OPTIONZ: Boston Pride Party</name><id>8113267</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213322400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostondykemarch/events/8113267/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/9/3/global_4414499.jpeg</photo_url></item>