<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hike at the Andrew Kenneth Webster Preserve, an NCLT property. This hike is about 3 miles and at a moderate pace. This property was acquired several years ago and includes 30 acres. Enjoy scenic overlooks of Railroad Brook Valley and Valley Falls Park. See three of the largest vernal pools in Vernon. Bring lunch for optional post-hike stop at the Valley Falls Park pavilion. Meet at Valley Falls Park parking lot on Valley Falls Road in Vernon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leader: George Arthur (NCLT)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NCLT contact is Jerry Stage, Chairman of the Land Stewardship Committee  (860) 870-4255. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is brought by an alliance between the NCLT and Hartford Area Hiking (HAH).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: One of the last remaining privately owned parcels in the Valley Falls area was acquired from the Knapp family in 2003.  The acquisition was enabled by a combination of funding from the Connecticut Open Space Matching Grant program, a private grant from the Bafflin Foundation, and a generous gift from an anonymous supporter.  Fronting Valley Falls Road adjacent to the town-owned Valley Falls Park and state-owned Belding Wildlife Management area, its trails wander up steep slopes, crossing the Rails-to-Trails path, and onto the top of Echo Ridge where it intersects the Echo Ridge property.  The property is named for Andrew Kenneth Webster, whose family wished the &amp;quot;woodlot&amp;quot; of their childhood memories to remain undeveloped.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northern Connecticut Land Trust (NCLT)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/Lists/Properties/DispForm.aspx?ID=5" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org/Lists/Properties/DispForm.aspx?ID=5" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1142912900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NCLT “Discover Your Land Trust” Hike in Vernon  CT</name><id>4881216</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1144504800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4881216/</event_url></item>