<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/photos/10128472"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/photos/10128472"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/f/a/event_17192762.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;   By signing up for this biking event you and your guest if applicable. agree to the terms of the liability waiver below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duration: 2 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 22 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Difficulty: moderate. Mostly flat but you should have some riding experience.  &lt;xobject height="113" width="200"&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/photos/10128472"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/photos/10128472"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;This path has quite a bit to offer. Water Falls, Canals from days of old, wildlife, and it meanders by the Blackstone River. This time of Year, it is beautiful, everything is so green &amp;amp; vibrant. The path is relatively flat with just one incline. The total path ride is about 22 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; The Blackstone River Bikeway is the state's third-longest bike path, stretching 11.6 miles from Lincoln to Woonsocket. The path is envisioned to connect Providence to the Massachusetts border through a series of on-road and off-road segments. Other path segments to the north and south of the current bikeway are in various phases of design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Short notice I know, but I figured if I was going I would see if anyone wanted to join me. The weather may be iffy I'll check the latest forecast later. You might want to bring a rain jacket in addition to water and a snack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Riders really should be carrying a spare tube and a pump or a flat kit. You never know!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>former drive in is a parking lot for  the path John St. AKA RI rt 123</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370293225000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1370208547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Take a ride on the Blackstone River Bikeway</name><id>122561712</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370268000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/122561712/</event_url></item>