<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Part 1 –  of this&amp;quot;Chicago Style&amp;quot; Stepping Workshop with our guest instructors and founders of the Steady Steppers Larry Collins and Kammal Smith is for all levels of steppers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time:  10am – 12pm (Noon) with lunch included (from 12pm -1pm)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A &amp;quot;Chicago Style&amp;quot; Step dance instructional workshop power packed with lead techniques for the male and follow techniques for the female.  The focus will be on learnings' that progress from understanding the beat; to count; to technique; to timing.  The instruction will be in the 8-count, 3 beat methodology with an introduction to lane structure, lane management, right turns, left turns and reverse turns.  Couples will be introduced to arm/hand positioning, body positioning with a male focus on giving correct lead techniques and a female focus on techniques with the ability to ‘read the lead’.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is for All Levels&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free Parking. Cash Bar. &lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Please purchase all beverages (water &amp;amp; soda) from the bar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The purchase of the Part 1 Workshop includes Luncheon.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Pricing for this workshop is $30 p/p, (cash/check). Advanced Payment and RSVP is Required &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;PayPal payments should be sent to &amp;quot;  &lt;a href="http://www.paypal.com" target="_blank"&gt;steppersboston06@aol.com&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See Lady Tracey or Gentleman Scott to make your cash or check purchase to reserve your place in the workshops. Or purchase this workshop via PayPal using your credit card.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE STEADY STEPPERS:&lt;br /&gt;The  Steady Steppers™ were founded in 2003 by two inspiring and charismatic Steppers', Kammal Smith and Larry Collins of Detroit (MI).  They have attained a nationally known presence and prominence in Stepping communities throughout the nation through their interpersonal skills, Stepping skills and dance instructional skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Steady Steppers™ have a distinguished record for training and instructional methods and are broadly recognized for their outstanding leadership qualities.  They hold themselves and others to the highest standards of integrity and demonstrate respect for people at all levels of the dance.  They have mature and balanced judgement and always put the interest of their students and colleagues first.  In return, they have earned the respect of both local and national dance communities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gentleman Scott</member_name><member_id>4548946</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracey </member_name><member_id>5014779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295805417000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Original Steppers of Boston</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Steppers-of-Boston</urlname><id>1340809</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Original Steppers of Boston Inc. 2006</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268198837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Part 1 Steady Steppers -  Progressive Movements Workshop 10am-12pm w/ Lunch  </name><id>12836497</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278770400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Steppers-of-Boston/events/12836497/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/6/global_13569670.jpeg</photo_url></item>