<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>165 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.734776</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-244-3311</phone><name>Chowder Pot IV</name><city>Hartford</city><id>219703</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.659450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yeh i knowe you like the line above for this event....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OH IF YOU WANT TO GET A DATE go to the alternative dance with the Singlesevent group...&lt;br /&gt;they are looking for any new ladies..etc..guys too...Our group wont pester you with the high pitched self sales to get a date stuff, we just are inviting.nor do intend to beg for your number or freely give out our numbers looking like a despirate salavating dogs ...but seriously..the guys there just want a girlfriend..most of us are looking for a fun partner to do a lot of activities together..so the choice is yours.... this chowder pot event is a bit different but very simillar to the other one..We are a small group in a sea of outsiders there and tend to have fun withing our little group there, if someone else looks interestd there,, invite them in....this group is very open...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well those who have been here in the past with us know all abut wht this place is and how it is.. its a place that seems safe for us..never have had any problems or complaints...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you that have not bben here..Chowder Pot is a pretty good place to dance...and eat some food Buffet..&lt;br /&gt;we do that in the BALL ROOM..not the restaurant part.. enter at the Ball Room..&lt;br /&gt;i will get there earlier and grab a table..but otherse do the same thing...one person sitting at a large table is not good..a few of us can do a better job at reserving..unless someones BIRTHDAY is about then..then i call in to reserve a table... fess up now... tell me you are just turning 40.. ok ...chickem i see..well they give you some cheap champain.. to boot..., ok just drink it...&lt;br /&gt;Fess UP...no birthday spanking here... ahh but on the dance floor...emmm ...im not telling...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dinner is buffit type starts at 8 coffie and cookies stuff later..&lt;br /&gt;Dinner: usually bred, salid, zities in spag saus, chicken, and my favouritr..muscels cooked in butter garlick spicy stuff..(keeps away the ladies which want to bite me)..dont ask me what it is but it works....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut ConTacts, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;SPONSORING DANCE PARTIES FOR SINGLES &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;, Sept. 28     Chowder Pot, Hartford&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;its now 20 bucks to get in... no jeans..too bad..jeans on Ladies look fine to me..maybe thaey dont want them to bust on the dance floor while all that HOT activity is going on...might need the fire hoses.........&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok getting there:&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the U.S.S. CHOWDER POT IV&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;165 Brainard Rd., Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From New Haven:  I-91 N to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd.). 1st right off exit. Immediate right into Chowder Pot parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Springfield &amp;amp; Points North:  I-91 S to Exit 27(Brainard Rd.). Left off exit onto Airport Rd. Go to end of road &amp;amp; turn right at light onto Brainard Rd. Go through one traffic light. Chowder Pot is on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Danbury &amp;amp; Points West:  I-84 E to I-91 S to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd.). Turn left off exit onto Airport Rd. Go to end of road &amp;amp; turn right at light onto Brainard Rd. Go through one traffic light. Chowder Pot is on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Manchester:  I-84 W to Charter Oak Bridge Exit. Go over bridge and take 2nd exit (Exit 87, Brainard Rd.). Go right off exit. Chowder Pot is on right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i dont like maybees for events that i have to save table space for.. AWAY FROM THE SPEAKERS for conversation and for safety..(reason below LOL)&lt;br /&gt;either you go or not..if you are a maybe in reality..things depend i know..then say &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; ... in the NO area..then change later to yes..&lt;br /&gt;but one day or so before, if i make the reservations..and there is not enough chairs for you because you dilly dallied..you will get to sit where the despirate geek  guys hang out...(their stomaches, toungs and xx hang out) and see them with their hands buried in their pockes so deep their elbows are only visible..&lt;br /&gt;believe me ya dont want to sit there to see that part of the show..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191197232000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188667969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>High Octaine, Pumping, Thumping, Grinding Dirty Dancing Event</name><id>6280800</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191024000000</time><rsvp_limit>200</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6280800/</event_url></item>