<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>384 Harvard St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.344681</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-277-9155</phone><name>Congregation Kehillath Israel</name><city>Brookline </city><id>848711</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.125746</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Jewish? Single? 45-65? Please join us for another great event hosted by Ken Bresler! Enjoy beautiful music, a lovely venue, delectable deserts, champagne, &amp;amp; a friendly and gender-balanced group of congenial singles. THE BOSTON JEWISH MUSIC FESTIVAL has kindly set aside a section for singles at Basya Schechter&amp;#146;s concert, &amp;#147;Songs of Wonder.&amp;#148; Following the concert, Congregation Kehillath Israel, the concert site, has reserved a beautiful space for a singles&amp;#146; dessert and champagne reception. As &lt;b&gt;THIS WILL BE A GENDER-BALANCED EVENING&lt;/b&gt;, preregistration AT THE WEBSITE BELOW is absolutely required. IMPORTANT: REGISTRATION here at meetup DOES NOT HOLD YOUR SPOT. For full details and to register, please go to: www.bresler.us. When registering, please mention that ***ELANA SENT YOU**** :) Hope to see you there! &lt;i&gt;In setting the Yiddish poetry of the revered Jewish philosopher and civil rights activist, Rabbi Abraham Joshua Heschel, to music, Basya Schechter has created a rich new collection of Yiddish songs with a contemporary touch. This exciting project blends Basya&amp;#146;s lovely voice, Heschel&amp;#146;s powerful poetry, and some of the finest musicians in the NYC Downtown Jewish Scene. What better place to hear this music than in the synagogue where Heschel often spoke!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330910337000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327467680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concert &amp; Desert/Champagne Reception</name><id>49524142</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330822800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/49524142/</event_url></item>