<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The actual starting time is 3:50 pm.  As usual I'll be holding a sign in the front of the theater and we'll meet afterwards at an area restaurant for discussion.  No doubt there'll be much to discuss about this one.  Hope to see you next Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This highly anticipated biographical film about legendary singer and songwriter Bob Dylan follows six distinct characters, depicting different stages of Dylan's life, embodying a different aspect of his life story and music. Cate Blanchett, Richard Gere, Heath Ledger, Christian Bale, Ben Whishaw and Marcus Carl Franklin all take turns playing Dylan, and Julianne Moore and Charlotte Gainsbourg appear as two of the women in his life. Lyrical, poetic and highly stylized, it's the first biographical feature project to secure the approval of the music legend. Directed and co-written by Todd Haynes (Far From Heaven, Velvet Goldmine). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ty Burr, Boston Globe: &amp;quot;I'm Not There&amp;quot; is an epic rock un-biopic, a work of staggering cinematic craft that's part jigsaw puzzle and part meditation on the mysteries of art and stardom. -- 4 stars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Owen Gleiberman, Entertainment Weekly: What's finally so moving about I'm Not There is that it's a story of loss. Dylan, as the film portrays him, is a revolutionary who loses his innocence, his idealism, his wife and family, his connection to his audience, his sanity, even his dog. He finds no direction home. Yet the ultimate thing that's lost is what his music is ? and Dylan, in the sublime final moments, is right to say that we always knew it wasn't ''folk.'' It's something holy and unnameable and beautiful and pure. I'm Not There lets you hear it again, more majestically than ever.  Grade: A &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Roger Ebert, Chicago Sun Times:  &amp;quot;I'm Not There&amp;quot; is an attempt to consider the contradictions of Bob Dylan by building itself upon contradictions. Maybe that's the only way to do it. If you made a biopic with Dylan played by the same actor all the way through, it might become the portrait of a shape-shifting schizophrenic. Todd Haynes' approach is to create six or seven Dylans, depending on how you count, and use six actors to play them. This way, each Dylan is consistent on his own terms, and the life as a whole need not hold together.  3 1/2 stars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196728989000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195845629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>I'm Not There -- Saturday, 12/1/07, 3:50 pm</name><id>6792155</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196541900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6792155/</event_url></item>