<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We had such a fantastic time here last time, that we just HAVE to go back!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK, I hope this date is better for everyone because I'll go by myself if I have to.  Please join me for a fun and unique experience at &lt;a href="http://www.fire-ice.com/locations/cambridge.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fire and Ice&lt;/a&gt;, in Harvard Square. If you've never been there before, you're in for a fun surprise! FiRE + iCE offers diners an endless array of culinary possibilities waiting to be fired up to your taste on an over-sized round open grill. With a colorful and quirky atmosphere, FiRE + iCE entices guests to have a fun and exciting time while enjoying great food and drinks. In an age when diners have grown accustomed to asking for meals to be specially prepared to suit individual tastes, FiRE + iCE allows guests full control in the opportunity to personally select ingredients and sauces to create the perfect meal. Guests present their favorite selections to the chefs behind the grill and are invited to supervise as their food is prepared. It's such a blast to keep returning to the grill with different combinations to try.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is easy to get there by T. It is located just around the corner from the Harvard stop on the Red Line.   I do NOT recommend driving unless you know where to park or you can carpool. The lot across the street is very pricey..  I'll try to help arrange carpools for those who are interested and the restaurant will validate your ticket for a couple of bucks off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don't want to miss this one!  I guarantee you'll have a blast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;debbie&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael B</member_name><member_id>2958968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196121955000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>divorcesupport-249</urlname><id>368805</id><group_lat>42.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston/Burbs Life after Divorce Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194042501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Night for FiRE &amp; iCE</name><id>6665614</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195948800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/divorcesupport-249/events/6665614/</event_url></item>