<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>310 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357006</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 482-6439</phone><name>Old South Meeting House</name><city>Boston</city><id>669048</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 11px"&gt;A broad and  growing concern for animals has many people talking about animal rights.  At the same time, confusion about the meaning of the term is also  widespread. Whether you're curious to learn more about animal rights,  opposed to the idea, want to know how best to help animals, or even if  you already advocate for animals, you won't want to miss this upcoming  one-night-only lecture by animal rights pioneer Gary L. Francione.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Ov&lt;span&gt;er  the decades, Professor Francione has developed the abolitionist  approach to animal rights through his work, incluing several books,  ranging from Animals, Property, and the Law to Animals as Persons:  Essays on the Abolition of Animal Exploitation. The night of May 7th, he  will summarize his views and engage the audience in a substantial and  informative question and answer period. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Lecture is followed by  Q&amp;amp;A &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This program is presented free in collaboration with Old  South Meeting House as part of their *Partners in Public Dialogue*  series &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;About the speaker: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Gary L. Francione is  Distinguished Professor of Law and Nicholas deB. Katzenbach Scholar of  Law and Philosophy at Rutgers University School of Law-Newark. Professor  Francione has been teaching animal rights and the law for more than 20  years, and he was the first academic to teach animal rights theory in an  American law school. He has lectured on the topic throughout the United  States, Canada, and Europe. He has been a guest on numerous radio and  television shows. He is well known throughout the animal protection  movement for his criticism of animal welfare law and the regulation or  reform of animal use, as well as the property status of nonhuman  animals, and for his abolitionist theory of animal rights. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;About  the venue: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From the historic meeting of 5,000 colonists on  December 16, 1773 that led to the Boston Tea Party up to the present,  the Old South Meeting House has been an active gathering place for  discussion and celebration and a haven for free speech in the heart of  downtown Boston. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;How to get there: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;310 Washington Street &lt;br /&gt;Boston,  MA 02108 &lt;br /&gt;617-482-6439 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Old South Meeting House is  accessible to public transit, including the Red, Orange, and Blue subway  lines (and a short walk from Green line at Park Street) to the #92 and  #93 buslines. &amp;nbsp;Downtown street parking is rarely available, though there  are numerous paid lots. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you are *driving* to this event,  discounted parking is available (enter the garage after 4 pm) at the 33  Arch Street Garage (entrance on Hawley Street) and the garage at Post  Office Square (off of Milk Street). Use the zip code in your GPS system  or to use the address &amp;ldquo;1 Milk Street&amp;rdquo; because many GPS systems will take  you to the wrong Washington Street otherwise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maynard S. Clark</member_name><member_id>83043</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304952517000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300048099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Lecture by Gary L. Francione</name><id>16906731</id><headcount>85</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304805600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/16906731/</event_url></item>