<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 East Wheelock Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03755</zip><lat>43.703922</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hopkins Center for the Arts</name><city>Hanover</city><id>3537492</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.282280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A Dangerous Method Part of Telluride at Dartmouth (HOP is the Hopkins Center for the Arts on campus...just east of the Hanover Inn) In 1904, Sabina Spielrein (Keira Knightley), the daughter of wealthy Russian Jews, is diagnosed with acute hysteria. The young Swiss doctor Carl Jung (Michael Fassbender) begins treating her with psychoanalysis, the radical new &amp;#130;&amp;#148;talking&amp;#148; cure. His success connects him with the pioneering Dr. Sigmund Freud (Viggo Mortensen) until Jung&amp;#146;s growing passion for Sabina and his own poetic imagination clashes with his mentor. David Cronenberg (History of Violence) deepens his mastery of adult psychological drama in this new high point of his career. Cronenberg, Fassbender and Mortensen transform an intellectual power struggle into an almost hypnotic dance. And Knightley, the film&amp;#146;s astonishing heart, makes Sabina&amp;#146;s violent sexuality and incisive intelligence both extraordinary and believable. (UK, 2011, 98m) Courtesy Sony Classics After the flick we'll go to a local spot for coffee, dinner or drinks (Mollys, Dirt Cowboy cafe, etc.) to discuss (re: psycho-analyze) the movie. Please add a comment in your response with regards to which of the options you'd like to participate in.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317040294000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316184669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie: "A Dangerous Method" at the HOP, Hanover, 4pm</name><id>33797792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316808000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/33797792/</event_url></item>