<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51, Room 315</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>836742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084771</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;ANOTHER TRIPLE: TALKS BY PETER DAVIS, JOYCE LEVINE AND BERNIE MARCINIAK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 3: Trading in the Energy Markets by Bernie Marciniak&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bernie Marciniak is a member that lives and breathes the energy markets. In this short talk he will tell us what trades he is currently making. Bernie says &amp;quot;How to buy them at wholesale prices and sell them at retail prices.&amp;quot; It will be an entertaining moment for us. Since Wolf Musow we've been without an energy expert; it would be good to have someone to rely on for energy insights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Bernie Marciniak is a swing trader taking positions from one day to sixty days. He is a partner in a small independent energy trading group made of retired energy executives. He worked for Pack &amp;amp; Kahn, a crude oil shipper and and refiner. He brought a Very Large Crude Carrier into Boston Harbor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Talk 2: Avoiding the Black Swan – How Astrological Cycles Impact Social, Political, and Economic Trends  And How This Can Benefit Your Portfolio by Joyce Levine&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A black swan is a highly improbable event with three principle characteristics:  It is unpredictable; it carries a massive impact; and, after the fact, we concoct an explanation that makes it seem less random, more predictable than it was.&amp;quot;  &lt;u&gt;The Black Swan, The Impact of the Highly Improbable&lt;/u&gt; by Nassim Nicholas Taleb &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Knowledge of astrological cycles allows you to avoid black swans by knowing what's coming ahead of time.  Investment strategies that worked before may not work in the future.   Joyce has been warning for years to learn how to invest money.  She cautioned clients about real estate before this downturn and before the late 1980s downturn.  In this short, 30 minute, talk, Joyce will share her thoughts about how astrological cycles will affect the next few years. We will fit as much of Joyce's insights and your feedback as will fit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Joyce Levine lives in Cambridge and has been attending our meetings since we moved to MIT. Joyce is a full-time professional consulting astrologer with over 30 years experience. Joyce is the Clerk of the National Council for Geocosmic Research and the President of its Boston Chapter, the Past President of the New England Astrological Association, and a certified professional member of the American Federation of Astrology since 1979.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Talk 1: Market Talk by Peter Davis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Market Talk is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker - usually for the next month and sometimes including longer range predictions. The speaker then makes a short case for defense of the prediction - usually taking about 10 minutes.  The audience is expected to probe or support the speaker's ideas. In general the audience participation portion of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. Historically this market discussion is lively and insights come from all around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Peter Davis is a full-time graphic designer and part-time trader. His trading philosophy is based on the premise that all markets in all time frames are driven by psychology, primarily that of fear. His trading method seeks to take advantage of &amp;quot;emotionally-stretched&amp;quot; markets. While he is a strict technician, he also believes everything is relative and that markets should be traded with an understanding of the current dynamics. In addition to his trading, he works as the designer and brand strategist for TheWizard.com, a subscription-based trend-following system covering stocks, ETFs, futures and forex.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING of the Tiger Financial Network starts at 5:30 PM.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; See &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;the announcement here&lt;/a&gt;. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers by Bob Podd&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Doug&lt;br /&gt;7:15 Market Talk by Peter Davis&lt;br /&gt;7:45 Stockpicks&lt;br /&gt;8:15 Break&lt;br /&gt;8:25 Avoiding the Black Swan – How Astrological Cycles Impact Social, Political, and Economic Trends And How This Can Benefit Your Portfolio by Joyce Levine&lt;br /&gt;8:55 Trading in the Energy Markets by Bernie Marciniak&lt;br /&gt;We will stick to this schedule. Please do not ask to change the time limits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Print Your Handouts for this meeting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can, please print out an extra set for those who RSVP too late to get this notice or forget to bring their own copies:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/web/PeterDavis_ibd_012809.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Davis - The Market Talk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/81154/Joyce%20Levine%27s%20Avoiding%20the%20Black%20Swan.ppt"&gt;Joyce Levine - Avoiding the Black Swan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bernie Marciniak - Trading in the Energy Markets - will have no slideshow&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be sure to thank Peter and Joyce for providing these in advance of the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233360544000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>51</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229916867000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors January Main Meeting</name><id>9374317</id><headcount>51</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233187200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9374317/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>