<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Hazard Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.989895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hazard Grille</name><city>Enfield</city><id>950610</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.579881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>September Book Choices:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fiction Selection:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;This is Where I Leave You, by Jonathan Tropper&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon Best of the Month, August 2009: Jonathan Tropper writes compulsively readable, laugh-out-loud funny novels, and his fifth book, This Is Where I Leave You  is his best yet. Judd Foxman is oscillating between a sea of self-pity and a &amp;quot;snake pit of fury and resentment&amp;quot; in the aftermath of the explosion of his marriage, which ended &amp;quot;the way these things do: with paramedics and cheesecake.&amp;quot; Foxman is jobless (after finding his wife in bed with his boss) and renting out the basement of a &amp;quot;crappy house&amp;quot; when he is called home to sit shiva for his father--who, incidentally, was an atheist. This of course means seven days in his parent's house with his exquisitely dysfunctional family, including his mom, a sexy, &amp;quot;I've-still-got-it&amp;quot; shrink fond of making horrifying TMI statements; his older sister, Wendy, and her distracted hubby and three kids; his snarky older brother, Paul, and his wife; and his youngest brother, Phillip, the &amp;quot;Paul McCartney of our family: better-looking than the rest of us, always facing a different direction in pictures, and occasionally rumored to be dead.&amp;quot; Tropper is wickedly funny, a master of the cutting one-liner that makes you both cringe and crack up. But what elevates his novels and makes him a truly splendid writer is his ability to create fantastically flawed, real characters who stay with you long after the book is over. Simultaneously hilarious and hopeful, This Is Where I Leave You  is as much about a family's reckoning as it is about one man's attempt to get it together. The affectionate, warts-and-all portrayal of the Foxmans will have fans wishing for a sequel (and clamoring for all things Tropper)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Non-Fiction Selection:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kitchen Confidential, by Anthony Bourdain&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most diners believe that their sublime sliver of seared foie gras, topped with an ethereal buckwheat blini and a drizzle of piquant huckleberry sauce, was created by a culinary artist of the highest order, a sensitive, highly refined executive chef. The truth is more brutal. More likely, writes Anthony Bourdain in Kitchen Confidential, that elegant three-star concoction is the collaborative effort of a team of &amp;quot;wacked-out moral degenerates, dope fiends, refugees, a thuggish assortment of drunks, sneak thieves, sluts, and psychopaths,&amp;quot; in all likelihood pierced or tattooed and incapable of uttering a sentence without an expletive or a foreign phrase. Such is the muscular view of the culinary trenches from one who's been groveling in them, with obvious sadomasochistic pleasure, for more than 20 years. CIA-trained Bourdain, currently the executive chef of the celebrated Les Halles, wrote two culinary mysteries before his first (and infamous) New Yorker essay launched this frank confessional about the lusty and larcenous real lives of cooks and restaurateurs. He is obscenely eloquent, unapologetically opinionated, and a damn fine storyteller--a Jack Kerouac of the kitchen. Those without the stomach for this kind of joyride should note his opening caveat: &amp;quot;There will be horror stories. Heavy drinking, drugs, screwing in the dry-goods area, unappetizing industry-wide practices. Talking about why you probably shouldn't order fish on a Monday, why those who favor well-done get the scrapings from the bottom of the barrel, and why seafood frittata is not a wise brunch selection.... But I'm simply not going to deceive anybody about the life as I've seen it.&amp;quot; --Sumi Hahn&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are in the back room - just tell the host that you're part of the book club!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meagan</member_name><member_id>6521348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285897745000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279760102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September Meetup - This Is Where I Leave You and Kitchen Confidential!</name><id>14175410</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285797600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/14175410/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/e/global_17816974.jpeg</photo_url></item>