<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Just off Route 16</address_2><address_1>Pinkham Notch Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03846</zip><lat>44.231195</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rocky Branch Trail Head</name><city>Jackson</city><id>1267672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.255031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hiking Mt Isolation, Saturday January 19th from Rt 16 via Rocky Branch, Engine Hill Bushwhack, Isolation Trail, and Davis Path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have hiked Isolation a couple times but never in winter and never utilizing the Engine Hill bushwhack. I estimate this hike to be 14.4 miles round trip without utilizing the bushwhack, my research says the bushwhack cuts off 2-3 miles.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; I think this can be done in under 8 hours, maybe under 7 with favorable conditions. This is a bushwhack, not staying on trails. I have done a good amount of off trail travel, following are some pages covering Engine Hill Bushwhack, I would appreciate if you become familiar with the route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://dailey7779.blogspot.com/2011/02/iso.html"&gt;http://dailey7779.blogspot.com/2011/02/iso.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/32876400@N08/5568941948/in/set-72157626248161103"&gt;http://www.flickr.com/photos/32876400@N08/5568941948/in/set-72157626248161103&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://mattshikes.blogspot.com/2012/02/freezing-on-mount-isolation-feb-12-2012.html"&gt;http://mattshikes.blogspot.com/2012/02/freezing-on-mount-isolation-feb-12-2012.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/isolation-bushwhack.html"&gt;http://home.earthlink.net/~ellozy/isolation-bushwhack.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an intermediate/advanced hike, you are responsible for yourself and are expected to have all necessary winter gear and clothing. I do not expect crampons to be necessary, please bring them, we will decide at the trailhead, you should have snowshoes, microspikes, and a headlamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For your reference if you need it is a link to AMC’s list for &lt;span&gt;Essential Winter Gear for Northeastern Hikes&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/publications/outdoors/2002/2002-winter-gear.cfm"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/publications/outdoors/2002/2002-winter-gear.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I do not think you are equipped or in shape for this hike I will not allow you to hike with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will have my black lab Bond with me. Dogs are welcome as long as they are well behaved, in shape, and have done similar winter hikes. Please let me know with your RSVP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not available to carpool as I will be staying in Bartlett Friday night. I you are interested in lodging please ask. Please coordinate carpooling using the webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will try to limit the group size to 10. I will be posting this for my MOAC friends in Maine also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at the Rocky Branch Trailhead at 8AM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the trail by 8:30 AM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be bringing my butt sled, bring yours if you'd like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone will be waitlisted so I can get a feel for how prepared you are for this hike. I will require a phone number for last minute communications if needed. &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I have a busy week so please be patient in waiting for answers to your questions and getting off the waitlist. I have the slight (10%) possibility of being called into work on Saturday, in that case I may have to cancel or postpone until Sunday.&lt;/span&gt;  I will know for sure by Friday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Time dependent for those interested I would like to have light dinner and possible libations at a local establishment to follow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am working on finishing my winter 4Ks this year, if you are interested in joining me just ask, I will send you my tentative schedule of hikes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3987cb"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver VW Jetta</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim Gregory</member_name><member_id>10228942</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358611571000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358306340000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Isolation from Rt 16 via Rocky Branch, Engine Hill Bushwhack</name><id>99827352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358600400000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/99827352/</event_url></item>