<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>211 Airport Access Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02842</zip><lat>41.531380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newport State Airport</name><city>middletown</city><id>4885832</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.283241</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/5/a/6/event_81566022.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This is a MONDAY Jan 2 Fly out. Many have the day off. Wanna Fly?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Twas the week after Christmas and all through the house, we had new GPS', headsets and no place to go" OK, so it doesn't ryme...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's take the short hop to KUUU. We'll hitch a ride into Newport and tour one of the Mansions in grand style. Gawk at the rich and famous lifestyles and (try not to) steal the silverware. This is an event not to be missed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe eat breakfast there before a tour. If all goes well, we should be back by 1:00ish....maybe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost varies from $ 16 (one house) to $ 28 ( three houses). [url=&lt;a href="http://www.newportmansions.org/page9668.cfm]http://www.newportmansions.org/page9668.cfm[/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.newportmansions.org/page9668.cfm]http://www.newportmansions.org/page9668.cfm[/url&lt;/a&gt;] "Music, tours, and spectacular decorations highlight the celebration of Christmas at the Newport Mansions. We invite you to make holiday memories with your family by visiting The Breakers, The Elms and Marble House, all decked out for the holidays. Thousands of poinsettia plants, spectacular evergreens, trees, wreaths and fresh flowers and 19th century style ornaments turn the houses and their grounds into a Yuletide wonderland. Dining tables set with period silver and china and mannequins dressed in authentic costumes complete the elegant setting. All three houses are decorated and open daily for tours from November 15 through January 4. The Breakers opens daily at 9 a.m., The Elms and Marble House open at 10 a.m. The last tour admission at all three houses is at 4 p.m., and the houses &amp;amp; grounds close at 5 p.m." Don't miss this one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll need some sort of headcount to see about ground transportation. Your responses will also help us with who's flying or being a pax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great way to start the new year!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325522695000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324690761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Newport Mansions Tour Christmas Style! Fly Out #1 2012!</name><id>45361532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325512800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/45361532/</event_url></item>