<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a two part adventure for the strong willed and happy heart.  Part one is hiking up Mohawk Mt., part two is a cookout in that area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;=====PART 1=====&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohawk Mt. rises 1,683 above its surrounding.  Our hike will be 1200 ft of vertical gain and will offer a 360 degree view of the area.  We will travel on the Mohawk trail and the Mattatuck trail to see the stone lookout tower, climb the Pinnacle and then summit Mohawk Mt.  As happens a lot, we climb steeply right off the bat.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike distance is 6 miles with 1200' elevation gain.  I have no concrete time to finish so I suggest you try not to be on a schedule. We are a group and hike as a group.  We start and finish together.  If you are unfamilar with group hiking dynamics then carefully consider your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be summer and hot.  You need sturdy hiking boots, at least 2 liters of water, bug spray, sunscreen, snacks.  Try to not wear cotton.&lt;br /&gt;As always with me, NO DOGS, NO CHILDREN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the Mapquest link to the area.  We will road park around the corner of Valley Rd and 1 Essex Hill Rd.  DO NOT USE YOU GPS AS I DO NOT HAVE AN EXACT ADDRESS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=West+Cornwall&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Essex+Hill+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06796-1810&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.83891&amp;amp;longitude=-73.328819&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;=====PART 2=====&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who hike are invited to a cook out at the campground at Lake Waramaug in Kent, south of the hike site.  A few of us have two camp sites there and will be cooking and reclining by the water.  You will need to bring your own food but we should have stoves.  Bring chairs and bug spray.&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions about the party please email me directly.  No dogs at dinner please. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Site for Lake Waramaug camping:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/DEP/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325232" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/DEP...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279234374000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275348592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Mohawk Mt. and Cathedral Pines, Cornwall CT</name><id>13650617</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278770400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13650617/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>