<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 80. North wind at 6 mph becoming south. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I cant go to the Kayak Jamboree nor list it since its too far away and i cant deal with crowded parking lots and traFfick again..IM SAVING THE PLANET THIS WAY...LOL,&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested go the the SKG site for info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/StamfordKayakGroup/calendar/9944914/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides, i have a local paddle event on Sunday on the Farmington River..&lt;br /&gt;But it may rain..dont know yet..that means like last weekend..EVERYONE WANTS TO HIT THE ONLY BEACH DAY..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a place to do some FREEEEEEE TUBING down a a fine river,&lt;br /&gt;all you have to do is bring some flotation tube, raft or whatever,,(Maybe all you need is a big fat azz).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tubes can be gotten from Walmart and the similar..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the cheap ones are ok, but get what you want..we most likely will return here on the 100 degree days..&lt;br /&gt;Global warming ???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I DONT KNOW THE WEATHER YET.. BUT SO FAR ITS LOOKING GREAT.&lt;br /&gt;AND I DONT WANT TO FIGHT BEACH TRAFFICK AGAIN LIKE LAST WEEK.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some Pot Luck food &amp;amp; something for the Riverside Barbie-Q and wood for the after party fire. Leave it in you car till we have chosen a place (Either the existing fire pit or one we will make ).&lt;br /&gt;Bring your favourite bugg juice too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I HAVE SOME SCRAP WOOD AND A FAKE LOG I WILL BRING ALONG WITH THE &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW AND IMPROVED&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; GRILL AND SOME OTHER STUFF IN THE FRIDGE, MAYBE FISH, DONT KNOW YET..LOL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Location that is prime for so many things, last summer it was a place for us to play in the water, tubing, and have a barbie -q a few times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its also a good walking trail along the river.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving and parking directions DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 91 to the Scantic Rapids Parking lot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 47 East. Go eastbound 2.7 miles on RT-190 (Hazard Avenue) from Enfield to Hazardville.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At intersection of RT-190 and North/South Maple (RT 192)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~&amp;gt; turn right (South) onto South Maple.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park in the Barn Parking Lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walk over the bridge and look at the rapids area, I will stick the orange pole by the water or fire pit area,&lt;br /&gt;you have to look a bit since this is a popular local's location also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>LOOK for ORANGE 6 foot  POLE , Stryped Traffic Cones &amp; Slow Adults at Play Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250784783000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249321500000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>****FREE**** TUBING &amp; WALKING EVENT AT THE SCANTIC RAPIDS w/ Pot Luck Barbie-Q.</name><id>11023642</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249747200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11023642/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/6/global_3541542.jpeg</photo_url></item>