<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The public is invited to a special &amp;quot;Boon Island Day&amp;quot; event at Old York's Visitor Center at the Remick Barn, 3 Lindsay Road, in York, Maine, on Sunday, January 23, at 1:00 p.m. Five guest speakers will focus on the history of Boon Island, a remote, barren outpost about eight miles from the shores of York. The event is sponsored by Museums of Old York, with the assistance of the American Lighthouse Foundation (ALF).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy D'Entremont, president of ALF and operations manager of Friends of Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouses, will present an overview of the history of the island and its lighthouse, established in 1811. Bob Trapani, executive director of ALF, will speak about his first hand experience with the lighthouse, which is under ALF's care. Maine author/historian William O. Thomson will discuss the colorful human interest stories of Boon Island Lighthouse keepers and their families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Erickson of Portsmouth will discuss his surprising conclusions reached in his book on the infamous 1710 Nottingham Galley shipwreck at Boon Island. Warren Riess, a nautical archaeologist associated with the University of Maine, will focus on the archaeology of the Nottingham Galley wreck site and the 1995 recovery of cannons from the ship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is expected to last about three hours. Admission is $10, and refreshments will be served. Call (207) 363-4974 for more information. The storm date will be January 30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy D'Entremont</member_name><member_id>12517576</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295888836000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294575797000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Boon Island Day"</name><id>15978457</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295805600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/15978457/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/4/global_18198436.jpeg</photo_url></item>