<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373271</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)876-2700</phone><name>Crema Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>693403</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120426</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be the second of what I'm planning to make a monthly "social" for Boston-area libertarians -- or for anyone interested in meeting some open-minded, critical-thinking individuals. &amp;nbsp;Two of our main goals with this event are to (1) introduce new people to the philosophy of liberty and (2) add some cohesion to the existing libertarian scene in Boston;&amp;nbsp;though our primary goal on any given night will be to have a good time. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll keep it on the Cambridge side of the river this time (most of our attendees last time seemed to be located on this side), but let's try meeting up in Harvard Square. &amp;nbsp;We can start off at Crema Cafe (&lt;a href="http://cremacambridge.com/"&gt;http://cremacambridge.com/&lt;/a&gt;), and then we'll move out to a local pub, probably around 9pm. &amp;nbsp;Try my phone if you want to meet up with us later on (614-582-5901).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please encourage others to come, libertarian-leaning or not. &amp;nbsp;I'm sure they'll learn something, as last month's attendees can probably attest!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, feel free to call/text my phone if you have trouble finding us or plan to show up later: 614-582-5901&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you can't spot us, call my phone: 614-582-5901</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3732659</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301067114000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>People like to go out on Thursday nights anyway!</why><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-349</urlname><id>593245</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Libertarian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300070901000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drinks and socializing, with a libertarian theme</name><id>16910903</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301011200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-349/events/16910903/</event_url></item>