<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We all have a right to know. Right?&amp;nbsp; All things considered, I think that there is a presumption of a right to know UNLESS there are countervailing considerations that outweigh it. Here are a few possible discussion points: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Privacy&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; "It's none of your damn business!&amp;nbsp; No, those black lace stockings aren't mine!" Retort: "But it is my business, because I'm your wife!"&amp;nbsp; Clearly, the relationship between the one wanting to know and the one who knows has much to say about the right to know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The pedophile next door&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; This came up in the previous Impromptu Philosophizer during which I announced this discussion.&amp;nbsp; If you have children and a convicted pedophile has moved next door you are not only going to want to know, you're going to want the ex-convict out of the neighborhood.&amp;nbsp; However, once a pedophile has been released from prison, even he has rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Going to war&lt;/span&gt;. It might seem to be a huge jump to go from withholding information from a friend or a spouse or knowing that a pedophile has just become your neighbor, to questions about a nation going to war.&amp;nbsp; But, ultimately, these controversies are all about the right to know.&amp;nbsp; Before the U.S. invaded Iraq we were told that the U.S. was threatened by Iraq's WMDs (weapons of mass destruction).&amp;nbsp; It turned out that Saddam Hussein's regime didn't have any WMDs or they had been previously destroyed (we do know that he did use poison gas against the Kurds).&amp;nbsp; However, many of you may have seen the recent "60 Minutes" CBS news program that showed that the military's "intel" about the WMDs was a hoax perpetrated by a low-level Iraqi engineer as part of his (successful) effort to establish residence in Germany.&amp;nbsp; Perhaps the most important question is how the U.S. military and intelligence community could have been duped by a character so thoroughly unbelievable (as evidenced in his interview). Was the real hoax that the Bush administration's acceptance of the shabby evidence was only an excuse for it to invade when they either knew or should have known that the evidence was false?&amp;nbsp; Was there a manipulation of the people's right to know?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Freedom of Information Act&lt;/span&gt;. Even after the Clinton Administration&amp;rsquo;s expansion of the act, there are sure a lot of blacked out passages done for reasons of "national security," privacy and other matters.&amp;nbsp; Is the Freedom of Information Act too easily abused.&amp;nbsp; Should there be a non-partisan advisory board to oversee&amp;nbsp; blocks or barriers that prevent freedom of&amp;nbsp; access?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Brookings Report&lt;/span&gt;. In 1960 the Brookings Institution published a report, commissioned by NASA.&amp;nbsp; "While not specifically recommending a cover-up of evidence of extraterrestrial life [it] does suggest that contact with intelligent extraterrestrial life (or strong evidence of its reality) could have a disruptive effect on human societies. Moreover, it does mention the possibility that leadership might wish to withhold evidence of extraterrestrial life from the public under some conditions." (&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brookings_Report"&gt;click here for Wikipedia reference&lt;/a&gt;) Do you believe that such an unprecedented discovery should be kept from the public?&amp;nbsp; Is the U.S. government, in particular, more inclined than other Western countries to impede the right to know in matters related to UFOs? (answer: Yes.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The right to know, in the present framing of the issue, seems to be a relatively recent issue. Most likely, the extraordinary advances in communication,&amp;nbsp; technology and knowledge in general are in the middle of this.&amp;nbsp; It's a big issue, but perhaps not as broad as it appears.&amp;nbsp; The right to know is about understanding basic human rights, but requires a basis for knowing when the right is legitimate and not merely a pseudo-right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt; (Green Tea Restaurant)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be  sitting at the two big round  tables in the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1306537377000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303144771000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Right to Know"</name><id>17346314</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304722800000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/17346314/</event_url></item>