<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>DAR Constitution Hall&lt;br /&gt;1776 D Street NW&lt;br /&gt;Washington DC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy your tickets today at Ticketmaster. **Tickets will be available the day of at the C Street Entrance from 12 pm on - cash only.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basic admission is $15 and includes the program, get out the vote materials, and a free t-shirt - it does not include dinner.  General admission is $25 and includes a t-shirt, and Red, Hot, &amp;amp; Blue BBQ dinner. VIP admission is $75 and includes a t-shirt, premier seating, and reception with FreedomWorks Chairman Dick Armey, select FreedomWorks PAC-endorsed Champions of Freedom, and other special guests.   **VIP tickets are SOLD OUT** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to FreedomWorks members only and by attending you affirm your existing membership or volunteer to join FreedomWorks free of charge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are available online at Ticketmaster. Please note that the price listed does not included additional service charges that Ticketmaster applies.  The venue requires that we use the company.  Tickets will also be available the day of at the C Street entrance of the DAR Constitution Hall starting at 12:00 pm - cash only basis.&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * 5:00 pm: Doors Open at DAR Constitution Hall&lt;br /&gt;    * 6:00 - 8:30 pm: Program&lt;br /&gt;    * 8:30 - 9:30 pm: BBQ (!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speakers include: Mike Lee (Candidate, Senate, UT), Charles Lollar (Candidate, MD - 5), Mick Mulvaney (Candidate, SC-5), Morgan Philpot (Candidate, UT-2), FreedomWorks President Matt Kibbe, FreedomWorks Chairman Dick Armey, Rev. C.L. Bryant, Rep. Michelle Bachmann and others!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shirley /W.MA</member_name><member_id>5445158</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282950883000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>We Surround Them</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Western-Mass-912-Project</urlname><id>1394602</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6299972534</group_lon><name>The Original WMass 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282755412000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREEDOM WORKS - Washington DC</name><id>14538074</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282946400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Western-Mass-912-Project/events/14538074/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/9/global_7591481.jpeg</photo_url></item>