<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>270 Washington Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02359</zip><lat>42.094570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Heaven On Earth</name><city>Pembroken</city><id>5302572</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.793999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vincentgenna.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/Ad-for-Spirit-Of-Change.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.vincentgenna.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/Ad-for-Spirit-Of-Change.jpg" width="396" height="330" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We create our lives consciously or subconsciously. However, only 2-5% of the human mind is in conscious awareness. That means 95-98% of the mind is unconscious and acts automatically. If you are NOT creating the life you want, you are stopping yourself without even knowing it! At the Stop Stopping Yourself lecture, Vincent demonstrates the mechanisms that are blocking you from your true divine gifts and abilities, including your passion and purpose. Become the master of your life, change all you want, manifest complete abundance, and fulfill your dreams!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this lecture, you will discover:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• How you are dishonest with yourself almost every day;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• That you’ve done a lot of work to get this far, and there’s just one last thing to do;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• The scar from the story of your youth is your tattoo…purposely; and most importantly,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• How to connect all your dots, override all the crap and stop stopping yourself to become unstoppable!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a special addition to this lecture, Vincent will go through the audience and provide gallery psychic medium messages for certain individuals, as guided. Although not all the attendees will receive personal messages, the Universe brings together in one place all those who would benefit from hearing another person’s guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will have also the opportunity of scheduling a private 30 minute reading with Vincent during the rest of the afternoon on Saturday and from 10:00am-3:00pm, Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361643052000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Healing Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-healers-network</urlname><id>511093</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Healers Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358307695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stop Stopping Yourself and Become Unstoppable!</name><id>99830492</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361631600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-healers-network/events/99830492/</event_url></item>