<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>143 Argilla Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.665340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-356-5366</phone><name>Russell Orchards</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>669213</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.803215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Time to cram all of your fall must-do's in one lump sum.  Join in a midday jaunt of apple picking, (and apple cider donut consuming) at Russell Orchards followed by the Marini Farm maze.  We did this combo last year, and while the corn maze almost did us in, we had a blast, collapsing at a cozy Italian restaurant in Ipswich for dinner.  Heh, if we've got the stamina, we can even check out the campside ghost stories back at Marini's once darkness hits....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Russell Orchard's has become a stand-by for fall, giving us a favorite spot to pick some apples, sample some homemade wine, and forage for lunch at their kick-butt farm stand (think cheese, crackers, and a wide variety of local made products).  You can also bring some of your own and use them to supplement.  While eating, we can groove to the tunes of the Back Woods Ramblers.  Check out all the details at: &lt;a href="http://www.russellorchardsma.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.russellorc...&lt;/a&gt;.  Please note there is a charge for apple picking, and any food you purchase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we've picked and eaten to our hearts content, we'll drive over to Marini's farm to brave this years maze, &amp;quot;Lost Treasure of Castle Hill&amp;quot;.  You can see a photo of the maze we braved last year and a diagram of this years maze (brownie points if you can memorize it and lead us through ;-) at their website link: &lt;a href="http://www.marinifarm.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.marinifarm...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;Check out all of Marini's details at their website.  They've got a farm store of their own, so we'll have plenty of opportunities to snag all kinds of fall produce, including your Jackolantern pumpkins:-)&lt;br /&gt;Group vote (and ticket availability) dictates whether we head back for some ghost stories once darkness falls (see website for details:-)  Please note the ticket costs for the maze and ghost stories.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone interested, we'll be meeting at the Framingham, MA Park and Ride between 9:45-10 am and carpooling up for the day.  &lt;a href="http://www.ctps.org/bostonmpo/7_links/1_getting_around/1_park_and_ride/f/framingham.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctps.org/b...&lt;/a&gt;.  Scroll down to the &lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;second location for Rte 9 East, near exit 12&lt;/span&gt;.  If you're looking anywhere near Flutie pass, you won't find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Otherwise, look for us at Russell Orchards at 11:30 munching on apple cider donuts and sipping hot cider.  As ever, I'll have my cell phone on surrounding our meeting times (from 9:30 until about noon).  If you're only free for the afternoon and want to join us for mazing, make a note in your RSVP and we'll try to let ya know when we're heading over. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain will likely cancel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, bug Lisa :-)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will send my cell number and more details to my yes's and maybe's the afternoon prior.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287247639000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286462854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Classics cram: apple picking and corn maze</name><id>15033755</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287243000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/15033755/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/e/global_9846494.jpeg</photo_url></item>