<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This meetup is to say a farewell to meetup member Shane Donnelly. His wife is being stationed on Hawaii and will be leaving early next month before the next meetup. Here is what he had to say: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I want to see everyone before I go, because this group is very special to me. Also, I would like to show my final exam project to everyone. It is 30 minutes in length. It is documentary on Holocaust survivors,which was for my class at RISD. Jeff has agreed to let us use his studio&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm hoping everyone can make it to enjoy his documentary work and to bid him a fond farewell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be held at Jeff Haynes Studio in the Millworks Gallery in Uxbridge. Here are the directions Jeff sent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the easiest way (I think) to the mill. For&lt;br /&gt;MapQuest fans, the street address is 19 Depot Street,&lt;br /&gt;Uxbridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Worcester, take 146&lt;br /&gt;south to Uxbridge. You'll see an exit for route 16,&lt;br /&gt;which runs through Douglas and Uxbridge. Take a left&lt;br /&gt;at the end of the ramp toward Uxbridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow 16 into town, where you'll eventually come to a&lt;br /&gt;traffic light, where 16 meets Main Street. Turn right&lt;br /&gt;onto Main at the light, and once you're on Main, get&lt;br /&gt;in the left lane, so you can turn left at the next&lt;br /&gt;light. (the next light comes up fast) Turn left onto&lt;br /&gt;Mendon Road (which is also the continuation of 16), go&lt;br /&gt;under the railroad bridge, and take the next road on&lt;br /&gt;the right, which is Depot Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Depot, you should see a cemetery on your left,&lt;br /&gt;and the mill on your right. Just park on the street&lt;br /&gt;(on the cemetery side), and enter the mill under the&lt;br /&gt;big sign that says &amp;quot;Millworks Gallery.&amp;quot; We can meet&lt;br /&gt;people there in the lobby, and/or post signs to guide&lt;br /&gt;people to the studio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any problems getting there or need more information about the area, call Jeff at 508-928-1142&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1148499675000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Event: Meetup at Jeff Haynes for a Farewell to Shane.</name><id>4949804</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1149204600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/4949804/</event_url></item>