<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The details come from the site localattitude.com, which is at :&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www321.pair.com/oaries/mylestandhike.htm"&gt;http://www321.pair.com/oaries/mylestandhike.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At about 8 miles, this hike is relatively long&amp;mdash;allow about 4 hours for the loop. Terrain is mostly flat, but trails can be sandy and wear you out faster than usual.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the forest headquarters, walk a few yards on Cranberry Road and take Jessup Road on your right. Follow it for about 2.5 miles until you reach Bare Hill road, a paved road. Cross it and continue straight on Federal Pond road. Pass the underground gas line (markers) and turn right at the next intersection onto Sabbatia road. At the end of this trail, turn left until you reach the paved Lower College Pond road. Turn right on the road that will bring you back to the parking lot in about 1.5 miles. Traffic is generally light and the road very scenic. Still, always walk facing incoming traffic and watch for vehicles.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first reaction is that most of this would be on the paved roads, but Jessup is one of the dirt fire roads, as are Federal Pond and Sabbatia. &amp;nbsp;Therefore, only the last mile and a half are on paved roads and we can easily switch to the hiking trail or the bike path once we reach the East Head Reservoir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I'm up for one of the &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/travel/explorene/specials/outdoors/galleries/great_local_hiking_spots/"&gt;"15 Great Hikes".&lt;/a&gt; How about you? Should be a piece of cake after this last one.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, Lower College Pond Road was flooded out in the spring. Should we be hit with heavy rains again, we'll find our way around the flooding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Owing to the length, you will probably want to bring more water than usual along with snacks and your lunch. We suggest bringing at least 2 half liter bottles per person. (More if it heats up.) Good hiking shoes are essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Anyone with concerns about the 8 mile distance may want to consider joining DCR ranger Amy up in the Blue Hills for a 3 mile 3 Peaks hike on the same day as our hike. Visit &amp;lt;a href="&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-SE-Mass-Environmental-Education-Meetup-Group/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/The-SE-Mass-Environmental-Education-Meetup-Group/&lt;/a&gt;"&amp;gt; SE Mass Get Outside! meetup group&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Most of the longer AMC hikes have a screening process, whereby members have to be approved by the hike leaders before they can join one of the longer hikes. &amp;nbsp;We have never had such a process, since the terrain in Myles Standish is not very challenging and most of our hikes are less than two hours. &amp;nbsp;This hike is longer than our usual hikes. We are counting on you to make your own assessment as to whether or not this hike represents a reasonable undertaking.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Forest Headquarters main parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bescherer</member_name><member_id>650729</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302282943000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><why>The Globe just published a list of 15 Great Hikes including one in our own Myles Standish State Forest.  It's 8 miles long and sounds like fun.</why><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299607879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One of the Boston Globe's "15 Great Hikes"</name><id>16846283</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301835600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/16846283/</event_url></item>