<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join the best Fashion Industry Meetup in the world. We have members who are experts in different aspects of the industry, &amp;amp; many who are beginners looking to find help from you. We have fun, great networking time, and projects to get involved in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our present project is a Fashion Expo, &amp;quot;Let's Wake Up the World to the Boston Fashion Industry&amp;quot;, Sept. 18, at Lesley University, as a part of Boston Fashion Week, &amp;amp; as our Sept. Meetup. We need all types of fashion workers &amp;amp; entrepreneurs to join us, &amp;amp; get table/booths for showing and selling your fashion products &amp;amp; services. We have an Expo room for booths, and an atrium with a stage for symposiums and mini presentations. For beginners and aspiring designers, etc. we need you to help, and you will learn a great deal about how the Boston Fashion Industry works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to our July 17, meetup, and learn all about how to get involved. We look forward to meeting many more fashion people and seeing all the familiar ones as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA directions to Positive Image, 135 Mass Ave. &lt;br /&gt;Its advisable for everyone to park their cars at a convenient MBTA station and take the train to Park Street Station. Get on the Green Line heading outbound, any train, B,C,D, except NOT E. Get off at Hynes Center. Go up stairs to Mass Ave. Take a left to lights and cross Boylston Street to Berkeley School of Music; then immediately cross Mass Ave. and you will see 135 Mass Ave. Ring bell for 3rd. Floor. Positive Image photo studio. And take elevator to 3rd. Floor.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on your Organizer, see my web site, &lt;a href="http://www.shirleywillett.com" target="_blank"&gt;ShirleyWillet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shirley, Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be greeting each member as they arrive</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley Willett</member_name><member_id>1480973</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217007538000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213916738000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Fashion Industry July Meetup</name><id>8175483</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216332000000</time><rsvp_limit>44</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/8175483/</event_url></item>