<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mobile Apps: How entrepreneurs are developing the money making 'picks and axes' of the future&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfnov2012.eventbrite.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes a successful mobile app company? How do you create value in your company? What is patent worthy? What are the options for early financing to get your business off the ground? How do you pitch an investor? How do you make your mobile app rise from the crowd? These questions, and more, will be discussed by our panel of angel investors, entrepreneurs, and media experts. Bring your own questions for our distinguished panel and learn from other entrepreneurs in the audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The introduction of the iPhone five years ago marked the beginning of a mobility revolution that now has dozens of smartphones and tablets in the hands of consumers around the world, all using apps to enhance every aspect of daily life. The mobile revolution has ushered in the "app'lification" of consumer technology. This digital goldrush has attracted entrepreneurs from all corners of the world. The barriers to entry for developing and selling mobile apps is low. As a result, there are hundreds of thousands of apps available in the various consumer app stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/George%20McQuilken.jpg" alt="McQuilken" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George McQuilken, Angel Investor &amp;amp; Member of eCoast Angels&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

George McQuilken has over 30 years of experience as a successful entrepreneur and advising other entrepreneurs. He has been CEO at numerous companies and has led them to successful exits. He is now an active member of the eCoast Angels network, a group of like-minded investors formed in 2000. The group's focus is on early-stage companies involved with advanced technology, e-commerce, healthcare, and industrial products and services, principally located in the New Hampshire coastal region. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/johnny_monsarrat.png" width="100" height="110" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Johnny Monsarrat, CEO, Hard Data Factory &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Johnny Monsarrat was previously Founder, CEO, and Chairman of Turbine Entertainment Software, which now employs 250 people. Then, forming his own strategic consultancy, his clients included top-level executives of Citigroup and General Electric, and he played stopgap VP roles for numerous firms over a decade. He has an MIT BS and MBA, and also attended Harvard and Brown University. He is an award-winning public speaker and has lectured on entrepreneurship at MIT, Brown University, and Wellesley. Johnny has appeared in the Boston Globe, CNN, USA Today, Mass High Tech, and the Wall Street Journal. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/Alex%20Bakman.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alex Bakman, Founder &amp;amp; President, Snappii&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Alex Bakman has been a serial entrepreneur. Prior to founding Snappii in 2010, he founded and grew 3 companies from zero to $10+ million in sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/Nick%20Pic5.jpg" width="98" height="122" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nick Zeckets, CEO and co-founder of Alumni Connection Platform QuadWrangle, Inc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nick Zeckets is CEO and co-founder of Alumni Connection platform QuadWrangle, Inc of Boston. He is a successful business development leader with experience in the market research, mobile, advertising, Higher Education, and consumer internet industries. He's regularly called upon to speak and write about his areas of expertise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Nick also runs sales, marketing, new product development and strategy for TRU, the world leader in Millennial consumer insights. Before TRU he built new businesses for The Nielsen Company and The Corporate Executive Board. He is an alumnus of the University of Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/owenjohnson.jpg" width="98" height="98" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Owen Johnson, Founder and Managing Partner of Betaspring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Owen is a founder and managing partner of Betaspring. His past ventures include Investment Instruments Corporation, provider of online residential real estate services Rentomatic.com and Rentometer.com; and Interdimensions Corporation, a high-growth interactive agency. In 2004, he founded Connect Providence, a group helping to connect newcomers to the City of Providence, RI. In 2009, he started the Providence chapter of the Awesome Foundation. He serves on the board of directors for Location, Inc., the Providence Community Library, and the MIT Enterprise Forum of Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He regularly mentors aspiring entrepreneurs, has been a team mentor for the MIT 100k Business Plan Competition, and a business plan judge for the Brown Entrepreneurship Program Business Plan Competition. Owen holds an S.B. in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and is an active member of the MIT alumni community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfnov2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/"&gt;http://entretechforum.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like us on Facebook: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/#!/entretech"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/#!/entretech&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353465011000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348155419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mobile Apps</name><id>83282942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353454200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/83282942/</event_url></item>