<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Faneuil Hall </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359961</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dick's Last Resort</name><city>Boston</city><id>972418</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056753</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>***EVENT UPDATE - PLEASE READ - Due to the popularity of Dick's Last Resort Mardi Gras Party, we have over 125 people between the 6 invited groups who have RSVP'd Yes or Maybe for this event. On Monday morning, Dick's needs an exact number for the 6:30 pm Dinner Reservation. Please Update your RSVP to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; followed by the comment &amp;quot;6:30 Dinner&amp;quot; with guest names if you want to be seated at a reserved table for dinner. Only those who RSVP for dinner will be seated in this section. All guests arriving later are welcome to hang at the bar, join us in our section as others depart, or be seated elsewhere if capacity permits. Dick's can not guarantee additional seating due to space limitations. RSVP's for this event will be closed on Monday morning when Dick's contacts us for an RSVP count and guest list. There may be lines so please update your RSVP now or ASAP. THE RESERVATION FOR ALL 6 GROUPS HAS BEEN MADE UNDER THE RED SOX NATIVES. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Mardi Gras event takes place Rain, Snow or Shine! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an Annual Event at Dick's Last Resort! It is always crazy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Booze Club will be attending along with several other groups including Boston Happy Hour, Social Fun, The Skidaddlers Ski and Sports Club, The Boston Gingers.... We will have only ONE RESERVED SECTION FOR THOSE ORDERING DINNER AND DRINKS at 6:30 p.m. Later arrivals can join us any time in our section or hang at the bar. We expect to be there well into the night as the live music stops after 11 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE CHECK THE EVENT CALENDAR FOR FUTURE UPDATES ON THIS EVENT. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Circle February 16 in your black book cuz that's the day confetti will fly and multi-colored beads will be flung as Natives celebrate Mardi Gras Madness 2010 at Dick's Last Resort. The wearing of feathers and masks will be encouraged as party-goers rule from quittin time til whenever. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to expect??? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No cover &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live entertainment by Sidewalk Driver from 8 - 11 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2.75 Southern Comfort Hurricane Drinks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$3.50 Harpoon IPA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free stuff (feathery masks, doubloons, beads, and other junk) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dick's full menu available for purchase &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Servers dressed in their most garish garb &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Characters (some flashing) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted parking at the Garage at 75 State Street (Take T, please) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be lines! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is sponsored by Harpoon Brewery so that insures it will be good! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266536464000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>BOOZERS</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BOOZE-CLUB-Boston</urlname><id>1553338</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>! BOOZE CLUB - Boston !</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264571088000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fat Tuesday &amp; Mardi Gras Madness 2010 at Dick's Last Resort </name><id>12436326</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266363000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BOOZE-CLUB-Boston/events/12436326/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/5/global_12820645.jpeg</photo_url></item>