<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 53/Lake Dunmore Rd.</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05769</zip><lat>43.908890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Silver Lake Trailhead</name><city>Lake Dunmore</city><id>6367942</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.087502</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will meet in the trailhead parking lot at 11am. Just a short walk from the parking area is a waterfall we can explore and find different views for those with cameras. We will then go up to some cliffs with a beautiful view overlooking Lake Dunmore and looking west to the Adirondacks (if it's a clear day). Bring your lunch and we can eat on the cliffs. We'll then back track a bit and head up to Silver Lake. I believe there is a trail going around the lake we can take as well. The hike should end up being about 4 miles total. The elevation climb is no more than 850 feet and the trail up to the lake is an old carriage road. I'm not sure on their policy with dogs but I do believe they need to be leashed, especially around the falls. DIRECTIONS: Take route 4 west into Rutland, turn right onto Route 7 north. Follow Route 7 for about 16 miles and bare right onto McConnell Road which is at a 'Y' by a Citgo station. Continue 3.3 miles and turn right onto VT-73 (Forest Dale Rd). After a half a mile, turn left onto State Route 53. After about 5.5 miles, the trailhead parking lot will be on your right. From White River Junction, this should take about an hour and a half to an hour and 45 minutes. CARPOOLING: I won't be able to bring anyone with me but I can meet anyone who wants to at the Woodstock municipal parking lot at Benson Place, just off of Pleasant Street at 9am and you can follow me.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333372873000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332728448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Falls of Lana &amp; Silver Lake</name><id>57851462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333206000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/57851462/</event_url></item>