<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>43 Commonwealth Rd. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.311058</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508.653.9641</phone><name>Cochituate State Park</name><city>Natick</city><id>715468</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.374553</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Le's see how much of the lake we can explore.  We'll start out by heading north, paddling under the Mass Pike up into the northern section of the lake and travel around the shore line.  We'll head back into and through the middle lake and paddle through a small tunnel that leads to the southern portion of the lake.  Total distance traveled will be between 6-10 miles depending on the stamina of the group.  There is a little beach on the south side of the tunnel that leads from the middle to the southern part.  If needed, some people could rest and wait there while others explore the southern portion (about an hour tops). Expect the duration of the trip to last from 3-5 hours including a stop or two along the way.  Due to the distance, you'll need to have experience staying with a group at a decent pace.  If weather is bad, I'll postpone to later in the week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is usually a $5 fee to enter the park (but, I am not sure if you will have to pay this early in the season on a weekday).  Follow signs to boat launch (it's to the left after you enter the park).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please arrive in time to have "butts in boats", ready to paddle by 10:00 AM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***PLEASE NOTE*** The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Required items: PFD (worn) and whistle. Optional/recommended: Pump/bailer, set of dry clothes in drybag, water, snack, insect repellent and sunscreen as needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369076329000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365433677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Paddle at Lake Cochituate, Natick, MA</name><id>113283252</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369058400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/113283252/</event_url></item>