<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;h2&gt;Come One - Come All! &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be creating sacred space and sharing in the energies of our connection.  Whether you are an experienced drummer or just starting out, there is space for you in our circle.  And what would a circle be without dancers?  So come and join us for this joyous celebration of life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;2:00pm Beginner's Class&lt;/b&gt; - Are you new to drumming?  No problem!  We'll have a beginner's class available just before the actual drumming begins.  Come out and learn the basics of good drumming form.  We'll learn a couple of very basic Native American rhythms, how to find the beat in the circle, and the etiquette of the drum circle so that we can all be good drumming citizens.   Class is free - donation is appreciated.  Bring your drum if you have one, if not, there will be drums to loan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;2:30pm The Sacred Drum Circle&lt;/b&gt; - Each month we'll cover a different aspect of the drum circle.  Learn about the energy of the drums, the interaction of the drummers and the dancers, how to use the energy of the circle to shift things in your life, and more.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Setting the Space &lt;/b&gt;- Together we will create an altar that sets the tone for the circle for the day.  Bring with you something to place on the altar that represents you.  We'll create that container together.  We're working on a theme of clearing.  In July we cleared out the things in the physical world that didn't serve us and brought in focus and clarity.  August had us clearing out emotional baggage and emotions trapped in the body that didn't need to be there.  &amp;lt;b&amp;gt;This month's theme will be clearing on another level: clearing out beliefs and assumptions that limit us.&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3:00pm Open Drumming &lt;/b&gt; - Bring your drums, rattles, Native American flutes, digeridoos, etc.  We will open up the room and get it rocking with the rhythms.  There will be space made for both heart-pounding beats and softer rhythms with room for voices and instruments.  There will be some instruments available for borrow, but it would be best in the beginning if everyone brings what they have so we are certain to have enough to go around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;4:30pm Mid-Circle Break&lt;/b&gt; - We'll take a break at roughly the half-way mark to allow people to introduce themselves and say what they bring to the container.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6:00pm - Closing Circle&lt;/b&gt; - We'll close the space as we opened it with a circling up of the participants and a closing of the energy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost: &lt;/b&gt; Guess What?  After months of searching, we found a venue so happy to have us there that they are not charging us for the space.  &lt;b&gt;So, that means the event is FREE.  (YAY!!)&lt;/b&gt;  We will put out a donation basket for those who choose to contribute.  (Suggested Donation is $7, but give what you can.) Donations will go to cover the costs of maintaining this meetup group, obtaining and repairing instruments, and the costs of electricity and heat for the church.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The First Parish in Malden, a Unitarian Universalist congregation, is located three blocks west of the Malden Center T station at 2 Elm Street (intersection with Pleasant Street), just off Route 60. Convenient, free parking is available between the church and the Beebe Elementary School. Visit MaldenUUA.org for directions and map. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We run this event once each month on the third Sunday of the month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelle Sparta</member_name><member_id>1953058</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255892610000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Rhythm Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-drum-circle</urlname><id>617617</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250508880000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Drum Circle, Dance, Jump &amp; Jive September Meetup</name><id>11128836</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253469600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-drum-circle/events/11128836/</event_url></item>