<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;IMPORTANT: Please be sure to read the entire event listing before you RSVP - then answer the questions that are part of the RSVP process. While the objective of this event is to enjoy ourselves, your safety, and the safety of the others, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands, overestimate your skills and abilities, or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If I haven't yet hiked with you, I will contact you to ensure that this trip will indeed constitute an enjoyable and safe fit with your background and interests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIFFICULTY RATING:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Advanced / Level 4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip entails 12 miles of hiking over rugged terrain, with approximately 3000' of elevation change, including two miles of intense bushwhacking.&amp;nbsp; We will hike this route at a &lt;strong&gt;moderate&lt;/strong&gt; pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What We Are Doing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a very special winter visit to the Hancocks. In addition to South (4319') and North (4420') Hancock, we will bushwhack over to NW Hancock (just over 4000'), on the Trailwrights 72 list. This trip will entail 12 miles of hiking (including 2 miles of bushwhacking), and approximately 3,000' of elevation gain, all at a moderate pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip includes some major bushwhacking.&amp;nbsp; After heading down to NW Hancock from North Hancock, we'll decide based on conditions and our timing&amp;nbsp;whether to bushwhack back up the way we came, or to head straight down from NW Hancock.&amp;nbsp; Due to the nature of this bushwhack, be sure to bring face/eye protection that's clear enough to allow visibility in low light conditions; sunglasses will not work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because we &lt;strong&gt;will be starting early&lt;/strong&gt;, we recommend&amp;nbsp;arriving and staying over in the Lincoln, NH area the night before.&amp;nbsp; Contact the leaders for info on cost-effective lodging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there is sufficient interest, we will grab a quick dinner locally before heading home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important Notes on Participation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I haven't hiked with you before, I will contact you as soon as I can to ensure that this trip will indeed constitute an enjoyable and safe fit with your background and interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests are permitted only if&amp;nbsp;you provide me with everyone's full name,&amp;nbsp;e-mail address, cell phone number, and responses to all the sign-up questions.&amp;nbsp; I can then follow up with people as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a dog friendly trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, or other situations and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here - meaning we might not reach the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.09547572946637&amp;amp;lon=-71.5045166015625&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for the current weather conditions and forecast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full winter gear is required for this hike.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If you are not sure what this means, please check out this &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Winter_Dayhike_equip.pdf"&gt;winter day hike gear list&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Except for full crampons, you do not need to bring the gear specified under "Above Tree Line".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Registration, Directions and Carpooling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you say "I'm Going" on this meetiup, then please also register for it on the AMC registration system&amp;nbsp;at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.hbbostonamc.org/registrationSystem/204"&gt;https://www.hbbostonamc.org/registrationSystem/204&lt;/a&gt;. If you have not used this system before, you will need to take a few minutes to create a login profile for yourself that you'll then be able to use to register for this and future trips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we approve you for this trip, you will have access to the detailed location and directions &lt;a href="https://www.hbbostonamc.org/registrationSystem/204"&gt;at that same registration URL&lt;/a&gt;, as well as everyone's contact info and carpooling (encouraged!)&amp;nbsp;plans/needs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Legal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to being posted as a Random Group of Hikers meet-up, this trip is also an official AMC trip, and you will need to sign the AMC's standard release agreement when we meet.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; If you are not familiar with this agreement, you can see it here:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease-2.pdf"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease-2.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions?&amp;nbsp; Don't hesitate to contact me as needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip</member_name><member_id>5187997</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329169132000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327444400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Winter Visit to the Hancock Family (Advanced)</name><id>49479382</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329044400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/49479382/</event_url></item>