<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note that this month's meeting will be on the SECOND Monday of the month to accommodate our guest speaker's schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freethought lecturer Robert Green Ingersoll was America&amp;rsquo;s most famed and controversial orator, yet few today recognize his name. He may be the most remarkable American most people never heard of. Ingersoll is not alone in being forgotten by history. West-Central New York (centered on the Erie Canal between Utica and Rochester) was a cauldron of social ferment, including freethought, abolition, women&amp;rsquo;s rights and more. &lt;br /&gt;

 You may recognize Tom Flynn as the Executive Director of the Council for Secular Humanism, editor of Free Inquiry magazine, a journalist, novelist, entertainer, and folklorist. Tom Flynn is also the director of the Ingersoll Birthplace Museum in Dresden, New York, in the heart of the Finger Lakes. We&amp;rsquo;re very pleased that Tom will give us an illustrated lecture on the life and accomplishments of Ingersoll, and discuss highlights of the surrounding Freethought Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start with thirty minutes of coffee and conversation at 7:30 p.m. The talk will follow brief announcements at 8:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will most probably be in the Social Hall near the main entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Siddall</member_name><member_id>1140632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331726388000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330097204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting: Tom Flynn - Robert Green Ingersoll</name><id>53632912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331595000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/53632912/</event_url></item>