<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>96 Winthrop Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372364</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-864-0655</phone><name>Tommy Doyle's Irish Pub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>969478</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Dinner&lt;/b&gt;: 7:00 pm - 8:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TV show&lt;/b&gt;: 8:00 pm - (is this an hourlong or two hour long episode?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note on the RSVP if you are joining us for dinner or just dropping in for drinks and watching the show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Don't be frightened... we mean no harm...&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;V is coming... &lt;b&gt;Tuesday, November 3rd, 2009&lt;/b&gt; at 8:00 pm on ABC. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us at &lt;b&gt;Tommy Doyle's&lt;/b&gt; in Harvard Square watching the first episode of this new mini-series downstairs in the &lt;b&gt;Crimson Lounge&lt;/b&gt;. There is a seating capacity of 50. The manager, Garett Tingle, will tune into ABC at 8:00 pm on their 50 inch plasma screen so we can all watch it, and pipe in the audio for the show. Yes, they serve the same menu as the main bar. Thanks Rebecca Watson from &amp;quot;Boston Skeptics in the Pub&amp;quot; for the contact information!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Care to grab dinner before the show comes on? T.J. will be waiting outside Tommy Doyle's by 6:45 pm rounding up people. We can head in at 7:00 pm to grab tables. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Wikipedia:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/V_(2009_TV_series" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;V is an upcoming television series remake to be broadcast on ABC during the mid season of the 2009-2010 television season. It is executive produced by The 4400 creator Scott Peters, Jace Hall, Steve Pearlman and Jeffrey Bell and is based on the science-fiction franchise created by Kenneth Johnson. The series will premiere on November 3, 2009, and air for four weeks, before being put on hiatus until March 2010&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Personally I have fond memories of the original, especially Robert Englund's character, but also according to Wikipedia: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;E! Online rated the pilot episode 'on a scale of 1 to 10, we give it an 11. V is the best pilot we've seen in, well, forever.' The website Seat42F rated the pilot episode A+, applauding its cast and effects and naming it one of the best pilots in years. USA Today's Robert Bianco named V on his list of the top ten new shows, stating that the remake is well-made and &amp;quot;quickly establishes its own identity&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... this sounds intriguing, in spite of the fact that it sounds like the PR department of ABC put that review on Wikipedia. ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cast:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Mitchell as Erica Evans&lt;br /&gt;Morris Chestnut as Ryan Nichols&lt;br /&gt;Joel Gretsch as Father Jack Landry&lt;br /&gt;Lourdes Benedicto as Valerie Stevens&lt;br /&gt;Logan Huffman as Tyler Evans&lt;br /&gt;Morena Baccarin as Anna, the leader of the Visitors&lt;br /&gt;Laura Vandervoort as Lisa, a Visitor&lt;br /&gt;Scott Wolf as Chad Decker, a reporter&lt;br /&gt;Alan Tudyk as Dale Maddox (FBI investigator&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;According to the Hollywood Insider in Entertainment Weekly:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hollywoodinsider.ew.com/2009/09/25/abc-to-break-up-v-debut-first-four-episodes-air-in-november/" target="_blank"&gt;http://hollywoodinsid...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An ABC spokeswoman confirmed exclusively to EW that V, the network’s much anticipated reboot of the old NBC miniseries, will air for a limited, four-episode run in November and then return to the schedule after the Olympics in March. News of the show’s unique rollout comes amid rampant speculation that the Warner Bros. TV drama was undergoing a serious overhaul after news broke that it would halt production for a two-week hiatus. Now, an insider confirms, the hiatus will extend for another four weeks to prepare for the show’s previously announced Nov. 3 debut. An ABC spokeswoman says it was always the network’s intent to the run the science fiction drama in 'pod' form to treat it more like event programming&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...  not sure if I want to schedule all 4 episodes as Meetups. What if they suck? ;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailer&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://abc.go.com/shows/v" target="_blank"&gt;http://abc.go.com/sho...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Tommy Doyle's:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/harvard-square/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tommydoyle...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tommy Doyle’s in Harvard Square opened it’s doors in 2005 in the historic Hyde-Taylor house.  The building was once the site of the original “House of Blues.” With historic shoes to fill, we have committed ourselves to providing proper live music, nightly entertainment, and quality food &amp;amp; drink for the Harvard Square community.  Since opening we have become a staple for Harvard student life, and have had a great time doing it!  A vibrant and eclectic crowd on any given night, we boast tons of screens with all the games, Pub Trivia on Tuesday and Wednesday, Live Music 5 nights a week, DJ &amp;amp; Dancing Wednesday thru Saturday. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our lunch deals &amp;amp; creative  dinner specials keep  not to mention one of the widest selection of beers, single malt scotch, and Irish Whiskey around&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu (Harvard Square):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/tommydoyles_menu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tommydoyle...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257465956000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256156758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>V mini-series premiere @ Tommy Doyle's Harvard Square</name><id>11680359</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257292800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11680359/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/7/global_11345399.jpeg</photo_url></item>