<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Guys this is something that a lot of us were talking about and waiting for.&amp;nbsp;Penguin Roadracing School is the BEST school in the area and the OLDEST in the country.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As it is for now we only have 10 spots so RSVP and make your reservation with the school 
&lt;strong&gt;by phone&lt;/strong&gt; as soon as possible before spots are filled.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Partner up with a fellow rider to keep the costs down.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; I will bring some extra gear and equipment&amp;nbsp;to the track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;If you RSVP yes you will need to register&amp;nbsp;by phone&amp;nbsp;and pay the fee of $250.&lt;/strong&gt; Call Penguin Racing School at (978) 400-8204, and ask for Kathy. 
&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Let them know you are with New England Sportbike, or Boston Tier 1 Riders. 
&lt;strong&gt;DO NOT REGISTER ONLINE.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; The regular price is $280 so you must call and mention&amp;nbsp;you are with our group to get the discounted rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Penguin Racing School website:&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.penguinracing.com/pages/8_faq_s.cfm"&gt;http://www.penguinracing.com/pages/8_faq_s.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;#65279;&amp;#65279;&amp;#65279;&amp;#65279;New Hampshire Motor Speedway&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;1122 Route 106, Loudon NH&amp;nbsp; 03307&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The most important thing you can do to ensure a great day at the track is to arrive early.&amp;nbsp; You should arrive at the track early (preferably the night before) to give yourself ample time to unload and get through registration, which opens at 0700am.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Motorcycle Preparation&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; - Your motorcycle should most importantly be clean and oil tight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; Tires and brakes that are in good condition (50% material or more) are a must.&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; You should remove your mirrors, tape up all of your lights (and remove the fuse so the tape does not melt), and its a good idea to cover up your speedometer (helps focus on the track).
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; We also highly recommend removing your side stands, although its not required.&amp;nbsp; Be aware that they can drag on many bikes.&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; You also need to remove all of your antifreeze and replace it with&amp;nbsp;Water Wetter&amp;nbsp;or approved race coolant.&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; If you plan to ride to the track, leave yourself plenty of time to prepare your bike in the morning.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; 
    &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Highly Recommended but not required:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; change your brake fluid (every 6mos), change your brake pads with race pads (you will do a lot of heavy braking), Stomp Grip pads (to help keep you on the bike while leaning off), wire your oil filter with race wire and a regular hose clamp (for safety). Race Plastics (about $500-800).
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Safety Wire Install Instructions 
    &lt;a href="http://www.rc51.org/wire1.htm"&gt;http://www.rc51.org/wire1.htm&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Rider Equipment&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Helmets must be at least Snell 2005 approved and be in excellent condition.&amp;nbsp; They must be no more than 5yrs old.&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; You need gauntlet (over the wrist) gloves and over the ankle boots (work boots are OK, Sidi are the best) with socks.&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; Your riding suit is required to be full leather and if it is two-piece it MUST be zipped together at the waist.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &amp;nbsp; Highly recommended but not required:&amp;nbsp; Back&amp;nbsp;Protector (that little hump on the back of your suit does not count), undersuit (this will help you slip in and out of your&amp;nbsp;leathers fairly easy, and wicks away the&amp;nbsp;sweat.&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;If your equipment does not pass tech. inspection, the Penguin Racing School has a full line of rental equipment available.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;All rental equipment should be reserved in advance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Recommended Hotels&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Red Roof Inn (10% for Penguin Students) 603-225-8399&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hampton Inn Concord/Bow 603-224-5322 x506 (20% off - mention Penguin Racing School @ time of registration)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Fairfield Inn by Marriott 603-224-4011 ($59/night - mention Penguin)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;#65279;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Email from Cathy from Penguin Racing School&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;"Thank you for your phone call.&amp;nbsp; I think your riders will have a great track experience with Penguin School.&amp;nbsp; We have a program dedicated to what your group is looking for.&amp;nbsp; Track time and classroom instruction to enhance riding on both the street and track.&amp;nbsp; It is built around both the first time track rider and experienced riders alike.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;If any rental equipment is needed the pricing is 40.00 for leather suit, 15.00 for boots and 10.00 for gloves, and we can take care of that on an individual basis.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Thanks again for your interest and if you have any questions please either email or call me.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Cathy Curtin&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Penguin Road Racing School&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;105 Baldwinville Rd&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Winchendon, MA 01475&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;978-400-8204&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;866-434-5199 (fax)&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Things to do and/or bring&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;get a good night's sleep&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;be at the track early for tech inspection at 0700&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a buddy (don't go alone, have someone with you that has your important information should something happen)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5gal gas can (fuel may not be available until around noon, so make sure your bike is fueled up in the morning, and bring a gas can if possible.&amp;nbsp; Race fuel is expensive!)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Duct tape and/or Painter's tape&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;water and some simple snack foods&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;air compressor, Tire gauge!!! (don't ride a trackday without studying your tire pressure religiously) With tires like my slicks my window for traction is +/- 2psi on the rear. any more or less than 25 HOT for me Im sliding around like an ice rink. All tires are different as well as what temps outside and on the track are.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;generator (quiet) for tire warmers if you use them&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Basic tools for changing your own wheels out incase you need to have new tires installed, also any tool to remove all your fairings is crucial. I never go without just about everytool I own but thats just me. A basic Metric set of 8mm to 19mm sockets and 6mm to 10mm T-Handles are like Gold. I highly recommend ones shaped like an L that have two ends, one short and one Long with a ball like tip for angled stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;JB Weld (get the quick kind for temp stuff that dries in like 1hr or the regular kind for overnight permenant fixes like broken engine covers and such. Its a life saver)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ear plugs if your using any kind of after market pipe too. I swear I shaved off time by not having my loud ass pipe screaming in my ear.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Call the track to see if they have any power you can tap into and if its free. Some tracks rent garages that have electricity and air hookups which are very nice.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;cash&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;cell phone and charger&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pop-up tent with tie downs (dont be&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;That Guy&lt;/span&gt; with the tent flying across the track)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fold out chairs (after running full bore in the heat you are going to need to relax and Hydrate big time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Side Notes&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    A Go Pro HD (or similiar) video camera may be mounted on your bike for the Track Day.&amp;nbsp; I will bring mine and try to get as much footage as possible for those not able to attend our first event.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Guests/family are allowed to attend at no extra charge. The gates will be open.
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Motorcycles or gear can be rented, but must be reserved in advance
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Track Day Guide 2011&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;If you are attending this event then you should read this 
&lt;a href="http://am3.olivesoftware.com/olive/am3/RoadRacingFree/default.asp"&gt;http://am3.olivesoftware.com/olive/am3/RoadRacingFree/default.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Anyone riding to Loudon on July 10th evening, can meet Shashank at Starbucks, 99 Commerce Way, Woburn MA at 5pm.
     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are going to meet up at the Hampton Inn &amp; Suites, 195 Laconia Rd, (603)286-3400 on Monday morning at 0600 to arrive at Tech Inspection early.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Navy CFL</member_name><member_id>8858593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310478104000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><id>1535765</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306513928000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Penguin Racing School Joint Meetup w/Boston Tier 1 Riders SOLD OUT!</name><id>19961801</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310382000000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/events/19961801/</event_url></item>