<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Capitol Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.762972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bushnell Park </name><city>Hartford</city><id>921453</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.695278</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;World Laughter Day Celebration in Hartford's Bushnell Park May 2, 2010 12 noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come together to Laugh, Picnic, and Help Contribute to Spreading World Peace and Understanding!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mayor Eddie A. Perez and the Hartford City Council has issued a proclamation announcing the official celebration of World Laughter Day in Hartford.  It will be celebrated annually the first Sunday of May.  This year this world-wide event will be held on May 2, 2010.  A celebration will be held in the city’s downtown Bushnell Park at 12:00 PM.  The event is designed to promote healthy living and create community bonding to foster peace and understanding. Admission is free and open to all.  The only requirement is an openness to laughter!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What:  Reading of Mayor’s Proclamation, lots of fun, simple no-stress Laughter games to get &lt;br /&gt;             everyone laughing, picnic (bring food to share with your fellow laughers!)&lt;br /&gt;When: Sunday May 2, 2010 @ 12 noon&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Bushnell Park, Hartford, CT  (near the bandshell)&lt;br /&gt;Warning: You might laugh so much you’ll feel happy for DAYS afterwards!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;World Laughter Day was created in 1998 by Dr. Madan Kataria, founder of the worldwide Laughter Yoga movement. In each subsequent year, more and more events have been held across the United States and around the world. This coincides with the phenomenal explosion of interest in laughter therapy and the amazing powers of laughter.   The celebration of World Laughter Day is a positive manifestation for world peace and is intended to build up a global consciousness of brotherhood and friendship through laughter. Its popularity has grown exponentially with that of the Laughter Yoga movement now counting over 6000 Laughter Clubs in more than 65 countries.&lt;br /&gt;Why World Laughter Day?&lt;br /&gt;Steve Wilson, founder of the World Laughter Tour, says &amp;quot;The world is so out of balance that it needs to lighten up and laugh more in order to maintain perspective. We set aside this day to send a message to get more people laughing, urging the world to lighten up!  Systematic exposure to true mirthful laughter in a supportive environment, can contribute to world peace by fostering attitudinal healing.  Regardless of the reason you laugh, the primary purposes of laughter have to do with reducing the terrible effects of stress, and connecting with other people; laughter plays a huge role in maintaining relationships. Actually, we need laughter more now than ever!” &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Laughter causes the body to release endorphins, which are the body’s ‘Feel Good’ hormones, into the bloodstream which can tend to generate feelings of happiness, warmth, love, bonding, tolerance, forgiveness, generosity, and compassion.  The presence of these endorphins counters the  production of stress hormones that can correspond with hatred, fear, violence, jealousy, aggression and the emotions associated with war and oppression. “When you laugh, you change and when you change the whole world changes around you.” Dr. Madan Kataria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrating World Laughter Day&lt;br /&gt;World Laughter Day is customarily celebrated on the first Sunday of May every year. This year on the 2nd of May, the world will once again come together to laugh and spread the word of happiness and joy. The Laughter Clubs movement is a global initiative to unite entire mankind through unconditional love and laughter. It is a non-religious, non-racial and non profit organization committed to generate good health, joy and world peace through laughter. This revolutionary idea has positively changed the lives of hundreds and thousands of people around the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Route 91 to Rt 84 west exit 48 Asylum St.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet near the west end of the park at the Bandshell</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Sherry</member_name><member_id>5650811</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273363396000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Partners in Laughter</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup</urlname><id>1384386</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Laughter is the Best Medicine and Fun Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272167774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Laughter Day Sunday  May 2: Celebrate With  Laughter!</name><id>13281667</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272816000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup/events/13281667/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/6/global_7339158.jpeg</photo_url></item>