<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Revanche at the Coolidge Corner theater (showtime 7:25)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had hoped to see this last week while it was still playing on one of the bigger screens.  It is now on screen 3, and it's actually being held over an extra week.  It looks very good.   Dinner &amp;amp; discussion afterward at Pho Lemongrass.  Due to short notice, no MAYBE rsvps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main synopsis below is from Rotten Tomatoes (RT rating 93/7.8) ...a bit of Wesley Morris's review is  below that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis:  At once a gripping thriller and a tragic drama of nearly Greek proportions, Revanche is the stunning, Oscar–nominated, international breakthrough film from Austrian filmmaker Götz Spielmann. In a ragged section of Vienna, hardened ex-con Alex (the mesmerizing Johannes Krisch) works as an assistant in a brothel, where he falls for Ukrainian hooker Tamara (Irina Potapenko). Their desperate plans for escape unexpectedly intersect with the lives of a rural cop (Andreas Lust) and his seemingly content wife (Ursula Strauss). With meticulous, elegant direction, Spielmann creates a tense, existential, and surprising portrait of vengeance and redemption, and a journey into the darkest forest of human nature, in which violence and beauty exist side by side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below..the end of the review by Wesley Morris from the Boston Globe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie's element of surprise emanates from how these characters behave, how they ache, and how their ache is tied to matters of conscience and acts of regret. It doesn't ruin much to say that Alex holds Robert responsible for botching his clean getaway that afternoon and wants to make him pay. Robert, of course, is wracked with his own post-traumatic stress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All the stillness, particularly in the country, where Alex chops wood with erotic abandon, implies a kind of anticipation. You're lured in by seemingly placid shotmaking then knocked out by what transpires within the frame. The strangers we meet in the first hour have become far more fascinating to us by the second, mostly without the film divulging much. We have to wait for Spielman to unspool his story and guide us to where it's headed. He's too smart a storyteller to tell us everything. The screenplay overreaches to connect characters, but his offbeat visual touch legitimizes the contrivances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Revanche&amp;quot; was a foreign-language Oscar nominee this year, and it's a better movie than most of the films in the main race. The word &amp;quot;revanche&amp;quot; means &amp;quot;revenge&amp;quot; in German, but &amp;quot;waiting&amp;quot; would have been just as good. The passing days begin to both dispel and enrich Alex's thirst for revenge. &amp;quot;Revanche&amp;quot; presents a world in which one man's wrenched fury can be another's rationalizing balm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a moral beauty in the movie's consideration of violence and vengeance. A man can accept a moment of true clarity even if it's from someone who doesn't know you've planned to kill him.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Front of the theater near the screen after the movie</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242575486000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242054156000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revanche</name><id>10385075</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242342900000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10385075/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/1/global_8585617.jpeg</photo_url></item>