<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The topics this month will be performance optimization (specifically for MySQL and Rails) and service monitoring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, David Berube will deliver his “High Performance Ruby on Rails and MySQL” talk, originally presented at MySQL Conference 2009 in April:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Database access in Ruby on Rails can be extremely slow, but it doesn’t have to be: this talk will discuss ways you can get massive performance speedups by increasing your query efficiency and by minimizing ActiveRecord object creation. This can keep your application scalable and responsible even under large datasets and modest hardware.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Turnbull will then take us on a tour of Monit, and show us how to use it to manage production services. Monit is, of course, not just useful for Ruby tools but for all UN*X daemons and services, so make sure to spread the word to others you know who might be interested:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Monit is a flexible, open source utility for monitoring, reporting, and acting on processes, files, and servers to keep your deployed application healthy, secure, and running. This month, Brian Turnbull will share his real world experience installing, configuring, and running monit in production UN*X environments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, we hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>nap</member_name><member_id>6144459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245972853000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhruby</urlname><id>885450</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The NH Ruby and Rails Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242246634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH.rb Monthly Meeting</name><id>10404502</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242946800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhruby/events/10404502/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/f/global_4005199.jpeg</photo_url></item>