<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pawtucket Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.643787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-459-0802</phone><name>Heritage Farm Ice Cream &amp; Restuarant</name><city>Lowell</city><id>1314481</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Well, Sandy, Sandy, Sandy&lt;/span&gt; you kept us from our walk last Monday. But, I don’t think we had a shortage of exercise, cleaning up of tree debris, and starting those generators (except, of course, those spoiled few that have AUTO back-up systems ;). Wow, what a mess, and such a disaster in some places. Our hearts go out to those unfortunate folks that lost their homes and the loved ones that had fallen victim to Sandy’s destruction and devastation. This was truly a storm that will long be remembered, but sadly, not in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A reality check will forge us thankful for the opportunity to walk &amp;amp; talk, while enjoying our natural surroundings &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/2/event_175982722.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;and our flourishing friendships. I, for one, couldn't ask for a better place to be on a Monday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now that Daylight Savings Time has come to an end (Sunday), we will adjust our start time back to the original of 5:30pm. Why, you ask? Well why not, it will be dark earlier and some of us are just simply NOT able to sneak out of work THAT early. Oh, still confused? Well look at the photo, and observe the pathway. &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/d/0/event_175982512.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;It’s very well lined with street lights, popular to many, quite safe, and policed. Also remember that there are always several of us and no one will be left behind. With the trees almost void of all their leaves, a new and brilliant view of the sky opens up above us. The night sky and the reflected lights on the water from across the way make for a pleasurable walk along the river……and don’t forget the echoing of the Lowell band that always seems to fill the air when we walk by.&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/4/event_175982452.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come on you regulars and you new folks too! We now, not only walk &amp;amp; talk; we try a different eatery every week! So much for our calorie burning! But, hey, &lt;strong&gt;It’s all-ways a GOOD time!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll meet between 5:30 - 5:40pm at the concert park benches just across the street from Heritage Ice Cream &amp;amp; Restaurant. My cell #; (603) 204-1657 &lt;br /&gt;

 This is also a DOG FRIENDLY WALK, so bring them along if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352225111000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351821904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Walk &amp; Talk Along the River!</name><id>89581572</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352154600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/89581572/</event_url></item>