<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mallinckrodt Building, Harvard University, 12 Oxford St, Cambridge 02138</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pfizer Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1630603</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.138908</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/4/0/event_55466432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;So after you've gotten a taste of SITN at Science by the Pint, join us the next evening for a full blown lecture from these guys.  They'll be talking about the Neglected Diseases of the Bottom Billion - nasty ailments that inflict themselves upon the less fortunate corners of the earth, and what is and is not being done about them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science in the News is an organization of Harvard graduate students dedicated to bringing cutting edge research to the public in a fun and informative format.  Their lectures are clear and well presented, and allow for lots of questions and interaction from the audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture is from 7:00 to 9:00 (or thereabouts).  We'll begin gathering in the hallway at the entrance to the lecture hall about a half hour beforehand, then go in and get seats about 10-15 minutes before it starts.  There are snacks and refreshments, and afterwards we'll head to one of many Harvard Square watering holes for food, drinks, and discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group beforehand, just look for us outside the auditorium afterwards - we won't be too hard to find.  Just look for the two nerd herders wearing Meetup pins :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From SITN:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The “big three” infectious diseases (HIV, tuberculosi&lt;span&gt;s and malaria), inflict massive health and welfare burdens and get a whole lot of attention from nonprofits and the news media. But for the “bottom billion” people of our planet who live on under $1.25 per day, a handful of neglected diseases take an additional toll seldom recognized in the developed world. While neglected diseases claim at least half a million lives each year, they harm hundreds of millions more by disabling adults and stunting the mental and physical development of children, locking families and communities into a vicious cycle of poverty with suffering, stigma, and lost opportunity. Sadly, many neglected diseases are curable or can be effectively prevented with the right public health measures. We’ll discuss the identity of these neglected diseases, why we should care about them, what sort of efforts are underway to control them. We’ll close with a discussion of how science and technology might help the bottom billion gain the upper hand over neglected diseases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the entrance to the auditorium...we'll be wearing our Meetup pins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>23</waitlist_count><updated>1337277208000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335566768000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science in the News Spring Lectures: Neglected Diseases of the Bottom Billion</name><id>62441782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337207400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/62441782/</event_url></item>