<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wow, slim pickings in the month of August, but this might be good. A buddy cop comedy with Mark Wahlberg playing straight man to Will Ferrell. From the team that brought you &amp;quot;Talledega Nights&amp;quot; which often doesn't mean much but if it's half as good as that movie, it'll be worth seeing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are seeing the movie at 7:35!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will wear my red meetup hat. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be waiting by the tables by the big window. If the movie is downstairs, I'll be waiting behind the rope across from the refreshment stand. I'll be at the theater at 7:00, and we should go in and get seats at 7:20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I strongly encourage folks to buy tickets ahead of time at &lt;a href="http://www.amcentertainment.com/BostonCommon" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amcenterta...&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure to buy for the 7:35 show!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, no worries, you can meet us after. We gather outside the doors of the room showing the movie afterwards. Then we head out for some munchies and a beer. Or two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Synopsis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set in New York City, &amp;quot;The Other Guys&amp;quot; follows Detective Allen Gamble (Will Ferrell), a forensic accountant who's more interested in paperwork than hitting the streets, and Detective Terry Hoitz (Mark Wahlberg), who has been stuck with Allen as his partner ever since an embarrassing public incident with his quick trigger finger. Allen and Terry idolize the city's top cops, Danson and Manzetti (Dwayne Johnson and Samuel L. Jackson), but when an opportunity arises for the Other Guys to step up, things don't quite go as planned. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D6WOoUG1eNo" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to watch the trailer on YouTube.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825820000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279677020000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Other Guys</name><id>14164631</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281135600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/14164631/</event_url></item>