<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>163404</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dr. Robert M. Bowman, Lt. Col., USAF, ret. is President of the Institute for Space and Security Studies, Executive Vice President of Millennium III Corporation, and retired Presiding Archbishop of the United Catholic Church. The recipient of the Eisenhower Medal, the George F. Kennan Peace Prize, the President's Medal of Veterans for Peace, the Republic Aviation Airpower Award, the Society of American Military Engineers' ROTC Medal of Merit (twice), the Air Medal with five oak leaf clusters, the Meritorious Service Medal, and numerous other awards, he is one of the country's foremost authorities on national security.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Colonel Bowman flew 101 combat missions as a fighter pilot in Vietnam and directed all the DoD &amp;quot;Star Wars&amp;quot; programs under presidents Ford and Carter. He has been an executive in both government and industry, and has chaired 8 major international conferences. Professor Bowman taught at 5 colleges and universities, serving as Department Head and Assistant Dean. His Ph.D. is in Aeronautics and Nuclear Engineering from Caltech. He has lectured at the National War College, the United Nations, Congressional Caucuses, the Academies of Science of six nations, and the House of Lords.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Bob Bowman ran for President in the Reform Party in 2000 and was the Democratic candidate for the US Congress from the 15 th Congressional District of Florida in 2006. Bob and his wife of 54 years, Maggie, have 7 children and 21 grandchildren. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on Bob Bowman, visit &lt;a href="http://www.thepatriots.us/" target="_blank"&gt;ThePatriots.us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone interested, on the day of this presentation, Bob Bowman will be meeting with us for a program at&lt;a href="http://gctv.org" target="_blank"&gt; GCTV&lt;/a&gt; beginning around 2:00 PM. Contact Jonathan Mark for more information.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In media room in back of Woodstar Cafe building, ground floor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Caputo</member_name><member_id>9333748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271373433000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270501871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Take Back America - Dr. Bob Bowman - Northampton</name><id>13095236</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271199600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/13095236/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/0/global_14173920.jpeg</photo_url></item>