<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 302, near AMC Highland Center at Crawford Notch</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.258121</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Webster-Jackson Trailhead</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>7689122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.441193</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a quick hike to Jackson (on the NH48 list) in order to help fellow Randomite, George Fraley, complete his NH 48 4000' list. We will be limiting the list size to allow for additional, non-random members to join us for this occasion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Plan:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Webster Jackson Trail starts at Route 302 at the northwest end of the Crawford Notch State Park. The parking lot, which is about .25 miles from the Highland Center at Crawford Notch, is across the highway from the trailhead. The trail, blazed in blue, climbs 1.4 miles to the trail junction, where the choice is left towards Mt. Jackson or right towards Mt. Webster. We will head left straight up to Jackson, an additional 1.2 miles. Once relaxing at the summit we will head back to our starting location via the same route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total estimated distance for this hike is 5.2 miles. Due to the pace and elevation gain, this trip is considered intermediate. We will move at a moderate pace (~2.0 mph).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please arrive early to get your gear ready so that you are ready to leave the parking lot at 10am (and not pull into the lot at 10am).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. &lt;br /&gt;

•Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests are not permitted. All participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs are permitted on this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did all of my research for this trip using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (e.g. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. The higher we climb the colder, windier, and wetter it will be - we will need to be prepared. Remember, on average it gets 3-4 degrees (Fahrenheit) colder for every 1,000 feet of elevation gain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or out on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•Footwear: hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the debris out of your boots. &lt;br /&gt;

•Clothing: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and conducts heat away from the body. &lt;br /&gt;

•Outerwear: Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood). Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. &lt;br /&gt;

•Food and Water: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip. &lt;br /&gt;

•Shelter: You should always be prepared to spend a night in the woods if you have to. Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces). &lt;br /&gt;

•Other Essential Gear: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in colder temperatures). Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Sunscreen is important since we will be traveling on exposed trails. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack. &lt;br /&gt;

•Optional Items: Trekking poles. Bug spray. Camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for George, he's about 6'5"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Audra</member_name><member_id>5480374</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1343861438000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342796683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Jackson (Intermediate)</name><id>74172022</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343570400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/74172022/</event_url></item>