<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>On a Dreamy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.372639</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>A Dreamy House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6198742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109650</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Happy third year anniversary! It was over three years ago when we began this odyssey, exploring the inner realms of dreams and visions. What a long strange trip it's been. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The theme for this party is three. Please bring three of something - three magic stones,&amp;nbsp; three friends, a three corner hat, three French hens, three wishes, three dreams, a dream story with three of something in it, or whatever you can imagine! We will play dream games, sing dream songs, dance dream dances, and play with dream cards and oracle cards! We will have fun! We always do at these dream parties. I hope you will join us! Costumes and masks are always encouraged, but not required. Some of us just love to dress up! Costumes and masks will be provided for the adventurous or you can bring your own. You are welcome to bring your friends! The more the merrier! Instruments are also welcome. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This is also a vegetarian potluck, so bring some dreamy veggie food with you when you come! What foods have you had in your dreams? Bring some food from your dreams if you like, just make sure it's edible and veggie. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be meeting in Cambridge, Massachusetts, 6 PM - 12 Midnight. This is a party, so you can drop in whenever you feel like it. Anyone wishing to attend the Third Anniversary Dream Party must RSVP to be sent the address of the party. Sorry, I can't put the address on the net. Complete address and directions will be sent to you prior to the event after you RSVP. Street parking will be pre-arranged with the city of Cambridge, so you can park near the house.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333994773000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331786217000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>We Are Three: The 3rd Anniversary Dream Party!</name><id>56431882</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333231200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/56431882/</event_url></item>