<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Park St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-742-4460</phone><name>Paulist Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>919550</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062737</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Justice for Fallujah Fundraiser with Noam Chomsky, Dahr Jamail and Ross Caputi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, September 16th&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm reception&lt;br /&gt;7:00pm speakers forum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Paulist Center&lt;br /&gt;5 Park Street, Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nearly twenty years of war and sanctions has destroyed Iraq's medical infrastructure and has polluted Iraq to such an extent that it has caused a major health crisis, most notably in the city of Fallujah. In Fallujah there has been an alarming rise in infant mortality, birth defects, and cancer rates. Children are often being born horribly disfigured, so much so that women are becoming afraid to have families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Muhammad Tareq Al-Darraji and Dr. Entesar Ariabi have written important reports about the health crisis in Fallujah, and their research points to weapons used by the U.S., like depleted uranium and white phosphorous, as the cause. Dr. Al-Darraji founded the first NGO in Fallujah. He is the director of the Monitoring Net of Human Rights in Iraq, and he is the president of the Center of Environmental and Reserves in Fallujah. Dr. Ariabi was head of the Pharmaceutical Department in Yarmouk Teaching Hospital in Baghdad during some of the toughest years of the war.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help us bring these doctors to the U.S. to speak about their research and experiences during the First Annual Remember Fallujah Week this coming November. We need to raise $4,350.00 to pay for their visas and plane tickets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The list of speakers will include Noam Chomsky, Dahr Jamail via video conference, and Ross Caputi (an ex-Marine who participated in the 2nd siege of Fallujah). We will be having a reception at 5:30 PM in the auditorium of the Paulist Center where we will be serving wine, beer, and snacks. The speakers will begin at 7:00 PM in the chapel. We are encouraging $50 donations to join us for the reception and the speakers, or a $10 donation to join us for just the speakers ($5 for low income and unemployed).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information or to make a donation, visit &lt;a href="http://www.thefallujahproject.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thefalluja...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Harris</member_name><member_id>5188497</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suren Moodliar</member_name><member_id>5714882</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284677336000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People for Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>stopthewars</urlname><id>708558</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Antiwar</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284340428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Justice for Fallujah Fundraiser with Noam Chomsky, Dahr Jamail and Ross Caputi</name><id>14747432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284672600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/stopthewars/events/14747432/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/global_2184137.jpeg</photo_url></item>