<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Pomfret, CT - The Tea Party Patriots of  Districts 44, 50 and 51 are hosting a “Meet and Greet the Candidates Social” event on Tuesday Jan. 12, 2010(snow date Jan 26) at Pomfret Community School from 7:00PM – 9:00PM. Attending the Meet &amp;amp; Greet will be US Senatorial Candidates Peter Schiff (R), Vincent Forras (I), and Rob Simmons (R) Representative – Campaign Assistant Anton Vulai, along with US House Representative Candidates Daria Novak (R), Dan Reale (L), and Scott Deshefy (G).&lt;br /&gt; Organizers of the Meet and Greet Social are local members of the CT 2nd District Tea Party Patriots Districts 44, 50, &amp;amp; 51. Some participants have attended various tea party activities across the state and nation, including last April’s Tax Day Tea Party, March on Washington DC on 9/12, the Washington DC House Call on 11/5, and various mini Tea Parties held across the state of CT. Many of the Tea Party Patriots are first time political activists fed up with the way government is acting and wish to effect change. They stand for limited spending, smaller government, and the free market system, all of which our current  Federal Government is opposed to. The Keynote Speaker is Jen Ezzell, the Ct. 2nd District  Tea Party Patriots Organizer.  Ms. Ezzell says “ We encourage everyone to be involved in this years electoral process, the Meet and Greet Social is the first step in getting to know those who seek to represent you.“. &lt;br /&gt;The format of the evening will be; a presentation of the Tea Party Patriots by Jen Ezzell, a statement by each of the Candidates, a question and answer session, where two prepared questions will be asked of each Candidate, followed by social time with light refreshments and a chance to personally speak with each Candidate.  The midterm election in Nov. 2010 is essential to the stability of the United States government.  This is an opportunity to become informed about your Candidates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details of the Event:&lt;br /&gt;WHAT:   Tea Party Social and Meet the Candidates&lt;br /&gt;WHO:   District 44, 50 &amp;amp; 51 Tea Party Patriots&lt;br /&gt;WHERE:   Pomfret Community School,  20 Pomfret St, Pomfret, Ct&lt;br /&gt;WHEN:   Tuesday   Jan. 12, 2010   7:00 – 9:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;SNOW DATE:   Tuesday   Jan. 26, 2010   7:00 – 9:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Media Contact: &lt;br /&gt;NAME:  Joanne Baker&lt;br /&gt;PHONE: 860 315-7581&lt;br /&gt;EMAIL: jgiord12@hotmail.com&lt;br /&gt;WEB: www.ct2nddistrictteapartypatriots.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263514030000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262726024000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet and Greet the Candidates Social</name><id>12232110</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263340800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/12232110/</event_url></item>