<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Near MIT Sailing Pavilion along the Charles</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Memorial Dr &amp; Ames St</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>7962782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join me @6:00pm in a photo shoot of the moon rising over Beacon Hill at Sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 2nd is the day before the full moon and the moon will rise at 7:24 -- an hour before Sunset (8:25pm). This is the perfect time to capture a moon rise on the Boston skyline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is also "magic hour" on the Charles with beautiful tones and light from the setting Sun. There will be a short technical briefing at 6:30 to remind you of camera settings, subject and lighting tips, and the shooting opportunities as the Sun sets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a subject. Here's a chance to get some nice photos of your model,  significant other, friend, or practice target dujour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your camera: If you have a DSLR, that's great and you will have lots of opportunities to vary your settings! You will also get some nice shots with a point and shoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other optional equipment:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•Lens(es): a standard 50mm will get you great shots. An 18-70mm or 24-105mm will give you more options (we'll talk about that). If you have a 70-200mm with a DX sensor (less than full frame eg. Nikon D50/60/70/80/300/3100/5100/7000 or the Cannon equivalent - sorry I don't know the Cannon series as well) this will give you an effective focal length of 105-300mm and (after blowup) you can get a nice moon (face-only) picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•A built-in flash is good for subjects. If you have a power flash with an off-camera cord, bring it to get some amazing shots of your subject. If you are not shooting a subject, you may want to illuminate the foreground lightly (the boats) or not at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•Tripod: great if you've got one, else brace yourself on the railing for the night shots. &lt;br /&gt;

 (and make sure your camera strap is wrapped around your neck/wrist so you won't lose it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Schedule(approximate):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•6:00 pm Meet and greet &lt;br /&gt;

 •6:30 Briefing and review of techniques  &lt;br /&gt;

 •7:00pm -7:30pm Boston Skyline at Sunset shoot  &lt;br /&gt;

 •7:30pm -8:25pm Moon-rise over Beacon Hill / Boston skyline shoot &lt;br /&gt;

 • 8:25pm-8:45pm Sunset afterglow shoot (great for subjects with an off-camera flash) &lt;br /&gt;

 • 8:45pm-9:15pm Evening shoot, Skyline with reflections. (tripod comes in handy here)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and my equipment along the Chrales between MIT boat house and Ames St</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Domenico</member_name><member_id>9296355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341565854000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340955536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Moon-rise photo shoot by the Charles/MIT</name><id>71251442</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341266400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/71251442/</event_url></item>