<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a somewhat advanced hike (due to the slides involved) to make the loop over the Tripyramids. These are two NH 4000 footers. We will be hiking up the north slide and down the south slide and back&amp;nbsp; to the&amp;nbsp;trailhead via a combination of the trails that branch off of the Old Livermore Road trail. I have not done this route before. The trail descriptions and trails are in the WMG. This will be a slow but steady paced trip approiximate 11 miles long and 7 hour book time. (we most likely will be longer than book time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would not recommend this for entry level hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring gear appropriate for the day and time of year&amp;nbsp;including adequate water as the loop is potentially without water sources. Although we plan to make it out long before dark please bring a working flashlight or headlamp in addition to normal hike safe gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been suggested that the best access to the trailhead is via the Tripoli road which has its own eixt on RT 93 north of the Waterville exit. This is a partially paved dirt road with a 25 mph speed limit. Please plan accordingly. I will be driving down from the northcountry and therefore folks I probably will be of no help for a car pooling option. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If no one has signed up by Saturday at 6PM I will cancel the meetup and go on the hike anyhow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Livermore Road trailhead in Waterville Valley NH</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318253019000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317931490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tryipyramids via the Slides Sunday Oct 9th</name><id>36435202</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318161600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/36435202/</event_url></item>