<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Spend the July 4 long weekend in Montreal for the 2009 Jazz Festival! For those of you who haven't been before, Montreal knows how to throw a party! A large part of downtown is closed off and several outdoor stages erected for the free concerts.  Make your reservations now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of us will stay once again at the Hotel Viger, where rooms start at $68. They have a 48 hour cancelation policy so you can reserve in advance without worrying. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with past trips to Montreal and Quebec, there is an itinerary of events for the weekend. You can join the group for every event or skip some events and wander off on your own for a while. Everyone is responsible for their own transportation and accomodation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The schedule:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fri 3rd&lt;br /&gt;2:00 visit the Botanical Gardens and Olympic Stadium (meet at 1:00 at the Hotel Viger, 1001 rue Saint-Hubert)&lt;br /&gt;7:00 supper in Old Montreal at L'Aventure, 438 Place Jacques Cartier&lt;br /&gt;9:00 take in several free outdoor shows beginning with Florence K - La Nocha de Lola playing at the &amp;quot;scene General Motors&amp;quot; on rue Jeanne Mance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sat 4th&lt;br /&gt;9:00 light breakfast in Old Montreal at Cafe Van Houtte, 165 rue St Paul ouest&lt;br /&gt;10-1 sightseeing in old Montreal&lt;br /&gt;1:00 lunch at the Pub St Paul, 124 rue St Paul Est&lt;br /&gt;2-5 Jet-boating ride through the rapids, 47 de la Commune west, $65 thrill ride my Montreal friends recommended&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00 The Lost Fingers concert at Club Metropolis, $30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9-11 take in several free outdoor shows beginning with Cordero, at the &amp;quot;scene du festival&amp;quot; on Ste. Catherine street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sun 5th&lt;br /&gt;12:00 Tam Tams drum circle in Jeanne Mance park, on Ave du Parc near Rachel St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;June 15 update - I bought my tickets for The Lost Fingers, playing 6pm Sat July 4 at CLub Metropolis.  Check out their website, listen to their music and let me know if you'd like to go. (have you seen The Sisters of Belleville?!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://thelostfingers.com/en" target="_blank"&gt;http://thelostfingers...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday afternoon July 3 - visit Montreal Botanical Gardens&lt;br /&gt;With its collection of 22,000 plant species and cultivars, 10 exhibition greenhouses, some thirty thematic gardens, and teams of researchers and activities staff, the Montréal Botanical Garden ranks as one of the world's largest and most spectacular botanical gardens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www2.ville.montreal.qc.ca/jardin/en/menu.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www2.ville.mon...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.montrealjazzfest.com/Fijm2008/accueil_en.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.montrealja...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hotel-viger.com/en/index-home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hotel-vige...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247182021000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228674741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Montreal Jazz Festival !!</name><id>9296620</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246662000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9296620/</event_url></item>