<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Meford Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.450626</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>503682</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.230660</lon></venue><fee><label>Movie Ticket cost</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>16.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Per the Regent Theater Website &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/events/banff2007.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regentthea...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Banff Mountain Film Festival is on the road across North America and around the world. Whether you are an experienced mountaineer or an armchair adventurer, this event is for everyone. Don?t miss the excitement! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hot on the heels of the largest, and one of the most prestigious, mountain festivals in the world, the Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour has hit the road, with stops planned in more than 275 communities and 30 countries across the globe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year?s tour features a collection of the most inspiring and thought-provoking action, environmental, and adventure mountain films. Traveling from remote landscapes and cultures to up close and personal with adrenaline-packed action sports, the 2007/2008 World Tour is an exhilarating and provocative exploration of the mountain world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour is produced by Mountain Culture at The Banff Centre, and features award-winning films and audience favorites from approximately 300 films entered in the annual festival in Banff. Every year, the Banff World Tour team chooses about 25 films that feature a range of styles and themes, including climbing, skiing, kayaking, biking, adventure, culture and the environment. Join Hermitlake.com and chunkymonkey productions when the Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour brings the spirit of outdoor adventure to the Boston outdoors community, at the Regent Theatre &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the film schedule is, as yet, undecided. Films will be posted here soon and at www.Hermitlake.com. Also note that the Wed Feb 20 films will be a repeat of the Mon Feb 18 films, and the Tue Feb 19 will be a completely different night of films. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Many Wedelns will be headed back from the club President's day 2/18 - the first night the movies are shown.  So some of us will try to go to one set of films Tuesday night. Others will try to see the original set of films shown Monday night and will be repeated on Wednesday night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets ($16.50) can be purchased at the Regent Theatre or off of their website. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regards,&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203715258000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>It will be a fun group of folks and better that your average movie!</why><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202252726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Banff Mountain Film Festival World Tour - Part A</name><id>7271158</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203465600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/7271158/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/e/global_2109326.jpeg</photo_url></item>