<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Hotel Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02128</zip><lat>42.366482</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hilton Boston Logan Airport</name><city>Boston</city><id>9351792</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.024361</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;LOCATION CHANGE - THE DOUBLETREE GOT CAUGHT IN THE STORM AND HAD A FIRE - WE WILL BE AT THE HILTON AIRPORT, 1 HOTEL DR, BOSTON, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commercial Real Estate is RED HOT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Terry Hale is the leading expert on how to buy land and commercial property at 30% - 50% of appraised market value with none of your own money, credit or previous experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 reasons YOU MUST see Terry Hale in person &lt;br /&gt;

1. Terry is The Only Person On The Planet That Will Show You The Secret System in Place to Explode Your Wealth In Commercial Real Estate and get deep-discounted wholesale deals offered by motivated sellers in your area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Terry Will Dispel The Myths on Why Most People Stay Away From Commercial - And why it's such a benefit to you regardless if you want to do Apartments, Self Storage, Mobile Home Parks, Office, Retail, Shopping Centers or Land with HUGE bargain-prices with aggressive terms so you can get in the game with none of your own money credit or previous experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Terry Will Personally Walk You Through The Transition From Residential to Commercial Real Estate - Many investors are focused on foreclosures and smaller paydays, ANYONE can get into commercial NOW through my Made Easy system and explode their net worth with less work…in commercial It Only Takes One deal to set you up for early retirement!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Terry Will Walk You Through The Simple Process of NO BANKS Needed – When you’re getting in on deals at 30% - 50% of Appraised market value, it’s a no-brainer and when it comes to financing there’s a system set up for success from day 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Terry Will Walk You Through The Steps To Success – His students are doing deals with Monthly Cash Flow and Huge Cash Profits Anyone can get into Commercial Real Estate…Terry and his team are there for YOU!! Make sure you don’t miss out on the most powerful presentation of the entire EVENT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monthly Meeting - September 20, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost - Free to members of Bostonareia, $25 for visitors, to learn about memberships visit www.Bostonareia.com/membership.php&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30pm networking, 6:30pm meeting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking validated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doubletree Suites&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;400 Soldiers Field Rd, Boston, MA&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348197792000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-756</urlname><id>633261</id><group_lat>42.9399986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>NH Entrepreneurs Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346164978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Commercial Real Estate is RED HOT!</name><id>79725242</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348176600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-756/events/79725242/</event_url></item>