<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Fitchburg Road, Rte 31</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01473</zip><lat>42.540001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Leominster State forest</name><city>Westminster</city><id>326804</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.910004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Crow Hill is likely the best climbing in MA.  Plenty of routes and a 90 foot tall wall in spots.  This will be a joint event with Tim's group (a socializing meetup group.) We will picnic, play Frisbee and swim with the kids down by the pond.  Some people might also hike.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have an informal (but safe) belay set up for new climbers.  This will be from 11AM to 2PM at the practice wall (far right corner of the cliff.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will set up our ropes and climb about 3 hours.  Please bring water, sunscreen, and any equipment that you might have.  (I have an extra harness.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet for car pooling at 9 AM.  &lt;br /&gt;Meet at the big red wind mill sculpture at Porter Square T stop.  Be on time.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Crow Hill.  Find Leominster State Forest (www.state.ma.us/dem/parks/lmsf.htm).  Take route 2 to rt 31 south (exit 28) go south 1.3 miles to park head quarters. There are two parking lots.  Go to the first parking lot on the left and pay $5 dollars for the picnic area.  I will be in this parking lot at 11AM then I will head up the hill.  (Look for my small Silver Toyota.)   &lt;br /&gt;This should be a great day of outdoor fun and sun.   &lt;br /&gt;Smiles &lt;br /&gt;Geoff &lt;br /&gt;617 501-6217 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS Any experienced climbers who would like to help - please call me. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear a red shirt. Or call me 617 501-6217 (reception might be on/off at the hill.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Geoff</member_name><member_id>3444525</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216827966000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Fun.</why><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215080887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crow Hill, top roping and Picnic. Great for Newbies.</name><id>8269484</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216566000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/8269484/</event_url></item>