<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Landsdowne Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.361757</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-421-9595</phone><name>La Verdad Taqueria</name><city>Boston</city><id>1153545</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097622</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The holidays are wrapping up and prime ski season is just beginning!  Let's celebrate and get pumped for our favorite months of the year!  Join us for a happy hour at &lt;b&gt;La Verdad Taqueria&lt;/b&gt; on Landsdowne Street in Boston, where we will enjoy a few mid-week cocktails (cash bar) and some complimentary appetizers, while we play our favorite ski films on the big screen TVs!  Check out their website:  &lt;a href="http://www.laverdadtaqueria.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.laverdadta...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great opportunity to meet and/or reunite with some Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors club members, learn about the club and the various events we have that go on during, and outside of, ski season.  We can tell you more about what it's like to stay at our house and talk about a good time for you to come up for a visit!  Actually, the weekend following our happy hour will be a great time to make a first (or second, or third) trip to Mt. Washington Valley for a stay at Wedeln!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come thirsty, leave informed...and if you've already been out skiing or riding this season, be prepared to brag!  Others will surely be jealous!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring friends!&lt;br /&gt;Happy Holidays!  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Wedeln event when you get there (pronounced "VAY-dah-lin")</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263081108000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261621321000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wedeln Prime Season Kick Off Party--La Verdad Taqueria</name><id>12140786</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262818800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/12140786/</event_url></item>