<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Boston area is filled with academic superstars - so why not bring them to the movies? With Science On Screen, the Coolidge presents a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting introductions by noted scientists in a related field. Previously, Meetup members have attended and enjoyed Science on Screen events for Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind and A Clockwork Orange. The speakers provide  a good scientific framework that helps inspire good conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Often referred to as one of the scariest films ever made, Kiyoshi Kurosawa's PULSE (2001) tells the story of a group of young friends rocked by the sudden suicide of one of their own, and his subsequent, ghostly reappearance in grainy computer and video images. Is their friend trying to contact them from beyond the grave, or is there something much more sinister afoot? The mysterious floppy disk they find in the dead man's apartment may provide a clue, but instead launches a program that seems to present odd, ethereal transmissions of people engaged in solitary activities in their apartments. But there is something not quite right in the appearance and behavior of these lonely souls. Soon, there are more strange deaths and disappearances within the group, terrifying rooms sealed in red tape, and the appearance of more ghosts as the city of Tokyo -- and the world -- is slowly drained of life.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Alan Lightman is a physicist, novelist, and essayist born in Memphis, Tennessee in 1948. He is professor at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and the author of the international bestseller Einstein's Dreams. His research articles have appeared in the Physical Review, the Astrophysical Journal, Reviews of Modern Physics, Nature, and other journals. His latest novel, Ghost (to be released Oct 23), tells the story of David, an ordinary man who experiences an extraordinary vision that no science can explain. David's struggles to understand what has happened to him serves as springboard for a provocative exploration of the delicate divide between the physical world and the spiritual world, between skepticism and faith, between the natural and the supernatural, and between science and religion. After the screening, Lightman will be on hand to sign copies of his book.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Science on Screen programs are $7.75 for students, Museum of Science members, and seniors, and $9.75 regular admission. Members of the Coolidge Corner Theatre get free admission to these shows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be hosted by Nicole, who will be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater during the credits. After the film, will head off to JP Licks for coffee, ice cream and discussion&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193871848000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191261681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science on Screen: Pulse</name><id>6464542</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193698800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6464542/</event_url></item>