<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>915 Walden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.439850</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Walden Pond State Reservation</name><city>Concord</city><id>669174</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.333939</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join me for a  4.0 mile trail run starting and ending at Walden Pond. The route begins along the pond shoreline. About halfway around the pond we will cross the railroad tracks into Lincoln woods. We'll run on multiple trails on a nice loop and finish back where we started from on the pond loop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trails are fairly level with limited rocks and roots and the pace will be approximately 9 min/per mile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the run we'll cool off with an optional swim in the pond. Some of the runners bring towels and swim gear while some of us just go in the water in our running gear. It's really your call. The reservation has changing rooms near the main entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual we'll be joining the friendly folks of "Waltham Trail Runners" meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Parking fee at the reservation is $5. There are also places to park at Concord high school (across RT 2). It's about a half mile away from the pond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We'll meet in front of the gift shop (which is next to the parking lots on Rt 126)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in front of the gift shop near the main entrance to the Pond.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul</member_name><member_id>4878639</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343654631000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342582245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walden Pond Trail Run/Swim</name><id>73820472</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343566800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/73820472/</event_url></item>