<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.227803</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.540063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's always hard to schedule a full-moon paddle.&amp;nbsp; Even though the moon rises at a set time, it takes it a while to get above the trees so we can see it.&amp;nbsp; On the actual date of the full moon (July 15), it rises in conjunction with the sunset.&amp;nbsp; That would be beautiful if you had an unobstructed view to the east and west and a clear sky. Taking our venue, moonrise time and the weather forecast into consideration (plus my schedule), I have planned this meetup.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;This trip is not suitable for beginners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Sunday night (forecast to be clear) the moon rises at 4:09 PM and it will be at its highest point in the sky at around 9:00 PM,&amp;nbsp; 79% illuminated. &amp;nbsp; Sunset is at 8:22.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be in your kayak and ready to paddle by 7:45.&amp;nbsp; This will give people a chance to admire the area before it gets dark.&amp;nbsp; Expect to spend about 2 hours on the water.&amp;nbsp; Required equipment will be a whistle, flashlight or headlamp (check your batteries before you leave home) and a properly fastened PFD to be worn at all times.&amp;nbsp; We will paddle in complete darkness with our only light from the moon.&amp;nbsp; Massachusetts law only requires using your flashlight or headlamp in time to avoid a potential collision.&amp;nbsp; Paddling without the headlamps will avoid being "blinded" by other paddler's lights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The boat launch is on route 135 between Westborough and Hopkinton Centers.&amp;nbsp; Use the intersection of Dale Road and Route 135 in Hopkinton if using a GPS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.&amp;nbsp; The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.&amp;nbsp; Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Ramp</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310495041000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310063834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle under almost full moon</name><id>24916911</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310341500000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/24916911/</event_url></item>