<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>43 Broad Street, Suite A408</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01749</zip><lat>42.388719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 562-5858</phone><name>Alt E Store</name><city>Hudson</city><id>1069740</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.563881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>September MeetUp at Alt Energy Store&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Greetings to All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope everyone had a good summer and I look forward to helping broaden our horizons through networking as we head toward 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did not schedule summer Meetups for July &amp;amp; August because of hectic summer schedules and other family activities that I was reminded of by several our members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our September Meetup is set for September 24th at the Head Quarters of www.AltEstore.com in Hudson, MA. Alt Energy Store started about ten years ago with just a few people and has grown to have a large internet presence, about 35 employees and three offices.  Alt E Store provides all things solar &amp;amp; wind including “Do It Yourself” live classes, webinars and a big selection of educational books &amp;amp; videos.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us at the Head Quarters in Hudson from 6:30 to 7:30 pm Thursday evening. Our hosts will be two of the founding members of the Alt Energy Store, Nick Albright from the Ohio office and Sascha Deri from the office in Costa Rica.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alt E Store&lt;br /&gt;43 Broad Street, Suite A408&lt;br /&gt;Hudson, MA 01749&lt;br /&gt;978 562-5858&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 495: Take Exit 25A onto Hudson Street. Go about one mile to the 2nd set of stop lights and take a left onto Route 85. Take your first right onto Broad Street. Follow Broad Street for about 3/4 of a mile. On the left hand side after you cross a small bridge you should see a large brick building, known as the Hudson Mills Building, 43 Broad Street. Park in the front and take the main lobby elevator to the 4th floor. The office is on the far Southeast side of the building. Follow the signs to find your way. Please try to be early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glenn P DeRosa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>4th Floor - Board Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glenn P DeRosa</member_name><member_id>4460952</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256079397000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Energy Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1402</urlname><id>654497</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Green Business Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253325040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September MeetUp at Alt Energy Store</name><id>11410373</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253831400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1402/events/11410373/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/f/global_5353295.jpeg</photo_url></item>