<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Grafton Village Cheese Company, 400 Linden St, Brattleboro, VT 05301</address_1><state>Ve</state><lat>42.863266</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Grafton Village Cheese Company, 400 Linden St, Brattleboro, VT 05301</name><city>Brattleboro</city><id>8491862</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.567215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will paddle Retreat Meadows and the Connecticut River if we choose. Retreat Meadows is an easy quite water paddle at the meeting of the West and CT Rivers. With lots of varying habitats, inland islands and some protected refuge, this is a great site for wildlife photos. We will surely see beavers, Canadian Geese, King Fishers and several different birds of prey. Motor boat traffic is allowed on the CT River, but not in the "meadows" water except to park at the Marina.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a 2 -3 hour paddle we will moor up at the Marina Restaurant for a leisurely lunch or dinner on the patio overlooking the water and our boats. We will end with a 1/2 hr easy paddle back to the launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marina Restaurant &lt;a href="http://www.vermontmarina.com/index.html%3Cbr%20%3E%3C/a%3E"&gt;http://www.vermontmarina.com/index.html &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; Rt 5, Putney Road Brattleboro, Vermont &lt;br /&gt;

 802-257-7563 &lt;br /&gt;

 Open for lunch and dinner 7 days a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Bringing Boats:&lt;/strong&gt; This group will put in at the Rt. 30 launch across from the Grafton Cheese Factory. Parking is on the road. After coordinating a meeting spot on the water, one person (likely me) will round up the group putting in at the Rt.5 rental launch. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Map:&lt;/strong&gt; 400 Linden Street, Brattleboro, VT 05301&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renting:&lt;/strong&gt; (see below). This group will go to the Rt. 5 launch at the rental place on the northbound side of Rt. 5, located on the north side of the bridge (there's a rusted train bridge on your right). Parking is across the street in the mini-mall on the southbound side of Rt. 5. One person (likely me) will come from the Rt. 30 launch and guide this group to an on the water meeting place with the rest of the group. This group can return their boats before or after dining as they choose. Returning before only requires you walk across Rt. 5 (to where your car is parked) and continue walking through this parking lot to the restaurant - a 5 minute walk. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Map:&lt;/strong&gt; 451 Putney Road (Rt. 5), Veterans Memorial Bridge at West River&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak Rentals (no website) &lt;br /&gt;

 802.257.5008 &lt;br /&gt;

 vtcanoe@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;

 Open: 7 days a week, 10am - 7pm or by appt before Memorial Day or after Labor Day&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Kayak (PFD &amp;amp; paddle included) &lt;br /&gt;

 $20 2 hrs &lt;br /&gt;

 $30 4 hrs &lt;br /&gt;

 $40 Full day&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Canoe (PFD &amp;amp; paddle included - based on 2 people. Add $5 for third person) &lt;br /&gt;

 $25 2 hrs &lt;br /&gt;

 $35 4 hrs &lt;br /&gt;

 $45 Full day&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347281281000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343784401000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle Retreat Meadows</name><id>75779002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347206400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/75779002/</event_url></item>