<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>292 Boston Post Road/Rt. 6</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06256</zip><lat>41.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-456-2659</phone><name>Willi Bowl</name><city>North Windham</city><id>222583</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.120003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Nutmeg Big Brothers/Big Sisters (BBBS) Program is having its annual Bowl for Kids' Sake on Saturday, March 24. There are bowl-a-thons at 3 different locations in CT that day, but EDEMG members will be at the one held at Willi Bowl in Willimantic. Bowling &amp;quot;shifts&amp;quot; are at 1pm and 3pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not familiar with BBBS, it is a great mentoring program for children who come from situations in which there is a single parent, a divorced home, or a troubled home in general. I have been a Big Sister for the past 3 years, and it has been an incredibly awarding experience. I am serving on the planning committee for the Eastern Nutmeg BBBS region's Bowl for Kids' Sake this year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of 2006, Nutmeg BBBS (along with many other CT agencies) was informed that they would not be receiving their usual $300,000 grant from the State in 2007. This is about 1/6 of the agency's budget. As a result, the Bowl For Kids' Sake is an especially important event this year. We hope that you will either participate in the Bowl-a-thon or will support other EDEMG bowlers through sponsorship. Kenny T. and Michelle already plan to bowl several strikes at this event! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPARE the time for three simple steps to join us!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to bowl: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Register in advance (online at www.nutmegbigbrothersbigsisters.org, or contact Michelle for a Sign-up Form). Bring a friend or form a team. A team can be 4-5 bowlers. Ask your family, friends, and co-workers - anyone you know - to join you. &lt;br /&gt;2) Spread the word, raise money, and get others involved! When you sign up online, you can create your own web page and email your friends. A link in your email allows them to charge a contribution online through a secure site.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each bowler must raise or contribute the minimum contribution fee.  &lt;br /&gt;-Adults: Raise or contribute $75.00 or more &lt;br /&gt;-NBBBS Mentors and Bigs: Raise or contribute $50 or more &lt;br /&gt;-Student: Raise or contribute $40.00 or more &lt;br /&gt;-Littles (Kids with NBBBS mentors):  Free when accompanied by an adult.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Enjoy a day of fun to BOWL you over! Each registered bowler plays two games and will receive a t-shirt, shoes rental, pizza and soda. There will also be raffles, music and prizes! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope that several EDEMG teams are formed to take on the organizers (bring it!), or that you will consider sponsoring a team.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To sponsor Kenny T. and Michelle's team, The Big Lebowskis, use this link:&lt;a href="https://www.kintera.org/faf/search/searchTeamPart.asp?ievent=219897&amp;amp;lis=1&amp;amp;kntae219897=A75260483D364A4583C7453A3A278AFD&amp;amp;supId=162531784&amp;amp;team=1778128" target="_blank"&gt;Team Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540955000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1170099058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bowl for Kids' Sake--Nutmeg Big Brothers/Big Sisters Fundraiser</name><id>5435204</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174755600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5435204/</event_url></item>