<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Water Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810606</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tannery</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1003074</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.866203</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;COME ONE, COME ALL! JOIN THE 2009 YANKEE HOMECOMING CELEBRATION!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YANKEE HOMECOMING PARADE&lt;br /&gt;High Street&lt;br /&gt;Admission free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;UPDATE:  Sorry guys but I forgot that Newburyport is having their Farmers Market on Sunday at the Tannery, so when you try to park in the lot you may need to park on the back side, meaning the side that the Nutcracker Bakery is at, it's the same row of building just the other side of the Tannery. Or anywhere on Federal Street that you can find a spot, sorry for the late update!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt; We are still meeting at the River Merrimack Restaurant!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginning at Three Roads on Storey Ave and continuing down High Street to Marlboro Street, Newburyport is sure to be lined with spectators for the 51st annual Yankee Homecoming Parade. Fire engines will start at 12:15 pm, followed by Grand Marshall Arline Patricia Sayward and General Chairman Kathleen Bailey.  Donations will be collected during the parade to support the Jimmy Fund, a Yankee Homecoming Tradition!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a very popular event, people come from all over to see this parade!  People will start lining up their chairs on High Street on Friday.  the earlier you can get to the meeting place the better parking spot you can get and the better we can get a front row seat.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to children of all ages, and remember to bring a chair or a blanket to sit on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to put your RSVP in for this event.  I might email everyone the day before the event with any updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seeing that this is a popular event in Newburyport we will only wait until 15 minutes after the meetup time then we will head to set up our chairs, if you are not able to make it by the meeting time please email me and I will give you my cell so you can call me and find us.  Parts of High Street will close to traffic as the parade gets going so again if you are running late you may have a hard time getting to us.  We will meet at the Tannery on Water Street, there is plenty of free parking and then there is about a 3-5 minute walk to High Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside River Merrimac</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249838221000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246706771000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come watch the parade!!!!</name><id>10800614</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249227000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10800614/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>