<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join fellow Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for our unprecedented 2nd visit to Strawberry Faire for Brunch!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be dining out for lunch at The Strawberry Fair Restaurant in Norwell on Sunday, April 6th.  Located on Route 228, a few yards from Route 53 and less than a mile from Route 3 at Queen Anne's Corner, the Restaurant has grown from a store into a quaint 3-room restaurant appropriately decorated with strawberries.  Strawberry Fair Restaurant offers a wide variety of food sure to please everyone's palate.  Entrees range from $5-$12.  For more information about The Strawberry Fair Restaurant please visit the website at www.thestrawberryfair.com.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy.  This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: This restaurant does not accept reservations.  We may have to wait up to 20-30 minutes.  Incomplete parties will not be seated.  The Organizers plan to arrive 10-15 minutes early to get our name on the waitlist.  We would appreciate anyone who can arrive a few minutes early to do so.  If you will be more than 15 minutes late please call the restaurant or one of the Organizers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash.  You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items.  Please plan to arrive a few minutes early to sign-in so we may be seated on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brunch&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, April 6th @ 1pm&lt;br /&gt;Strawberry Faire Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;14 Pond Street&lt;br /&gt;Route 228&lt;br /&gt;Norwell, MA 02061&lt;br /&gt;781-878-7878&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela and Mike&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Max of 12 people.  (Please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only if you are 99% sure you can attend.)&lt;br /&gt;Guests: None.  Group Members Only&lt;br /&gt;Fees: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 2pm on Saturday, April 5th.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions: From Rt 3&lt;/b&gt;, take Exit 14 and head North on Rt 228 towards Hingham/Nantasket. Follow Rt 228 for 1/2 mile to the intersection with Rt 53. Just before you come to the intersection, you will see a Saab dealership on your left. Strawberry Fair is the very next business on your left; a light yellow building with white trim. The driveway is on the near side of the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heading South on Route 53:&lt;/b&gt; Driving through Hingham, heading towards Norwell, you will pass Asian C (Chinese/Asian restaurant), then a Firestone dealership (both will be on your right). The next traffic light is the intersection of Routes 53 and 228 - turn right onto Route 228 (Pond St.) As you turn onto Route 228, you will see a Chili's restaurant on your right. The next building (light yellow with white trim) on your right is Strawberry Fair. The driveway is on the far side of the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heading North on Route 53:&lt;/b&gt; Driving through Norwell, heading towards Hingham, you will pass a Taco Bell, then a Hannaford Supermarket on your left, followed by a Kentucky Fried Chicken restaurant on your right. The next traffic light is the intersection of Routes 53 and 228 - turn left onto Route 228 (Pond St.) As you turn onto Route 228, you will see a Chili's restaurant on your right. The next building (light yellow with white trim) on your right is Strawberry Fair. The driveway is on the far side of the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If it's a nice day please meet us out back near the patio/seating area off the parking lot.  Otherwise, we will either be inside the doorway or near the hostess station.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207957458000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><why>You voted it your #1 Favorite Brunch Restaurant!</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205872899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Favorite Brunch: Strawberry Faire Restaurant</name><id>7558094</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207501200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7558094/</event_url></item>