<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Central Square</address_2><address_1>24 Pearl St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364033</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 354-8881</phone><name>Rangzen Tibet Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669154</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103241</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here we go again. I'm in the mood. Are you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Affordable family style dining in Central Square...many vegetarian dishes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a 1999 review which gives a sense of the cuisine:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://72.166.46.24/archive/food/99/06/03/RANGZEN_TIBETAN.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://72.166.46.24/a...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are not accepted so please be prompt so you can be seated with us&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Green Street Garage which is diagonally across from Rangzen has parking for $2 per hour&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA.com :&lt;br /&gt;Train: Central Square on the Red Line&lt;br /&gt;Bus: 1, 77, &amp;amp; 84 to name a few&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RULES for ENGAGEMENT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly for events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your expenses, which are mainly meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend an event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If an event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed. If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If an organizer changes you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must contact the organizer directly by calling or texting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An organizer will arrive at least fifteen minutes before the event to confirm seating as well as welcome diners.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a one room restaurant so it should be easy to see our Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204564027000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><why>All you can eat lunch buffet for less than $10</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203197349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rangzen Tibetan Lunch</name><id>7344232</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204390800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7344232/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/6/global_3242358.jpeg</photo_url></item>