<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 2 mile hike that is a nice and easy loop passing by a couple ponds. A wonderful way to start the morning in this fall like weather!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Osbornedale State Park is located in the Naugatuck Valley Hills just east of the Housatonic River in Derby and Ansonia. The land was once the lushly forested hunting grounds of the Paugussett Indians. The land was gradually purchased from the Paugussetts and new settlers cleared the land for farming. Though never commercially successful, lands now within the park off Silver Hill Road were mined for silver for a short period after the Revolutionary War. In addition, a spring water bottling business was part of the present park land.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the parking area on the left of the main entrance (near the pond, see the park map) by 9 AM sharp. There is no fee for parking. The hike is anticipated to take about 1 hour and should be done by about 10 AM. A trail map can be found at the park link provided. The hike will follow the Red trail in a clockwise loop starting south of Pickett's Pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Map for parking and trails&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/maps/osbogis.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** No parking or park fee **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions...&lt;br /&gt;From Route 8 south:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 17&lt;br /&gt;* Take a left at the end of the exit ramp&lt;br /&gt;* Take another left at the lighted intersection (Division Street)&lt;br /&gt;* Drive approximately ¾ miles&lt;br /&gt;* Osbornedale State Park will be on the right across from Derby High School&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Route 8 north:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 18&lt;br /&gt;* Take a left at the end of the exit ramp&lt;br /&gt;* Drive approximately ½ mile&lt;br /&gt;* Osbornedale State Park will be on the right across from the Derby High School&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PETS:&lt;br /&gt;Pets on a leash are permitted in picnic areas and on hiking trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/osbornedale.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/osbornedale.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540513000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1157714096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kevin's Hike at Osbornedale SP in Derby CT</name><id>5119223</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1157806800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5119223/</event_url></item>