<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you havent paid up, well, ya might not get in..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JULY 18 2009 EVENT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may have to contact Barbara and bribe her with ..something good..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like a good weekend so far as of July 13..things change though..we will have a few pop up canopees there also..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Write up:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Friendship at the Lake with Food, Activities and Boating.  See below.&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 18, 2009:  10AM to whenever.&lt;br /&gt;If you are planning to attend the daytime get to gether, &lt;br /&gt;please send a check for &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$10.00 made out to &lt;br /&gt;Barbara Giamattei, 3 Stephanie Court, Madison CT  06443.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will cover your entrance to the facility, papergoods and &lt;br /&gt;charcoal and some beverages.  Rowboats, canoes, and kayaks are &lt;br /&gt;included in this price.  Please send a check for $10.00 by July &lt;br /&gt;10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAMPING AND ATTENDING THE PARTY&lt;br /&gt;If you are planning on also attending the campout then the &lt;br /&gt;price will be &lt;br /&gt;$15.00 per person.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please send to above address.  If you are &lt;br /&gt;camping you need to send me this money right away.  There are &lt;br /&gt;only 8 sites and if we want them we need to book them &lt;br /&gt;immediately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Right now two sites are booked.  I would be happy to book more &lt;br /&gt;sites, but need   prepayment to ensure reimbursement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to phone me with questions,  203 314 9121 or &lt;br /&gt;bg3step@comcast.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you all and having what promises to &lt;br /&gt;be a great time!&lt;br /&gt;The camping cost can be shared among those that attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Private pristine lake and picnic area, owned by Yale University in East Lyme CT.&lt;br /&gt;Nestled on mile long Powers Lake, surrounded by 1500 wooded acres.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Picnic Pavillion, beach front with doc and raft. &lt;br /&gt;Activities Available:   Fishing Dock, Horseshoes, Basketball, Volleyball, Pingpong room, Hiking trails.&lt;br /&gt;Also available included in the price are free use of canoes, rowboats, and kayaks, LIfe jackets are available and required.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Since we will be having a &amp;quot;pot luck&amp;quot; please bring either a desert or side dish to share (for approx 8 people); and please bring your own grilling item.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will supply the charcoal and paper goods.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Oh, and please remember to RSVP.  Thanks!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions and brochure:  &lt;a href="http://www.yalebulldogs.com/facilities/facoec.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yalebulldo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by a member who works at Yale&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Questions:  email bg3step@comcast.net&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Updated closer to the event day.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95 North:&lt;br /&gt;to Exit 71 (Four Mile River Rd -- East Lyme), turn right off exit ramp and continue 1-1/2 miles to end of the road. Turn right onto Route 1, continue another 1-1/2 miles, turn left onto Scott Road. Continue two miles to front entrance on right side of the road. Follow dirt road 3/4 mile to check-in station and lakeside parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional Camping Feature:  Two overnight campsites have been reserved and will be available on a first come first serve response.  We will chip in for the sites which will be a very nominal charge.  Please note that there are very clean outhouses available/ a private bathhouse with hot/cold water.  If you'd like to camp, then please RSVP in advance to secure your space.   If we find that additional sites are needed we will try our best to book additional sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok this sounds like a good day to play in the water especially for those that dont have boats.&lt;br /&gt;Im not sure i will bring all my boats, maybe..will have to see, but will bring all the other party stuff.&lt;br /&gt;Gas grille, and fire pit if looks like no wood available..maybe some other interesting things..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1253195926000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244137871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>.Powell Lake Event at Yale Nature Ctr</name><id>10576244</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247922900000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10576244/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_5044665.jpeg</photo_url></item>