<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2345 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02466</zip><lat>42.346901</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-969-1000</phone><name>Newton Marriott</name><city>Auburndale</city><id>218993</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.258347</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ready for Spring?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some say it's already here, but I know there are many who are counting the days til the breeze turns sweet and the thermal layers come off. I sure am! With that I am posting the first event for Twisted Touring in 2012 very near to our historic opening day, the first day of spring!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully the weather for this event on March 24th will be as nice as it was today (Feb 1st ~ 60 Degrees!) We will descend on the Marriott Riverside Lounge for breakfast. Before &amp;amp; after we'll show and tell about our scooters. Get out the Plexus &amp;amp; chamois and make your ride shine then come and show it off, make friends and influence those looking to upgrade or get in the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have non-scooting friends thinking of buying, this is a great opportunity for them to get it straight from the horses mouth and see scooters in their natural setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breakfast is $20 for the buffet, though you can get less expensive things - not the greatest food, but they have lots of seating and big tables. We have had groups as large as 15 other years, lets do it again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;
So the plan is to ride up to Gloucester after breakfast, I'll be staying there and send you all off on you own adventures. We'll take 95 up to 128, 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the bunch of scooters in the back of the parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333986191000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328145781000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opening Day Show &amp; Tell</name><id>50654712</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332597600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/50654712/</event_url></item>