<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beverly rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quinsigamond College Track</name><city>Worcester</city><id>297088</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We need walkers to walk the track all night and day...here is the website to check it out all the great things that happen from the &lt;a href="http://www.relayforlife.org/relay/se" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.relayforli...&lt;/a&gt; walks.&lt;br /&gt;The event name is RFL of Worcester, Team captain is Marie Remillard, Team name is Hanover...use the link above and go to find an event put in worcester and you can register there...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't walk you can make a small donation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have questions please email me maybe we can have a quick meeting before next weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relay For Life® of Worcester is a fun-filled overnight event designed to bring together those who have been touched by cancer in our community. More than 200 Relays will be held throughout New England in 2007, all celebrating survivorship and raising money to help the American Cancer Society in its mission to save lives, help those who have been touched by cancer, and empower individuals to fight back. During the event, teams of people gather at schools, fairgrounds, or parks and take turns walking or running laps. Each team member pays a registration fee of $10 and is expected to raise a minimum of $100. Each team tries to keep at least one team member on the track at all times. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But, Relay is much more than a walk around a track. It is a time to remember those lost to cancer and celebrate those who have survived. It is a night for people who have shared the same experience to comfort and console one another. During this event, we honor survivors during the Survivors Lap and we remember those we lost to cancer during the Luminaria Ceremony. We also celebrate life, friendship, and a chance to work together toward a cancer-free future. Most importantly, Relay gives you the power to help in the fight against cancer. By joining together as volunteers and donors, our efforts help the American Cancer Society strive toward a future where cancer doesn?t take the lives of our friends and family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register today to become a part of the Relay phenomenon and fundraise online. Official team packets can be picked up at team meetings (see Event Schedule to the left) or by contacting your local American Cancer Society (ACS) office. Team Captains should contact your ACS office in order to ensure you are included in important information. Together we will fuel the work ? and the hope ? that can help make a cancer-free of the future.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541362000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177976241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>American Cancer Society Relay for Life</name><id>5726588</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181412000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/5726588/</event_url></item>