<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2861 Fairfield Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06605</zip><lat>41.157110</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203 . 814 . 6856</phone><name>The Gallery At Black Rock</name><city>Bridgeport</city><id>958918</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.226795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Anyone who attended the show Industrial Strength will tell you we were all drawn to Ambers work, lets see this exclusive show of Ambers work and meet her in person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Labyrinth&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amber Maida&lt;br /&gt;The Gallery at Black Rock is proud to present, Labyrinth. A solo exhibit featuring the paintings of Amber Maida. Opening June 4th, Artist Reception from 6 until 9 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;BRIDGEPORT -- If you like David Bowie, chances are you'll like the new Labyrinth solo show at the Gallery at Black Rock. The show opens with a reception for the artist, Amber Maida,  on Friday, June 4.&lt;br /&gt;Anyone who went to the White Space Gallery when it was on Chapel Street in New Haven has seen her work hanging by Dali's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;The Naugatuck artist's work has been featured in Art World News Magazine (September 2009) and Ink Magazine (January 2008). A suite of her paintings were selected by Richard’s of Greenwich for the 2009 Art to the Avenue exhibition in Greenwich.  Her work has also been in juried exhibitions at AIRS in New Haven, the Housatonic Museum of Art, the Silvermine Guild of Art in New Canaan and Lazy Pear Gallery in Montpelier, VT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;Her new body of work, “A Labyrinth Line Existence,” alludes to a quote from David Bowie’s interview on the 1993 “Black Tie White Noise” film. She plays Bowie's music often while in the studio.  &amp;quot;Bowie has been a strong influence on my work, which has developed into a visual vocabulary on the canvas,&amp;quot; Maida says. The work is simply stunning, particularly her mixed-media paintings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I create tactile counter-environments that express myth and uncover the mystery hidden within reality,&amp;quot; Maida explains. &amp;quot;I juxtapose dualities -- fragility/strength, ancient/contemporary, external/internal -- to exploit a tension...&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;&amp;quot;My materials are carefully chosen and strongly symbolic,&amp;quot; Maida continues. &amp;quot;My work contains recurring motifs and materials including golden labyrinths, fluid backdrops, crackled textures, vintage books, silks, feathers, eggshells, and line drawings of suspended worlds. I hope that my images take viewers deeper within their own realm of realization.&amp;quot;.  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;The Show opens on June 4 2010 and will run until July 23&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;Normal gallery Hours from Thursday through Saturday from 11 am to 5:30 pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask for Cathy or Eileen</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275862045000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271171087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Labyrinth - Reception</name><id>13169560</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275690600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13169560/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/f/global_15022399.jpeg</photo_url></item>