<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Skyline Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.282416</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Green Hill Park</name><city>Worcester </city><id>918893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.775371</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Every year, the Greater Worcester Humanists get together to get some sun and have a cookout! &amp;nbsp;We have burgers, hot dogs, veggie burgers for the morally superior, and lots of side dishes and wonderful desserts from the membership's fine chefs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Then, once we are all plump and satisfied, there's more time to get some sun and play outside. We have lively sessions of volleyball, frisbee, cricket, and whatever else we an find enough people to play. or, you can just sit back, soak it all in, and chat with friends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This year, we are doing things a little different. We are going to make this year's outing a special Father's Day event at a new location - Green Hill Park in Worcester! We are holding it on Sunday, June 19th from noon to four. &amp;nbsp;We would love for you to bring your whole family, whether you are a dad, you bring along your dad, or a special dad in your life. This is also our most kid-friendly event, so bring them along!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;So, we hope to see you all there - this event is free and open to members and non-members alike. This is also a great introductory event so feel free to invite that guy in the office who always asks about Humanism, or that friend who's been talking about wanting to hit a meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I'm passing around a sign up form for various things we will need, so please help make the event great by volunteering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you and your family there!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the ones grilling and chatting!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Lackey</member_name><member_id>7618967</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309787223000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>It's summer!  And we're social!</why><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305214009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Day Out at the Park</name><id>18120351</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308499200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/18120351/</event_url></item>