<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371369</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center for Digital Imaging Arts at Boston University</name><city>Waltham</city><id>723446</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236903</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone! In addition to being a beer fanatic I am a freelance filmmaker interested in morphing the two together. I just finished editing a film (see below the schedule of events for a blurb of the movie) that is screening at the Center for Digital Imaging Arts (CDIA) in Waltham. The Skellig, which is right down the street, is one of my favorite bars of all time (with a great beer list to boot) and I thought this would be the perfect opportunity to schedule a meetup. If you are not interested in watching the film, don't worry about it! You can meet us all at The Skellig anytime you want. Here is the schedule of events:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 - Meet at CDIA&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Film starts&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - Meet the filmmakers/network/hang out&lt;br /&gt;9:00 - Go to The Skellig and celebrate! &amp;quot;Celebrate WHAT?!&amp;quot; you ask? BEER!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Skellig&lt;br /&gt;240 Moody Street&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Film: BIRTH explores the benefits of natural childbirth and also the dangers mothers and babies are submitted to in today's high-tech and drug-filled maternity care environment. In the documentary, mothers who gave birth with drugs and other medical interventions, and subsequently birthed their babies naturally, share their experiences. In addition, childbirth experts give valuable information and enlightening insights about birth.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call me! Erin Gallagher - 339-306-6700</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237676973000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235685838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film Screening and Skellig afterparty!</name><id>9832461</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237503600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/9832461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/5/global_7469861.jpeg</photo_url></item>