<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Walk-In Registration</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Turning the Key:  Stop Sitting on your Assets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know that you could have tons of money available for your deals - right in your own backyard? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equity Expert, Pam Provo will be discussing how to use your own equity and other assets to safely and conservatively grow wealth, and triple your retirement assets! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She'll also cover strategies used by financial institutions and the affluent to help those at every economic level unlock the earning power of the assets they already have! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The strategies Pam shares not only open doors for funding deals, but also provide a great way to secure your financial future. Of note, she'll be speaking about:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*  Creating Millions by leveraging the &amp;quot;Idle Equity&amp;quot; in your properties &lt;br /&gt;*  Strategies used by the Ultra-Wealthy Banks that everyone should know &lt;br /&gt;*  Her three step system that will secure Your Financial Future &lt;br /&gt;*  Using your equity to reduce - and often eliminate - taxes &lt;br /&gt;*  Building equity faster and tripling your retirement assets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pam Provo is a Successful Asset Acquisition Advisor located in Shrewsbury, Massachusetts, and co-author of &amp;quot;Stop Sitting on Your Assets&amp;quot;. She was the Vice President of Provo Financial Services, Inc. for five years and has 15 years as a Consumer Advocate under her belt. She is passionate about helping people with fiscal responsibility, and even won the Worcester Business Journal's &amp;quot;Forty Under 40&amp;quot; Award in 2003 for business leaders who value giving back to the community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/6/" target="_blank"&gt;Pre-Register for Turning the Key&lt;/a&gt; and save $5.00!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3372062</member_name><member_id>3372062</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197158595000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193961969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turning the Key "Stop Sitting on your Assets!"</name><id>6659283</id><headcount>135</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196985600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/6659283/</event_url></item>