<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>City Hall Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357948</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston City Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>714754</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059172</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mayor Thomas M. Menino has announced that the city’s fifth annual Peace 2008 Hip Hop Festival, a free outdoor concert, will take place on Saturday, August 2, from 4 – 8pm on City Hall Plaza. The program will be headlined by hip-hop legend EMPD and will feature local up and coming acts. “I am delighted that this annual event has been such a great success,” said Mayor Menino. “Old school Hip Hop contains a strong positive message and it is our objective to deliver this message to our community. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The headliner this year is EPMD, one of the most prominent acts in East Coast hip-hop. Known for their massive underground hit “Strictly Business,” The group's brand of funk-fueled sample-heavy hip-hop proved to be a major force in the genre. In the late 80s and early 90s, the group was one of the top hip-hop acts on the live circuit. 1992 brought the hit song “Crossover.” The group split but got back together in the late 1990s. Recent hits include “The Main Event” and “Blow.” The group is once again a popular live draw.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Completing the headline is New Yorker Chubb Rock, known for the hit “Just The Two Of Us.” Also on this star-studded headliner program is Das EFX. Considered pioneers of the hip-hop movement the group’s debut album “Dead Serious” went platinum spawning hits such as “They want EFX” and “Straight out of the Sewer.” They are best known for making popular the ‘iggity’ prefix and the stream of consciousness of their lyrical delivery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local artists on the program include: Dorchester rapper, Acrobatik; dance troupe Static Noyze, Status Quo and Esoteric.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace 2008 Hip Hop is produced by the Mayor’s Office of Arts, Tourism &amp;amp; Special Events and sponsored by Scion, and Metro Boston. The Mayor’s Office of Arts, Tourism &amp;amp; Special Events is responsible for advancing the arts, tourism and culture in the city of Boston by providing advocacy, support, promotional and technical assistance, and by producing special events and public celebrations that reflect the city’s rich diversity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217878881000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216405156000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston 911 Truth @Peace 2008 Hip Hop comes to City Hall Plaza!!!! Show Up!</name><id>8365836</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217705400000</time><rsvp_limit>455</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/8365836/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>