<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 South Main St., Suite 100, West Hartford, CT 06107</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.758820</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wu Healing Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1626501</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.743515</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/2/5/8/event_105529752.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Vitality Express Referral Alliance is growing a network of more than 200 preventative health care providers in CT and growing nationally—including chiropractors, acupuncturists, massage therapists, Chinese herbals, Tai Chi, Qi Gong, Yoga, Life Coaches, dietitians, naturopaths, health food stores, herbal therapy, vegan restaurants, natural skin care &amp;amp; cleaning supply companies, as well as mind-body technicians (Reiki, medical intuitives, energy workers, psychics...etc)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This group will be meeting for an hour of intense networking. (The meeting will cancel if less than 3 people RSVP)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 minutes of introductions, also a speaker each week will share his or her unique healing abilities,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;30 minutes of exchanging our gifts (Chair massage, Reiki, Tui-Na, Sound Healing, hand treatments, palmistry...etc),&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20 minutes to exchange cards and become part of the alliance that will support you in marketing your gifts online and at events,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This alliance also will keep you connected with community and continue to refer you as you become a part of each clients healing support team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clients and anyone who would like to become a member of Vitality Express to  learn about alternative and complementary healing modalities are very welcome to join us...We have gathered a team of practitioners who are looking to connect and provide you with an affordable program so you can add preventative and complementary health care to you life. We thought it should be a part of your routine and we have made it possible through networking and the website. &lt;a href="http://www.vitality-express.com"&gt;www.vitality-express.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$10.00pp for use of healing space&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;when you RSVP please advise if you are bringing any equipment(massage/reflexology chairs etc) or if you need set up for any spa treatments...etc... Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Across from the West Hartford Town Hall on Main St. Free parking available until spaces are all taken</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vera</member_name><member_id>3058475</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334794695000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334276148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vitality Express Referral Alliance Networking and Healing Space</name><id>ddzcscyqgbxb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334790000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/60358462/</event_url></item>