<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Happy New Year everyone! With the new year, we bring new topics and new excitement to you, the Boston WordPress community. This month, we welcome the return of the 2-session meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ToolBox Session: Website Critiques (Kurt Eng)&lt;br /&gt;We will have 1 hour to critique as many of your sites as we can (5 minutes per site). Send us your site that you would like to have critiqued and everyone will have a say about your site, appearance, flow and content. But remember, take everything with a grain of salt. We are here to help you and give you tips and advice to improve your site. You will be asked to give us your site when you RSVP and we will choose about 20 sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dev/Design Session: Theming - From Design to WordPress (James Coletti)&lt;br /&gt;So you have a hand-drawn concept for your next website, or a fancy Photoshop mockup from a client, and you need to turn it into a working WordPress theme. Now what? It's been requested many times, and now we finally bring you a walkthrough of the basic art of theming WordPress. We'll take a basic, static design and code a working WordPress theme, incorporating a header, footer, blog posts, static pages, widgets, and WordPress 3.0 features like dynamic menus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda: &lt;br /&gt;7-7:30pm - Networking, Pizza &lt;br /&gt;7:30-7:45pm - Opening remarks, updates, any other business &lt;br /&gt;7:50-8:50pm - Sessions (Sampson/Paul) &lt;br /&gt;8:50-9pm - Wrap-up&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>James Coletti</member_name><member_id>7809368</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Eng</member_name><member_id>9694496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298941978000</updated><rating><average>4.84999990463</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>142</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294240441000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BWPM Jan 2011: Website Critiques (Toolbox) &amp; Theming (Dev/Design)</name><id>15927914</id><headcount>85</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296518400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/15927914/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/a/global_17306138.jpeg</photo_url></item>