<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Jesup Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06880</zip><lat>41.140418</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Levitt Pavilion </name><city>Westport</city><id>1042334</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.360560</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/f/0/event_133258352.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;OCTAVIO BRUNETTI TANGO ENSEMBLE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:15-9:30&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;they have decided to move the concert inside!!! see details below, I will still be attending as Ralph says, it is a pretty good place to see a concert....I will have on the black and white scarf with piano keys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RAIN LOCATION: The Auditorium at Saugatuck School, 170 Riverside Avenue. Call the Concert Hotline at 203-221-2153 at or after 4PM on the day of the show for location status. Note, no food or drink – other than water – is allowed inside the school. The auditorium is air-conditioned and has built-in seating. The dance lesson takes place even if the event is moved indoors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;One of the great Argentine tango pianists of our time leads a tango ensemble that thrills both dancers and listeners with its passionate, melodic, gorgeous sounds. Presented as part of the RiverSwing Series, evenings throughout the season on which a free pre-concert dance lesson, led by will professional instructors, is offered in the style &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/f/b/event_38459131.jpeg" width="69" height="50" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;of music about to be performed. RiverSwing Series is sponsored by Weston Capital Management, LLC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;Dance Lesson @ 7.15; Concert @ 8.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Octavio Brunetti&lt;/strong&gt; studied classical piano in his hometown Rosario, Argentina. Before graduated, he was already performing a variety of music styles, but the love for his country’s native tango prevailed and soon he was performing with many of Argentina’s most important tango musicians and singers, such as Alberto Castillo, Eladia Blazquez, Ruben Juarez, Domingo Federico, Rodolfo Mederos, Osvaldo Piro. He received two first prizes in a local festival as a composer and pianist of tango, performing his awarded piece, “Sencillez Tanguistica,” with the Orquesta Sinfonica de Rosario; and between the years 2002-2003 he was the conductor of the Orquesta Del Tango de Cordoba, Argentina.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;Mr. Brunetti moved to the United States in 2004 where his participation at the New York City International Tango Competition won him two first prizes: Best Solo Pianist and Best Duo (with Bernardo Monk, saxophonist).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #83674a"&gt;Since then, he has had a busy schedule as an arranger and orchestrator for several orchestras and chamber groups, as well as performing as a soloist and chamber player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will fly the black and white hellium balloons I will have on the black and white scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343444505000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340689225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OCTAVIO BRUNETTI TANGO ENSEMBLE</name><id>70769952</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343342700000</time><rsvp_limit>36</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/70769952/</event_url></item>