<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Beach Party ~ active SINGLES in their 30's - 50's! &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Association ~ Old Lyme, CT &lt;br /&gt;Private Residence (Gated Community) &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;We are asking everyone to bring enough food or drink for 4 to 6 people... &lt;br /&gt;There may be a request for a small contribution to offset some of the expenses... &lt;br /&gt;Please... no children or pets. &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;I have two grills, fire pit, and volleyball... &lt;br /&gt;It is two blocks to our private beach... &lt;br /&gt;The beach is between Sound View and Hawk's Nest Beach... &lt;br /&gt;There may be fireworks on the beach... TBD &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP to my email... &lt;br /&gt;Lynne Galipeau ~ lynnegalipeau@yahoo.com ~ my cell at (860)558-2046 or (860)434-7077 ~ &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Rte 9 South to end, &lt;br /&gt;go Left on Rte 95North &lt;br /&gt;- immediately over CT River, take first exit (#70 - Rte 156, Rte 1, Old Lyme). &lt;br /&gt;Right off exit, go 4 miles down Rte 156 to &lt;br /&gt;    South Shore Landing (commercial business) on Left - plenty of parking. &lt;br /&gt;#14 Miami Avenue is 4/10m further down on the right (gate will be up), 3rd house on Left (grey ranch). &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: You may wish to drop off your &amp;quot;stuff&amp;quot; at the party, then park and walk back to the house. &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Please RSVP to Lynne G. directly, indicating what you will be bringing. Remember, this is a private residnece, so she'll have to limit the number of attendees, as such, I suggest you RSVP ASAP! At last year's Memorial Day party, there were a few dozen participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Please post your RSVP on MeetUp and indicate if you need or are offering a ride to Car-poolers, but BE CERTAIN to RSVP DIRECTLY to Lynne, NOT Rob P. If you cancel, please inform Lynn directly, NOT Rob P.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lynne originally sent me this invitation via our &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; connection, but has graciously allowed me to post it on my MeetUp site. Again, this party is intended for active SINGLES in their 30's - 50's! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183741527000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183324868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SINGLES BEACH PARTY - Old LYME Private residence</name><id>5961378</id><headcount>43</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183568400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5961378/</event_url></item>