<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This has gotten pretty good reviews, and Sofia Coppola's work is always interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Academy Award-winning writer/director Sofia Coppola (Lost in Translation, The Virgin Suicides, Marie Antoinette) returns with Somewhere, a witty, moving and empathetic look into the orbit of actor Johnny Marco (played by Stephen Dorff). You have probably seen him in the tabloids; Johnny is living at the legendary Chateau Marmont hotel in Hollywood. He has a Ferrari to drive around in, and a constant stream of girls and pills to stay in with. Comfortably numbed, Johnny drifts along. Then his 11-year-old daughter Cleo (Elle Fanning) from his failed marriage arrives unexpectedly at the Chateau. Their encounters encourage Johnny to face up to where he is in life and confront the question that we all must: Which path in life will you take? Winner of the Golden Lion Award for Best Picture at the 2010 Venice International Film Festival. Original music score by the Grammy-winning French band Phoenix. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Like 'Lost in Translation' and 'Marie Antoinette,' 'Somewhere' is a study in gilded loneliness. And much in the way that 'Lost,' set in Japan, showed a debt to recent Asian cinema, so 'Somewhere,' which takes a voyage to Italy, betrays an engagement with the films of Michelangelo Antonioni. &lt;br /&gt;This is not a matter of imitation, but rather of mastery, of finding — by borrowing if necessary — a visual vocabulary suited to the story and its environment.&amp;quot; -- A.O. Scott, The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it on Saturday,&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294676154000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294198244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Somewhere</name><id>15923905</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294521300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15923905/</event_url></item>