<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Kendall Square</address_2><address_1>1 Cambridge Center, 10th Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362489</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-529-4266</phone><name>One Laptop Per Child</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1212564</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085338</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Not only is the CiviCRM Boston Meetup back in action, but we're back with a vengeance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLPC by-way-of Samuel Klein has been kind enough to provide us with the space for this meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So much has happened since we last convened and we have so much to catch each other up on. Civi's produced two new stable versions since we last met.*  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our colleague, the honorable Representative for Middlesex, Cambridge-Belmont-Arlington to the Commonwealth of Massachusetts's pilot CiviCRM architecture for GOTV and public service accountability has been received as so brilliant and useful that it has become a high priority in the Civi community to build a module out based on his effort. Under confidential terms, key members of the DNC data administration have expressed amazement -- and interest -- in what has been built and if there are ways to incorporate components of it into the VAN^&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;OLPC has a Drupal install in process we can all learn from, including a showcase of features Causecast has helped envision. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A stable Joomla 1.6 with its refined ACL system could be a game changer in CiviCRM utilization -- the last few betas have had more Joomla downloads then Drupal -- a striking and perhaps sustaining trend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We should talk about multi-system and duplicable installs: interest from our fellow meetup-practitioners working in Drupal and Joomla environments are savvy to dialogue about best practices in the matter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instead of organizing a pay-in take-out scheme, this time bring some food and we'll share. After, anyone interested might coalesce and find a nearby post-trendy meta-hipster dive bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to learning from you, Co-coordinator Kevin &amp;amp; by extension Riche, Tony and Eli&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;*Accolades to the solidarity of the EU Socialist movement and their support in creating an automated way to create printable name tags for any CiviEvent participant worldwide from here on out!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;^Our humble cell may just be the synapse that connects the institution that can fund the CiviEngage Module into existence! &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>elibeck</member_name><member_id>518656</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Novell</member_name><member_id>11247716</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tony Guzman</member_name><member_id>11514869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285234601000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-CiviCRM-Meetup</urlname><id>1462401</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston CiviCRM Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283809665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston CiviCRM Meetup: it's back -- stronger, faster, better, more.</name><id>14675925</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285108200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-CiviCRM-Meetup/events/14675925/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/f/global_8834671.jpeg</photo_url></item>