<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>142 Ferry Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06475</zip><lat>41.315003</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-510-0282</phone><name>Back Porch Restaurant</name><city>Old Saybrook</city><id>1014576</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.352275</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Betsy suggested going to the Back Porch restaurant in Old Saybrook. Its patio overlooks the CT river, has an extensive menu, and good entertainment on the weekends. Sounds fun, doesn't it?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet on the patio for drinks, dinner, and live music provided by Mass-Conn-Fusion. This group has gotten great local reviews, and starts playing at 8:00. The waitstaff has informed me that they don't really have large tables outside because of the fire pits and umbrella poles, but they will do what they can to accommodate us. Between the patio bar and tables, we should be fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****It's Friday at 4:00, and right now in Essex, the sun is out and it's very hot and muggy. So, the event is ON for tonight. We can dine on thei inside porch, where we can still see the river. The band starts around 8:00, and we can also check out the game room!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Give the hostess my name, and she will show you to our table. If you have any questions, please email or call my cell 860.227.7498  Keep your fingers crossed for good weather!!*****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check out their website at www.backporcholdsaybrook.com for more info, directions, and menus. It should be another great time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet on the patio; look for a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250286657000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>BBW/BHM and their Admirers.</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BigAttractions</urlname><id>667139</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Big Attractions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247875756000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset  on the Back Porch</name><id>10900928</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249079400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigAttractions/events/10900928/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/a/global_9713258.jpeg</photo_url></item>