<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1400 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373466</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Harvard Co-op</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>607202</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119300</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Alright guys, I'm making good on my threat to follow up last month's Scavenger Hunt with a tasting tour of Cambridge.  This is my old stomping grounds and I'm eager to see what establishments get included in the hunt (my humble way of saying, ya might wanna score me for your team:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the details from the Watson Adventures Newsletter:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Newsletter site: &lt;a href="http://watsonadventures.com/culture_boston.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://watsonadventur...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Munch Around Cambridge Scavenger Hunt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;You can literally taste victory on this hunt, as you see the best of Cambridge and Harvard while making stops along the way to sample tasty treats. Highlights include cricket lollipops, Revolutionary War bullet holes, Radcliffe Yard, ultra-rich hot chocolate, a tree of desserts, a famous blacksmith, Greek fries, the building an artist illegally tried to eat, a legendary book shop, bubble tea, the building where John Updike and Conan O'Brien got their start, carnivale crepes, Matt Damon's hangout and jalapeno ice cream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Price: $20 for one ticket.   In addition, bring $10 cash per person for food purchases. (We ask you to bring cash so that you can have a wide range of food options, to suit your taste and diet.) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our internal group sales office is now closed:-).  Thanks to everyone for all of their responses.   Currently the only option is to purchase your ticket on your own.   We will still meet in advance and can form teams then.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      Cost = $20.  Please order your ticket prior to RSVPing 'yes' and comment within your RSVP that your ticket has been purchased (or be prepared for emails of inquiry from moi:-)&lt;br /&gt;      Tix available at ovationtix: &lt;a href="https://www.ovationtix.com/trs/pe/350481" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.ovationti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If tickets are sold out, please contact Lisa directly:&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;doclmeet@yahoo.com&lt;/span&gt; to ensure no cancellations were made.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting in front of the Harvard Co-Op across the street from Out of Town News (and the Harvard Square T stop pit).  This location will be less chaotic than the pit itself, and provide some cover in case of inclement weather.  More details on how to find me, along with my cell phone number, will be sent directly to the yes's so make sure your RSVP's are accurate!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please plan on being there between 12:15-12:30.  At 12:45 we will head towards the Charles Hotel to meet with the rest of the Hunt participants, so if you're running late, let me know and we'll meet you there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am intrigued by the cricket lollipops.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to hunt with ya!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211291772000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><why>Hunting and Feasting.  It's an epic combination!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209060560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Munch Around Cambridge Scavenger Hunt</name><id>7804526</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211041800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/7804526/</event_url></item>