<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Harrison Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Encuentro5 (fifth floor)</name><city>Boston</city><id>610414</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The U.S. wars in Afghanistan and Pakistan are escalating. Saber-rattling against Iran is reaching dangerous levels. Extra-urban U.S. bases in Iraq are expanding in size and permanence.  Meanwhile the U.S. government refuses to use its power to break the siege of Gaza. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can we do here, in our region, to rebuild the movement and our ability to mobilize the antiwar majority?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come hear and discuss proposals for a one-day regional strategy session in January, for spring demonstrations, and for a large regional educational conference and plenary to call fall actions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perspectives on regional organization, education, and spring mobilizations.  Join a discussion initiated by coalition organizers from around the Northeast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hear:&lt;br /&gt;Joe Lombardo, Bethlehem (NY) Neighbors for Peace&lt;br /&gt;Lisa Savage, CODEPINK Maine Local Coordinator, PINKTank blogger: www.codepink4peace.org/blog&lt;br /&gt;Chris Gauvreau, Connecticut United for Peace&lt;br /&gt;John Harris, Greater Boston Stop the Wars Coalition and National Assembly liaison for the October 17 mobilizations  nationwide&lt;br /&gt;Cole Harrison, Afghanistan Task Force, Boston United for Justice with Peace and an organizer of October 17 march in Boston&lt;br /&gt;Mark Stahl, Rhode Island Mobilization Committee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business meeting to follow.  Planning for January Conference, spring mobilizations, and an April educational conference.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need you and your group, no matter what your group?s current size!  We are rebuilding. JOIN US!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257790773000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257434406000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What CAN We Do to Strengthen the Antiwar Movement?</name><id>11802522</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257616800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/11802522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/7/global_11654759.jpeg</photo_url></item>