<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ludcke Auditorium (looks like a church)</address_2><address_1>716 Stevens Avenue</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04103</zip><lat>43.683291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>University of New England</name><city>Portland</city><id>1388103</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.293858</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>donation</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;NEW DATE: FEB 15 DUE TO SNOW STORM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us for the next installment in our 2010|2011 "Bad News/Good News Movie Night Series, in which we will, in turn, immerse ourselves in some of the&lt;strong&gt; challenges of our time&lt;/strong&gt; and then &lt;strong&gt;explore the solutions at hand&lt;/strong&gt;.  The first three films (2010) could be considered the dark side and the next set of films after the new year will no doubt inspire, educate and motivate.  These films will be held the first Tuesday of each month on the campus of, and co-sponsored by, the University of New England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In February we continue with some inspiring fare with a showing of The Economics of Happiness, a film about the choices we are making and can make toward more localized and human-scale strategies.  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VkdnFYDbiBE" target="_blank"&gt;Here's the trailer.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"The Economics of Happiness describes a world moving simultaneously in two opposing directions. On the one hand, government and big business continue to promote globalization and the consolidation of corporate power. At the same time, all around the world people are resisting those policies, demanding a re-regulation of trade and finance&amp;mdash;and, far from the old institutions of power, they&amp;rsquo;re starting to forge a very different future. Communities are coming together to re-build more human scale, ecological economies based on a new paradigm &amp;ndash; an economics of localization."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This will be a potluck (bring an appetizer/snack or beverage to share for a grazing-style meal) and your potluck kit (plate/utensils/cup/napkin).  6:30 potluck and 7:00 announcements and film.  Discussion to follow.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lori Power</member_name><member_id>4201073</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297886995000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295373878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Bad News/Good News Movie Night Series: The Economics of Happiness</name><id>16093791</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297812600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/16093791/</event_url></item>