<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will meet at the Northampton end.  Bring your bike or walk a few miles ( yes I said m i l e s ).&lt;br /&gt;Pete's is about 3 miles from the Northampton end.  You can bike the 18 miles in 2 hours if you push it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This nine-milelong bikepath connects Amherst and Northampton, through Hadley, paralleling MA Rt. 8.5 and avoiding that heavily-traveled road. With its own bridge over the Connecticut River, it is the western end of the abandoned Central Mass. railway line, the eastern end of which is being considered for a Waltham to Hudson trail. A group in Belchertown is working on extending this path eastward, and there is a possible connection to a Connecticut Valley bikeway to New Haven, CT, on the Northampton end. A connection to the U.Mass. campus is also being considered. The state also has WWW information available. Pete's Drive-In in Hadley has a Web page touting its trail access. This network of bike paths, lanes and routes connects the towns of the Connecticut River valley in northern Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Norwottock Rail Trail is an 8.5 mile path linking Northampton, Hadley, and Amherst along the former Boston &amp;amp; Main Railroad right-of-way. The path's level terrain provides safe passage for pedestrians, wheelchairs, joggers, skaters, bicyclists, and cross-country skier of all ages and abilities. Motorized vehicles and horses are prohibited. Both ends of the path offer free parking for trail users ? Elwell State Park on Damon Road in Northampton and Station Road in South Amherst. Public restrooms are available at the parking area at Elwell Recreation Area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the east or west: Mass Pike (I-90) to exit 4, Rte 91 north to Rt 9 exit # 19. Through lights onto Damon Rd., parking at Elwell State Park on right. There is parking at both ends of the trail and on Route 9 in Hadley behind the Bread and Circus Market at the Mountain Farms Mall, at Station Road in Amherst and limited parking that provides wheelchair access at the junction of Mill Lane and Southeast Street in &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amherst.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North and South: &lt;br /&gt;From the North: Rte 91 south to exit # 20. At the bottom of the ramp-merge with traffic and enter Left lane.  Turn left at light-onto Damon Road.  Proceed ½ mile-parking is on the left at the Elwell Recreation Area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South:  Route 91 North to exit #19.  At the end of ramp- go straight through light.  Parking area is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Well I have a Blue Car, a Blue Mountain Bike, Blue sneakers, a Red Umass sweatshirt a Red Umass football hat.  I will be at the entrance by the information booth/rail bridge (Northampton side) You will look lost until you find me.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208790731000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We are a varied and very enteraining bunch of people.</why><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1514</urlname><id>824401</id><group_lat>42.0999984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5899963379</group_lon><name>Single Mingle Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206293398000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Norwottuck Trail - Hike and Bike</name><id>7587249</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208617200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1514/events/7587249/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/e/global_3300622.jpeg</photo_url></item>