<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1120 Chapel Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.308257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.432.1234</phone><name>Yale Repertory Theater</name><city>New Haven</city><id>875921</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.931451</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>11.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bossa Nova at Yale Rep&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Those interested in having a drink or a bite to eat before the show, meet us at Thai Pan Asian, at 6:00. Otherwise meet at the Rep at 7:20 for the ticket exchange.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thai Pan Asian&lt;br /&gt;1150 Chapel St&lt;br /&gt;NEW HAVEN, CT 06511 &lt;br /&gt;(203) 624-9689&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bossa Nova&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;World Premiere!&lt;br /&gt;By Kirsten Greenidge&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Evan Yionoulis&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yale Rep presents the world premiere of Bossa Nova, a poignant and powerful new play by Kirsten Greenidge, who has been praised for her “imaginative reach and affinity for rich dialogue” (The Boston Globe).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Dee Paradis has never fit in. Raised on the gentle swing of bossa nova and educated at elite, predominately white schools, she has led a life meticulously designed by her elegant and strong-willed mother, Lady. In the split second when she locks eyes with Lady in the mirror before a dinner party, Dee—nearly 30 years old and still torn between her mother's expectations and a former lovers ideals of authenticity—comes face to face with a choice that will determine her future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kirsten Greenidge's other plays include Sans-Culottes in the Promised Land (Actors Theatre of Louisville) and Rust (San Francisco's Magic Theatre). Resident Director Evan Yionoulis's most recent Yale Rep productions include The Master Builder and Richard II. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;parking map - &lt;a href="http://www.yalerep.org/resources/images/0910_parkingmap.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yalerep.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Street Parking:&lt;br /&gt;There is street parking available on Chapel, York, High, Park and Crown Streets. Meters charge $1.25/hour with a two hour limit until 7PM and accept nickels, dimes and quarters and the Parcxmart Card. The Parcxmart Card, which acts like a debit card, is available for purchase online or at many New Haven stores and restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chapel-York Garage&lt;br /&gt;Located at 150 York Street between Crown and Chapel Streets. Yale Rep Subscribers and Pass Holders receive coupons for parking discounts at the York/Chapel Garage. Patrons should present their parking coupons (distributed with tickets) to the attendant when exiting the garage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yale Center for British Art Lot&lt;br /&gt;Located directly behind the Yale Repertory Theatre at 153 York Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Central Parking System Garage (currently labeled as Kinney Systems garage)&lt;br /&gt;Located at 280 Crown Street at the Corner of High Street, and only a block and a half walk from Yale Repertory Theatre. Open during the daytimes only until 7PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking Express Lot&lt;br /&gt;Located on Howe Street (at Chapel Street). The Parking Express lot is two blocks walk to Yale Repertory Theatre.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby/will wear the BW Scarf with Piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291250000000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282940942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bossa Nova at Yale Rep</name><id>14565219</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291078800000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14565219/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/c/global_17498444.jpeg</photo_url></item>