<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm starting a monthly " 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Girl's Night&lt;/span&gt;"!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what are we going to do this this 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Girl's Night&lt;/span&gt;?! Whatever we decide! I'm hoping we'll have a theme for every month, and rotate to each others houses or to different locales. It'll be a great way to get out, make new friends, and have something to look forward to each month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the meeting, we will choose the date for the next Girl's Night, the location, the host, and the theme!
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; This Month's Girl's Night:
 &lt;br /&gt; 1. 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Date:&lt;/span&gt; Saturday, July 16th at 5pm
 &lt;br /&gt; 2. 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Location:&lt;/span&gt; Laura's House in Portland&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;*Address will be emailed out 1 week in advance
 &lt;br /&gt; 3. 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Host:&lt;/span&gt; Laura
 &lt;br /&gt; 4. 
&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Theme:&lt;/span&gt; Pirates
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; We'll hang out, eat yummy food, enjoy the ocean, and watch Pirates of the Caribbean!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Please come dressed in your best "Pirate" outfit!&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please sign up to bring one of the following by adding a comment when you RSVP:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. 
&lt;strong&gt;Goldfish.&lt;/strong&gt; Place goldfish crackers in various flavors on the tables as snack.
 &lt;br /&gt; 2. 
&lt;strong&gt;Swedish Fish.&lt;/strong&gt; Place a few pieces of Swedish fish gummy candy on each plate or attach to a piece of licorice to a straw and dangle into a cup filled with blue sports drink.
 &lt;br /&gt; 3. 
&lt;strong&gt;Caribbean Fruit Salad with Marshmallows.&lt;/strong&gt; Try this delicious 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/easy-hawaiian-luau-party-food-and-snacks/"&gt;Tropical fruit salad&lt;/a&gt; with mango, strawberries, kiwi, mandarin oranges and marshmallows. For a fun touch, use 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/resources/?psps_search=pirate+picks"&gt;sword party picks
&lt;img src="http://www.assoc-amazon.com/e/ir?t=teacakandtedb-20&amp;amp;l=as2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=B000W5JBEE" width="1" height="1" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ! important"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and let guests &amp;ldquo;stab their fruits to death&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;br /&gt; 4. 
&lt;strong&gt;Pirate Ship Sandwiches.&lt;/strong&gt; To make 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/mermaid-and-pirate-party-recipes/"&gt;pirate ship sandwiches&lt;/a&gt;, get sub sandwiches, cheese, salami and turkey.&amp;nbsp; Add in condiments, lettuce and tomatoes if you wish.&amp;nbsp; Print out free 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/pirate-sails/"&gt;pirate sails&lt;/a&gt; and use skewers to make sails.&amp;nbsp; Insert into sandwiches.
 &lt;br /&gt; 5. 
&lt;strong&gt;Pirate Grilled Cheese Sandwiches.&lt;/strong&gt; You will need two pieces of bread, cheese, and a pirate toast stamp.&amp;nbsp; Push the stamp firmly into the sides of the toast to make a pirate imprint.&amp;nbsp; Layer cheese on the inside and place in the toaster oven.&amp;nbsp; Set the temperature of the oven on medium.&amp;nbsp; Toast will come out light brown with a pirate imprint.
 &lt;br /&gt; 6. 
&lt;strong&gt;Pirate Pizza.&lt;/strong&gt; Make the dough like the shape of a skull and use pepperoni slices as eyes, mushroom as nose, and roasted red peppers as mouth.&amp;nbsp; Make 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/halloween-skeleton-bones/"&gt;Crossbones cheese breadsticks&lt;/a&gt; and place below the pizza skull head in a cross. &amp;ldquo;aRRRR Ye Famished yet?&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;br /&gt; 7. 
&lt;strong&gt;Cantaloupe Boats.&lt;/strong&gt; Make cantaloupe boats and add pirate masts on top just like the sandwiches.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/pirate-sails/"&gt;Download the pirate sails&lt;/a&gt; and simply use a skewer to insert them into the cantaloupe boats.
 &lt;br /&gt; 8. 
&lt;strong&gt;Ocean Blue Parfait.&lt;/strong&gt; Make pirate parfait with blue jello and gummy fish.&amp;nbsp; Top with white whipped cream sprinkled with blue sprinkles (for ocean waves) and a pirate flag toothpick.
 &lt;br /&gt; 9. 
&lt;strong&gt;Bone Bread Sticks.&lt;/strong&gt; Make 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/halloween-skeleton-bones/"&gt;bone bread sticks&lt;/a&gt; out of dough and dip in bloody marinara sauce.&amp;nbsp; Tell yer guests they taste bad to the bone!
 &lt;br /&gt; 10. 
&lt;strong&gt;Canon Balls.&lt;/strong&gt; Serve meatballs in Teriyaki sauce as canon balls. Stack them on several mini trays in pyramid style like canon balls ready for battle!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11. 
&lt;strong&gt;Treasure Chest Cake.&lt;/strong&gt; Make 2 loaf pound cakes and cut one in half lengthwise.&amp;nbsp; This part will be the lid of the treasure chest.&amp;nbsp; Place the other half on the bottom cake and ice together.&amp;nbsp; Place the lid on top and ice.&amp;nbsp; Decorate with fruit roll ups like leather chest buckles.&amp;nbsp; Place chocolate coins, and beads inside the treasure chest.&amp;nbsp; Decorate around the chest with brown sugar to look like sand.&amp;nbsp; Place gummy fish, star fish, chocolate shells, fondant 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/hibiscus-sugarpaste-flowers/"&gt;hibiscus flowers&lt;/a&gt;, and anything ocean or pirate related on the sand.
 &lt;br /&gt; 12. 
&lt;strong&gt;Pirate Ship Cake.&lt;/strong&gt; Make a large sheet cake and cut in half.&amp;nbsp; One half will be the ship.&amp;nbsp; Take the other half and cut out two triangles to make the front and back of the ship.&amp;nbsp; Ice the entire cake in chocolate icing.&amp;nbsp; Use large pretzel rods as masts and oars.&amp;nbsp; Pipe in yellow windows and add pirate figurines.&amp;nbsp; Download 
&lt;a href="http://www.toppartyideas.com/pirate-sails/"&gt;paper pirate sails&lt;/a&gt; and use skewers to hold in place.
 &lt;br /&gt; 13. 
&lt;strong&gt;Beer&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 14. 
&lt;strong&gt;Soda &amp;amp; Juice&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 15. 
&lt;strong&gt;Cheese &amp;amp; Crackers&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 16. 
&lt;strong&gt;An item of your choice&lt;/strong&gt;!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do not need to spend a lot. Our goal is to spend less than $20 for each item.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313437894000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289179829000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Girls Night! Theme: Pirates!</name><id>chcvpypkbmb</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310850000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/15648285/</event_url></item>