<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.359150</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 4, Room 231</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6010332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What does a second year commerce undergraduate, a blind man and a tribal woman have in common ? They can all be agents of change through the simple act of asking their government a question through RTI Act (Right To Information Act). Please join us to hear about these and other Stories from the Grassroots on how an AID Saathi, Pankti Jog, has been Transforming Lives through the Right to Information Act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pankti was born in a farming family in the Sonal district of Goa. Overcoming various hardships, Pankti graduated from Goa University in 1999 with a Masters degree. She then joined the National Institute of Oceanography in Goa as a research fellow. But Pankti's calling was elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pankti began an association with an NGO called Janpath in December 2001, where she volunteered to work on post-earthquake rehabilitation in Kutch. Today, she is one of the key program leaders with Janpath. She serves as their Advocacy Coordinator as well as coordinator for the Mahiti Adhikar Gujarat Pahel (MAGP).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The MAGP is a people's forum to enable good governance through the Right To Information (RTI) Act. In May 2006, MAGP launched the RTI helpline, the first of its kind in the country that enables quick intervention and guidance to any citizen throughout the state for making use of Right to Information. Till date more than 98000 calls have been received by this helpline. In recognition of its work, the helpline has also received a National Award. In March 2008, 'RTI on Wheels', India's first mobile RTI clinic was launched. Recognizing the enormous potential of this venture to bring RTI to the masses, AID funded the alteration and redesign costs for the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pankti draws upon vast levels of experience working at the grassroots as she aspires to address issues such as Right to Food, Right to Shelter and Livelihood in the context of tribal, nomadic and de-notified tribes. AID has also been proudly supporting Pankti Jog as an AID Saathi (or Fellow) for the last 3 years. &lt;br /&gt;

facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/242282129220934/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/242282129220934/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339967997000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339641495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Transforming lives through the Right to Information</name><id>69101882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339956000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/69101882/</event_url></item>