<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318722</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Frances Crowe community room</name><city>Northampton</city><id>8578042</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633698</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;On the day before the 10th anniversary of Senator Paul Wellstone's death, Valley 9/11 Truth plans to show some of the Snowshoe film documentary:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wellstonetheykilledhim.com/"&gt;Wellstone: They Killed Him&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The film examines the killers' means, motive and opportunity. High on the motive list is that Senator Paul Wellstone -- one of 23 senators who voted against the Iraq war -- was "sticking his nose into 9/11." Wellstone intimates say he was asking questions about 9/11...and thus was publicly executed as a warning.  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;They Killed Him&lt;/span&gt; at 10:18&lt;/strong&gt;, the plane is disabled, seven miles from the airport. The King Air A-100 turbo prop flies treetop level over shocked witnesses, five miles out: no lights, crabbed cockeyed, engines spooling down, so low witnesses are amazed it stays airborn. Three more miles and the plane stalls, dropping into the woods, killing all eight on board: &lt;strong&gt;Sen. Paul Wellstone (D-Mn), his wife Sheila, daughter Marcia, aides Mary McEvoy, Tom Lapic, Will McLaughlin, pilot Richard Conry and co-pilot Michael Guess.&lt;/strong&gt; How to account for the experienced pilots behavior, unless they had been disabled? But why would anyone go to such trouble to so publicly kill the senior senator from Minnesota? Cui bono? Who benefits? That’s the question VFW veterans in Willmar, Minnesota have. They heard the Senator tell of the threat Vice President Cheney made to Wellstone shortly after the Senator's No vote on the Iraq War. &lt;strong&gt;‘Go along with the program, if you know what’s good for you and Minnesota.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stop sticking your nose into 9/11.’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intimidation&lt;/strong&gt; was one tactic used by the FBI on witnesses who had been directed to the FBI (local cops were frozen out) which then suppressed their testimony, just as the FBI sanitized the crash site 8 hours before the NTSB came on the scene. The national media began the cover-up right away: bad weather, icing; that scenario didn’t work so the NTSB blamed it on the pilots. Though a high profile crash that many in Minnesota were skeptical about, the NTSB couldn’t afford to hold a public hearing; the truth would quickly become evident. This film, begun the day after the crash, gives voice to the people of the Iron Range: witnesses, first-responders, citizens, assassination experts such as Prof. James Fetzer and Four Arrows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.wellstonetheykilledhim.com/images/imgboxanddvd.jpg" width="200" height="234" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Filmmakers Interview by Kevin Barrett on &lt;a href="http://www.truthjihad.com/"&gt;TruthJihadRadio&lt;/a&gt; -&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://youtu.be/H4F9AzLVydc" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;click here to listen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Article-link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://minnesota.publicradio.org/projects/2010/wellstone-files/feature/"&gt;From protester to senator, FBI tracked Paul Wellstone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By &lt;a href="http://minnesota.publicradio.org/about/people/mpr_people_display.php?aut_id=30439"&gt;Madeleine Baran&lt;/a&gt;, Minnesota Public Radio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other film clips may be included, and hopefully heart-felt discussions, and perhaps we can discuss what we can do to honor this special Senator who spoke truth to power on October 25th, ten years later..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul Wellstone was killed in the midst of a grueling re-election campaign on Oct. 25, 2002 when his small chartered plane crashed near an airport runway. His death came 11 days before the election. His wife, Sheila, and daughter Marcia were on the plane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://images.publicradio.org/content/2010/10/25/20101025_wellstonegreenbus_33.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://images.publicradio.org/content/2010/10/25/20101025_wellstonegreenbus_39.jpg" alt="Larger view" width="347" height="230" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Paul Wellstone, D-Minn., and his wife Sheila jog to their campaign bus after casting their ballots in their hometown of Northfield, Minn.,Tuesday morning,Nov. 6, 1990.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(AP Photo/Jim Mone)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.wellstonetheykilledhim.com/images/imgwellstonecampaignsign.jpg" width="200" height="127" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In back of the Woodstar Cafe building on first floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351175953000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348675959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paul Wellstone, martyr for truth?</name><id>84186352</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351119600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/84186352/</event_url></item>