<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>My friend Ken asked me to post this on our site... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peruvian Andes Exploration  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two Peruvian Andes’ trekking experiences in the Cordillera Blanca Range for June 20 – 30, 2011 and the Cordillera Huayhuash Range for July 11 - 22, 2011 have been established to take the Meetup trekking adventurist into this pristine world of unsurpassed beauty. These two spectacular ranges are rated as some of the world’s most magnificent trekking routes. You will trek in the land of the Inca’s, be face to face with Peru’s most spectacular spiraling white-capped peaks, meet and interact with the warm, gentle, Quechua mountain people, see their stone-thatched dwelling in the natural environment in which they have lived for thousands of years as you capture the adventure travel experience of a life time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you seek to live your best now and want to crystallize your desire for a “national geographic” trekking experience, then this adventure is not out of bounds for you. I encourage you to sign-up now and experience the life-changing consequences of your decision. Want inspiration? Come preview these adventure treks on Tuesday, 11/30/10 at 6:00 PM (presentation starts at 6:30 PM). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vlora Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;545 Boylston Street &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02116 &lt;br /&gt;(617) 638-9699  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(www.vloraboston.com/directions) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Order a dinner and a drink if you like and enjoy yourself because both this Andes presentation and Vlora’s fine food are 10’s on the drool scale. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our base camp and launch-point is a one hour regional flight north of Lima to the city of Huaraz (10,170 ft) at the heart of and gateway to the Cordillera Blanca and Cordillera Huayhuash ranges.  &lt;br /&gt;Nice cozy guest houses, tasty meals, supply accommodations and Peruvian crafts are inexpensive  &lt;br /&gt;in Huaraz. From our Huaraz base we will begin our altitude acclimatization hikes and start our high Andes’ adventure treks.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The adventure guide company, Inkaland Journeys, is custom designing these treks based on the Meetup client’s personal desires. Inkaland Journeys will safely guide us through this pristine wilderness of breathtaking peaks. All of our logistic travel and trek details will be meticulously planned and executed. You simply enjoy the trekking while Inkaland Journeys fully manages the details from the moment you land to the moment you depart Peru.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peaks with ancient Quechua names such as Huascaran (wahs car rahn), Yerupaja (year ru pa ha), Jirishanca (here e shan kah), Chopicalqui (cho pee call key), Chacragu (cha car rah who) and Siula  &lt;br /&gt;(see you la) Grande (made famous by Joe Simpson in Touching the Void), are a few of over 40 peaks in the Cordillera Blanca and Huayhuash ranges over 6,000M (19,685 ft) with Huascarán (22,204’) being Peru’s highest. Alpamayo (Al pah my yoh) at 19,511 ft has been declared the &amp;quot;World's Most Beautiful Mountain&amp;quot; by an international survey.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The landscape appears rugged and mountainous affording photo rich panoramic views over very wide areas. Most of the trekking, and most of the campsites, are above the 13,000 ft tree line with the snowline starting at approximately 15,700 ft so these majestic peaks are right up close. You become the experience.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On these Meetup treks, while decent physical conditioning and acclimation hikes are necessary, you’ll only need day packs since Arrieros (burro drivers) with their burros transport your personal gear, the tents, cooking/dining equipment and supplies. Professional UIAGM certified guides with rescue horses and mountain cooks making delicious meals are all there to support and facilitate your Andes adventure experience. A 5% discount is offered for Meetup and AMC members. Whats better, the 5% discount is off of Peruvian trip rates, not US trip consolidator rates. Become what you think and elevate your expectations. With the clicker in your hand, hit the next adventure trip button and capture the Andes spirit…experience the journey on this unforgettable Meetup/AMC Andes’ trip. The more the merrier… it holds true for both our group size and our discount. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call Greg Horton at (860) 977-5017  for any questions regarding affordability of cost and travel logistics and sign up now through info@inkalandjourneys.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291287725000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290056847000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peruvian Andes Exploration</name><id>15486321</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291158000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15486321/</event_url></item>