<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Kick back and play at our post-holiday Open Studio Day! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, Dec. 26, 1 to 8 p.m. (or later, if people want). Come for an hour or two; come for the whole day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AGENDA:&lt;/b&gt; No scheduled activities. Arrive and leave when you want. Work on your own projects at your own pace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/b&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $5, regardless of how long you stay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/b&gt; Any member of the NE ATC+ or Altered Art/Assemblage Meetups who has already attended at least one regular Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt; Your own materials and projects to work on (just as you do for the regular Meetup). A few basic supplies--scissors, glue, tape, etc. -- are available for loan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/b&gt; You must RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. If your plans change, switch your RSVP to no ASAP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/b&gt; If you must cancel less than 24 hours in advance -- or after the Open Studio has started -- &lt;u&gt;you should also call the Open Studio host&lt;/u&gt;. The host's phone number will be e-mailed to you after you RSVP, along with the Studio address.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;If we need to cancel due to weather or for any other reason, we'll post a message here AND e-mail anyone who's RSVP'd as far in advance as possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you can't make it this time, don't fret -- we'll be offering MANY more of these.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230753874000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229729858000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ArtStudio 360 Open Studio Day</name><id>9365520</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230314400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/9365520/</event_url></item>