<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join us for the Boston premiere of the award-winning documentary Forgetful Not Forgotten. Forgetful Not Forgotten is an intimate portrait of a family coming to grips with the realities of early-onset Alzheimer's disease. When John Wynn is diagnosed with the disease at the relatively young age of 57, his son, Montreal filmmaker Chris Wynn, decides to chronicle his family's journey to John's final days. An honest, moving, and at times heartbreaking film, Forgetful Not Forgotten weaves past and present to both celebrate the man who was and mourn his painfully slow and steady disappearance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are very fortunate to have Chris Wynn, the director, on hand to answer your questions about the film following the screening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can watch a trailer for the film here:&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QeTBAUpl2ZQ&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;movie trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shannon, one of the members of the Canadian meetup is personally affected by Alzheimer's disease as her mother was also diagnosed with Alzheimer's while she was in her early 50s. Forgetful Not Forgotten is a poignant depiction of the struggles that my family and so many others face. Thus, I hope you will join me to see this remarkable film and to support this important cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets for the event are $20 and can be purchased at the door. All ticket sales support the MA/NH Alzheimer's Association. Proceeds go directly to improve the lives of those affected by Alzheimer's, by providing enhanced care and support for all affected, and through the advancement of research.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copies of the film will also be available for purchase following the screening for $20.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>2881088</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274920631000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272896229000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie Premiere: Forgetful Not Forgotten</name><id>13366562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274916600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/13366562/</event_url></item>