<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Red, white, rose, sangria, whatever. There's something wine-related that spells &amp;quot;summer&amp;quot; to you -- so bring a bottle or two of it for us to taste and tell us why!  Wine should be priced between $10 and $20 but if your favorite is $22.99, we won't turn it away! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we've talked about all the wines and sampled some of the ones that interest us (I know we have some &amp;quot;red-only&amp;quot; purists in the group that don't want to taste white), we can grill ourselves some dinner. I'll provide one or two grill-friendly entrees, a large salad or other side dish, plates, utensils, etc.  I hope that others will contribute food as well. . . please email me to tell me what you'd like to bring so we can try to keep things compatible and avoid duplication. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: This meetup is intended to take place in the back yard of my condo and assumes that I will be acquiring new outdoor furniture beforehand. We may need to move it if the furniture doesn't materialize or the weather is unfriendly. My condo is too small to accomodate the group indoors and someone is certain to be allergic to my cats, so if anyone else has a space they'd be willing to offer, please let me know!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be sent to members</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243781232000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242271599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Summer's Favorite Wines" tasting and cookout</name><id>10408563</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243198800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/10408563/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/1/global_8127057.jpeg</photo_url></item>