<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>343 Gorham Rd.</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636397</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Panera Bread</name><city>South Portland</city><id>1434694</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.329988</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #99ccff"&gt;Broken Harbor by Tana French&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #99ccff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Mick "Scorcher" Kennedy, the brash cop from Tana French’s bestselling &lt;em&gt;Faithful Place&lt;/em&gt;, plays by the book and plays hard. That’s what’s made him the Murder squad’s top detective—and that’s what puts the biggest case of the year into his hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On one of the half-built, half-abandoned "luxury" developments that litter Ireland, Patrick Spain and his two young children are dead. His wife, Jenny, is in intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first, Scorcher and his rookie partner, Richie, think it’s going to be an easy solve. But too many small things can’t be explained. The half dozen baby monitors, their cameras pointing at holes smashed in the Spains’ walls. The files erased from the Spains’ computer. The story Jenny told her sister about a shadowy intruder who was slipping past all the locks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Broken Harbor holds memories for Scorcher. Seeing the case on the news sends his sister Dina off the rails again, and she’s resurrecting something that Scorcher thought he had tightly under control: what happened to their family one summer at Broken Harbor, back when they were children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With her signature blend of police procedural and psychological thriller, French’s new novel goes full throttle with a heinous crime, creating her most complicated detective character and her best book yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photo.goodreads.com/books/1330675374l/13123877.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;ALL MEETUPS Policy&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Please remember, RSVP yes only if you plan to attend an event to allow us to plan accordingly. If you RSVP yes and change your mind on attending, you MUST provide at least 24 hours notice or you will be considered a "No Show". After 5 "No Shows", you will no longer be able to attend meetup events.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at one of the big tables. I'll leave the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356194921000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335123220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Book Club - Broken Harbor by Tana French</name><id>dcmxmdyqqbjc</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355961600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/61660442/</event_url></item>