<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Gulu-Gulu has a regular Monday night game night that they are looking to beef up the attendance for, and I am more than happy to oblige by posting an event on our calendar.  This event is posted for early October, and I am keeping my fingers crossed that Salem won't be too crazy yet on a Monday night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have quite a few members who are interested in word games.  Please, don't be afraid of joining us, because even though we have some word game grand masters, I know that I for one am at the lower end of the totem pole in word game skill.  So, come and bring your favorite word game with you (mention it in your RSVP so we don't wind up with 9 Scrabbles or 9 Boggles for 9 people).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gulu-Gulu is accessible to most of downtown Salem. Parking can usually be found on Washington St., in the Church St. lot, and in the lot between Lynde and Essex Streets (by the YMCA). Gulu-Gulu has a great food and beverage menu that can be found at www.gulu-gulu.com. I do request that when we hold Meetups in food or drink establishments that everyone in attendance order at least one item or beverage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note, the above listed phone number belongs to Liv not to Gulu-Gulu. It is to be used should you need to contact me the evening of the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223921965000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219970114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Word Games at Gulu-Gulu</name><id>8643793</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223332200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/8643793/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/5/global_2882981.jpeg</photo_url></item>