<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Socialism and libertarianism, beyond their doctrines, are also ideals.  That both ideals are embraced by millions who otherwise seem to get along quite nicely may, perhaps, suggest that these two socio-political philosophies need not be trapped in a state of fixed polar opposition.  If we can escape the constraints of dogma and doctrine the argument might be made that a socialist can value “rugged individualism” and a libertarian need not bury his or her compassion.   Are freedom, social flourishing and artistic perspective the exclusive properties of one side or the other?   Is the desire for social welfare incompatible with the desire for less government interference?  Philosophy is sometimes a display of passionate insights, but these insights can become hardened into inflexible ideals.   In this discussion, we will explore the possibilities and/or  actualities in which these purportedly opposite philosophies express concrete complementarity.  There must be a reason why I can enjoy reading &lt;i&gt;both&lt;/i&gt; Ayn Rand and Herbert Marcuse!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the mustachio'd guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260835710000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257610429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Socialism and Libertarianism. Are they compatible?</name><id>11818913</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260230400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/11818913/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/6/global_7925510.jpeg</photo_url></item>