<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer - Larry Peck (978)886-6041&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 =========================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a spur of the moment hike that my wife and I will be doing. I thought I'd post this as a meetup if anyone would like to join us. My wife(Kelly) is a beginner hiker who hikes at a beginner pace with lots of breaks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**This is a cross post with the Random Group of Hikers Meetup**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP INSTRUCTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you RSVP "YES" the next page displayed is the questions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Answer all questions that are part of the RSVP.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device or accept from the announcement Email, the questions may not show up.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Use a computer, on the Upper Right of the page in the Green Box click "CHANGE RSVP", select "Yes" and click RSVP, the next page displayed is the questions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO LOGIN WITHIN THE NEXT THREE DAYS TO ANSWER THE QUESTIONS OR YOU WILL BE MOVED FROM "GOING" TO "NOT GOING".&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If for some reason you cannot get the the Questions and you have REREAD these instructions and FOLLOWED them please send me an email.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we'll be doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire hike will be on the Mount Pemigewasset Trail, which is accessed from the north side of the Flume Visitor Center parking lot on Rt 3. The actual trail begins about 150 yards on a paved walkway. The complete hike is about 3.6 miles round trip. I don't expect this hike to be more than 3.5 hours in duration but I'm never in any hurry so we can take as much time as needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The forecast for Saturday is Partly sunny and in the low 80s. Make sure you bring plenty of water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be at a slow paced hike catering to beginner hikers. The goal is to tag a 52 With A View peak and enjoy the scenery at the top without killing ourselves. Even though this is a beginner hike, you should have some cardiovascular capability as we will be gaining over 1200' of elevation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to know what you are expected to have, review the following list:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/462914/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail map can be found &lt;a href="http://www.reptiliandesigns.com/files/Mt-Pemi.pdf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*HERE*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- are from Route 93 north, NH border and looks like it's about 1hour 45 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the google map of the parking lot can be found &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/MNIqg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*HERE*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for the 2004 Gold Toyota Tacoma Pickup or 2000 pewter Chevy Suburban&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email me your questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Peck</member_name><member_id>10414539</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345927026000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345657481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>52WAV: Mt Pemigewasset  EASY PACE</name><id>78880572</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345901400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/78880572/</event_url></item>