<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;It's traditional, Pilgrim!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, the above is not really an authentic John Wayne quote, but that is doubtless what he WOULD have said if anyone had ever asked him to describe the food at the Run of the Mill Tavern in Plymouth. Located in the same building as the Jenney Grist Mill, an authentic water-run corn mill built in 1636 (The restaurant isn't that old!), Run of the Mill serves a menu of fresh seafood and old-fashioned New England comfort food to appreciative locals and tourists, seven days a week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be heading there for lunch on Saturday, June 27th at 1:00. Mike, who has been eating at Run of the Mill since before he moved to Plymouth, is looking forward to sharing with the group a spot that is a favorite for its dependably well cooked food and folksy, casual atmosphere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Run of the Mill Tavern&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6 Spring Lane, Plymouth&lt;br /&gt;508 830-1262 &lt;br /&gt;No website&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maximum number of attendees:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Moderate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; No Event Fee for current Annual Members. Other Members and Guests: $2.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, June 26th @ 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; The Run of the Mill Tavern is located at 6 Spring Lane in downtown Plymouth, in the same building as the Jenney Grist Mill. We are providing directions from Route 3 for members who may be driving from a distance, but people people coming from the local area may find it convenient to pick up the directions from Route 3A.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3 North (Coming from Cape Cod):&lt;/b&gt; Take Route 3 to Exit 6, Route 44 East and Samoset St. Coming off the ramp, merge onto Route 44 East towards Plymouth Center, passing a large Hess gas station on your left. Follow directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3 South (Coming from Braintree):&lt;/b&gt; Take Route 3 to Exit 6A, Route 44 East. Coming off the ramp, &lt;b&gt;merge onto Route 44 heading toward Plymouth Center&lt;/b&gt;, passing back under Route 3, going straight through the traffic light at Westerly Rd and passing a large Hess gas station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 44, passing straight through a flashing yellow light at Chestnut St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next traffic light is at the &lt;b&gt;intersection of Route 44 and Route 3A&lt;/b&gt;. This is where Route 44 ends. Turn &lt;b&gt;right&lt;/b&gt; (South) onto Route 3A. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will find yourself driving through the heart of Plymouth Center, with rows of shops on both sides of the street. At the &lt;b&gt;next stoplight&lt;/b&gt;, you will clearly see a giftshop called &lt;b&gt;Windemere&lt;/b&gt; on the far right corner. Turn &lt;b&gt;right&lt;/b&gt;, then immediatley turn &lt;b&gt;left&lt;/b&gt;, keeping &lt;b&gt;Windemere on your left&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The John Carver Inn will be on your right. Pass the entrance to its parking lot and turn &lt;b&gt;right&lt;/b&gt; onto &lt;b&gt;Summer St&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spring Lane is in sight once you've turned onto Summer St.  Pass Sparrow House Pottery on your left, pass the building immediately after Sparrow House and turn &lt;b&gt;left&lt;/b&gt; onto &lt;b&gt;Spring Lane&lt;/b&gt;. The sign reading &amp;quot;Spring Lane&amp;quot; is partialy oscured by tree branches but you will clearly see &lt;b&gt;blue signs&lt;/b&gt; on a granite post that say &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Shopping&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Historic Sites&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Parking&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go slowly as you start down Spring Lane. You will immediately pass between Town Brook on your right and the Jenney Grist Mill building on your left. A sign reading &amp;quot;Mill Stone Creamery&amp;quot; is clearly visible in front of the mill building. Pass the mill and park in the free parking area just beyond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you've parked, walk back to the mill. Do not take the stairs leading down to the water wheel and the Mill Stone Creamery. Instead, follow the path that runs to the right and behind the mill building. Once you've turned the corner of the building, you will see a ramp intended for wheelchair access. The entrance to the Tavern is at the top of the ramp.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247436114000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245033667000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Not Your Run of the Mill Lunch!</name><id>10652654</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246122000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10652654/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/2/global_9158690.jpeg</photo_url></item>