<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>257 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 629 8717</phone><name>Diesel Cafe</name><city>Somerville</city><id>705077</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Privacy?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some states that charge sales tax are seeking to force online retailers like Amazon to report on purchases by state residents.   Should the state be able to look over what you purchased at Amazon?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Federal law requires banks to report your transactions above a certain dollar amount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A proposal in Congress would would require communication companies to have the ability to decrypt messages.  Countries like India and Saudi Arabia seek to require Blackberry RIM to break their encryption, so they can read messages sent from Blackberries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google's street view program recorded emails, usernames, passwords, etc from open wifi base stations. How much information on you are iPhone apps and android apps sharing about you to third parties? If you combine a web surfers browser type, IP address, and other characteristics can companies track your visits to separate web sites?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Just how much information are web sites collecting on you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should the law protect or prohibit anonymous postings?  Time for your blog page to be registered with the FEC.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You turned off cookies, but did you know about Flash cookies?  Are advertisers tracking what your favorite books, tv shows and movies are?  Tracking what comments you post online?  When you visit a web site do they already know your age, gender, income, zip code, health issues, and the name of your pets? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What are your expectations of privacy online?  How is it changing?  What can you do to protect your privacy?  Come to our discussion of privacy, technology and the law.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the large table all the way in back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288465606000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288210206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Privacy, the web and the law</name><id>15250394</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288393200000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/15250394/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/d/global_8294813.jpeg</photo_url></item>