<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Reservation Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01375</zip><lat>42.503792</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Toby State Reservation</name><city>Sunderland</city><id>710040</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.529472</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The intensity of this hike depends on member interest.  I like to walk along the logging road and meander through the trails around Cranberry Pond.  Some of you may want to try the 4 mile hike, up the Tower Road to the firetower atop Mount Toby.  There is a shorter, steeper route to the top along a section of the Robert Frost Trail.  The foliage should be fairly impressive at this time of year.  You'll see outcrops of a coarse conglomerate called pudding stone, steep ravines, forested hollows, marshy bottoms and dry ridges.  The Tower Road is closed to vehicles, and most of the way the trail is next  to a mountain stream.  Please be sure to have your dog on-leash, at least to begin with, until we know how we all get along.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the junction of Massachusetts Route 63 and 47 (in Sunderland, 4.5 miles south of Millers Falls, 8 miles north of North Amherst center), go south on Route 47 for 1 mile and turn left onto Reservation Road.  Find the gated trailhead on the right in 0.5 miles, with parking in another 50 feet next to a small headquarters building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Route 47 and Route 116 intersection in the center of Sunderland, go north on Route 47 for 3.8 miles and turn right onto Reservation Road.  Kristi's cell is 413-230-6757 if all else fails.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the entrance sign with a  black lab on a blue leash</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257006228000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252268964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploring Mount Toby, Sunderland</name><id>11304928</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255280400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/11304928/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/6/global_4769302.jpeg</photo_url></item>