<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let's kick-off the New Year with a Friday night dinner @ Asian C in Hingham!  Your suggestions and votes have brought the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group to the newest Asian restaurant in Hingham.  For more information on this restaraurant, please read Christine Ordway's review in The Patriot Ledger by clicking on thia link.  &lt;a href="http://ledger.southofboston.com/articles/2006/09/06/life/life02.txt" target="_blank"&gt;http://ledger.southof...&lt;/a&gt;  With appetizers ranging from $4-$10 with entrees ranging from $8-$15 this makes this reasonably priced restaurant one worth trying new cuisine.  Please join us for a Friday Night Dinner at this charming Asian restaurant!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, January 4th @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Asian C&lt;br /&gt;48 Whiting Street&lt;br /&gt;(Route 53)&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-740-0688&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp &lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: No maximum at this time.&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Sorry, this Meetup event is for Group Members Only.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 4pm on Wednesday, January 2nd&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizers: Angela and Susan&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: In the Lobby (near the host station) of Asian C.  (We will be seated within 10-30 minutes of our arrival.  Please look for us in the Lobby before attempting to go to our table.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please Note: The restaurant has requested that we finalize our RSVP 48 hours in advance if there are more than 8 people in the party.  Therefore, the following RSVP rules are being implemented for this event.  You may change your RSVP from &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; up until the deadline (which is listed above).  If you are no longer able to attend after the deadline please update your RSVP and follow the directions below.&lt;br /&gt;1. If you change your RSVP Wednesday night or Thursday day there will be no penatly.&lt;br /&gt;2. If you change your RSVP between 4pm Thursday and Noon on Friday and no one takes your place it will be counted as a No-Show.&lt;br /&gt;3. If you change your RSVP after Noon on Friday it will be counted as a No-Show.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 15/Derby Street, Hingham.  Exit off the highway heading towards Derby Street in Hingham.  Drive past the Derby Street Shoppes.  Go straight thru the next set of lights staying on Route 53 (and 228).  Asian C will be on your right before the next set of lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: Free and ample parking.  There is a large parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may also want to try maps.google.com or mapquest.com for an aerial map and/or door-to-door directions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Event Organizers will be in the Lobby area near the Host Station w/ the Sign-In and RSVP Sheets.  At least one of the Organizers should have a clipboard as well.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200147901000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197943202000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Dinner</name><id>6930357</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199489400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/6930357/</event_url></item>