<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This isn't a hike but come join in on this multi-meetup group holiday event! This event is for adults only. There will be food, dancing, the oportunity to purchase drinks, and there will be a Sexy Santa drawing if you wish to participate. I'm limiting the maximum size of our contingent to join this event so if you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; it must be a firm yes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOLIDAY PARTY 2009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Meet up Holiday Party&amp;quot; was started in 2005, making this our 5th year of getting together to celebrate the Holidays with our Meet up friends! It's our pleasure to keep the tradition going &amp;amp; we look forward to many more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEDITERRANEAN BUFFET&lt;/b&gt; will be served from 7pm to 9pm &lt;br /&gt;Chef Vincent Barcelona will prepare for us a Mediterranean Buffet which will include Chicken, Pasta, assorted vegetables, salad, coffee and sweets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LIVE MUSIC&lt;/b&gt; from 8:30pm to 11:00pm - TERI LAMAR &amp;amp; NEW COMPANY will have us dance to Rock n' Roll, Motown, Disco and R&amp;amp;B.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEXY HOLIDAY SANTA&lt;/b&gt;: Bob is going to coordinate the Sexy Santa portion. You do NOT need to participate in this if you don't want to, but the last couple of years that we did do it were a lot of fun.. (hey, we're all adults here.. *_*)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details: To participate in Sexy Santa - bring a wrapped gift of a sexual (think &amp;quot;naughty,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;silly,&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;nice&amp;quot;) nature - limit $10-15 - when you put a gift in - you will then pick numbers out of a hat - low number goes first - picks a gift - unwraps it - then the next one goes. And this is where the fun comes in as higher numbers have the chance to exchange their gift with anyone of a lower number at their choice...If you want to indicate in your RSVP that you are participating in the Sexy Santa, it would be appreciated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In DECEMBER of 2007 we held our Holiday Party at Mighty Joe Young's for $27.50. This year we can have a similar buffet in a much nicer place for an agreed upon cost of $10 so please keep this in mind when purchasing drinks. I'm not suggesting that we drink in excess but that we do the right thing for the establishment that is allowing us to have a fabulous evening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to keep the party at around 150 to 160 (overall, Hartford Area hiking has limited its maximum contingent to the event) – so please make a note on your Calendar and a promise to show up, so that you don't reserve the space that someone else could have used.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;$10 admission&lt;/b&gt;. No children I'm sorry to say, just adults. Carpooling is advised as parking may get tight with 150 people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location of event&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;HARVEST-ON-HUDSON  &lt;br /&gt;1 River Street&lt;br /&gt;Hasting-on-Hudson, NY 10706&lt;br /&gt;(914) 478-2800 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; to HARVEST-ON-HUDSON:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Harvest+On+Hudson+Restaurant&amp;amp;city=Hastings+On+Hdsn&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=1+River+St&amp;amp;zipcode=10706&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=40.994346&amp;amp;longitude=-73.884669&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=1326369" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat=40.994346, Long=-73.884669]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll just meet inside! Don't forget to bring $10 cash at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261094988000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259806030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Multi-Group Christmas party in Hasting-on-Hudson, NY</name><id>12005158</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260921600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12005158/</event_url></item>