<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SHIMMY YOUR WAY TO HAPPINESS!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to the class to meet other women who want to get in touch with their inner spirit in a relaxed setting!  The one-hour class brings together women of all backgrounds for a fun and exciting low-impact workout.  Movements are broken down into body isolations which tone and strengthen muscles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginners or advanced beginners who have had some training but would like to sharpen their skills and anyone who just loves the magic of dance are welcome!  We will explore basic belly dance movement, Middle Eastern music and rhythm and look into the history of this beautiful dance.  These classes also focus on posture with a warm-up and cool down. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As both a Belly Dance instructor and student, and performer, I’ve seen how these classes have given women a chance to meet other women and make long lasting friendships.  It is also comforting for women to know that this is the only dance form where each woman’s movements do not have to be exactly like another's  and that weight is not a requirement or an issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fee for these classes is $60 for the first six sessions (the first 10 students will receive a 7th class free) and $10 per class thereafter.  Membership discounts are available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information or to contact Danita at (860) 794-1817 or go to www.growinggreenevents.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>danita thomas</member_name><member_id>11226615</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266102593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264724660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Basic Bellydance Movement</name><id>12454248</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265929200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12454248/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/d/5/global_12973493.jpeg</photo_url></item>