<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have the occasional weekday off with my job so I&amp;#146;m looking to hike Smart Mountain about 15 miles north of Hanover on Friday. I&amp;#146;m actually open to having this hike on Saturday. I didn&amp;#146;t want to clash with other hikes, but at 7.6 miles, over 2000 foot of elevation gain, and a book time of around 5 hours, this hike would appeal to a different crowd and ability Rain may also move this Saturday or Sunday. Respond yes if you&amp;#146;re interested in the Friday hike and comment if open to Saturday as well. Respond no if you&amp;#146;re not interested in Friday, but make a comment if you want to go on Saturday as well. I might even go both days. Smarts Mountains is over 3000 feet. Great views and with foliage colors it should be a beautiful hike. More info at the link below from Dartmouth outing club. Lets meet at the trail head at 10am. Arange for carpools in the comment section. How To Get There: Take Route 10 north from Hanover into Lyme. Coming around the green in Lyme, bear right at the white church and follow signs for the Dartmouth Skiway. Pass through Lyme Center 1.8 miles from the green in Lyme, and continue winding around for 1.3 more miles to where the wide gravel Lyme-Dorchester Road forks to the left. Take this fork for 1.8 miles until, just before the iron bridge over Grant Brook, a small parking lot is reached on the left. Orange signs mark the trailheads. Park here. The Dartmouth Outing provides some info on the hike here &lt;a href="http://www.dartmouth.edu/~doc/hiking/smartsmountain/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dartmouth....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317469251000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316973063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike: Smarts Mountain, just outside Lyme, NH Fri 9/30, 10am</name><id>34897412</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317391200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/34897412/</event_url></item>