<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Climb a hill for nice views extending from the surrounding Merrimack Valley to the Boston skyline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails link three major hills – Shrub, Boston, and Holt – and looking out from their summits you can see how the property melds with the surrounding landscape. The “Solstice Stones” mark the grassy summit of Holt Hill, the highest point in Essex County. This compass-like arrangement of stones indicates the cardinal points on the compass, the points of the summer and winter solstices, and the points of the spring and autumnal equinoxes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;To start, we will climb to Holt Hill at a rather slow pace as this area is rather steep.  This will be a little over a 1-mile loop&lt;/u&gt;. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the base of Holt Hill, step onto a boardwalk that leads to Pine Hole Pond, at which point you may ask: Is this water or land? In fact, you are walking across a rare quaking bog, comprised of concentric rings of floating vegetation, each with unique growing conditions. The bog is home to a number of interesting plant species, including orchids and insect-eating pitcher plants. Stop at the numbered stations along the way, each of which signals an interesting botanical or geologic feature. Pick up an interpretive booklet at the bulletin board to follow numbered stations along the boardwalk and learn more about this rare natural phenomenon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;We will take the the bog trail next, which is about a half mile round trip.  BRING BUG SPRAY!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;If there is anyone who knows the trails and who would like to lead part of the group that wants a longer hike from Hilt Hill onto one of the other loops, please let me know.  Otherwise, go as far as you want and as fast/slow as you want as long as someone is with you and you have a map or knowledge of the park.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE NOTE THAT THERE ARE NO RESTROOMS ON SITE SO PLEASE USE FACILITIES BEFORE YOUR ARRIVAL!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails &lt;br /&gt;Almost 10 miles of trails, easy-to-moderate hiking, strenuous in places. Some of the trails here are part of the Bay Circuit Trail, a regional greenway linking the North Shore and South Shore.  The reservation totals 700 acres. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;From I-93 Exit 41, take Rt. 125 North 5 mi. Turn right onto Prospect Rd. and follow for 0.3 mi. to entrance and parking on right. From Rt. I-495 Exit 42, take Rt. 114 East 1.7 mi. You will pass Merrimack College on your right shortly before you need to turn right onto Rt. 125 South or Andover Bypass Street.  (It's more like a right fork).  Follow Route 125 South for 1.6 mi. Turn left onto Prospect Road and follow for 0.3 mi. to entrance and parking on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note, if you are using a GPS, the address for parking is 59 Prospect &lt;u&gt;Road in Andover&lt;/u&gt;.  (Things get tricky because the park covers areas of North Andover and Andover- you want Andover.  Also, there is a Prospect Street in North Andover that you don't want- you want Prospect Road.)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone is interested, we can go for snacks/coffee after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on Ward Reservation, here is the website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/ward-reservation.html#t1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot and will have meetup stickers on.  We will leave at 12:40.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>11</waitlist_count><updated>1277745610000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277143411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slower Ward Reservation Hike </name><id>13865452</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277656200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13865452/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/6/global_13059190.jpeg</photo_url></item>