<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>294 Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.551907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-922-0004</phone><name>Organic Garden Cafe</name><city>Beverly</city><id>598589</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.879082</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Open Thanksgiving Day from 11am to 3pm (must be seated by 3pm) &lt;a href="http://www.organicgardencafe.com/thanksgiving_pay_it_forward.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.organicgar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SIGN UP AND CALL TO MAKE A RESERVATION CALL 978/922-0004.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the true spirit of this holiday season, we are offering a limited menu* on a sliding scale on Thanksgiving, Thursday November 24th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* sliding scale is available on the following: Thanksgiving Dinner, Salads and Bowls Pay from $0 to full price, or by paying more you can take this opportunity to "Pay it Forward" for others in need of an inspirational meal! See full details on the dinner.&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://organicgardencafe.com/thanksgiving_meal.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://organicgardencafe.com/thanksgiving_meal.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the spirit of this special day, we also will have a community table for those who wish to make new friends and share glad tidings! So make a reservation &amp;amp; let others know you are coming!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our gourmet raw meal will feature the UN-Turkey you've come to love with Pecan Mushroom Gravy, Cranberry Relish &amp;amp; sides. We'll also make sure to have plenty of butternut squash on hand for soups and Harvest Bowls. In order to facilitate a large crowd, this day will NOT offer table service or a juice bar. Come and be part of a joyous event and history in the making! Our normal menu prices are already the best deal in organic &amp;amp; raw cuisine and there is no pressure for you to pay more or less than the standard price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider this day to be one of the early seedlings of a new paradigm for business enterprise, 'Pay-It-Forward Commerce'. You get the opportunity to be on either side of the equation, if you choose so, (or right in the middle); as it is good to receive and it is good to give. Thanks for making our last Pay-it-forward New Year's Weekend a success!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May the LIFE FORCE reside in you,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May you embody the true spirit of this holiday of gratitude and generosity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rawbert and the Amazing OG TEAM&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rawbert</member_name><member_id>11144266</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322258045000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321654467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Organic Garden Cafe 11am-3pm</name><id>41669172</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322150400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/41669172/</event_url></item>