<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our next theatre night at the North Shore Music Theatre will be on Saturday, Aug. 2, 2008 @ 7:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone remember seeing the movie &amp;quot;Bye Bye Birdie?&amp;quot;  Brings back memories for many of us, I'm sure!  The next musical production of the season at the NSMT, running from July 15th-August 3rd is &amp;quot;Bye Bye Birdie.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Return to a simpler time in the ultimate feel-good musical, winner of four 1961 Tony® Awards, including Best Musical. The plot revolves around rock 'n' roll superstar Conrad Birdie (loosely based on Elvis Presley), who, to the dismay of his adoring fans, is about to be drafted into the army. But, comic complications ensue when, as part of a publicity stunt cooked up by his agent, he promises to give a good-bye kiss to one lucky girl from Sweet Apple, Ohio on &amp;quot;The Ed Sullivan Show.&amp;quot; The upbeat score features &amp;quot;Put On A Happy Face,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;A Lot of Livin&amp;quot; To Do,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;One Last Kiss.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book by Michael Stewart.&lt;br /&gt;Music by Charles Strouse. Lyrics by Lee Adams.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our member Jill has obtained 1/2 price tickets for our group.  The Box Office will hold 20 tickets aside for us @ $30.00 each (regular price is $60.00).  Call the Box Office directly to pay for your ticket:  978-232-7200.  You should reference my name (Jill) and the Merrimack Group.  Carol, who works in the Box Office, has been handling our group ticket sales so far this season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North Shore Music Theatre - Bye Bye Birdie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  Anyone interested in meeting for dinner beforehand, please mention it in your RSVP.  We can keep it simple and inexpensive!  The idea of getting together ahead of time is to have a chance to socialize, renew friendships, or form new ones!  An evening at the theatre doesn't lend itself easily to much socializing, so do consider if meeting up earlier will suit you!!  Looking forward to another great production at the NSMT!  ~~~~ Jill&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218635837000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215908829000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bye Bye Birdie at NSMT</name><id>8329777</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217719800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/8329777/</event_url></item>