<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I made this at 11 AM since it is a bit further than many of our walks.  It is 1hr 10min from me in Amesbury.  A gorgeous place - incredible views.  Long term weather for the date says sunny and 49 degrees.   Expect at least a 2 hour walk, but there will be places to turn back for those who wish a shorter walk.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the website for further info:  &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/halb.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halibut Point is a uniquely beautiful coastal seascape. Looking seaward on a clear day, the view stretches from Crane Beach in Ipswich to Mount Agamenticus in Maine and the Isles of Shoals off the coast of New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Formerly the Babson Farm granite quarry, the park is managed for scenic, historic and conservation purposes by the DCR and the Trustees of Reservations. An adjacent property, Sea Rocks, is owned by the Town of Rockport and open for public use. Here you can explore the park's trails and tidepools, picnic on its rocky ledges, enjoy its sweeping views, and learn about Cape Ann's historic granite industry.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking Lot-Joan's Silver Honda Fit</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joan C</member_name><member_id>5518283</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240245015000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239363154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halibut Point State Park Hike - Rockport, MA</name><id>10157822</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240066800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/10157822/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/6/7/global_8081479.jpeg</photo_url></item>