<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>122A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01543</zip><lat>42.374469</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-886-6333</phone><name>Rutland State Park</name><city>Rutland</city><id>948468</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.959659</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Where:&lt;br /&gt;Rutland State Park&lt;br /&gt;Rte. 122A&lt;br /&gt;Rutland, MA 01741&lt;br /&gt;508-886-6333&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greater Worcester Humanists invite New England Atheists, Humanists, and Freethinkers to join them for their annual Summer Outing at Rutland State Park. All friends and family are welcome. Guests are encouraged to bring sports and game gear, and are asked to contribute to the potluck buffet. (An updated list of what people are bringing will be below.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will not be an official speaker or program. Our main purpose is to network with other New England area freethinkers in a casual, social setting in order to strengthen our community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, Greater Worcester Humanists is having a drive to provide school supplies for needy families in the Worcester area. We were told by the staff of the food pantry that recently opened at the UU Church of Worcester that there is a real need for school supplies, and we thought this would be an appropriate need for our group to address. Therefore we'll be taking donated school supplies at this meeting. Supplies would include: Pencils, colored pencils, pens, markers/crayons, notebooks, loose-leaf paper, crafts supplies, and backpacks. Thanks for helping.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rutland State Park has more than 300 acres of walking/biking trails and also a pond for swimming. The GWH has reserved the use of the main pavillion for this event. Parking is $5. For directions and more information about the facilities, please visit &lt;a href="http://mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/rtld.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://mass.gov/dcr/p...&lt;/a&gt;. No alcohol is allowed at Massachusetts State Parks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From east or west: Rte. 2 to Rte. 31 south, Rte. 122 north, right on 122A, follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;From Worcester: Rte. 122 west, right on 122A, first left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a limited amount of spaces for the outing. Please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IT WILL BE HAPPENING, RAIN OR SHINE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from the event page at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/calendar/13302081"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/calendar/13833424/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Will</member_name><member_id>1945640</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277573166000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>atheists-488</urlname><id>259726</id><group_lat>42.2599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Atheists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277214618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Worcester Humanists Annual Cookout</name><id>13874187</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277568000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/atheists-488/events/13874187/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/2/global_463138.jpeg</photo_url></item>