<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Start:December 17, 2010EIGHT TO THE BAR  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: 848 PARK AVE, CRANSTON, RI  &lt;br /&gt;Come party with us at this beautiful new venue within the Park Theater! Drink, Dine, and Dance. Celebrate the Holidays with us and enjoy this great band. Their CD's will be available including a brand new CD called &amp;quot;The Romper Room&amp;quot; Hope all will join us for this very exciting night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drawing its musical influences from American roots music – swing, boogie woogie, rhythm &amp;amp; blues, soul, Motown, – Eight to the Bar is known for its outstanding instrumentalists and sophisticated musical and vocal arrangements, highlighted by female vocals. &lt;br /&gt;With the support of independently-produced albums and videos, Eight to the Bar has cultivated a large, enthusiastic following that has put them in clubs from Disneyland to Disney World as well as Europe and the Carribean. Their rigorous performing schedule (approximately 200 dates per year), has included opening spots for Big Bad Voodoo Daddy, Manhattan Transfer, Robert Cray, Neil Young, Roy Orbison, and Ray Charles. This is their first public club appearance in RI in quite awhile. Please don’t miss this special holiday performance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who signs up for this event should be kind enough  to attend because i will try to reserve a table for us. I will also only allow for No or Yes so reservations can be made. Only allowing for 10 people so if you have interest in this event sign up soon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner Menu &lt;br /&gt;Salad &lt;br /&gt;Antipasto &lt;br /&gt;A delicious assortment of cold cuts, olives, and cheeses- 10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Caesar  &lt;br /&gt;Parmesan, housemade croutons, and Caesar dressing over fresh romaine- 6 &lt;br /&gt;Add Chicken or Shrimp- 5 &lt;br /&gt;Add Tenderloin- 8 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Insalata Caprese &lt;br /&gt;Sliced fresh mozzarella and tomatoes, seasoned and drizzled with extra virgin olive oil and balsamic glaze, garnished with fresh basil- 8 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mista &lt;br /&gt;Fresh tomatoes, cucumbers, carrots, kalamata olives, red onions, candied walnuts, crumbled blue cheese, and balsamic vinaigrette over field greens- 6  &lt;br /&gt;Add Chicken or Shrimp- 5 &lt;br /&gt;Add Tenderloin- 8 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soups &lt;br /&gt;Clam Chowder &lt;br /&gt;Stage Door’s own New England Style Clam Chowder- 5 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;French Onion Soup &lt;br /&gt;Classic French Onion Soup-5 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chef du Jour &lt;br /&gt;Chef’s Choice-5 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panini &lt;br /&gt;All served on Ciabatta Bread with choice of Chips, Field Greens or Fries &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicken Toscana &lt;br /&gt;Pesto, provolone and mesclun greens- 10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Stage Door  &lt;br /&gt;Mortadella, prosciutto, salami and provolone with lettuce and tomato, oil and vinegar- 12 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grilled Tenderloin &lt;br /&gt;Grilled Tenderloin with caramelized onions, mushrooms, and crumbled bleu cheese- 15 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grilled Shrimp Pesto &lt;br /&gt;With mesclun greens, roasted red peppers and a pesto aioli- 12 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small Plates &lt;br /&gt;Fried Calamari &lt;br /&gt;With hot banana pepper rings served with our own garlic butter sauce and marinara- 10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clam Zuppa &lt;br /&gt;Native Shellfish cooked to perfection in a spicy sauce. Your choice of red or white- 10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clams Casino &lt;br /&gt;Native Shellfish with a red pepper and onion stuffing topped with bacon- 10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruschetta &lt;br /&gt;Fresh tomatoes marinated in garlic, olive oil, and basil, topped with fresh mozzarella and served over grilled ciabatta- 8 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lemon Lime Tequila Shrimp &lt;br /&gt;Jumbo shrimp sautéed in a tequila lime sauce- 10 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angel Hair Marinara &lt;br /&gt;The thinnest of pasta cooked to perfection and then smothered in Stage Door’s own house made marinara- 6  &lt;br /&gt;Add Chicken, Shrimp or Clams – 5 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pizza &lt;br /&gt;Margherita &lt;br /&gt;Fresh mozzarella and tomato sauce topped with just the right touch of extra virgin olive oil and fresh basil- 12 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pesto &lt;br /&gt;Chicken Stage Door’s own fresh made pesto with Mozzarella Cheese- 12 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Pizza &lt;br /&gt;Our own take on the classic white with roasted red peppers, artichoke hearts and kalamata olives- 12 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets to this event will be $10.00/ person. &lt;br /&gt;Changed Numbers on RSVP ( will be able to change it If more than 15 sign up) &lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you are all going to also have dinner with us or just going to dance?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Host at restaurant will seat you with us/ cell phone number mailed to you prior to event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Claire</member_name><member_id>4222330</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292704812000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Exciting People Having Some Fun!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mingle-with-singles</urlname><id>1452082</id><group_lat>41.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Mingle with singles 45+ Socializing and dancing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291077153000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eight To The Bar/ Stage Door Restaurant and Lounge</name><id>15589088</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292628600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mingle-with-singles/events/15589088/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/0/global_10652416.jpeg</photo_url></item>