<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trinity College</name><city>Hartford</city><id>353193</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.699997</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Good Morning All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you Jo (MeetUp member) for coming up with this idea.  We have our second MeetUp. Albeit a little short notice.... I have been reading the emails going back and forth between Jo &amp;amp; Marina as well as everyone elses and this one stuck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone wants to get a feel for what some of our grandparents or parents had to endure coming from the old counrty to a new world. This is the film. It's a Martin Scorcese film to boot. It's won many film festival awards.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 2 times - 2:30pm &amp;amp; 7:30pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trailer is amazing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks again Jo - This is what this group is about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NUOVOMONDO (THE GOLDEN DOOR) &lt;br /&gt;(Italy, 2007) &lt;br /&gt;120 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Written and directed by Emanuele Crialese. Director of photography: Agnès Godard. Cast: Vincenzo Amato, Charlotte Gainsbourg, Aurora Quattrocchi, Vincent Schiavelli.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;While writer/director Emanuele Crialese?s title of The Golden Door refers to a line from Emma Lazarus? poem inscribed on the Statue of Liberty, the film gets its magic from an immigrant family just before they take that irrevocable step into an unknown new world. Vincenzo Amato (Respiro) stars as a widower from an isolated Sicilian village, who is driven by the same fantastical images of limitless opportunities that draw new immigrants today. Charlotte Gainsbourg co-stars as a mysterious, aloof Englishwoman, who is taken under the protective wing of the extended Sicilian family. The spectacular widescreen Cinemascope photography of Agnès Godard dazzles with images of the color-saturated Sicilian countryside and a stunning first glimpse of New York. ?There?s an old Zen saying, ?It?s the journey, not the destination.? The Golden Door offers an extraordinary journey of its own? - Steven Rea, Philadelpia Inquirer. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Web Page: goldendoor-movie.co &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lorenzo</member_name><member_id>4408109</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188326040000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Amici Italiani</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-452</urlname><id>535327</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>Connecticut's Viva Italia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187871089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An afternoon/evening at the movies - Sun.Aug26</name><id>6229928</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188153000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-452/events/6229928/</event_url></item>