<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you feeling like a Wall Flower?  Not sure who to talk to?  Well, our cure for the Wallflower Blues is our quarterly &lt;b&gt;NETWORKING EXTRAVAGANZA&lt;/b&gt;!  If you thought our networking segment at March?s meeting was fun, then BE AT THIS MEETING!  It?s an entire night devoted to &lt;b&gt;NETWORKING&lt;/b&gt;!  The only complaint we got in March was, ?I had no idea you were doing this, I didn?t come prepared, I don?t have enough cards!?  Sorry!  I guess you have to be prepared because Ann and I like to shake it up?You never know what we?ll do next.  You can always expect more fun, more networking, more motivation and more tips and techniques.   Oh?and you Wall Flowers, at April?s meeting, Bring Extra Dance Cards and EXPECT to FILL THEM! Well, you KNOW what I mean!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I DID IT&lt;/b&gt;! I am so excited about the networking meeting and getting as many folks there to network that I twisted Ann?s arm until she agreed!  For the month of April only, all &lt;b&gt;FIRST TIME VISITORS who come and pay the regular visitor door fee of $25 can BRING YOUR DANCE PARTNER FOR FREE!&lt;/b&gt;  If you?ve ever thought you might be interested in real estate investing ? this is the night to come!  The movers and shakers in real estate investing in the Boston and surrounding areas will be at this meeting!  YOU NEED TO BE AT THIS MEETING!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PSSST?.I?m working on some other things that are going to make April?s meeting the best you?ve been to?but?you can?t let Ann know?you know the old adage, ?It?s better to ask forgiveness??well you know...gotta go now!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216988292000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206052753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association April Meeting</name><id>7572336</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208467800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/7572336/</event_url></item>