<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 16, .8 mi north of Glen Ellis Falls</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03846</zip><lat>44.205025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pinkham Notch Visitor Center/Joe Dodge Lodge</name><city>Pinkham Notch</city><id>1140554</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.226110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come hike and watch one of the big events in the Whites!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuckerman Ravine&lt;br /&gt;First skied in 1926 only the experienced dared to hike &amp;amp; ski its slopes. Famous for its steep snow filled ravine, the spring ritual lives on to this day. Ski clubs throughout the northeast started the tradition &amp;amp; in 1939 as many as a thousand skiers were found in the bowl with a few daredevils on the headwall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When racing began in Tuckerman Ravine contestants wore red avalanche strings from their trousers in case they had to be dug out. The most famous of all ski races held in 1934 in Tuckerman's was called the Inferno. The Inferno started in at the top of Mt. Washington with the course winding its way down the mountain, over the famous headwall down into the bowl to the Sherburne Trail ending at the AMC hut at the bottom. In 1934 Hollis Phillips won the race in just over twelve minutes. This record remained unchanged until 1939, the year of the last Inferno &amp;amp; the year when international skier Toni Matt plummeted into the ravine &amp;amp; disappeared into the Sherburne Trail at a speed witnesses said they had never seen before. Toni won the race in a time just under 6 &amp;amp; one half minutes, a record that still stands today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is 2.4 miles and 1879 feet of elevation gain to the Hermit Lake Shelter (known as HoJos). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking time is typically 1.5 to 2 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there it is about another 40 minutes over 0.7 miles and 538 feet to the &amp;quot;Lunch Rocks&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring sunscreen, sunglasses, extra clothes that will keep you warm during the inactivity of sitting, and plenty of snacks, food, and water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The round trip is 5.4 miles, about 1400' of elevation gain, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expect it to be crowded. carpooling is advised. Post in your comments if you are interested in carpooling and details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet on the front porch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271549953000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269562550000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tuckerman Ravine Picnic on the Lunch Rocks &amp; Come Watch The Skiers </name><id>12994834</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270990800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12994834/</event_url></item>