<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>According to the forecast, we are expecting a beautiful day tomorrow! I reopen the event and hopefully all of you can make the trip to Lowell folk festival. Most likely the festival will draw a big crowd tomorrow, so far we have a total of 65 people sign up for this meetup event, I won't be able to look for ANYONE, so please come on time and look for me or &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/members/3847345/"&gt;Biagio&lt;/a&gt;, the organizer of Social Fun group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I normally send out a reminder along with my cell# for a small event, but this time I decide not to. I will be at Market Street Stage around 11:30 and wear a blue/white callaway cap like &lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1169/members/3609570/"&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt; until 12:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please bring the meetup schedule with you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in case you are late or have problem to locate the group. The festival map will be available on the event website and at the festival. If this is your first time attending meetup event, please arrive at Market Street Stage before 11:45am, so I will be able to introduce you to the other group members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One more thing, there is a big chance that we won't be able to sit together this time but will try our best to keep everyone stay close.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring On The Music!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emilie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;==========================================&lt;br /&gt;Updates as of July 20th -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are total 60 Yes, 30 from Social fun, 19 from Beantown and Beyond Singles and 11 from Cambridge Single Parents. New RSVPs are now CLOSED for this event. To all Yes RSVPs, if your plan has been changed, please update your RSVP accordingly. I will send out an email one day before the event. Hope to see you all at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;===========================================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lowell Folk Festival - the largest free folk festival in the United States - six outdoor stages, three days of traditional music and dance, street parades, dance parties, ethnic foods, and craft demonstrations presented throughout the City of Lowell. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lowell Folk Festival will be held July 24th - 26th, 2009. Performers from past folk festivals have included country music sensation Alison Krauss, Irish stepdancing legend Michael Flatley, Cajun powerhouse Michael Doucet and Beausoleil, boogie-woogie queen Marcia Ball and hundreds of this nation's finest musicians, dancers, storytellers, and puppeteers representing the diversity of America's customs and traditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Website: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;biography of performers: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/performers.html"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/performers.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will gather at Market Street Stage at 11:40am, if you are late or have problem to find us, here is our schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00pm-12:30pm Market Street Stage, Capoeira Luanda&lt;br /&gt;12:45pm-1:30pm Market Street Stage, The Brotherhood Singers&lt;br /&gt;2:00pm-2:45pm Boarding House Park, Genticorum&lt;br /&gt;3:00pm-3:45pm Lee Street Stage, Two Fiddles &amp;amp; The Sugar River String Band&lt;br /&gt;4:00pm-4:45pm Lee Street Stage, Accordion Traditions with Niamh Ní Charra, Eddie Forman, and Patrick Farrell&lt;br /&gt;5:00pm-6:00pm Dutton Street Dance Pavilion, Trudy Lynn (blues and soul) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are three parking garages at the event. Parking in all garages is $10 all day during the festival. If you want to carpool to the event, please add comments here or indicate in your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a joint event, please just RSVP YES to ONE group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248710237000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246249488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lowell Folk Festival</name><id>10757693</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248536700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10757693/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/3/global_9406051.jpeg</photo_url></item>