<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.794332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 278-2670</phone><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>716384</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.664378</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This month's PHOENIX ART AFTER HOURS looks pretty good.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by The Phoenix Companies, Inc.  &lt;br /&gt;Rise Up Remix Block Party is August 5, 5:00-9:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5 / Free for Phoenix Employees, Museum Members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Phoenix Art After Hours provides a stimulating setting for mingling with friends after work. Sip a cocktail, enjoy music and other live performances, attend a gallery talk, and even see a classic movie or art film. The Wadsworth Atheneum is open until 8 pm the first Thursday of every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RISE UP REMIX&lt;br /&gt;The museum joins forces with The Amistad Center for Art &amp;amp; Culture, Taste of the Caribbean and Jerk Festival, West Indian Social Club and Young! Studios to celebrate all things Caribbean on the Travelers Plaza&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGGAE&lt;br /&gt;Special guest Turbulence, featured in Rise Up, performs his hit song Notorious, and is joined by other local talent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BEATS AND BRIDGES&lt;br /&gt;An exhibition of photographs illustrating the power of music created by students from The Amistad Center’s Neighborhood Studios &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REFRESHMENTS&lt;br /&gt;Receive a taste of Ten Penny Ale from Olde Burnside Brewing Co. (free while supplies last), enjoy a Rum Punch (for the first 100 guests), and sample food ($$) provided by Hartford area Caribbean restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FILM 8 PM- RISE UP &lt;br /&gt;Back by popular demand! A film that depicts an uplifting journey into the heart of Jamaica—the island that gave birth to the worldwide cultural phenomenon of Reggae. In a society where talent abounds and opportunity is scarce, three distinct artists fight to rise up from obscurity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GALLERIES and THE MUSEUM SHOP OPEN TILL 8&lt;br /&gt;Convenient parking available at the Front Street Garage, off Prospect Street, behind the museum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is $7 max for the evening (includes the film) or $3 for the first hour, $2 for each hour after &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie-&lt;br /&gt;Rise Up is an uplifting journey into the heart of Jamaica—the island that gave birth to the worldwide cultural phenomenon of Reggae. In a society where talent abounds and opportunity is scarce, three distinct artists fight to rise up from obscurity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim </member_name><member_id>6478306</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281180141000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280713639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wadsworth  First Thursday</name><id>14285950</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281042000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14285950/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/4/global_15939476.jpeg</photo_url></item>