<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Livingston Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.511795</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crystal Lake</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1283325</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.645336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Brian Ditter and Tara McLaughlin invite HAC to a barbecue and pot luck this Sunday, July 4, noon to 4pm at Crystal Lake Park in Middletown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP by phone&lt;/b&gt;: Brian Ditter: (860) 262-1291, (860) 704-0439 or Tara McLaughlin: (860) 545-5065&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian and Tara will provide burgers/steaks, beverages, chips, and fixings. Please bring a dish to share.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From New Haven: take I-91 N to exit 15 for CT-68 toward Yalesville/Durham. In 0.3 mi turn right onto route 68. In 0.9 mi  route 68  takes a left. Follow 68 for 4.2 mi, when you will turn left onto route 17/Main St. Take your 2nd right (0.5 mi.) onto Haddam Quarter Rd. In 1.7 mi.turn left at Arbutus St. In 1.4 mi. take a slight right onto Livingston Rd. The entrance to the park will be on your left in 0.6 mi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford: Take I-91 S and take exit 22S on the left to merge onto CT-9 S toward Middletown. Take exit 11. At the end of the exit turn left onto route 155 (Randolph Rd.) toward route 17 and Durham. In 0.7 mi. turn left at Millbrook Rd.(there's a traffic light and a fire station on your left). In 1.4 mi turn right onto Livingston Rd. and then turn right into the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 84: Take I-691 E toward Meriden and continue onto route 66 (eastbound). In 2.0 miles turn right onto route 147 S. In 2.3 miles turn right and continue on route 147 and route 157. In 2.5 miles  the road takes a sharp left (Middlefield Rd). At the end of the road, turn right and then take your first left onto Haddam Quarter Rd. In 1.7 mi.turn left at Arbutus St. In 1.4 mi. take a slight right onto Livingston Rd. The entrance to the park will be on your left in 0.6 mi.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the pavilion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Siddall</member_name><member_id>1140632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278283677000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278085773000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picnic at Crystal Lake, Middletown</name><id>13983221</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278259200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/13983221/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/global_5196186.jpeg</photo_url></item>