<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>There's live flamenco at Tasca Monday after next (Sept. 29).   Tasca is mid-priced and has good tapas.  It's a romantic cozy venue.  There are two seatings, 6:30 and 8:30.  If you are interested, let me know in the next day or two, the earlier the better.  This could fill up by tomorrow, or next week, but it will fill up.  I'll go with whichever time more people want.  The Green Line goes right to the restaurant, though it is slow.  They have valet parking.  Otherwise, parking is very difficult.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Harold&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the blurb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who missed our last sold out performances, the Fernando De Malaga Troupe will be performing live at Tasca on Monday 29th September. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two performances of live flamenco dancing will take place during dinner. Our regular menu is on offer for the evening. The purring castanets and colorful costumes of Isabella Rios and Sabrina Aviles will be backed up with passionate guitar playing of Juanito Pascal and the singing of Fernando de Malaga. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Juanito Pascal is one of the hottest flamenco guitarists to emerge in recent years&amp;quot; National Public Radio &amp;quot;Isabel Rios- more contained and erotic than her Riverdance counterpart&amp;quot; Boston Pheonix&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations for either Flamenco show may be made by return email: Please state the number in your party, whether you want the 6:30or 8:30 reservation time, and if you require a valet space. A $5 per person cover charge will be added to your dinner check. &lt;br /&gt;Classical Spanish Guitar Thursdays! &lt;br /&gt;Renowned guitarist Eric Anthony will be performing classical Spanish guitar music from 7 to 10 pm in the main dining room (no cover charge). Reservations are accepted and suggested.&lt;br /&gt;Best wishes,&lt;br /&gt;Dan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the hostess for the Meetup group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Harold</member_name><member_id>5109349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228093796000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-625</urlname><id>824450</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Food Snobs Unite (FSU) - Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221848338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Flamenco at Tasca (8:30pm)</name><id>8791652</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222734600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-625/events/8791652/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/4/global_2985684.jpeg</photo_url></item>