<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Revere Beach Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02151</zip><lat>42.407228</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Revere Beach (in front of the T station)</name><city>Revere</city><id>1049007</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.991365</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's squeeze every drop of Summer while it lasts by playing Beach Volleyball! Revere Beach, the oldest public beach in the US is easily accessible from Boston and a great place to play beach volleyball. This time we will setup closer to the &amp;quot;Bandstand&amp;quot; to avoid the the &amp;quot;rocky&amp;quot; area. There are outdoors showers and facilities, it's accessible by T and there's plenty of parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Players should hopefully fulfill this level: firm understanding of game strategy, with a varied grasp of skills (passing, setting, hitting; at least good in one), know the differences between the type of touches to do to the ball (and when to do them) and willing to do all the time the 3-touch dance (in order to achieve a spike at the end: pass, set, spike). If you notice that your level is a bit below other players, don't be afraid to ask for pointers. If you notice that you are slightly above other players, be helpful by pointing out tips.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Access by T: Revere Beach Station, walk straight to the beach and you will be by the &amp;quot;Bandstand&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:  There is ample parking along Revere Beach Blvd and Ocean Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommendation: bring bottles of water, or you will die by thirst while playing :D (especially the sunny days). I will be bringing my ice bag,&lt;br /&gt;you are welcome to keep your drinks cool. If your drinks occupy too much space, you have to share ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some rules that we usually like to follow (but may change if there is consensus, of course):&lt;br /&gt;- Rally scoring (there's point for your team even if you didn't serve).&lt;br /&gt;- If the ball touches the net while serving, it's a valid point.&lt;br /&gt;- We usually play sets of 25 points. At the end of the set, we exchange fields or mix teams (to try to make them more equivalent).&lt;br /&gt;- Every part of the body is valid to touch the ball.&lt;br /&gt;- Blocks don't count as touches for the touch count (3).&lt;br /&gt;- You cannot do a direct hit (from the net, as in a block) as a reception to the service.&lt;br /&gt;- When it's a set point for the team that serves, it has to be a &amp;quot;jump serve&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;- One of each team is normally selected as the setter (normally the one in the middle-up position, next to the net). Teammates should try to pass the ball to her so as she hits the 2nd touch to set. If no one calls the ball and the setter doesn't request &amp;quot;help&amp;quot;, the setter is supposed to do the 2nd by default (as in, in case of doubt). [This is not a rule, but a good practice.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO LET'S HAVE SOME FUN!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(If there are more than 12 people for a net, up to 14 people can play if 2 of them wait outside of the field for their position to be taken by rotation of the team. If we are more than 14, we will split by teams and play 15-point sets.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andres G. Aragoneses</member_name><member_id>8249754</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251834174000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251323325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beach Volleyball in Revere Beach (Recreational+)</name><id>11209602</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251660600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/11209602/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/3/global_1997523.jpeg</photo_url></item>