<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>12th Annual Red Dress Run for Women - A 5K event for all &lt;b&gt;participants&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A 5K run/walk celebrating women’s fitness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 11, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Start Time: 8:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;Asylum Avenue, Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 12th annual Hartford Women’s Race “The Red Dress Run For Women” is a 5K event that truly celebrates women’s fitness and health.  The start and finish line will be in beautiful Elizabeth Park, where over 15,000 roses will be in full bloom. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DEADLINE FOR RED DRESS RUN -&lt;/b&gt; Print, complete and mail or fax according to instructions on the form. Payment may be made by credit card or check (made payable to HMF). - Paper copies must by postmarked or faxed by - Friday, July 3, 2009. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Start Time: 8:30 a.m. &lt;br /&gt;Start in Elizabeth Park next to the Rose Garden. &lt;br /&gt;Counter clockwise around the full west loop &lt;br /&gt;Right to exit park onto Walbridge &lt;br /&gt;Right onto Bainbridge &lt;br /&gt;Right onto North Quaker &lt;br /&gt;Right onto Asylum &lt;br /&gt;Right on Prospect &lt;br /&gt;Into Elizabeth Park at first entrance &lt;br /&gt;Through park to finish line &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Post-Race Festivities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The positive post-race atmosphere is fostered by music, awards and the renowned buffet spread, which features our signature post race, guilt-free, FRESH STRAWBERRY SHORTCAKE for all participants and volunteers.   &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Also back by popular demand is the FINISH LINE VILLAGE, a vibrant festival of tents filled with information, goods and services important to athletic, fit women's lives.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2008 representatives included ConnectiCare, Women's Health Connecticut, Mary Kay, Lucy from Blue Back Square and many others. &lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in showcasing your business or product at this year's expo.  Sign up as expo vendor at the 2009 Red Dress Run for Women&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248992484000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>5K-Runners-Meetup</urlname><id>1354697</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>5K Runners Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245866728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>12th Annual Red Dress Run for Women </name><id>10726465</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247315400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/5K-Runners-Meetup/events/10726465/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/2/global_9325842.jpeg</photo_url></item>