<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Small Business Success Network for a no cost teleclass on powerful Facebook marketing strategies&lt;/strong&gt; with Mark Reinert and special guest Kim Reddington, business growth and marketing expert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discover Why Facebook is Quickly Becoming the Top Website in the World and Find Out How to Tap into over 800 Million People to Grow Your Business&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/4511552174/sbsnmtp"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/b/e/event_171790942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/4/a/event_171800042.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook has only been available to the public for a few years, but it has very quickly become an amazing marketing tool&lt;/strong&gt; for all types of businesses. There are many ways to market with Facebook. It’s easy to find a way that matches your personality, yet still be effective for growing your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This presentation will give you an overview of some important points to know about Facebook marketing.&lt;/strong&gt; There is a lot of talk around entrepreneurs about how to use Facebook effectively. Many of you have personal accounts, but are struggling with knowing how to use it for your business.  Kim has been using Facebook since 2007 and will share with you some personal stories of what Kim has learned and how you can apply that knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;During this presentation, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine whether you need to use Facebook for your business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discover the #1 little-known, yet powerful strategy that I use in Facebook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fnd out the main reason Facebook makes a great marketing tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discover the inside secret of why you should have a business page and a personal account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realize the types of updates and content you should be posting on your wall&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn what makes a great profile picture and how to get more advertising space out of your page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will walk away from this presentation knowing&lt;/strong&gt; whether Facebook is a marketing tool you should be tapping into (and the most effective way to use it for your business).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/4511552174/sbsnmtp"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/b/e/event_171790942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The featured speaker is Kim Reddington,&lt;/strong&gt; business growth and marketing expert. Kim’s entrepreneurial career started in 1995 after she decided that dropping her year old son off at day care every day was just too heart-wrenching. She realized the only way to have the flexibility she needed was to create it herself. That’s when she just quit and took off on her own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim’s journey has led her to helping other women entrepreneurs think big with their online marketing to get all the clients they need and is known as a Client-Generating Website Guru. She helps her clients to build a system around their website that will convert their prospective clients into paying clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Host: Mark Reinert,&lt;/strong&gt; Founder of Authentic Business Growth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Take Part &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cost for this training. Registration is required and you will be sent the access instructions immediately upon registration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/4511552174/sbsnmtp"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to reserve your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/4511552174/sbsnmtp"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/b/e/event_171790942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register above for free access. The recording will be made available to those who sign up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; We respect and protect your privacy. We will never sell your name or email address. When you sign up for a program, we will send information about the program, replays and related resources. You can unsubscribe at any time. Items offered in email, web content or on virtual events may be from carefully chosen affiliates who may (or may not) pay a commission to Authentic Business Growth if you purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure to mark your calendar now&lt;/strong&gt; so you don't forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Got Questions?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can post your questions below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Reddington</member_name><member_id>3156875</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Reinert</member_name><member_id>7305695</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351113796000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349755505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discover The Power of Facebook to Grow Your Business</name><id>86156562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351094400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/86156562/</event_url></item>