<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kennedy Plaza</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.825024</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greater Kennedy Plaza</name><city>Providence</city><id>701026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.410949</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey! Let's go ice skating Feb.4th,2012 at 6pm-7pm. Will meet-up at the Greater Kennedy Center, Providence, R.I. The ice rink is right there,across from Biltmore Hotel. Get rid of seasonal mood disorder or whatever it is and skate under the sky and bright lights of Providence R.I.!! So sharpen your skates,c'mon,lets meetup and have fun, would love to see LOTS of our awesome members there!!&amp;nbsp;Two other meetup groups are planning to attend also, and as you know, were planning on going out to the Piano Bar after ice skating at 7;30pm. You don't have to go ice skating, you can just go to the bar and meetup with our group and the other groups if you prefer. We have 18 awesome members right now for skating, and about the same for the bar,I have been told that it would be better if we&amp;nbsp;drive from Kennedy Center to Davol Sq. so we can work that out when we ice skate, I can take 4 people, sure we'll be all set. Rember that ice skating is weather permitting, but the bar is a go unless there is a blizzard! My tel.is 508 525 2719, call me if you need help finding us at the meetup, I'll try to use a cheat sheet and introduce everyone, I will need to know&amp;nbsp;if your going to the bar, I have to make reservations, so please keep that in mind,O.K.&amp;nbsp;that's it for now, hope to see you all&amp;nbsp;on Feb. 4th! Rich&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have on desert camo pants, my ice skating pants,can't miss me, call me if you need to.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332113911000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326126325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ice Skating</name><id>drtdlcyqdbgb</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328396400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/47335392/</event_url></item>