<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>415 Summer St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.344448</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 385-4000</phone><name>Boston Convention &amp; Exhibition Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>1563376</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.044821</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We need an assistant organizer to help on-site and the Auto Show Meetup is contingent upon someone volunteering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The New England International Auto Show is back in town at the Boston Convention and Exhibition Center in the Seaport District.  It is the premier showcase of the newest model year imported and domestic vehicles -- cars, vans, crossovers, hybrids, light trucks and sport utilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you have ever been to one of these shows you know that it is nice to go in a group but it is better to go with people who have the same show style.  Some people walk slowly through, booth by booth, others walk through quick and come back to what they want to see, and others just dart around.  My cousin is a true car aficionado and treats these like religious events, stopping to ask questions and pray to the road Gods of metal at every booth of auto worship.  I walk the aisles quickly and only stop when I see something that catches my eye (he will never miss it and if he did would mourn the whole year; and I haven’t been in years and only thought of it due to my role as assistant organizer).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At a headcount of 20 we can get a discount.  We will meet there, in the lobby, and try to break into smaller groups based upon styles.  Soooo, give some thought as to what kind of car show person you are…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;A full-on worshipper who will methodically work the show and stop at every booth (I may poke some good nature fun at this group but I have no issue with it – we each have our passions and interests and these folks take the show seriously);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;A casual stroller who will walk the floor in a methodical manner stopping here and there and attends as much for the atmosphere and people watching as for the cars;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;·&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;A&lt;/span&gt; zipper who (like the kid in the old cartoon series Family Circus) shoots around and stops only when something seems interesting and only so long as it holds their attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need an assistant organizer to help on-site and the Auto Show Meetup is contingent upon someone volunteering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Only sign up if you plan to go. We have had way to many no shows lately with the culminating comment being “Oh I sign up for lots of stuff and if I change my mind I just don’t go.”  No shows will be booted from the group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Take 75 seconds and read the whole listing…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Adults                         $12.00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Children (6-12)            $6.00 &lt;br /&gt;

 Children under 6          Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Discounts are available for groups of 20 or more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Show hours:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thursday, January 17: 12:00 PM - 9:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;

 Friday, January 18: 12:00 PM - 9:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;

 Saturday, January 19: 10:00 AM - 9:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunday, January 20: 10:00 AM - 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;

 Monday, January 21: 10:00 AM - 6:00 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Box Office closes 1 hour prior to the end of the Show each day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;*  The group discount is $3 per ticket.  For those who email about discrepancies in discounts, you will be sending $10 via PayPal and Paypal charges a transaction fee that includes a fixed charge per transaction of $0.30 plus 2.9%.  That is about  sixty cents per transaction.  We have rounded it to one dollar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.paragonexpo.com/index.php/NE-General/its-the-biggest-auto-show-in-new-england.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.paragonexpo.com/index.php/NE-General/its-the-biggest-auto-show-in-new-england.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will send out a meeting place the week prior to the event</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358619258000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>40-plus</urlname><id>1222683</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2699966431</group_lon><name>40/50 Something Year Olds - Men &amp; Women Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357478556000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Who wants to go to the Auto Show SATURDAY MORNING...</name><id>98173822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358607600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/40-plus/events/98173822/</event_url></item>