<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/3/b/event_31721531.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;This movie starts Taylor Lautner, the yummy shape shifter from the Twilight series as a super sleeper spy.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Lots of action and fun stunts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Show time is 5:45PM, I will be at the theater by 4:45 and we will go in for seats at 5:15.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Remember this is opening weekend, so if there is any buzz about a movie at all, it is a good idea to buy your tickets in advance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you miss the group before hand, we gather outside the room where the movie is being shown to discuss the film, allow for bathroom breaks and get a head count for all those who would like to head out for a drink and a bite to eat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Movie Details:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; September 23, 2011 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Lionsgate &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; John Singleton &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Shawn Christensen, Jeffrey Nachmanoff &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Taylor Lautner, Lily Collins, Alfred Molina, Jason Isaacs, Maria Bello, Denzel Whitaker, Michael Nyqvist, Sigourney Weaver &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Thriller &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.abductionthefilm.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Abductionthefilm.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; Taylor Lautner stars as a young man unwittingly thrust into a deadly world of covert espionage in Lionsgate's action-thriller, "Abduction," directed by John Singleton. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For as long as he can remember, Nathan Harper (Taylor Lautner) has had the uneasy feeling that he's living someone else's life. When he stumbles upon an image of himself as a little boy on a missing persons website, all of Nathan's darkest fears come true: he realizes his parents are not his own and his life is a lie, carefully fabricated to hide something more mysterious and dangerous than he could have ever imagined. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Just as he begins to piece together his true identity, Nathan is targeted by a team of trained killers, forcing him on the run with the only person he can trust, his neighbor, Karen (Lily Collins). Every second counts as Nathan and Karen race to evade an army of assassins and federal operatives. But as his opponents close in, Nathan realizes that the only way he'll survive &amp;ndash; and solve the mystery of his elusive biological father &amp;ndash; is to stop running and take matters into his own hands.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meeup pin.  The movie is upstairs, so I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317065102000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307976674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Abduction (5:45PM Show)</name><id>22009111</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316983500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/22009111/</event_url></item>