<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Lake Moxie Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04985</zip><lat>45.345524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>CrabApple Whitewater</name><city>The Forks</city><id>8342762</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.948799</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be rafting the Dead River on October 6 thru CrabApple Whitewater, Inc located at 3 Lake Moxie Rd, The Forks, Maine 04985. &lt;br /&gt;

 October 6th is a scheduled release of 6000 cfs which is considered a high water release. &lt;br /&gt;

 Below is a basic outline of the trip. &lt;br /&gt;

 For additional information, please go to their website at &lt;a href="http://www.crabappleinc.com/maine/index.shtml"&gt;http://www.crabappleinc.com/maine/index.shtml. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; When making reservations, please put your name under “The Boria Party”. This way we can ensure that we are in the same boats. &lt;br /&gt;

 Also, for those interested, we will probably schedule hikes/events for that Sunday and Monday. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost is $85.00 a person. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Dead River has ten special high volume dam releases each season that produce big whitewater action over 16 miles. The river bed drops steadily during the entire run and produces long, consistent action that builds throughout the day in Class III-IV rapids such as "Humpty Dumpty", "Elephant Rock" and "Spruce Ledges". Each rapid includes long wave trains and sudden drops into deep holes. The Dead continues to build through dozens of rapids and culminates in the LONGEST RAPID IN THE NORTHEAST, Class IV-V "Poplar Hill Falls". "Poplar" on its own is one mile of whitewater with huge standing waves and deep, turbulent holes. When you combine "Poplar" with the rest of this action packed trip, you have the finest raft trip in the Northeast! Don't miss this special river adventure which guides and rafting veterans cherish each year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL MEET AT THE ABOVE</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349535705000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343048683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rafting the Dead River on October 6</name><id>74514382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349524800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/74514382/</event_url></item>