<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you go through life with a feeling that something is missing? Do you carry around baggage from hurts in the past? Are there certain things in life that scare you and prevent you from feeling free to fully live? Is your body suffering or just not as healthy and vibrant as you would like it to be? Do you wish you could really know joy and fulfillment? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;True healing takes place on every level. It is a thorough process not only reserved for the special or the enlightened. People try medicines, herbs, the right vitamin or health regimen, psychotherapy, various energy modalities; but still there are no lasting results for the one who desires real healing. The healing has to be deeper than what these physical remedies can provide in order to create real and lasting results. If you want to feel free and whole on the inside, come to this workshop and learn what you will need to open your way to true healing at the spiritual level, which will shine out and heal your whole being and help you feel alive again. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------&lt;br /&gt;About the presenter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.centersoflight.org/mother_clare.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mother Clare Watts&lt;/a&gt; is a mystic; ordained priest; Master Teacher of Christian mysticism; and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 15 &lt;a href="http://www.centersoflight.org" target="_blank"&gt;Centers of Light&lt;/a&gt; in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she co-directs the effort to develop the &lt;a href="http://www.sophiapeacecenter.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Sophia Peace Center&lt;/a&gt;. She is the author of &lt;a href="http://motherclarewatts.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path To Enlightenment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347891000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283257067000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Healing Your Body, Mind, Heart &amp; Soul</name><id>14602409</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283470200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/14602409/</event_url></item>