<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/4/e/event_9103086.jpeg" width="286" height="227" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;"Congratulations! Today is your day! You're off to great places! You're off and away!", the immortal words of Dr. Suess. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Where do you go in your dreams? Places in dreams may have very significant meanings. A childhood home may represent your self. The basement of a house may represent your unconscious. An automobile driving down a roadway may be your journey through life. Flying up into the air may indicate soaring feelings of happiness. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We may visit other dimensions, planets, times, heavenly realms, forests, or tropical islands. Some people actually choose where they go in their dreams. Where would you choose to go to if you could visit a particular place in your dreams? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We will explore the meanings of place in dreams as well as how to visit particular places. Bring your dreams to share if you choose to. All are welcome, whether you choose to share your dreams or not. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This Meetup is facilitated by Deerheart, dream guide and experienced explorer of the dream realms. He has been studying dreams for over 25 years, including  dreamwork, shamanism, psychology, empowerment, and healing. For more information about him, visit his website, &lt;a href="http://www.visionarydreamguide.com/"&gt;Visionary Dream Guide&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left through angel doorway, into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342797008000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340855136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oh, the Places You'll Go!</name><id>71085282</id><headcount>6</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342566000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/71085282/</event_url></item>