<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Jim Roper, Universal Plastics, Holyoke&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jim Roper, Sales Manager at Universal Plastics, will provide a quick overview on selecting the correct plastic process for new products, then delve a little deeper into thermoforming and why it is a good choice for products that meet certain criteria. Jim will also   talk about the importance of market research and his experience with otherwise good products that have floundered because of lack of market research. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Universal Plastics is a 43 year old family run company in Holyoke that uses thermoform processes to make a wide array of products. – UP has been an industry leader in the development of the process. Manufacturing components for corporate giants such as Pratt &amp;amp; Whitney and Sikorsky and local companies such as Bay State Health, Universal Plastics has a very diverse portfolio that includes working with start up entrepreneurs needing prototypes and small runs of a few hundred or few thousand items. An article in the July 21, 2008 issue of Business West describes two such products, the Garden glide and a new table game. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Universal Plastics’ web site says: “As we have grown, we have refined and further developed the thermoforming process to allow the manufacture of large and complex products that could never have been conceived in the previous generation. Today's thermoformed products can match the quality and finish of injection molding, in high performance plastics, and in sizes that dwarf the capabilities of most molders.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.universalplastics.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.universalp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the SEC Education Room 1st Level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Cormier</member_name><member_id>6323188</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228348573000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220485946000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Innovators' Resource Network October Meetup</name><id>8683150</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222901100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/8683150/</event_url></item>