<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of MA State Routes 9 and 16</address_2><address_1>Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-650-3659</phone><name>The Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>87393</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a an off-topic activity suggestion, by one of the Meetup members who welcomes anyone to join him there! (Maynard, I tried to reach you by email but no luck so am adding this note for you! Similar event announcements, please email or post on board. OK to use the Meetup event feature to set a specific meeting time and place with Meetup members to attend events)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:00 Noon - A GREAT FAMILY OUTING (Last year's ASIAN delegation was incredibly LARGE - and that's heartening!)  At the intersection of state routes 16 and 27&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive and schmooze - walk around the Peace Abbey and take in the setting - that's the issue if we lose it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 PM VEGAN MEAL - pre-registered prix fixe (fixed price) meal (with Evelyn Kimber, BVS, EBKimber@GMail.com) &lt;br /&gt;

 Share delicious vegan cuisine. This has traditionally been a potluck, but we are exploring another option for this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The VeganDinner prepared by the former Country Life staff required pre-registration through BVS - &lt;a href="http://www.BostonVeg.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.BostonVeg.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Check with CDAJR@HotMail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Special treat: The Like No Udder vegan soft serve ice cream truck will be with us, serving up softies, milkshakes, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 3 PM SPEAKER PRESENTATION - GARY KOWALSKI &lt;br /&gt;

 BVS is pleased to present Gary Kowalski, author of bestselling books on animals, nature, history and spirituality. A graduate of Harvard College and the Harvard Divinity School, his work has been translated into German, French, Spanish, Japanese, Chinese and Czech. Gary's work centers on the connection of spirit and nature. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Among Gary Kowalski's celebrated titles: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Souls of Animals &lt;br /&gt;

 Goodbye, Friend: Healing Wisdom for Anyone Who Has Ever Lost a Pet &lt;br /&gt;

 Earth Day: An Alphabet Book (for children) &lt;br /&gt;

 The Bible According To Noah: Theology As If Animals Mattered &lt;br /&gt;

 Blessings of the Animals: Celebrating Our Kinship With All Creation (Fall 2012) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We'll use the large white UU church next to the Peace Abbey for the speaker program.  &lt;br /&gt;

 It seats 350, so there will be plenty of seats! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If you bring your own picnic and eat on the grounds, you can enjoy the Peace Abbey, the animals, other people, and Gary Kowalski's talk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maynard S. Clark</member_name><member_id>83043</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339851566000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338657976000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Off-Topic: BVS' annual event at the PEACE ABBEY - June 3 - 12 noon - 5 pm</name><id>67430982</id><duration>18000000</duration><headcount>145</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338739200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/67430982/</event_url></item>