<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:35, so &lt;b&gt;we'll meet right inside (or outside, if it's nice out!) the ticket lobby at 7:00.&lt;/b&gt; I saw the original CotT a few weeks back on AMC (the channel, not the chain!) and laughed at the pure cheesiness of the effects, while being impressed at the storyline. This time around, the story won't be new, but the effects surely will!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: This is a 3D movie, so &lt;b&gt;it costs $11, not the usual $8&lt;/b&gt;. Popcorn and soda are still $3 each, which is a huge deal because of the new pricing structure of the snacks at the concession counter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call me if you're running late, get lost, or have to change your RSVP last minute.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow for Clash of the Titans-3D!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trailers for &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810081563/info" target="_blank"&gt;Clash Of The Titans&lt;/a&gt; look like all the best (and most gorey?) parts of the Lord of the Rings series. Come for the creatures, stay for the popcorn!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ultimate struggle for power pits men against kings and kings against gods. But the war between the gods themselves could destroy the world. Born of a god but raised as a man, Perseus is helpless to save his family from Hades, vengeful god of the underworld. With nothing left to lose, Perseus volunteers to lead a dangerous mission to defeat Hades before he can seize power from Zeus and unleash hell on earth. Leading a daring band of warriors, Perseus sets off on a perilous journey deep into forbidden worlds. Battling unholy demons and fearsome beasts, he will only survive if he can accept his power as a god, defy his fate and create his own destiny. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($11.00 each for FMM members and their guests because it's a 3D movie). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Clash of the Titans!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271545718000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269369363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clash of the Titans-3D</name><id>12969802</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271372400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12969802/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>