<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Love Actually plays like a greatest-hits album of modern British comedy, spinning all your favorite tunes in just the right order.&amp;quot; - Bill Muller, Arizona Republic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The film lives up to its hype&amp;quot; - Stina Chyn, Film Threat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Plenty of entertainment in this well acted ensemble comedy that Robert Altman could easily have put his name on.&amp;quot;  - Wesley Lovell, Oscar Guy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Whatever the actors are given to do they make so delightful -- or so delightfully moving -- that Love Actually wins out over its wobbles.&amp;quot; - Stanley Kauffmann, New Republic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;... a terrific film&amp;quot; - Richard Roeper&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This summer, the Boston Public Library has decided to show Christmas movies and specials throughout July and August. The movies are free and they have a good setup for showing movies, as well as a loyal following of people who show up every Monday for the free film regardless of what it is (probably because it's free).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Love Actually is a romantic comedy from the same people who brought you Notting Hill, Four Weddings and a Funeral and Bridget Jones' Diary. The film is set mostly in London and revolves around about a dozen love stories. There are several great actors and actresses in the film including Emma Thompson, Liam Neeson, Colin Firth, Laura Linney and even Rowan Atkinson. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know the starting time is a bit on the early side, but I don't think the film will really start until 5:45 or 6, since sometimes the films at the library get a late start and there's a 13 minute short preceding Love, Actually -- Silent Night: The Story of the Christmas Carol, which was filmed in Austria and shows the factors that contributed to the creation of that song. Also, Love, Actually is very long for a romantic comedy (2 hours and 15 minutes, which Ebert and I both think was too long for that film), so you're not going to miss a lot if you get there half an hour into the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film should get out a little after eight, so I was thinking that maybe we could get coffee/tea or Thai appetizers afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215811883000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214532670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Christmas in July: Love Actually</name><id>8224924</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215639000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8224924/</event_url></item>