<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tonystrackdays.com/category/7744/schedule-and-group-info.htm"&gt;Tony's track day - NJMP - April 29,30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tonystrackdays.com/category/3385/new-jersey-motorsports-park.htm"&gt;New Jersey Motorsports Park &lt;br /&gt;

 8000 Dividing Creek Rd., &lt;br /&gt;

 Millville, NJ 08332&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most important thing you can do to ensure a great day at the track is to arrive early. You should arrive at the track early (preferably the night before) to give yourself ample time to unload and get through registration, which opens at 0700am. Some good items to bring along are an air bottle and air gauge, fuel cans, a tool box, duct tape, and a friend (if possible). Do not duct tape your friend! You can rent gear for any of the track days - be sure to make reservations in advance. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.tonystrackdays.com/category/99/bike-preparation.htm"&gt;Motorcycle Preparation&lt;/a&gt; - Your motorcycle should most importantly be clean and oil tight. Tires and brakes that are in good condition (50% material or more) are a must. You should remove your mirrors, tape up all of your lights, and its a good idea to cover up your speedometer (helps focus on the track). I also highly recommend removing your side stands, although its not required. Be aware that they can drag on many bikes. You also need to remove all of your antifreeze and replace it with water or approved race coolant. If you plan to ride to the track, leave yourself plenty of time to prepare your bike in the morning. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.tonystrackdays.com/category/3375/rider-preparation.htm"&gt;Rider Equipment&lt;/a&gt; - Helmets must be at least Snell 2005 approved and be in excellent condition. They must be no more than 5yrs old. You need gauntlet (over the wrist) gloves and over the ankle boots (work boots are OK). Your riding suit is required to be full leather and if it is two-piece it MUST be zipped together at the waist. Anyone looking to rent gear, please &lt;a href="http://www.tonystrackdays.com/category/3638/leather-rental.htm"&gt;check out the details here&lt;/a&gt;. All rental equipment should be reserved in advance. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.njmp.com/facility/accommodations-rentals/places-to-stay-millville-nj-hotels.html"&gt;Recommended Hotels near NJMP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a side note: A Go Pro HD (or similiar) may be mounted on your bike for the Track Day. Fuel is available at select times (usually around noon). Please bring your bike fueled up for the track, or bring a 5gal gas can with you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a yellowish-green BMW in the garages at the track</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shanks</member_name><member_id>8162172</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335697925000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><id>1535765</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326385150000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tony's track day - April 29, 30 @ NJMP Thunderbolt</name><id>47816072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335693600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/events/47816072/</event_url></item>