<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Winner of the Grand Jury Prize at the 2011 Cannes Film Festival, the deeply moving new film by brothers &lt;strong&gt;Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(L'Enfant, Rosetta)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;delves into the emotional life of troubled 11-year-old Cyril, played with riveting intensity by newcomer Thomas Doret. When his father (J&amp;eacute;r&amp;eacute;mie Renier) abandons him, Cyril at first refuses to admit it, claiming his father just forgot to say where he was going. Eventually forced to face hard reality, Cyril then obsessively tries to get his bicycle back (also missing). Almost by accident, he becomes the ward of a kind hairdresser (C&amp;eacute;cile de France,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hereafter, L'Auberge Espanole&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;), a woman who seems surprised to find herself so determined to help him. With his wild, unpredictable behavior and his disastrous search for father figures, Cyril risks losing her&amp;mdash;though she refuses to give up without a fight. Full of heartbreaking betrayals and unexpected grace,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Kid with a Bike&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a film about a child alone, learning to become good. Nominated for 4 European Film Awards, winning Best Screenplay.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ifcfilms.com/films/the-kid-with-a-"&gt;The Kid With a Bike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.avclub.com/articles/jeanpierre-and-luc-dardenne,31135/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.avclub.com/articles/jeanpierre-and-luc-dardenne,31135/" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;"The characters move restlessly within fences and walls both real and imagined, often bumping hard against the limits that confine them. They are creatures of need, lonely and deeply vulnerable, but with an almost-feral determination to survive and hold on to the minimal things that constitute their lives. Where other filmmakers draw the parameters of their world through establishing shots, the Dardennes merely follow their heroes&amp;mdash;over the shoulder, with a handheld camera&amp;mdash;as they find the borders on foot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After, we'll enjoy an dinner and conversation at one of Kendall Square's Restaurant Revival Hot Spots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will gather the group after close of credits in the lobby area INSIDE the Kendall near the ticket taker so that we can use the restroom and meet</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333595729000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332032108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Kid With a Bike</name><id>56774932</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333311300000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/56774932/</event_url></item>