<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1187 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343877</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Temple Ohabei Shalom</name><city>Brookline</city><id>831141</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Fresh from her premier at Filter Magazine's Cultures Collide Festival in Los Angeles, the Boston Jewish Music Festival is proud to present the area debut of Israeli singer/songwriter/actress Efrat Ben Tzur. She will be performing on Wednesday, October 10 at 7:30 pm at Temple Ohabei Shalom, 1187 Beacon Street, Brookline. Specially priced student tickets of only $10 are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An acclaimed Israeli singer and actress, Efrat released her debut album "Diving" in 2001 and her second album "Efrat Ben Zur" in 2006; both albums received enthusiastic reviews. Her new album "Robin" was released at the end of March and was voted the #2 Album of the Year by readers of Haaretz newspaper. It's a collection of Emily Dickinson's poems set to music composed by Ben Tzur. She will be performing these songs as well as others based on the poetry of Leah Goldberg in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concert is part of Daniel Pearl World Music Days, inspired by and dedicated to the legacy of this a Jewish American journalist/musician who became an icon of the borderless outreach of music and a symbol of Jewish pride, American pride, love of Israel and an unchallenged indictment of the ideology of hate.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349927647000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349223379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Israeli Artist: Efrat Ben Tzur</name><id>85210062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349911800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/85210062/</event_url></item>