<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Kennedy School - Belfer, Weil Town Hall, Lobby Level</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10300462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Governance as Leadership&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Approaches to Governing Nonprofits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Harvard University Frontline with Faculty Seminar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All Frontline with Faculty seminars are open to the public.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WILLIAM RYAN | Adjunct Lecturer in Public Policy, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, November 20 &lt;br /&gt;

12:30 – 1:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Belfer, Weil Town Hall, Lobby Level, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably no feature of nonprofit organizational life is as vexing and challenging as the board of directors. In this session, Bill Ryan proposes new approaches to governing nonprofits, focusing on the challenges of both boards and the executives who must figure out how to lead alongside them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;William P. Ryan is Adjunct Lecturer in Public Policy at the Harvard Kennedy School and is a consultant to nonprofit organizations and foundations. Both his consulting and research focus on nonprofit organizational effectiveness. He has explored how several forces—including board governance, access to capital, foundation grant making practices and competition with for-profit firms—shape the capacity of nonprofits to deliver on their missions. He currently directs the Nonprofit Governance and Accountability Project, a joint initiative of the Hauser Center and Harvard Law School aimed at engaging Harvard researchers in critical questions related to nonprofit governance. He is co-author of Governance as Leadership: Reframing the Work of Nonprofit Boards (honored with awards from the Association of Fundraising Professionals, Council for the Advancement and Support of Education and Independent Sector) and High Performance Nonprofit Organizations: Managing Upstream for Greater Impact. His articles include “Virtuous Capital: What Foundations Can Learn from Venture Capitalists” and “The New Landscape for Nonprofits” in Harvard Business Review.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frontline with Faculty Series is a venue for Harvard faculty affiliated with the Hauser Center to share their work and research with faculty colleagues, as well as students in an informal setting that will allow for spirited discussion, debate and exchange. The seminars link faculty experts from Harvard Schools and beyond on a wide range of topics.  The Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations at Harvard University seeks to expand understanding and accelerate critical thinking about civil society among scholars, practitioners, policy makers and the general public, by encouraging scholarship, developing curriculum, fostering mutual learning between academics and practitioners, and shaping policies that enhance the sector and its role in society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353443485000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352816239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Governing Nonprofits</name><id>91198492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353432600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/91198492/</event_url></item>