<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;PyCon 2012 is coming up in March in Santa Clara. In this second of two sessions, four Boston-area speakers will practice their presentations. If you can't make it to PyCon, this is a great way to see some of the PyCon talks, and also help your fellow Bostonians polish their presentations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stop Writing Classes&lt;/strong&gt;, Jack Diederich (Intermediate)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Classes are great but they are also overused. Classes must be nouns but not every noun must be a class. If your class only has two methods and one of them is __init__ you probably meant to write a function. This talk will describe examples of class overuse taken from real world code and refactor the unnecessary classes, exceptions, and modules out of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pragmatic Unicode, or, How do I stop the pain?&lt;/strong&gt;, Ned Batchelder (Novice)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python has great Unicode support, but it's still your responsibility to handle it properly. I'll do a quick overview of what Unicode is, but only enough to get your program working properly. I'll describe strategies to make your code work, and keep it working, without getting too far afield in Unicode la-la-land.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity in practice: How the Boston Python Meetup grew to 1000 people and over 15% women&lt;/strong&gt;, Jessica McKellar &amp;amp; Asheesh Laroia (Intermediate)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you bring more women into programming communities with long-term, measurable results? In this talk we'll analyze our successful effort, the Boston Python Workshop, which brought over 200 women into Boston's Python community this year. We'll talk about lessons learned running the workshop, the dramatic effect it has had on the local user group, and how to run a workshop in your city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pizza will be provided by &lt;strong&gt;HubSpot&lt;/strong&gt;, first drinks at Meadhall by &lt;strong&gt;WebReply&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ned Batchelder</member_name><member_id>1824278</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332462484000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>127</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318108515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PyCon on the Charles, part 2</name><id>36663162</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330560000000</time><rsvp_limit>140</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/36663162/</event_url></item>