<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Amory St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.316986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>Center Of Light ~ Boston</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>350786</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102680</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Workshop:  Silence&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, February 6 • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Donation: $25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is said that true inner silence can bring one into contact with the divine or the &amp;quot;still small voice within.&amp;quot; Various spiritual traditions speak of the importance of quietude and the stillness of mind and spirit in order for transformative and essential spiritual growth to occur. How, then, does one come to this place of spiritual silence and stillness when our minds are filled with chaos and chatter? In this seminar you will learn the origin of the chaos and chatter and how to connect with the source of true silence within and all around you. Don't miss this opportunity to know for yourself the peace that lies dormant inside of you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has devoted his life in service to God; for over 20 years, he has served as a Priest and Master Teacher. Currently, he serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ/Sophia, teaching and ministering to his spiritual students, and guiding fifteen Centers of Light and their ministers around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father Peter's music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within. Listen to his music on Sophia Radio. When not traveling, Father Peter lives at the Center of Light in Chicago, IL.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Located just around the corner from the Stony Brook T-stop on the orange line.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234139857000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229625595000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop:  Silence</name><id>9359122</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233966600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/9359122/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/0/global_6658400.jpeg</photo_url></item>