<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1678 Asylum Avenue</address_2><address_1>St Joseph University</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06117</zip><lat>41.779681</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>646 688 6038</phone><name>Hoffman Auditorium in The Bruyette Athenaeum</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>872424</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.731273</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A unique event!&lt;br /&gt;Saint Joseph College presents the documentary &amp;quot;The Cheese Nun&amp;quot;, a one-hour PBS film.  It will include a live question-and-answer session with Mother Noella Marcellino, the subject of the film.  She took science courses at UCONN, focusing her research on the microbiology of cheese ripening.  She used an electron microscope to study the fungi and bacteria which developed on the surface of the cheese.  She won a Fulbright to study in France to collect fungi from cheese caves and stayed on for three years on a grant from the French government.  Her studies brought her worldwide fame.  This event will take place on March 11 from 5:00-6:30 and includes a cheese tasting reception. FREE&lt;br /&gt;Then, come on over to Panera (distance 1 mile) for our 7:00 groupe de conversation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Asylum Avenue is easy to find.  It is the next avenue south of and parallel to the Albany Avenue where Panera is.  The college is between Steele Road and Trout Brook Drive.  The hard part is: There are TWO driveways into the college.  Use the one closest to Trout Brook Drive.  Park in the first lot on the left.  Walk across the driveway and the first building you come to is the one you want. It has a long name:Carol Autorina/Bruyette Atheneum/Hoffman Auditorium  but really it's just the first door on the right.  Come for the college event or Panera  or both!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236978910000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French</urlname><id>459167</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Groupe de French</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233978081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Double event:Second Wednesday Groupe de French and Cheese Tasting!</name><id>9691456</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236805200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French/events/9691456/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/7/global_1365207.jpeg</photo_url></item>