<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Ipswich St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347467</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-437-0300 </phone><name>Jillians</name><city>Boston</city><id>790541</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094019</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>group fee + $5 for pool</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We're heading to Jillian's* for Billiard's for Justice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't worry if you don't rock the cue stick. Lots of people aren't that great at pool, but some SoJusters have claimed to have the skills. So show up for lessons, laughs, or just good people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have a few tables reserved for the pool sharks, but plenty of non-billiards hanging out as well. Jillian's has some great appetizers and a full bar which no doubt we'll be taking advantage of...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while avoiding hitting the 8 ball, are seeking like-minded progressives to play pool with in Boston, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. If you want to build a strong cross-issue social justice movement, SoJust is for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pool tables are reserved from 6:00-8:00PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Sorry, this event is 21+ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Take the Green line to Kenmore Square, bear left onto Brookline Avenue, take the second left onto Lansdowne Street, at the end of the street make a left onto Ipswich Street - you will see the entrance on the left hand side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the 'Message Board' and are encouraged to suggest and co-host events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt;  Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and learn about our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/pages/Annual_Membership_Fee_details/"&gt;Suggested Annual Membership Fee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239836578000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235927316000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Billiards for Justice</name><id>9851482</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238104800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/9851482/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_7503099.jpeg</photo_url></item>