<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Kilmer Park is a large wooded area in south Brookline with many wide trails, a pond and a stream running through it.  We will walk through the park and then over to the Allendale Farm Stand which opens Apr 3. We will walk along road on the side of the farm and up to Walnut Hills Cemetery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the walk we will have lunch at the Arboretum Village Coffee House where we started the walk. Apparently they have some really unique sandwiches there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arboretum Village Coffee House&lt;br /&gt;1420 Centre St&lt;br /&gt;Roslindale, MA 02131&lt;br /&gt;(617) 327-9256&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From their website:&lt;br /&gt;www.allandalefarm.com&lt;br /&gt;Allandale Farm is Boston’s last working farm. We are located on the Boston/Brookline line near the Arnold Arboretum and the Faulkner Hospital. The farm specializes in sustainably grown fresh produce grown on our farm and marketed primarily through our own retail market.  We also sell fresh produce through Whole Foods markets in Brighton, MA and Cambridge, MA and through a local broker and a few restaurants. Our field crops are Certified Naturally Grown using organic methods. The farm specializes in hardy annual and perennial plants in the spring, cut flowers and vegetables in season, hardy ‘mums, pumpkins, fresh native turkeys and Christmas trees as the seasons wind down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our retail market specializes in local, sustainably grown fresh produce. We will buy from other local producers first to supplement our own production then out-of-region, if necessary. The market also carries a nice line of products from other local or MA producers which complement our own product (viz. salad dressings, snacks).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allandale Farm has tilled the same soils for more than 250 years.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the coffee shop</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239028868000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237767696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kilmer Park / Allendale Farm walk</name><id>10011853</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238855400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10011853/</event_url></item>