<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Here is the camping info I promised for the weekend of adventure in Charlemont, MA at Zoar!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your not doing the rafting on Saturday or the Zip-lining on Sunday, your still welcome to join our group for the camping!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be staying at Mohawk Park in Charlemont, MA.  The campground is about 2.3 miles away from Zoar.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This campground has wooded, sunny as well as riverside sites.  It has a restaurant with a full lunch and dinner menu.  They also have a nightclub on the promises with weekend entertainment and I've been told it's a popular place with the locals.  It was recommend to me by the people at Zoar.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohawk Park &lt;br /&gt;559 Tea Street, Route 2 &lt;br /&gt;Mohawk Trail &lt;br /&gt;(413)339-4470 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is located on Mohawk Trail (Route 2) From I-91 in Mass take exit 26 to Route 2 west.  It's about 20 miles from Route 91 on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will be putting a block of sites aside for our group.  Please let them know that you are with the Ivone and The Fun Single party and they will put you in our &amp;quot;block&amp;quot; or if all &amp;quot;our&amp;quot; sites are already taken, as close to us as possible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have booked my site from the afternoon of Friday, September 11th through the evening of Sunday, September 13th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call them as soon as you can to book your site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They charge by the tent not the site, the price is $30 per tent with a maximum of 4 people per tent.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Fun Single or Ivone camp site</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281130664000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Ma-NH-Singles-Club</urlname><id>1356935</id><group_lat>43.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Trailblazers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250719341000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping weekend</name><id>11151562</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252704600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Ma-NH-Singles-Club/events/11151562/</event_url></item>