<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Longfellow Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375848</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Friends Meeting House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>918727</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.127358</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Learn the key to experiencing hands-off, clothes-on, full-body orgasms. Everyone has the dormant ability pre-wired in their nervous system to experience full-body orgasms. It just takes learning the key to awaken this inherent ability. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open yourself to the invigorating flow of your own vital energy! Become enlivened by the co-created field we all tap into. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be working with breath, intention, movement, and sound to move sexual energy through the various energy centers of the body. You will learn fun techniques you can practice any time, alone or with a partner! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover how these ancient practices can enhance your life with more peace, vitality, joy and expansive pleasure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to all, regardless of relationship status, gender identity or sexual orientation. No previous experience or partner necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Bodyworker, Tantra Educator and Intimacy Coach with over twenty years experience in the fields of Somatics and Consciousness. Through a unique synthesis of diverse modalities Brynn assists individuals and couples in increasing their capacity for Intimacy and Pleasure, and in accessing their full Aliveness and Passion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email Brynn (organizer) for information on Private Tantra Instruction and Intimacy Coaching. Limited summer appointments available. On-going sessions available in person, by phone or skype.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>enter the building on the left.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280754183000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277078244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Erotic Energy Play</name><id>13858584</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280446200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/13858584/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/6/0/global_15857984.jpeg</photo_url></item>