<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Summer St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06901</zip><lat>41.054741</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-353-4363</phone><name>MARIA FIORAS DANCE STUDIO &amp; CLUB</name><city>Stamford</city><id>798607</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.540680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a party for those that are single and have single friends they think would have a blast meeting others to date or be friends. A speed dancing mixer will be hosted by Maria Fiora- who will teach some fun swing, and latin dancing - we will also play the dating game, drinks, food and more=sINGLES WHO miNGLE&lt;br /&gt;aDMISSION IS -you must bring a single friend who isnt attached and  $15 admission( helps with having a couple staff members to help clean up and assist with dancing) with the catch of bringing at least one single friend who is not in a relationship- bring a drink also or food item to share, we will also have items. After there will be dj's music,giveaways, and more. &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP me directly at mariafiora@optonline.net or call me&lt;br /&gt;if you are coming from new haven area there is no traffic at that time coming south. &lt;br /&gt;Dress is sexy and nice-no jeans. age group please 30-60's&lt;br /&gt;What have you got to lose but have a great time and meet some really run people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check in between 7:30-8pm -then the fun will start&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301704677000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>WE NEED TO GET A BIGGER FUN GROUP and MIX SINGLE FRIENDS FROM ALL OVER CT.</why><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298810689000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SMINGLE ON APRIL FOOLS</name><id>16721155</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301700600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/16721155/</event_url></item>