<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bay State Rd. and Sherborn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.350321</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Soldiers Field Playground</name><city>Boston</city><id>845399</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100365</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello dearest runners!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COME ONE COME ALL to the NIFTY-est 5k and Food Fundraiser of 2009!!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you cool cats may already know, but this coming Spring I am embarking on an adventure of a lifetime.  &lt;b&gt;I will be running across America, from Boston to San Diego!&lt;/b&gt;  This has been a dream of mine for the last 10 years of my life, and now, it's time to put my feet to the road.  WHY?!?!  I am 100% passionate about empowering people to follow their passions and dreams.  Look inside yourself and embrace what you love and pursue it!  Using this run as a metaphor, I will be spreading this message across the country, and FUNDRAISING for a charity that empowers girls through running - &lt;a href="http://www.gotr.org" target="_blank"&gt;Girls on the Run&lt;/a&gt;.  You can learn more about my run and donate on my website &lt;a href="http://www.paveyourlane.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.paveyourlane.com&lt;/a&gt;. (My website is still a work in progress.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 9-month TransAmerica run will also cost a bit of dough...and I could really really really use your help...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, this 5K and Food Fundraiser goes like this.  Meet at the playground at 2pm and we will run to &lt;a href="http://www.veggieplanet.net" target="_blank"&gt;Veggie Planet&lt;/a&gt; for an ALL YOU CAN EAT PIZZA, ETC. BUFFET!  Veggie Planet has amazingly donated all this food for up to 50 people, and I will collecting donations (suggested $20) at the door to go towards my run's costs and the charity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you cannot make it to the 5K but want to come to Veggie Planet to EAT, meet us at 2:45pm at Veggie Planet.  &lt;b&gt;You must RSVP if you will come to eat because it is limited to the first 50 people!&lt;/b&gt;  Email me at Katie.Visco@gmail.com to RSVP for food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions?!  Email or call me at 630.660.4597.  I really hope you all can make it!  It would mean the world to me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Love,&lt;br /&gt;Katie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ps.  Soldier Field Playground is the playground along the south side of the Charles River Path, about .3 miles WEST of the Mass Ave. Bridge.  Pretty convenient.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for playground and big group -on Charles path just west of Mass Ave Bridge.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233602420000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231284612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Run Across America 5K and Food Fundraiser!</name><id>9462253</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233428400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/9462253/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/0/global_6860176.jpeg</photo_url></item>