<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Fort St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01103</zip><lat>42.103832</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Student Prince</name><city>Springfield</city><id>791616</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.593380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Es ist Oktober und wir haben kein Oktoberfest gefeiert!&lt;br /&gt;Wir haben eine lange Strecke zwischen Meetups so...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you decide last-minute to come, that's OK. Just call my cell phone 860-573-3501 to let me know. Danke!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, to try something new before then, we have a &amp;quot;field trip&amp;quot; to the Student Prince!&lt;br /&gt;This is a German restaurant in Springfield, Mass.  Es is seit 1935 geoffnet and according to Gourmet Magazine &amp;quot;one of 21 legendary restaurants you must visit&amp;quot;.  You can look at the menus on their website - they have a lot of choices and it is less expensive than the other restaurant that was mentioned. I have never been there, so it will be an adventure!&lt;br /&gt;YOU WILL NEED TO LET US KNOW THAT YOU ARE COMING.  The restaurant needs to know how many are coming.  This will be a chance to have some German time on a Sunday. It's open to all of our group- plus maybe some people who are unable to join us on Thursday nights will be able to come.&lt;br /&gt;For those who would like to carpool, we could meet at the Panera parking lot at 4:30.&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you'd like to come, and please pass the word on to others who might be interested in practicing their German. THIS WILL BE OUR 50th MEETUP!!  Come celebrate with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next Kaffeeklatsch at Panera is November 6th - just after election day!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask for Dianne or the German group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226015782000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Deutsch speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>german-425</urlname><id>438488</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford German Kaffeeklatsch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224275151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>German Restaurant trip!</name><id>8981389</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225054800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/german-425/events/8981389/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/b/b/global_3413819.jpeg</photo_url></item>