<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Howard Hill Rd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02825</zip><lat>41.785290</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Foster Center</name><city>Foster</city><id>7423412</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.720345</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; Foster Center is at interscection of South Killingly and Howard Hill,   we'll take Howard Hill 2.2 miles to Briggs right back to HH take a right onto Walker Rd, which ends at 5.4 miles, sounds easy but it might be the toughest 5 you've ridden.  the FIRST 2.2 miles is going uphill,  at a slight incline, 10-15 degrees...  but at points, the prettiest too.  Walker ends after 5.4 miles, the curviest, up and down, mostly down, I know.  those done then can ride So Killingly to the right back into Foster Center.  The rest can turn left and follow S. Killingly up a number of small hills, and up a long hill (along the way  we pass Balcom on the right and some may opt to go that way and meet up on North Rd and await us when we go by) At the top of the hill is a former governer's mansion, which at the  top of it is another nice ride down, then slight up to Boswell Rd,at 7.3 miles where we take a right, thru the pretty countryside, til we make another right onto North Rd, as we go down to where we pass North Rd and Balcom), further down and some small hills, past brooks, fields and other meadows, etc.  when North Rd ends, at 10.2 miles, we take another right, back up Foster Center Rd to Howard Hill again, about 0.5 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is only 10.5 miles, sounds easy, until you ride it.  If you are in for more, I can lead on more back roads, more hills, etc.   This will be a slower ride, up hill the first 2.2 miles at an incline, but enjoy the way the country is.  Go slow, you will really enjoy the ride.  It isn't flat road like a bike path.  You finish the first five miles, and you should be proud of yourself.  Finish all ten, and enjoy all the beauty of it, we'll go to HELEN's on Rt 6 for a beer after... and a snack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the ups are lengthy, the beauty ongoing, I hope we will ride single file, two tops, thru all of this, and those in front switch back at points to bring up the rear... this way, we all do it all together, not miles apart.  This ride is for fun.  I drove it thru today, and was amazed at what I'd forgotten, besides the incline for the first 2 miles. For it to be fun for all, I ask we ride together, or don't join at all. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*** Take Rt 6 West from Providence, to Rt 94S to Foster Center.  Rt 146 S to 295S to Rt 6W from North,  395S to 6E from Webster MA, and other points North.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>follow mapquest to take rt6 west out to rt 94 south , right just before fire station down one block to foster center.  the center is a baptist church, a one room schoolhouse turned library, and the tiny town clerks office.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick Clark</member_name><member_id>17851281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342960262000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336333794000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>bike ride through backroads in Foster RI</name><id>63672052</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342879200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/63672052/</event_url></item>