<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 East Head Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.838276</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Carver</city><id>1529274</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.695015</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SEMPBA Conservation Projects &lt;strong&gt;Pine Barrens Mapping and Assessment Program&lt;/strong&gt; SEMPBA Pine Barrens Assessment Field Training &lt;br /&gt;

Thursday, May 23, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

9:30 am &lt;br /&gt;

Myles Standish State Forest Headquarters Parking Lot &lt;br /&gt;

194 Cranberry Road, Carver, MA &lt;br /&gt;

Headquarters phone: 508.866.2526 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://pinebarrensalliance.org/pbagraphics/Default%20Line.gif" width="400" height="1" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Our Pine Barrens need help. 
&lt;p&gt;You can help the Southeastern Massachusetts Pine Barrens Ecoregion by participating in a project to collect data on the remaining Pine Barrens in your community. Collected data will be used to assess the extent and viability of our Pine Barrens and to help determine conservation priorities.&lt;/p&gt;
What's so special about Massachusetts' Pine Barrens? 
&lt;p&gt;We live in a globally rare ecoregion of Pitch Pine-Scrub Oak Barrens, Atlantic White Cedar Swamps, Coastal Plain Ponds, and Coastal habitat types. Each of these habitats supports a number of rare animal and plant species, some of which occur only in the southeastern Massachusetts "Pine Barrens" region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Southeastern Massachusetts contains the world's 2nd largest block of Pine Barrens remaining in the world (the New Jersey Pine Barrens is the largest).  Even so, the information and data necessary for ensuring the viability the region's diverse natural resources still has yet to be collected. Volunteers are needed to collect the data that will enable land managers across the region to develop management plans for each parcel.&lt;/p&gt;
Learn to assess Pine Barrens 
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, May 23, Ecologist Pat Swain of the Massachusetts Natural Heritage and Endangered Species Program (NHESP) has agreed to conduct a field outing for volunteers interested in Pine Barrens data collection and assessment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pat will show us a good example of a natural Pitch Pine-Scrub Oak community within the Sly Pond Natural Heritage Area, or at another location in the Myles Standish State Forest. She will explain how to fill out field assessment forms for other occurrences of Pine Barrens in our neighborhoods and favorite conservation lands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bescherer</member_name><member_id>650729</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369343386000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368312357000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pine Barrens Mapping 101</name><id>118931052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369315800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/118931052/</event_url></item>