<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/6/e/event_83922862.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/8/a/event_83923402.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; We'd love to share this hidden treasure with you called Muddy Pond in Westminster,MA. (Photos are compliments of Carol)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;A special thank you to Ralph, Carol and Jean for your help with this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read the details of this event.&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great hike for folks new to the group and/or winter hiking since it's an easy hike and we will have a chance to socialize together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless we get a few days of thawing before this event, there will most likely still be some icy areas on the trails. Micro-spikes or some kind of foot stabilizers are highly suggested. Please see the comment section below for Bob's suggestion on where to purchase them if you need a pair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a site to see where it exists on a map and another one to view some photos of the pond and shelter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://noahhunt.org/Sebastian/Wildwood/MuddyPond/MuddyPond.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://noahhunt.org/S...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/Watatic000407.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralph has suggested that a gathering might be fun at the shelter to cook hotdogs, smores, etc...over the fire. We would all have to carry in and out our own foods and drinks. BYO long skewers or sticks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;To make things easier and keep our back packs lighter, please only worry about your own food for this hike. We can each bring in our own foods.....yep, every man for himself sort of thing;-)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: the grates are not in good condition so anyone cooking on them may want to bring a piece of foil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only seating will be on the shelter floor or on the ground which is a very nice pine needle covered ground. Some folks may choose to bring something to sit on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sparks from the fire can be dangerous especially if wearing nylon, rayon or fleece like materials so please plan accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Very important: IF the wind is too strong, we may not be able to have a fire as planned. So, in that case, please bring an alternate lunch that you don't need to cook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralph and I checked out parking areas and places to hike in from yesterday so here are further details as promised....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our best spot to hike in from (we've found so far anyway;-) is indeed Bragg Hill Road. The hike in will be as Carol stated in the comment section, thank you Carol, approximately 3.73 miles round trip and about 1 1/2 hours round trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a parking area, however it is very uneven and icy and not very large. Maybe can hold 8+ cars. It is best suited for 4 wheel drive vehicles or cars with a high clearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The road is not very wide but we did notice a few spots had some adequate pull off areas. This is the first parking area you come to from the South Asburnham Road side of Bragg Hill Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we have such a nice large assembled group, which is wonderful, We are asking those who wouldn't mind carpooling in as a group to meet at the parking lot for &lt;strong&gt;Meetinghouse School in Westminster by 9:20 am. This location has been changed as I spoke with someone at the Wesminster Police Department who recommended we park here rather than Joseph's Bistro. We are also asked to make a list of our plate #'s to give to them. The police department is across the street.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The address for Meetinghouse School is 8 South Street, Westminster, MA 01473. Please use the web address below for directions from the school to Bragg Hill Road and you can also use that location on the map to find your way to the school parking lot.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Please note: The meetup spot is actually the parking lot across from the Westminster Police Station- NOT at the Westminster Elem. School! For whatever reason, Google maps thinks Meeting House school is down the street a bit. For those not familiar with Westminster, South Street is the side road next to the Westminster Cracker Building and the police station is approx. 200 yards down the road. We are meeting at 9:20 in the parking lot across from the police station.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;This new map is accurate: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://g.co/maps/p59gg"&gt;http://g.co/maps/p59gg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The parking area closest to Asburnham Rd off Bragg Hill Rd. OR commute from Meeting  House School parking lot at 9:20am</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329706082000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326848541000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Hike/ Snow Shoe Mid-State Trail to Muddy Pond/ cook out at shelter</name><id>48537612</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329576300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/48537612/</event_url></item>