<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Arrow Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.370087</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-910-0822</phone><name>Club Oberon</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1058452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113556</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are going to return (for the 10th time, for me!!) to my favorite dance venue in the Boston area....all the disco and rock music we love and THE party atmosphere of all times....THE DONKEY SHOW. We are being given a special group rate of $30 (instead of $38), so please sign up ASAP so that I can give a head-count and get this rate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are meeting for dinner at the Grafton Pub at 6:30, then on to make wild merry at Oberon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;This is a joint event with BOSTON 35+ WINE, DINE, DANCE AND BE MERRY MEET UP!  I won't be able to attend.  I'll be at the Indian dance event.  Marianne is the contact person for this event.  Her e-mail is hellomarianne@gmail.com. E-mail Marianne directly for tickets.  RSVPing on this site will not hold you a spot for the show. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;============&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You haven't danced and partied if you haven't experienced the Donkey Show...this will be my tenth time!! It is FANTABULOUS. The most fun and hilarious event in Boston with the greatest dance music to which everyone is rocking the minute you walk in - studio 54-style - actors and public all together...nothing like it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The celebrated smash hit The Donkey Show has taken Boston by storm - and now this crazy circus of mirror balls and feathered divas, of roller skaters and hustle queens, will continue to shower the city with glitter every Friday and Saturday night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;========================&lt;br /&gt;The Donkey Show - WHAT THEY SAY ABOUT IT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Donkey Show is the intoxicating international sensation that takes you behind the velvet ropes into a glittered wonderland of decadence, divas, and disco, inspired by Shakespeare's A Midsummer Night's Dream. Come party on the dance floor to all the disco hits you know by heart as The Donkey Show unfolds all around you. It's a show . . . it's a party . . . it's the ultimate disco experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The most alive, immersive piece of theater I've ever been dunked in.&amp;quot; - Boston Phoenix&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Riveting. . . . So visceral that words seem almost beside the point.&amp;quot; - Boston Globe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come party on the dance floor to all the 70s disco hits you know by heart as the show unfolds around you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet at 6:30 for dinner at the Grafton Pub then at 7:30 in front of Oberon's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at 6:30 for dinner at the Grafton Pub then at 7:30 in front of Oberon's</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289699419000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289213654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dance and make merry at the Donkey Show</name><id>15376431</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289694600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/15376431/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/2/global_13743234.jpeg</photo_url></item>