<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harborside Learning Lab</address_2><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.358925</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New England Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>735569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050636</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Aquarium Lecture Series has started again! Like last year, the New England Aquarium appears to require you to register with them to attend these free lectures. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the New England Aquarium Site&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Healthy Oceans, Healthy Humans:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kathleen Frith, Assistant Director, Center for Health and the Global Environment&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Harvard Medical School&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Center’s mission is to further understanding of human health and global environmental change connections. The Healthy Oceans, Healthy Humans program aims to create educational materials that inspire marine conservation by demonstrating how human health depends on a healthy ocean environment. The Center’s assistant director, Kathleen Frith, will present Once Upon a Tide, a 10-minute film produced by the Center&amp;quot;. Register for this event with the New England Aquarium at &lt;a href="http://support.neaq.org/site/Calendar/82445428?view=Detail&amp;amp;id=102421" target="_blank"&gt;http://support.neaq.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside the Harborside Learning Lab. Facing the main building of the Aquarium, the IMAX theater on the right, just before the IMAX theater there is a sidestreet with a row of offices on the right. The Harborside Learning Lab is the last entrance on the right. [ See the &lt;b&gt;Map of the Aquarium Front Plaza - Exterior &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/visit_planning/maps_directions_and_parking/images/AqMAP_web.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/v...&lt;/a&gt; ]. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After, anyone want to go to the New England Aquarium? First we learn about fish, then we eat 'em! ... I wonder whether Legal Seafood's servers the winners or the losers of the Aquarium's gladitorial matches? ... the Aquarium does do gladitorial matches, don't they? ... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Aquarium Lecture Series&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Aquarium has been providing free lectures and films by scientists, environmental writers, photographers and others since 1972. The Aquarium Lecture Series is presented free to the public through the generosity of the Lowell Institute, which has been providing funding for free public lectures at universities and museums since 1836.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lectures are free and open to the public. Registration is requested. All programs start at 7 p.m. in the Aquarium's Harborside Learning Lab, unless otherwise noted below.  Programs last approximately one hour followed by a reception&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Kathleen Frith:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://chge.med.harvard.edu/about/staff/frith.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://chge.med.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kathleen Frith plays a leadership role in all the Center's activities, providing expertise on science communication and education and helping the Center achieve its mission to further understanding of human health and global environmental change connections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kathleen directs the Center's Healthy Ocean, Healthy Humans program that aims to increase awareness about the human health connections to the ocean environment by developing media and exhibitry for educational institutions such as aquariums and museums. Kathleen is the co-director of the Center's Healthy and Sustainable Food Program that educates the public on food that is healthy for humans and the environment. This program recently launched Healthy Harvest guides, a tool to help people know when regional produce is available. Kathleen is currently the Acting Director of the Harvard Garden Project that will implement Harvard’s first kitchen garden in the heart of Harvard Square this spring. Kathleen leads the communication aspects of the Center's activities, including media outreach, publications, and website development&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Healthy Ocean, Healthy Humans:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://chge.med.harvard.edu/programs/healthyoceans/" target="_blank"&gt;http://chge.med.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Healthy Ocean, Healthy Humans program aims to create educational materials that inspire marine conservation by demonstrating how human health depends on a healthy ocean environment. The program is based on our belief that by using the powerful, direct connection of human health people will be moved to think about the ocean not just as a vacation spot or mysterious underworld, but as part of the system that fosters human life. This is a collaborative program, working closely with advisors and partners across the nation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The project currently consists of several components. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Center has recently finished production of a 10-minute educational film with award winning filmmakers (Sea Studios Foundation) and animators (LAIKA/house and Funjacket Enterprises) titled &lt;i&gt;Once Upon a Tide&lt;/i&gt; that reconnects its audience to the importance of the marine environment for all life on Earth, including human life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Unlike conventional natural history documentaries, Once Upon a Tide is a fictional narrative that blends the moral and visual elements of a mystical fairy tale to inspire us to recognize the importance of ocean conservation. Narrated by Academy-Award winner Linda Hunt, this modern day fable is an innovative educational approach that will be shown in aquariums, museums, theaters and schools nationally and internationally. In addition, the Center is currently developing an extensive website with an educational section for teachers, educational 'take-away' guides for viewers as well as hosting a series of community discussion events based on ocean and human health&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/visit_planning/maps_directions_and_parking/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The closest subway stop is just 100 yards from the Aquarium. It is the Aquarium stop on MBTA’s Blue Line. All other subway lines connect to the Blue Line, and stops off all of the lines are only a short walk from the Aquarium, including the State stop on the Orange Line (8-minute walk), the Government Center stop on the Green Line (10-minute walk), and the South Station stop on the Red Line (10-15-minute walk)&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Anybody want to put the &amp;quot;4/5/2010: Hermit Crab Shell-Choice Behavior: Finding a Dream House on a Small Tropical Island&amp;quot; on the calendar? Crouching Tiger / Hidden Dragon will be playing at the Coolidge Corner theater then... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269472481000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267029677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healthy Oceans, Healthy Humans @ New England Aquarium, Harborside Learning Lab</name><id>12695364</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269298800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12695364/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/3/global_13305667.jpeg</photo_url></item>