<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4054 Mystic Valley Parkway (Rt. 16)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02153</zip><lat>42.418400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bertucci's</name><city>Medford</city><id>1279425</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Join us in Medford for an update on Citizen Petition efforts - pick some up to help collect signatures! Also, hear plans for our effort to collect signatures in Boston on 10/13.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;We have a special guest attending as well.&lt;/strong&gt; Yan Bielek born on September 11, 1951, one of three children raised by parents who where teachers in Czechoslovakia. Yan graduated from the Slovak Technical University Bratislava - College of Chemistry in 197&lt;span&gt;5, married Nora and had their first child that same year. Their daughter was born only three years later in 1978. His family of four emigrated in the summer of 1984. Yan continues to thrive in his original profession as a chemist. He currently lives with his wife in Cumberland, Rhode Island and lives the life he&amp;rsquo;d always dreamed of. His son and daughter are also both married. He has also two grandchildren. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Yan will present his life story told in his book "Just Don't Turn Around", in inspiring story of his family living the ordeal of daily life in socialism stricken Czechoslovakia.&lt;/strong&gt; The never ending pressure from the socialist government makes him snap and despite the great danger of facing machine guns at the border, he takes his small family of four and sneaks out of the country, leaving everything behind. They endure months in a refugee camp in Austria before finally making their way to the USA. Yan's book will be for sale for $18.&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Private Dining Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christen Varley</member_name><member_id>9247789</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318378977000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318270283000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Medford Meeting - Greater Boston Tea Party</name><id>36847662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318374000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/36847662/</event_url></item>