<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I've been asked by a couple of members to do a tutorial on capturing movement in water. I am not an expert so I'm asking anyone interested in sharing knoweldge to join us. And what better time to do it than right before the Four Falls outing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the AMC store entrance. Hopefully they will allow us to use the cafeteria area to sit in. (I'll drive back up this weekend and see if it's OK.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the agenda for the half hour class. (I am looking for an expert who can help with the lesson)&lt;br /&gt; - Camera settings:&lt;br /&gt;    Shutter Speed: we are going for that silky effect that is so common in classic waterfall photography. To do this we are going to need a slow shutter speed. By using a slow shutter speed the movement of the water becomes blurred and this is what creates the silky water effect. A shutter speed of 1 to 5 seconds will give excellent results. Of course, I recommend you experiment and try out various speeds to see what works best for each image.&lt;br /&gt;    FStop: I find an F22 gives me the best images for my camera. But since I am shooting digital I tend to constantly play with the shots until I get the one that is perfect in my eyes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Filters: Increasing your shutter time means more light will be entering the lens. In many cases, you will find that this causes your images to be over-exposed, even with a smaller aperture. Polarizing, Neutral Density and Warming filters all come in very useful when trying to correct this problem. These filters will all reduce the amount of light that enters the camera. I would personally try a polarizing filter first, followed by the ND filter. Check your results and see which one works best for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Ideal conditions: What if you don’t have any of these filters for your lens? Try photographing the waterfall around sunrise or sunset when the light is not so bright. You can also choose a nice overcast day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please prepared and bring a tri-pod. If you do not own one you can get a very sturdy one at Walmart for under $30 bucks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP now so I know if I need to be there at 11 !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, &lt;br /&gt;Eileen&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the inside to the right of the AMC store. My photo on the site.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240849578000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238012590000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To: Capture water movement  - Pre hike 'Round Table'</name><id>10034960</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240671600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/10034960/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/a/global_7837242.jpeg</photo_url></item>