<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;This documentary ( 87 min.) is  from this year's Boston Jewish Film Festival which explores and celebrates the common musical heritage that is shared between all people living in the Middle East.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What do Tel Aviv, Cairo, Beirut, Damascus and Aleppo have in common? Beyond the conflicts that rock the Middle East, these cities share a common heritage: classical Arab music. French filmmaker Florence Strauss takes us on an enchanting journey in search of the roots of this timeless art, uncovering hidden aspects of her own Jewish heritage along the way.  Festival Desription&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, a music documentary that?s got its priorities right?it?s about the music. Arabic classical music, to be precise, as played in Damascus, Lebanon, and mostly in Israel, by both Arabs and Jews. Some of the talk about music bringing people together and leading to world peace sounded forced and unreasonably idealistic (to say nothing of repetitive), but the discussions of musical and religious styles coming together and influencing each other proved worth listening to. And best of all, there?s the music?haunting, exciting, and digging into the depth of your soul. The musicians are captured, for the most part, not in concerts or recording studios, but playing together in living rooms, and director Florence Strauss keeps the camera tied on their faces, capturing their infectious exuberance.   Bayflicks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194365179000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192581791000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Between Two Notes: A Documentary about Modern Mid-Eastern Music</name><id>6562976</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194192000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6562976/</event_url></item>