<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 First Avenue, Charlestown</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.375751</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Community Room</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>9544552</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053619</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/7/e/event_161796222.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Guest Speaker will be Conservative Comedian Eric Golub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eric lives in L.A. and began his political blog "&lt;strong&gt;Tygrrrr Express&lt;/strong&gt;" on March 11, 2007, the 3 year anniversary of the Madrid bombings and the exact midpoint of 9/11. He is the author of 3 books: "&lt;strong&gt;Ideological Bigotry&lt;/strong&gt;" &lt;strong&gt;“Ideological Violence”&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;“Ideological Idiocy"&lt;/strong&gt; (books will be available for purchase). He has had numerous media appearances and has spoken to conservative groups all across the country. Mr. Golub currently has three fatwas against him: One from a Palestinian group, one from the Daily Kos, and one from the National Organization for Women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be watching Ryan vs. Biden in the VP Debate afterwards. Bring your own beverages and we'll order pizza!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*** CHANGE OF VENUE *** We are NOT meeting at Lir this month and are considering a new venue for future meetings. For this meeting, at least, we will be at 250 First Ave in Charlestown (right down the street from the USS Constitution). It's the last building on the street, by the new Spaulding Rehab construction site. You can park around the corner on 5th Ave (off of 13th and 16th streets) at the Partners Parking Garage. Open 24 hours, it's $4 for the first hour, $1 each additional hour. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

DRIVING: Coming from Boston, you'll go over the Charlestown Bridge and turn right onto Chelsea St (following signs for the Constitution). At 3rd stoplight, turn right onto 5th Street and then left onto First Ave. Go to end of street, last building on the &lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;right hand side. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Coming from 93 N, get off at Charlestown exit. At stoplight, you'll reach a roundabout (Sullivan T Station on the right hand side). Take 2nd roundabout exit by the Teamster's building and turn left onto Medford St. At end of the street, turn left onto Chelsea St, then right at stoplight onto 13th St. Go to end of st, turn left onto First Ave. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

T RIDERS: The closest T stop is North Station, about a 10-15 min walk. Walk over the Charlestown Bridge and follow the freedom trail through the historic navy yard, walk straight through the yard and you'll be on First Ave. Walk to the end of the street and the building is at the end on the right. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

There's a free shuttle that picks up at North Station (in front of CVS) called Partners (blue and white shuttle), every half hour on the 15 (7:15, 7:45, 8:15 etc). You can take that to 13th Street, get off and walk to the end of the street to First Ave. The building is across the street on the lefthand side.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kat </member_name><member_id>9811897</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Morabito</member_name><member_id>10170370</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Austin Hess</member_name><member_id>10643147</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350045379000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347903253000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Meeting - Greater Boston Tea Party</name><id>dccbtcyqnbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349996400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/82798702/</event_url></item>