<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/8/event_192663672.jpeg" width="378" height="280" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;First Saturday Lowell Open Art Studios&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Where:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Western Avenue Studios 122 Western Avenue, Lowell, MA 01851&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;When:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Saturday,  from 12:30-2:30PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Where to park:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The building is next to the train tracks and the area is little bit run down to be honest and to warn you, but it should be safe in the daylight. There is a large parking lot so try to park in there. If it is full try parking on the street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;How to find us:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The open studios are on the Floors 2 thru 5. Please enter on the left side of the buidling in the attached photo, enter via the white enterance.  Then come find us on the 2nd floor by Studio 221 Gray Cat Studio for Mixed Media art. We'll be moving up from floor 2 to floor 5 so if you miss us please try to find us in some of the open Studio on that floor as we will be working our way up from floor to floor so if you missed us at the start keep going up from floors 2 to 5 until you find us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; More than 180 Working Artists. Here you will find 2 buildings, 3 floors and 143 studios filled with artists working in all disciplines, media and styles. The studios are located in a brick mill building at 122 Western Avenue in Lowell, Massachusetts, near the heart of downtown. Since opening day, Western Avenue Studios has become an integral part of the cultural life of the city of Lowell. In addition to participating in the annual citywide Lowell Open Studios and holding monthly First Saturday Open Studios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will all tour the studio for about 2 hours. As we move from studio to studio we discuss art from an Artist’s viewpoint and see if we can get comments from some of the local artist showcasing at this Lowell Open Art Studios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;For car drivers:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Directions to 122 Western Avenue (Yes there is free parking here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;From the Lowell Connector, take the Thorndike St. exit. After the third set of lights take the ramp on the right. At the second set of lights at the top of the ramp, turn left onto Middlesex St. Middlesex Street bears to the right just after the Boys and Girls Club, follow to first set of lights which is School Street. Turn right on School, at the crest of the hill turn right onto Western Avenue. Western Avenue Studios is the five story red brick building on the right and the 3 story building on the left (the buildings form an "L") at the end of Western Ave.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Online Map: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=122+western+avenue,+lowell,+ma+01851&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;g=122+western+avenue,+lowell,+ma+01851&amp;amp;iwloc=addr"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?q=122+western+avenue,+lowell,+ma+01851&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;g=122+western+avenue,+lowell,+ma+01851&amp;amp;iwloc=addr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For T Bound members there is the Lowell Commuter rail train that get you up here and you can walk or talk a cab to Western Avenue Studios 122 Western Avenue, Lowell, MA 01851.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thanks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Biagio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Open studios  is on Floors 2 thru 5. Please find us on 2nd floor  by Studio 221 Gray Cat Studio for Mixed Media art. We'll be moving from floor 2 to floor 5 so if you miss us please try to find us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365425125000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362437207000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Saturday Lowell Open Art Studios (Free)</name><id>107612292</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365265800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/107612292/</event_url></item>