<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Hudson St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.350721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chinatown Gate</name><city>Boston</city><id>739110</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059870</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Every year for a few days at the beginning of September, a vacant lot near Chinatown Gate is transformed into a large outdoor movie theater showing Chinese cinema. This is called Movies at the Gate and it's a program run by the Asian Community Development Corporation in conjunction with Chinatown residents. People watch movies outdoors while enjoying wonderful take-out from area restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year is provides a more special treat since the Red Heroine is being shown. This is the earliest existing martial arts film. Many films we  see as a group are rare, but this may be the rarest of them all since there is only one copy of this film, which is owned by the Beijing Film Archive. Luckily, the Boston-based Devil Music Ensemble has gotten permission to tour the country with this film. In fact, the Devil Music Ensemble will be performing their own soundtrack written especially for the film for the first time at this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Heroine (1929) is the only surviving film of a 13 part serial. The film, which was made at the height of the 1920s martial arts craze in Shanghai, depicts the rise of a young woman warrior. A young maiden is captured by the army raiding her village and her grandmother is killed. Luckily, the maiden is captured by the Daoist Hermit, White Monkey and later reemerges as a full-fledged warrior ready to deploy her newly learned magical powers in order to avenge her grandmothers death.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information about the film can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massdist.com/DME/Red%20Heroine/Red%20Heroine%20page.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massdist.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.filmsatthegate.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.filmsatthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film doesn't start until 7:30, but please show up early as I don't know how crowded things will get.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, please bring your own seating if at all possible. There is only a limited number of folding chairs to go around. Snacks and beverages to share, while not required, would be much appreciated by the group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TBD - I will probably have a red balloon.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222529718000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218997899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Heroine - Rare Chinese Silent Film with Live Music at Chinatown Gate</name><id>8563329</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220653800000</time><rsvp_limit>48</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8563329/</event_url></item>