<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1741 S Willow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.953915</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-668-5557</phone><name>Barnes and Noble</name><city>Manchester</city><id>759357</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our book for discussion in February and March is &amp;quot;The Buddha's Teachings on Prosperity - At home, at work, in the world&amp;quot; by Bhikkhu Basnagoda Rahula, published by Wisdom Publications (wisdompubs.org), Boston, Massachusetts (paperback, $16.95). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Buddha had a keen insight into what people with everyday concerns need to know. This book presents the particular teachings that he gave to the many laypeople he encountered. Bhikku Rahula explains the difference between the Buddha's teachings for monks and nuns, and his teachings for the lay community. The author &amp;quot;denies the popular but erroneous view that the Buddha discouraged striving for success.&amp;quot; He explains, &amp;quot;The Buddha clearly recognized and admired happiness in life. He not only encouraged people to obtain wealth but instructed them on how to save, invest, and manage their wealth as well. He also offered guidance to his lay community on successful interpersonal and social relationships, decision-making, and healthy personality development. Above all, he showed the lay community the path to happiness.&amp;quot; Throughout the book, short excerpts from the Buddha's teachings are presented in new translations from the Pali, with notes to refer the interested reader to the original texts if further study is desired. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Born in Sri Lanka, Bhikkhu Basnagoda Rahula became, during his childhood, a novice monk at Attanagalla Royal Temple in his native country. After receiving Higher Ordination and a bachelor's degree in Buddhist philosophy, he emigrated to the United States in 1990. He earned his M.A. in literature from University of Houston-Clear Lake and his Ph.D. in English from Texas Tech University in Lubbock. Currently he serves the congregation of the Houston Buddhist Vihara and teaches English at the University of Houston-Downtown.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268265798000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263226047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Buddha's Teachings on Prosperity" - Chapters 9 to 14</name><id>12286669</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268092800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/12286669/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/d/global_12599517.jpeg</photo_url></item>