<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Braintree, MA</address_2><address_1>128 Town Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.203080</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>n/a</phone><name>Braintree High School</name><city>Braintree</city><id>172533</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.021370</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join Members of the SSFMG as we participate in our second President's Fitness Challenge Assessment of the year!  Aerobic Fitness, Muscular Strength and Endurance, Flexibility and Body Composition are what will be tested and measured.  This is a great way for each of us to assess our individual current fitness levels and to set realistic goals that can be measured and attained.  Ideally we plan to run this event quarterly, or roughly every 3 months.  This way we can measure our success and other members can join us as their schedule allows and as they join the Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a perfect opportunity to burn a few calories, assess your fitness level and meetup with other Group Members.  In addition, this is a great event for first-time attendees (new members!) to attend.  Whether this is your first or 2nd time participating in the PFC Assessment this is sure to be a fun and enlightening event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What To Wear: Workout Clothes, Sneakers, Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Bring: Data Collection Form, Pen, Water, Hat, Sunglasses, Beach Towel or Bath Towel &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional Items to Bring: (If you decide to bring an item please include it in your RSVP Comments.  The Event Organizer(s) will strive to bring these items but it doesn't hurt to have an extra.)&lt;br /&gt;Yoga Mat for our Push-Ups, Sit and Reach, and Sit-Ups&lt;br /&gt;Timer for timing walk/run and pulse before and after walk/run&lt;br /&gt;Masking Tape to mark measurements for Sit &amp;amp; Reach and Sit-Ups&lt;br /&gt;Scale for Weighing (we can compare if there's more than one, mine's hard to read and old but working)&lt;br /&gt;Yard Stick for Sit and Reach&lt;br /&gt;Measuring Tape for Height and Waist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have formed a Group to take the President's Challenge together.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is it?  The President's Challenge is a series of programs designed to help improve anyone's activity level. Joining a group is a great way to make staying active easy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about the President's Challenge, go to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.PresidentsChallenge.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Presidents...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why join?  Staying active with others can be a lot of fun. They'll help keep you motivated - even when you don't really feel like it. Groups are a great way to meet new people. There are even programs for people at different activity levels: the Active Lifestyle program aimed at beginners, and the Presidential Champions program for those who are already active.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Signing up for a group is simple. And there's no limit to how many you can belong to. You can join or leave at any time. All you have to do is register. It's quick, and there's no cost just to participate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO JOIN:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Go to &lt;a href="http://www.PresidentsChallenge.org/login/register_individual.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Presidents...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Fill out the registration form.&lt;br /&gt;  * Be sure to include the following info during registration *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group Name: SSFMG&lt;br /&gt;Group ID Number: 79699&lt;br /&gt;(Please note there was an option to assign Group Member #s but we chose not to do so.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) After registering, start logging your activities. As you log activities you'll be able to track your progress toward winning a President's Challenge Award or Medal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President's Fitness Challenge&lt;br /&gt;Monday, July 26th @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;(Plan on about 1-1.5 hours)&lt;br /&gt;Braintree High School&lt;br /&gt;128 Town Street&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain Date: Wednesday, July 28th @ 6:30pm (Please RSVP for this event separately.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website w/ Data Collection Form: &lt;a href="http://www.adultfitnesstest.org/adultFitnessTestLanding.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.adultfitne...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please print and bring the 1-page Data Collection Form to the event.  You are welcome to read the Instruction Booklet, however, you do not need to print or bring it to the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Angela and Amy M.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: &lt;b&gt;NONE - This event is FREE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Max/Min: We desire to have a minimum of 6 people by 8pm on Wednesday, July 21st.  There is no maximum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: One Guest per Member.  $2 donation requested from Guests but not required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Please see our Weather Policy on the About Us page.  We will update this a few days before the event once we have a forecast.  We are working on an indoor/outdoor location nearby in case of inclement weather.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 6pm on Sunday, July 25th&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Please see “Directions to Frequently Used Venues” Discussion Thread on the Message Board.  You may click on the following link.  &lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/198/messages/boards/thread/5042039"&gt;http://fitness.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet us on the Track in the straightaway section near where we meet for C25K training.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy M</member_name><member_id>11602166</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280270521000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277561623000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>President's Fitness Challenge Assessment</name><id>13916906</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280183400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/13916906/</event_url></item>