<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>613 Queen Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06489</zip><lat>41.633958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-621-6611</phone><name>Starbucks</name><city>Southington</city><id>1158459</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.873507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Do you yearn for some mental stimulation...do you love to read? Have you ever read a really good book and wanted to be able to discuss it with someone? Have you ever read a book and had some unanswered questions? Do you enjoy hanging out with fun people and having intelligent conversation? This is why we decided to form this book club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are avid readers, love to talk about books and would love to meet and socialize with some new people in the area. We will meet monthly to select a book, read it and discuss it at the next meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our book club is being led by a lifelong and very dear friend of mine, who happens to be an educator. She has taught in the Connecticut school system for 36 years. Rose possesses a keen mind, a warm personality and a humorous side, which is refreshing. We are so lucky to have her!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We plan to meet and greet at our first meeting. Let's get to know each other...perhaps share a little of what we foresee for the group and select a book which we can read and discuss at our February meetup...all while having fun and a few laughs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out and join us...meet some great folks...and socialize with friends that share the &amp;quot;bookworm&amp;quot; side of life. Happy Reading!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264118859000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262846873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading With Rose...Our First Meetup...</name><id>12249339</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263945600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12249339/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/3/global_12527619.jpeg</photo_url></item>