<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>-</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.929740</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 424-3200</phone><name>Shenipsit State Forest</name><city>Ellington, Somers, Stafford</city><id>111151</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.383120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This hike is a long one with an early-out option. The hike will be 3 hours or 5 hours for the full hike and will cover about 5.3 miles or 9.1 miles total for the full hike on the blue blaze trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** 4/6/07 I updated the distaces slghtly to more accurate values. **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike would start from the trailhead on Hopkins Rd., a dirt road just off of Rte. 140 in Ellington across from Lake Bonair. The hike would be moderately difficult with a fair amount of up/down on the trail and a respectable length of a hike. We will hike to the top and those who wish to have the early option can leave via the .7 mile walk down a paved road to a parking lot (arrive at trailhead at 8:15 - 8:30 AM to arrange cars if you want to do this). The rest of us will go back down the mountain about a third of the way by dirt road and then the rest via some of the same trail we used to get up the mountain back to the beginning. The peak's view is nice to the North.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet and park on the shoulder of the Hopkins Rd. dirt road about .1 mile from the intersection with Rte. 140 at ** 9 AM **. Those wishing to do the early out option will meet at Hopkins Rd. at ** 8:30 AM ** and then we'll drive as a group to the parking lot on Gulf Rd. in somers and back before 9 AM. We'll shuttle back to Hopkins Rd. via my van which can seat up to 6 people. The early out option should end at about 11:30 AM and the full hike should end at about 2 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be about 33 F to 40 F for the hike so wear layers for warmth (avoid cotton material). Wear boots as it WILL be muddy! Bring a quart of water and some trail food/lunch for energy especially if you are doing the full hike. We can stop somewhere to eat after for those who wish to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one in Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total distance from Hopkins Rd. start:&lt;br /&gt;* 2.9 miles to trail intersect with Sykes Rd. (dirt)&lt;br /&gt;* 3.4 miles to trail intersect with Parker Rd. (dirt)&lt;br /&gt;* 4.6 miles to peak &amp;amp; observation tower&lt;br /&gt;= 5.3 miles for early-out option to parking lot near Gulf Rd. (paved)&lt;br /&gt;* 5.8 miles to intersection of Soapstone Rd. &amp;amp; Parker/Webster/Sykes Rds. (dirt)&lt;br /&gt;* 6.2 miles to Sykes Rd. and trail intersect&lt;br /&gt;= 9.1 miles to Hopkind Rd. start&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/Directions via MapQuest for Hopkins Rd. approximate trailhead (on right of Rd.):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;address=%5b1%2d19%5d%20Hopkins%20Rd&amp;amp;city=Ellington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06029&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=4YWq4%2f6LEHnb7KcPQYTqXzAZv9Lg3%2f%2bvvkDT5UtoEdqBJjTWFKz7f9MGRaO7yalWkG3OIleRkDXgncOOFEjdbgEHM25yoblV3Z%2f25Jm6jZSLP4J7onkQFrBXU6UfV%2buxDYkYHsfNiIlpZ9flYEQPhg%3d%3d&amp;amp;ambiguity=1"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/Directions via MapQuest for parking area (Soapstone Rd. just off of Gulf Rd.):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=350+gulf+rd.&amp;amp;city=somers&amp;amp;state=ct"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/shenipsitgis.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1176123845000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175817951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Soapstone Mtn. in Ellington and Somers CT</name><id>5642416</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175950800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5642416/</event_url></item>