<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Kendall doesn't announce its schedule until Friday, but this movie is currently showing there at both 6:45 and 7:30 pm; so I assume that this Saturday it will be showing at least once around 7:00.  I'll update everyone with the exact time on Friday, when it will be official.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After, let's go to the Friendly Toast, if it has a full menu - otherwise one of our old standby's:  either Cambridge Brewing or Tommy Doyle's.  I know this is in direct competition with Tom's horror flick - but I get nightmares even thinking about horror movies and don't want to let myself in for torture.  We'll consider this the Battle of the Sams:  Sam Remi vs Sam Mendez.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a short synopsis of the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exploring the comedic twists and emotional turns in one couple’s journey across contemporary America, Away We Go is the new movie from Academy Award-winning director Sam Mendes (American Beauty). Longtime (and now thirtysomething) couple Burt (John Krasinski) and Verona (Maya Rudolph) are going to have a baby. The pregnancy progresses smoothly, but six months in, the pair is put off and put out by the cavalierly delivered news from Burt’s parents Jerry and Gloria (Jeff Daniels and Catherine O’Hara) that the eccentric elder Farlanders are moving out of Colorado—thereby eliminating the expectant couple’s main reason for living there. So, where, and among whom of those closest to them, might Burt and Verona best put down roots to raise their impending bundle of joy? The couple embarks on an ambitious itinerary to reconnect with old friends and family, and to evaluate cities. Co-starring Allison Janney, Maggie Gyllenhaal, Paul Schneider and Chris Messina. Featuring music by singer/songwriter Alexi Murdoch. Official Web Site&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the right front of the theater after the movie</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245108309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Away  We Go</name><id>10658700</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245538800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10658700/</event_url></item>