<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Understanding open source licensing.  Our panel of legal experts will shine some light on the OSS alphabet soup of licensing and its impact to and interaction with open standards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karen Copenhaver - General Counsel, Blackduck software: prior to joining Black Duck, Karen was a partner in the Patent and Intellectual Property Group of Testa, Hurwitz &amp;amp; Thibeault LLP practicing in the area of technology licensing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ira Heffan - Associate, Goodwin Proctor LLP: regularly counsels clients on intellectual property licensing matters, including negotiation of software license agreements and appropriate use of software distributed under “free” and “open source” licenses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Updegrove - Gesmer Updegrove LLP: has broad range experience representing both mature and emerging high technology companies of all types in all aspects of their legal affairs. Since 1988, he has also represented and helped structure more than 70 worldwide standard setting, open source, promotional and advocacy consortia, including some of the largest standard setting organizations in the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry Ilardi - Copyright Counsel IP &amp;amp; L, IBM Corporation: has been Chairman of the Intellectual Property Owners Association (IPO) Open Source Committee since its inception in 2001 and is an advisor to the American Law Institute’s Principles of the Law of Software Contracts project. He is a member of the GPLv3 Committee B and has presented on the subject of Open Source Licensing and Mass Market Contracts &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Corner of Rogers &amp;amp; First Streets, right next to the CambrideSide Galleria and opposite on a diagonal to the Sonesa Hotel. Parking is available on the street only or in the CambridgeSide Galleria Mall. The CambridgeSide Galleria is located at the Lechmere T on the Green Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.BostonPHP.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.BostonPHP.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonPHP....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1139359035000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston PHP Meetup March Meetup</name><id>4849500</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1141342200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/4849500/</event_url></item>