<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Common Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.395386</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-404-7261</phone><name>Belmont Lions Club</name><city>Belmont </city><id>1170360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.176365</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us in celebration of Global Breathwork Day by participating in a day-long Holotropic Breathwork workshop. This event will be held at the Belmont Lions Club located in Belmont Massachusetts, just a short ride from Harvard Square in Cambridge MA, easily accessible by public transportation and with nearby parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holotropic Breathwork™ is a powerful and deeply personal practice that allows individuals to engage in a process of self-exploration and healing that integrates the latest insights from modern consciousness research with anthropology, various depth psychologies, transpersonal psychology, eastern spiritual practices, and mystical traditions from around the world. It combines breathing practices and evocative music in a safe set and setting, allowing individuals to access non-ordinary states of consciousness and activating the natural inner healing process of the individual's psyche. The process is simple yet profoundly transformative. With the inner healing intelligence guiding the process, the quality and content brought forth is unique to each person and for that particular time and place. It can bring about transformation at all levels of self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;visit www.holotropicma.com for more information and to register.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individuals attending this event may be interested in a free public talk the preceding evening. First-time breathers are recommended to attend both.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365901311000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Healing Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-healers-network</urlname><id>511093</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Healers Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361038506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holotropic Breathwork Workshop</name><id>104901812</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>43200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365858000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-healers-network/events/104901812/</event_url></item>