<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Working for a Corporate Client Workshop - Phase 1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You asked for it you got it! This workshop is set up with a real client someone with real photography needs. We will be provided a shot list and agenda from the client outlining their photo requirements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is your chance to learn how to build a client relationship, expand your skill set, partner with assistants, and learn what it is like to be on a real photography assignment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ll need to be prepared for any possibility. This means you could be photographing environmental portraits, executive portraits, location or architecture, lifestyle images, editorial, Annual Report imagery, etc… Bring your gear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It would be wise to pick a partner to work with before the day of the shoot but we may let you loose on your own as well. Again you’ll need to be prepared to take on whatever assignment is handed to you when you show up at the location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 4PM in the Visions by Baker Studio parking lot. At this time, you will get the address to the place we are photographing at. You will be required to have your digital files works on and ready for the client within 7-9 biz days from the shoot. In return you will get feedback on your images from the client as well as Scott and Donna. If your images are chosen, and to be used by the client, you will receive tear sheets for your portfolios as well as credit for the images used in any printed materials or web use. You cannot resell any images for profit from this shoot, it is strictly for the client and you can use them for your personal promotion. If needed, The clients will manage the model releases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna will be working on getting a Press Release created about our Workshop to try and generate additional interest in this project. All participants will have their names included in this Press Release, and copies will be made available to you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please send me any of your questions at donna@erbphoto.com. But I will not disclose the location or client until the meeting time on July 8th. I hope you will be able to make plans to participate in this workshop. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the parking lot to lead the group to the space we will be shooting</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248148022000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244056166000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Working for a Corporate Client Workshop-Phase 1</name><id>10567868</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247083200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10567868/</event_url></item>