<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cambridge</address_2><address_1>485 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374886</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-221-2140</phone><name>Sackler Museum</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>436126</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114555</lon></venue><fee><label>Typical coffee tab</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This week we'll go to &lt;a href="http://harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=1943" target="_blank"&gt;the Helen Vendler talk &lt;/a&gt; on Yeats at the Sackler museum at 6 PM and afterwards head off en masse to a Harvard Square cafe or pub to discuss the talk and to workshop our own poems. If you are unsure how to find us, call Nora at: 857-221-2140. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HELEN VENDLER examines &lt;br /&gt;Our Secret Discipline: Yeats and Lyric Form &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store and the Humanities Center at Harvard University are honored to host HELEN VENDLER, whose new study takes a comprehensive look at Yeats and the lyric form itself.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fundamental difference between rhetoric and poetry, according to Yeats, is that rhetoric is the expression of one's quarrels with others while poetry is the expression (and sometimes the resolution) of one's quarrel with oneself. This is where VENDLER's Our Secret Discipline begins. Through exquisite attention to outer and inner forms, Vendler explores the most inventive reaches of the poet's mind. This book is a space-clearing gesture, an attempt to write about lyric forms in Yeats in unprecedented and comprehensive ways. The secret discipline of the poet is his vigilant attention to forms?whether generic, structural, or metrical. Yeats explores the potential of such forms to give shape and local habitation to volatile thoughts and feelings.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VENDLER remains focused on questions of singular importance: Why did Yeats cast his poems into the widely differing forms they ultimately took? Can we understand Yeats's poetry better if we pay attention to inner and outer lyric form? Chapters of the book take up many Yeatsian ventures, such as the sonnet, the lyric sequence, paired poems, blank verse, and others. With elegance and precision, Vendler offers brilliant insights into the creative process and speculates on Yeats's aims as he writes and rewrites some of the most famous poems in modern literature.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542457000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193270883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Poetry Meetup--Helen Vendler talk, followed by pub/cafe</name><id>6612036</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196290800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/6612036/</event_url></item>