<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those with reserved tickets will meet at Tanjore, an Indian Restaurant at 18 Elliot St., which is right next to the Thai restaurant we go to after the Brattle. Here is a link to a map: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?address=18+Eliot+St&amp;amp;city=Cambridge&amp;amp;state=ma&amp;amp;zip=02138&amp;amp;country=us&amp;amp;zoom=8" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;   This is a special event. Arthur Penn director of great American classic films such as Bonnie and Clyde, The Miracle Worker, and one of my favorites, Little Big Man will be present on this night as two of his films, Night Moves and Mickey One will be screened.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've talked with the folks at the HFA and they are going to reserve 12 tickets for us at the group rate of $8. Last Fall, The Film Archive really increased the number of such director-led Q&amp;amp;A screenings but this is the first time they have had an American director of this stature appear. We will be holding more like events at the HFA, but I really can't  wait for this one as we get to hear one of the truly great American directors speak about his films and (hopefully) on the current state of the  American film industry. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's how it works. &lt;br /&gt;The first 12 people who email me -please use Arthur Penn Film Discussion as your subject and include your full name so I can provide the HFA a list, that they will attend will get the tickets, but I will also give some consideration to members who have proven reliable in the past. Since I'll be paying in advance, if a ticket is reserved for you, you will owe me the $8 if you attend or if you don't. The deadline is Sun. Jan. 20. There maybe other tickets available (and I believe HFA members can reserve tickets) on the day of the show, but these will be limited and you might have to get there 2 hours or so early to get in line. I'll confirm by email those who have tickets reserved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should prove to be a great night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Night Moves&lt;/b&gt;  1975 99 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Private eye Harry Moseby (Gene Hackman) is dedicated to his job, but his dedication does not make him happy or powerful in his personal life, and his wife (Susan Clark) is cheating on him. Aging actress Arlene Iverson (Janet Ward) hires Harry to find her trust-funded daughter Delly (Melanie Griffith), distracting Harry from his marital problems as he tracks the lascivious runaway teen to Florida. In the Keys, Harry has an affair of his own with Paula (Jennifer Warren), and he succeeds in locating Delly, even as he learns that finding her is only the beginning of a much larger case. As the &amp;quot;accidental&amp;quot; deaths multiply, Harry discovers that everyone has his or her own motives and that he cannot do much to stem the tide of deep-seated depravity.  All Movie Guide &lt;br /&gt;Night Move's sinister tale of conspiracy and intrigue powerfully evokes the Watergate era and stands as one of the quintessential American films of the 1970s. HFA descripton &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mickey One&lt;/b&gt;  1965 93 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Warren Beatty, Alexandra Stewart, Hurd Hatfield &lt;br /&gt;Strangely underrated, Penn's wonderfully offbeat and inventive film is an extraordinary tour de force and one of his most stylish and satisfying works. Warren Beatty gives a brilliant turn as Mickey, a stand-up comedian on the lam who descends, like Orpheus, into a strange back alley underworld that just might be of his own invention. At turns haunting and comic, Mickey One offers a mysterious allegory of fear and redemption that features gorgeous photography by Robert Bresson's favorite cinematographer, Ghislain Cloquet, and an improvised soundtrack by jazz great Stan Getz.  HFA description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll provide more information as we near the event date. &lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200436367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Legendary Director Arthur Penn Appearing at HFA</name><id>7123684</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201996800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7123684/</event_url></item>