<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/5/e/event_13717726.jpeg" width="314" height="239" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This is the second in a series of three trips along the outstanding Mousam River in Kennebunk, Maine.&amp;nbsp; This middle section of the river begins above a dam just west of town.&amp;nbsp; Here, the river is a quiet, meandering, tree-lined stream, with little perceptible current.&amp;nbsp; We can paddle for miles with only the tree frogs and kingfishers to accompany us.&amp;nbsp; There are many side passages to entice, and dead trees and aquatic plants sprout from the water all around.&amp;nbsp; Great blue heron&amp;nbsp;hunt alongside river otter and many, many beavers from the looks of the trees.&amp;nbsp; This would be a great trip to have your binoculars handy.&amp;nbsp; All boat types are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a snack and we'll get something more substantial to eat once we return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Rental Kayak Available.&amp;nbsp; Ask Larry for details.&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The address is approximate. Stay on Mill St. until you reach the river.&amp;nbsp; There are unpaved places to park on both banks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Liability Release&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : small"&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;hold&lt;/span&gt; harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fee is for meetup site expenses and planning.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-Larry Pilla&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There is wooded parking on both sides of the river, opposite the dam. I'll be on the north side.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315441487000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314329070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middle Mousam Meander</name><id>30985701</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315238400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/30985701/</event_url></item>