<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Haven’t we all had those experiences where we were in the midst of a powerful dream, and then just as things were getting really interesting the alarm clock goes off, or your partner rolls over and whacks you in the head with an arm, or the cat decides that 5AM is feeding time and sits on your chest to get your attention. Waking up suddenly from a dream can leave the memory clear in your mind, but that doesn’t always satisfy the fact that it was cut short just as it was getting interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attempts to revisit dreams through dreaming practices are certainly a possibility but are no guarantee since the mind doesn’t work like a dvd player where you can go just flip back to an earlier scene and pick up where you left off. Or can you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shamans all across the world are noted for their ability to shift their state of consciousness at will and enter what they call the Otherworld or in some cultures “The Dreaming.” During our next gathering we will learn a bit about the methods used by shamanic cultures to enter non-ordinary states. Even though we do not live in indigenous tribal cultures where such traditions are readily available to us, the ability is buried within us. The skills of the shaman can be reawakened and used to help us explore the imaginal/spiritual realms for gathering knowledge, for personal exploration, or for healing. In our case we will be using the shamanic drumming journey to slip back into previously interrupted dream experiences and re-exploring them with a focus on finding resolution, or what I like to call “a sense of completion within the greater cycle of incompletion.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are just as welcome to bring a finished dream and re-explore it to gain a different perspective or additional insight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The technique we will be learning is simple to practice even if difficult to comprehend, and it is something you can experiment with safely on your own at home, adding it to your ongoing dream studies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to the meeting please review a particular dream from your journal or memory that you would like to re-explore. Also, be aware that we will spend a period of time laying on the floor so please feel free to bring along any of the following optional items:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A journal for writing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A blanket or mat to lay on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A eye shade, handkerchief, scarf, or anything that can cover your eyes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A small pillow for your head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Any personal/sacred objects that help you in your work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A playful spirit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Allen Howell&lt;/b&gt; is a professional architectural designer &amp;amp; independent artist, an ordained Druid and long-time member a local Grove (spiritual community) within the International Order of Bards Ovates &amp;amp; Druids (OBOD), and a trained shamanic practitioner and counselor having studied with the Foundation for Shamanic Studies (FSS) as well as several independent teachers including Alberto Villoldo and Tom Cowan. He is also a certified Grof Transpersonal Holotropic Breathwork™ Facilitator offering workshops in the greater Boston area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is welcome to attend and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/suggestion/" target="_blank"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 25 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions and other information about Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swedenborg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266461038000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262657611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dream Re-visitation Workshop</name><id>12223717</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265760000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/12223717/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/9/b/global_12507995.jpeg</photo_url></item>