<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Attention: Meetup time has been CHANGED to Monday night at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since several people from Beantown Gamers enjoy playing Battlestar Galactica: The Board Game, but it has often been difficult to organize games at regular meetups of this group, I have decided to host the game at my apartment this Monday night. I own the base game, which accommodates up to 6 players; if you own any expansions and would like to play them, feel free to bring them, as I would also like to try them. If there are more than 6 people interested, we may have to have consecutive games, time permitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will try to have beer, soda and snacks available, but feel free to bring any food or drink of your own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking: I am located at 87 Madison St. in Malden, which is in a blind driveway behind another house, 83/85 Madison. If you simply look for number 87, you will not see it. You will need to go into the driveway behind 83/85, which is a red house, to the white house behind it. HOWEVER, I would strongly recommend parking on the street. If you are the first car to arrive, there is one parking spot you can take behind my car, the gray Nissan Maxima, all the way on the right side of the driveway. The other spots in the driveway are not mine to take, and will lead to angry neighbors, so if this spot is taken, please park on the street (sorry!) Ring the doorbell all the way on the right, or call me at 617-429-6403 when you arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public transportation info: My house is located about 0.8 miles from Malden Center station on the Orange Line. It is about a 15 minute walk; the 97, 99, 105 and 106 buses all go near my street as well; HOWEVER, if you are taking any of these buses, please make sure you get the bus at the FRONT of the station, first island; if you get any of these buses from the back of the station, they will take you the wrong way. You should be heading toward Wellington or Sullivan Square station and ride past Stop &amp;amp; Shop/Walgreens; if the bus is headed toward Broadway, Lebanon St. or Boston Regional Medical Center, you are going the wrong way. Please use Google Maps and the MBTA site maps for more info; if you get lost give me a call. I may also be able to pick you up from the station if you arrive early and a game has not started yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meetup may be canceled if there is a lack of interest. Please, do not hesitate to contact me with any questions. Hope to see some of you here!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315928330000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315240348000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Battlestar Galactica Frakkin' Board Game Meetup</name><id>32316352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315868400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/32316352/</event_url></item>