<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please know that the Manchester Historical Society and the Manchester Land Trust join forces for a free Cheney Rail Trail walk on Saturday, September 30, starting at one p.m. rain or shine. The walk takes several hours and covers 5+ miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The speaker/leader will be Dr. Tom Lewis, Professor Emeritus of Geography at Manchester Community College (MCC). Recommended highly; old-timers who knew him as a colleague and newcomers will certainly enjoy his presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants should meet behind Farr?s Sporting Goods at 2 Main Street , Manchester. Parking is available at the nearby shopping plaza and the Eighth Utilities District office building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The former South Manchester Railroad, built in 1869, connected the Cheney Silk Mills to the main rail line in the North End of Manchester. At 2.5 miles, it was the shortest freight-and-passenger railroad, but the longest private railroad in the United States.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions may be directed to the Manchester Historical Society at 860-647-9983 or the land trust at 860-646-4081.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***I don't know of a map for this event***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership is planned to be at this event. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159808702000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1157605938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MHS &amp; MLT Walk at Cheney Rail Trail in Manchester CT</name><id>5117006</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1159635600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5117006/</event_url></item>