<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Intensive Hands-On Seminar with Paul Esajian, star of “Flip This House!”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is absolutely FREE and part of CT REIA's Open House Month!&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday Aug. 13th from 6:45pm - 8:45pm in Cromwell, CT.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It really is a crazy and unfair world out there...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the one hand, there are people who bust their proverbial butts working year after year...slaving away for bosses and managers who don't appreciate them...to earn a paycheck that does little more than pay the bills ... never really getting ahead in life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the other hand, there are those who seem to have found a better way. I'm talking about people who live life on their own terms in the real estate business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They're people who have all the money they need, yet they seem to work when they want to...where they want to...for whom they want to.  What's more, they have all the free time in the world to travel, to spend with their kids, lower their golf score and really enjoy life - on their terms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may know some of these people. And my guess is...you'd like to be just like them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In fact, it is proven someone like you can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How is this possible? Let Paul Esajian show you on Wednesday August 13th from 6:45 to 8:45. He'll teach you how to make a fortune by buying, rehabbing, &amp;amp; selling homes by using his step by step system.  He'll show you how to thrive in the rehab business...and prove to you why NOW is the best time to buy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=97" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Register Now!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here's a list of some of what he will cover at the event:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * How to evaluate a house in disrepair and figure a total repair cost in 15 minutes&lt;br /&gt;    * How to interview and pre-screen contractors so you never get burned&lt;br /&gt;    * How to limit your liability when working with contractors&lt;br /&gt;    * How to control your rehab costs, so you never go over budget&lt;br /&gt;    * Where to find best deals on construction material&lt;br /&gt;    * How to rehab homes so they sell before you finish hammering the last nail&lt;br /&gt;    * How to organize and manage a project so you don't have to be on the jobsite 24 hours a day&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So mark your calendar for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DATE: Wednesday, August 13th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: 6:45 – 8:45&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: The Crowne Plaza, 100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell CT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A&amp;amp;E’s hit TV show &amp;quot;Flip this House&amp;quot; star Paul Esajian is one of the nations leading authorities on rehabbing properties. Paul's company is currently buying 10+ properties a month. In the past three years he has bought, rehabbed, and sold over 300 single family and multi-family properties. The key to his company's exponential growth are his cutting edge rehabbing systems he has developed which allow him to run over 20+ construction projects at any given time. Paul currently manages multiple teams of contractors and sub-contractors in four different states and over twenty different cities!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=97" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an event you CAN NOT afford to miss!  Register Now!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218840991000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217654055000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intensive Hands-On Seminar with Paul Esajian, Star of Flip This House!</name><id>8459773</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218667500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/8459773/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/0/global_5005120.jpeg</photo_url></item>