<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like the weather will be identaical to Saturday in many ways..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I STILL SEE WINDS PREDICTED  IN THE 5-10 MPH RANGE BUT WARMER TEMPS..IM  TEMPTED BUT  NOT WILING TO HAVE A SADDENING EXPERIENCE ON THE OCEAN,  ITS JUST NOT ENJOYABLE IN THE WIND..although the wind may be actually less tomorrow, a few people wrote to me indicating the sound was smoothe..not taking any chances...remember Mystic and Circle Beach, no one wanted to go through the wind to the deep..LOL&lt;br /&gt;Predictions then were less than 8 mph..&lt;br /&gt;I can only go by the predictions and make a decision based on the current weather report at the time of posting, besides its  a mixed group of recreationals and sea yaks along with different skills.. &lt;br /&gt;Oh well... im gonna pick and live with my choices.. Join me if you want to..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TO BE SAFE AND EASIER ON EVERYONE, I CHOSE SALMON COVE AND SALMON RIVER ALL THE WAY UP TO THE DAMM DAM FOR A TRIP, WE CAN STOP AND CHECK OUT THE OLD SUNRIZE RESORT ON THE WAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That spot also seems to be a good snack/Lunch location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best way to get to this PUT IN location by SALMON COVE is by using the same directions to GOODSPEED OPRAH HOUSE,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS use 117 East Haddam Moodus Road, East Haddam,&lt;br /&gt;The Meetup Map link above is correct.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Getting There, From Hartford, The meetup map link above seems to be accurate enough.&lt;br /&gt;take I-91 south: take Exit 22s. (left hand exit) = Route 9 South , take Exit 7, (rte 82 to the Goodspeed Oprah House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp take a left onto Middlesex tpk=rte 154 for a few hundred feet then back onto rte 82 east, cross the river and pass the oprah house and slow down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto rte 149  at the Gelston House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The State boat ramp sign and road is 1 mile north of the left you made at the Opra House..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE Pot Luck Barbie-Q AFTER PARTY    MAYBEE....WE DECIDE AT THE END OF THE PADDLE EVENT, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I WILL LOAD THE GRILL ANYWAY AND SOME FOOD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think Hurd park is a perfect spot for a gathering only because its close and no need to worry about ANYTHING..LOL but since its sunday we might just go home if its too late...lets see..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Hurd State Park: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boat ramp Road,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto rte 149 north&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to rte 609= Leesville rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;then left (really keep straight) onto rte 151&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep going to the intersection of 151/Hog Hill Road/Hurd Park Road,&lt;br /&gt;Take a sharp left onto Hurd Park Road, go apx 0.75 miles then the main park entrance is on the right,&lt;br /&gt;Follow the paved road apx 0.75 miles then there is a sign that says BALL field and SHELTER,&lt;br /&gt;take that right and go to end,&lt;br /&gt;we will be at the shelter at one of the fireplaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;..BRING SOME WOOD..YOUR CHAIRS, ....bugg juice and food..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available: Paddle &amp;amp; PDF with whistle included,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dougnation of 15 bucks for the kayak rented for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a yes and by persons i have some familiarity with..&lt;br /&gt;Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Blonde Necky Fiberglass Eliza. Short Sea Kayak 16 feet, 40 lbs = ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Homeless Bathtub, Recreational Kayak= Pungo 12' with F/R floataion bags installed= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper &amp;amp; Dipper, Sea Kayak= Riot Tourlite 15'= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna Snake, Sea Kayak= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer, Sea Kayak= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat, Sea Kayak= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the orange cones and ORANGE HAT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253988530000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253286404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salmon Cove and River Paddle trip</name><id>11405709</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253462400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11405709/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_5044665.jpeg</photo_url></item>