<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>3263282</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703496</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;DUNE:  Science Fiction movie based on the book of the same name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IMDb: Dune (1984)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;A Duke's son leads desert warriors against the galactic emperor and his father's evil nemesis when they assassinate his father and free their desert world from the emperor's rule.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/rg/em_share/title_web/title/tt0087182"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/rg/em_share/title_web/title/tt0087182&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://youtu.be/KwPTIEWTYEI"&gt;http://youtu.be/KwPTIEWTYEI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLOT: David Lynch wades through dark waters in his adaptation of Frank Herbert's cult science fiction novel. The story takes place in the year 10,191. The universe is governed through a system of feudal rule, presided over by Padishah Emperor Shaddam IV. In the kingdom are two rival houses -- the House of Atreides and the House of Harkonnen. Each house is trying to gain dominion over the universe, but that dominion can only be gained by the house that controls the Spice, a special substance that permits the folding of time. The Spice is only available on the desert world of Arrakis, or Dune. Shaddam, tired of the feuding between the two houses, permits the Atreides to take over the Spice production on Dune, while secretly working with the Harkonnens to launch a sneak attack on the Atreides and destroy them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SPEAKER: &lt;strong&gt;Peter Turchin&lt;/strong&gt; is one of the top cited authors in the field of Ecology/Environment. He is one of the founders of cliodynamics, the new scientific discipline located at the intersection of historical macrosociology, cliometrics, and mathematical modeling of social processes. Turchin developed an original theory explaining how large historical empires evolve by the mechanism of multilevel selection. His research on secular cycles has contributed to our understanding of the collapse of complex societies as has his re-interpretation of Ibn Khaldun's asabiyya notion as "collective solidarity". Turchin received his B.A. in biology from the New York University (cum laude) in 1980 and Ph.D. in zoology in 1985 from Duke University. Peter Turchin is a professor at the University of Connecticut in the Department of Ecology and Evolutionary Biology as well as in the Department of Mathematics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gabriele </member_name><member_id>11913420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365557986000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362768621000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science on Screen: Dune  @ Real Art Ways, Hartford</name><id>108299702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365546600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/108299702/</event_url></item>