<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a nice mostly clifftop hike of about 6 mi. I have done 3 times so far in the past month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out at the Route 66 parking lot at the western end of Middlefield at 2:30 PM and hike somewhat steeply in places up to the cliffs. Then things mostly level off as we hike the cliffs for a couple miles with occasional decents and ascents. If we have time, we might be able to make it to see a small stone arch I found at the northenmost section of the ridgeline. The hike should take about 3 hours at a pace people can keep up with given the altitude gain at either end of the hike. So, we should be done by no later than 5:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are good views to the west. Not as good as the views from the shorter Chauncey Peak and its associated cliffs. Higby Mt. is about 300 feet higher than Chauncey Peak. The last time I hiked there we had a great sunset in the stormy skies. This hike is an &amp;quot;out and back&amp;quot; style hike and not the more typical loop hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given that we will be hiking near the top of the cliff in a number of portions, I don't think this hike is advisable for young children. There are alternate paths in these sections where one can be further from the edge of the cliff if it bothers you. So far, there is no dinner planned for the group after this hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S is the lead on this hike so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No good map is available online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail is well marked up and along the cliffs. The northernmost portion of the trail, which we wont be hiking, goes into the woods and the blue trail blazes are hard to find and follow there to the end of the trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from the Hartford area:&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-91 South&lt;br /&gt;* Take the MIDDLE ST./COUNTRY CLUB RD. exit- EXIT 20&lt;br /&gt;* Turn LEFT onto MIDDLE ST.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn LEFT (East) onto COUNTRY CLUB RD.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow COUNTRY CLUB RD. to Higby RD. (on right, going South)&lt;br /&gt;* Go to intersection with ROUTE 66 and take a RIGHT (West), is first intersection where you can go right&lt;br /&gt;* Go what seems like a couple miles and on the right will be a small parking area at the trailhead&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1149735390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to Higby Mountain in Middlefield CT</name><id>4969506</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1150050600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4969506/</event_url></item>