<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update&lt;/b&gt;: Dinner. Border Cafe. Be there by 4:45 pm. Let's put our name in. It'll prolly be a 15 minute wait. Sign up at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/11793251/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Go and boil your bottoms, you sons of silly persons!&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Saturday an all-day movie festival is being held at the Brattle called the &lt;b&gt;Python-a-thon&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091107.html#a"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt; ! Screenings of &lt;i&gt;And Now For Something Completely Different&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Life of Brian&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Holy Grail&lt;/i&gt;, and &lt;i&gt;Meaning of Life&lt;/i&gt; will be shown. Come join Nerd Fun at the &lt;b&gt;7:00 pm&lt;/b&gt; screening of &lt;b&gt;Monty Python &amp;amp; The Holy Grail&lt;/b&gt;! ... I'd suggest we purchase tickets from the site beforehand. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Brattle Film site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091107.html#a"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Python-A-Thon&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Interactive Quote-A-Long!&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Action Pack presents&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Monty Python &amp;amp; The Holy Grail&lt;/b&gt; at 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(Tickets $10. This film screens as aSingle Feature, but you can stay all day with the PYTHON-A-THON all admission pass! It's just $30 &amp;quot;General Public/$25 Students &amp;amp; Brattle Members - click the PYTHON-A-THON ticket link above to buy yours!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(1975) dir Terry Gilliam and Terry Jones , w/ Graham Chapman, John Cleese, Terry Gilliam, Eric Idle... [91 min]&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update&lt;/b&gt;: Dinner. Border Cafe. Be there by 4:45 pm. Let's put our name in. It'll prolly be a 15 minute wait. Sign up at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/11793251/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will start herding nerds at 6:30 pm outside the Brattle Theater. The show is at 7:00 pm. We can grab seats at 6:40 pm. Let's try sitting in the second row. The screen is kind of small, and recessed back from the stage. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7 with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No, T.J. doesn't know if they will have inflatable swords to wave around or other props. They will probably have subtitles so even if you you have only seen the movie once or twice you can quote along with the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Knights of the Round Table&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0071853/quotes"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;We dance whene'er we're able. &lt;br /&gt;We do routines and chorus scenes with footwork impec-cable.&lt;br /&gt;We dine well here in Camelot, we eat ham and jam and Spam a lot.&lt;br /&gt;We're knights of the Round Table, our shows are for-mi-dable. &lt;br /&gt;But many times we're given rhymes that are quite un-sing-able&lt;br /&gt;We're opera mad in Camelot, we sing from the diaphragm a lot. &lt;br /&gt;In war we're tough and able, Quite in-de-fa-ti-gable. &lt;br /&gt;Between our quests we sequin vests and impersonate Clark Gable. &lt;br /&gt;It's a busy life in Camelot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I have to push the pram a lot.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Sir Robin:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0071853/quotes"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Bravely bold Sir Robin rode forth from Camelot. He was not afraid to die, oh brave Sir Robin. He was not at all afraid to be killed in nasty ways, brave, brave, brave, brave Sir Robin. He was not in the least bit scared to be mashed into a pulp, or to have his eyes gouged out, and his elbows broken. To have his kneecaps split, and his body burned away, and his limbs all hacked and mangled, brave Sir Robin. His head smashed in and heart cut out, and his liver removed...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Monty Python:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monty_python"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Monty Python [...] were a British comedy group that created the influential Monty Python's Flying Circus, a British television comedy sketch show that first aired on the BBC on 5 October 1969. Forty-five episodes were made over four series. The Python phenomenon developed from the television series into something larger in scope and impact, spawning touring stage shows, films, numerous albums, several books and a stage musical as well as launching the members to individual stardom. The group's influence on comedy has been compared to The Beatles' influence on music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The television series, broadcast by the BBC from 1969 to 1974, was conceived, written and performed by Graham Chapman, John Cleese, Terry Gilliam, Eric Idle, Terry Jones, and Michael Palin. Loosely structured as a sketch show but with an innovative stream-of-consciousness approach (aided by Gilliam's animations), it pushed the boundaries of what was acceptable in style and content&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The theatre entrance is on the left side of the building - look for our sidewalk poster case&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257900399000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257186327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monty Python and the Holy Grail @ Brattle Theater</name><id>11771861</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257638400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11771861/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/b/global_11608043.jpeg</photo_url></item>