<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>New London at Exit 7 Park'n'Ride West Greenwich, RI 02818</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>54961</zip><lat>41.656900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Big River Managment Area</name><city>West Greenwich</city><id>1603718</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.551470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;This week we're heading to new waters...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/5/2/6/event_155897702.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;hopefully, none of the trails are over our heads.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919 ; font-size : small"&gt;[I'm moving the date to the 12th, because after today's rains, we just might find ourselves, quite literally, above our heads...]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Ride&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;I'm expecting similar trails to Arcadia, yet with somewhat different currents. From what I understand, Big River has the same combination of fire roads and single-track, passing through forests and fields, over varied terrain, from smooth to rough, over rocks and roots, gravel and dirt (which will require a bit of technical skill), but the difference being these trails grew up around mountain biking, and because of that, I look forward to trails designed with that in mind. As always, there should be no worries, because we&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;will be following The Unwritten Primary Rules of Group Mountain Bike Riding: 1. We ride as a group; 2. We hike what we cannot ride; and 3. We wait at all major trailheads.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Our pace will be moderate and accommodating (no speedsters here), but you should know that the ride is filled with a number of short steep up and downs, and I ask that you believe yourself to be an intermediately skilled rider, or a fit beginner/intermediate rider willing to be challenged by the terrain. I will be riding a rigid single-speed (no shocks) w/ flat pedals, so my pace will not be blazing, nor will I be riding up every climb (I blame the single-speed); that my friends (the riding up every climb) is for another time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;PS: Please take note of the meet time. Plan to meet at 5:15 so that we can begin our ride close to 5:30; this will hopefully keep us from riding out, in the dark.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Take Exit 7 off of Route 95, bear left (for those coming from the north) or right (for those coming from the south), and head south on New London Tpke for 200 - 400 feet. Turn right into the Park and Ride, park... and ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=New+London+at+Exit+7+Park'n'Ride+West+Greenwich,+RI+02818,+West+Greenwich,+RI&amp;amp;hnear=New+London+at+Exit+7+Park'n'Ride&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?q=New+London+at+Exit+7...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Coordiinates: 41.6569, -71.55147&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Take Exit 7 off Route 95 &amp; turn south onto the New London Tpke; the Park &amp; Ride is on the right across from the Mobil Station. Cell: 860-460-1500</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>11024921</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347495794000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346717015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Big River Ride Ride</name><id>80695122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347484500000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/80695122/</event_url></item>