<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Middlesex will be the place to be this Friday Night! Come out and experience why we are one of the best meetup groups in Boston! All members are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**If the RSVP is full, please sign up on the wait list. RSVPs are not final until the day of the event, and I will be opening up more spots as the event date approaches**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are returning to Middlesex Lounge in Cambridge and this will be a great opportunity to meet new people and get your groove on! Middlesex has been a premiere spot in Boston since its opening, and it is known for great music and a great crowd. I expect a big turnout, so RSVPs will fill up quickly - don't miss it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE: I cannot emphasize enough the importance of going EARLY to Middlesex Lounge. Its status as a premiere lounge in Cambridge means the lines can become very difficult. I recommend getting there by 10pm. Going early avoids the line drama, and you have more time to talk with nightlife members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 8:30pm at Middlesex Lounge, which is located at 315 Massachusetts Ave in Central Square. I encourage everyone to arrive early to have time to meet people, as the venue will get louder and more crowded as the night progresses. Please look for me to find the group. Cover: $5 after 9pm, I believe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue. If traveling by T, Central Square the closest T stop on the red line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: Click on the link on the left-hand side for Andrew to find my picture. For help/questions, my cell: 617-459-5145.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! Andrew&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The Organizer reserves the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>2881088</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1253232468000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252444781000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night at the Middlesex Lounge!</name><id>11321435</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252715400000</time><rsvp_limit>47</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/11321435/</event_url></item>