<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>761 Old Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06067</zip><lat>41.666796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rocky Hill Community Center</name><city>Rocky Hill</city><id>707565</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.637995</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;ENERGY EFFICIENCY SEMINAR&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cut Your Home Energy Costs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wednesday July 16th, 7p.m.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;(This is our new meeting)&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                              &lt;br /&gt;CL&amp;amp;P is planning another rate increase. Home heating oil prices are likely to be there highest ever this season. Natural gas prices continue to climb.  What's a person to do?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Buddha Gaia, the Rocky Hill Residents Clean Energy Task Force, Cromwell Clean Energy Task Force and Clean Water Action to a local energy forum to learn about home energy solutions.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;1) We will bring you up to speed on recent and pending state energy legislation and what it means for you, and answer questions on how to become more efficient and save money on your energy costs. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;2)  Come and learn about practical ways to increase energy efficiency in your home (or apartment) and the programs and incentives available to help you make these improvements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who: Anyone interested in lowering energy bills and using less energy&lt;br /&gt;When: Wednesday July 16th, 7pm&lt;br /&gt;Where: Rocky Hill Community Center 761 Old Main Street Rocky Hill CT  &lt;br /&gt;This event is free and open to the public. Light refreshments will be served.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To help us set up the room and prepare materials, please RSVP to Chris Corcoran at 860-232-6232 or &lt;a href="http://ccorcoran@cleanwater.org" target="_blank"&gt;ccorcoran@cleanwater.org&lt;/a&gt; . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buddha Gaia?s President Mr. Joseph Hoydilla and other members will be attending so come along. Say hello to Joseph; if you do not know him, he is in the 30s, bald/shaved head, good-looking guy with goatee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To contact Buddha Gaia, visit their web site at &lt;a href="http://buddhagaia.bffct.net/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://buddhagaia.bffct.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://buddhagaia.bff...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Rocky Hill Community Center:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: 91 north, exit 24. Left at end of ramp on Silas Deane Hwy. Left at 4th light onto parsonage Road. Right on to Old Main Street. Community Center is on the left past the library, set back from road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north: 91 south, exit 24. Right at end of ramp on Silas Deane Hwy. Left at 5th light onto parsonage Road. Right onto Old Main Street. Community Center is on the left past the library, set back from road.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See Joe at seminar: 30something good lookin' guy &amp; fashionably bald/mustache</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216422543000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>make a positive difference in global warming, and other environmental and social issues. Also, this is a warm and friendly group. You'll like everybody. Lots of smiling and compassionate folks.</why><group><who>Spiritual Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-469</urlname><id>836707</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>12 Step Buddhist &amp; Recovery Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214161942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CUT YOUR HOME ENERGY COST SEMINAR July Meetup</name><id>8192126</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216249200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-469/events/8192126/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/7/global_4446391.jpeg</photo_url></item>