<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Fellow Snake Charmers, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This session should be of interest to experienced developers, those new to Python and those trying to introduce it in the work place.  We will have a presentation from John Ehresman and Stephan Deibel of Wingware. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wing IDE, Wingware's Python integrated development environment, will be the focus of our discussion.  The session will start with a 10-15 minute intro, another 10-15 minutes to talk about how Wing is developed, and the rest as Q&amp;amp;A.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great chance to get your hands wet, so go to Wingware.com and download Wing 3.0 beta before the session and build something.  John and Stephan will help you with any questions you may have about installing and using the tool. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wingware was founded in 1999 as Archaeopteryx Software, Inc by John Ehresman and Stephan Deibel.  The first version of Wing came out in September 2000.  Wing now runs on Windows, Linux, and OS X, supports Python 1.5.2 through 2.5, and provides many editing, debugging, and testing features for the Python programmer.  It is written in Python, uses the PyGTK GUI library, and is developed and debugged with itself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perhaps an IDE is just what you need to evangelize your company or maybe you just want to ask John and Stephan how they built Wing in itself.  In any case it should be a great presentation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drinks and pizza will be served -- thanks for the donations -- again.  Last time it seemed to work well after the presentation.  What do you all think?  Let us know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Marquez</member_name><member_id>4000314</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190437755000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187222638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cambridge Python September Meetup</name><id>6187888</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190242800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/6187888/</event_url></item>