<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This months meeting is a very special one. &lt;b&gt;We have world renowned air show performer and Red Bull Air Race pilot Michael Goulian.&lt;/b&gt;  Michael has highlighted the skies over AirVenture for many years and is the 2009 World Champion Red Bull Air Race performer. This will be a packed house. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...Michael Goulian surprised the favorites and a lot of people with his first career victory in Budapest - but not himself. The affable American always knew he had the right stuff to get on top. Goulian is likely to be among the top contenders in 2010 with his greatly improved speed and newfound focus. The man from Massachusetts had struggled in the second tier for most of his four-year career before finally getting everything out of his Edge 540 and breaking through to the top with a brilliant performance in Hungary...&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The exhilaration of aerobatics or racing against time is my ultimate obsession. Pushing the limits is what I live for, and flying at air shows and competing in the Red Bull Air Race World Championships is my passion. In the end nothing compares to the joy of sharing my experiences. Take a moment to step into my shoes, see what I see, and feel what I feel when flying. Here on my website you will find my thoughts and feelings as I travel the globe to perform and race.  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Perfection is expected, excellence will be accepted.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mikegoulian.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mikegoulian.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OSH Raffle Tickets will be on sale. Tonight Michael will be drawing the winning ticket.....   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks again to Program coordinator Jim Bisson aka Diamond Jim, for putting this together for us with Jim Adams. Yes ,this is another Wings Program as well! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FAMILY AND FRIENDS ARE WELCOME TO THIS EXCITING EVENT. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $25 bucks a year?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fly Often and Fly Safe,  &lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Russ Hume</member_name><member_id>4096811</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ed Murphy</member_name><member_id>5222447</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Bisson</member_name><member_id>6711202</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Louise Anderson</member_name><member_id>6714056</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Bortle</member_name><member_id>6715847</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary Archer</member_name><member_id>6716312</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Scales</member_name><member_id>6873008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273677381000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269121358000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 Monthly Meetup with Mike Goulian</name><id>lrkdnynhbpb</id><headcount>155</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273615200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/12942633/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/1/global_14565713.jpeg</photo_url></item>