<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Est. event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person (See Notes)</description><amount>17.25</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Camping, hiking, &amp;amp; caving from Fri., 6/16 thru Sun., 6/18 in western CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will tent camp at Lake Waramang State Park in Kent &amp;amp; arrive there Fri., 6/16 leaving Hartford area at 7 PM and getting there at about 8:30 PM. All parties must arrive before 10 PM to get in. We'll leave camp Sun. morning, 6/18 some time before Noon. There will be opportunities to swim or kayak on the lake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll do two planned hikes. One, the morning of 6/17 which is 6.4 scenic miles on a trail loop at Macedonia Brook State Park, Kent. We'd hike the Blue Trail across Cobble Mountain &amp;amp; other peaks for outstanding views of the Catskill and Taconic mountains. This hike should take about 3.5 hrs at a slow, enjoyable pace. The second would be in the morning of 6/18 after breaking camp &amp;amp; would be hiking a section of the Appalachian Trail. After this hike, we'll eat &amp;amp; then head for home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The caving will be on 6/17 in the late afternoon. The cave, Tories Cave, is a marble cave w/a few rooms &amp;amp; a crawl space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving time is about 1.5 hrs. from the Hartford area to the camp location. We must carpool as there is a 2 vehicle limit per campsite. We'll meet at a location TBD in the Hartford area. If you'd like to meet up for a portion of the trip or meet at the campground, Kevin S, the leader on this one, will send you directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pay attention to the Message Board as details will be hashed out there!&lt;br /&gt;(&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/boards/view/viewthread?thread=1786595"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** You do not have to go for the whole weekend! Please post what part you can go to so we know when to expect you. Also, I'll eat the extra cost and cap the camping fees per person at $12.25. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees (Do NOT pay via PayPal):&lt;br /&gt;-------&lt;br /&gt;The campsite fees are [we'll do 2 nights]:&lt;br /&gt;...$13/campsite/night&lt;br /&gt;...$9 reservation fee/campsite&lt;br /&gt;...$7/vehicle/day&lt;br /&gt;------&lt;br /&gt;Event Subtotal (2 campsites, 4 vehicles) : $98 est. (depends on vehicles)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Per person cost est.: $12.25 (8 people, 4 vehicles est.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling donation&lt;br /&gt;...$5/person suggested towards gas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total est. cost per person: $17.25 (8 people, 4 vehicles est.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***For the fees, we'll split the overall cost by the number of people going. Campsite and reservation fee will be paid up front by the leader. Vehicle fees will be paid once we get there. It is preferable if the fees and donation are paid at camp when we know how many people actually go.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Extra Details:&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;Each campsite can have 6 people max. and 2 vehicles max. We may be able to add additional campsites, if needed, for more people. 2 Sites are reserved (#12 &amp;amp; #13).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warm clothes &amp;amp; blankets/sleeping bags. Each person must bring enough food for the two nights of camping and two days of hiking/activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headlamp (preferable) or flashlight. A helmet of some kind is essential in the cave to protect your head from bumps. Acceptable helmets are: caving, bike, rock climbing, scateboard, hard hat (cheap is fine). It is cool/cold in the cave so dress wormly into the cave. Clothing into the cave may get tares from rocks so nothing expensive or new. You will get wet and muddy to some degree so a change of clothing is advisable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other items of note:&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------&lt;br /&gt;...Campground has swimming beach, bathrooms, showers, car-top boats can go in the lake (i.e. canoe, kayak), there ARE canoe and kayak rentals available (10 AM - 6 PM, $10/hr or $40/day), NO PETS allowed in the park (sorry!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAMPING:&lt;br /&gt;Lake Waramaug State Park&lt;br /&gt;30 Lake Waramaug Road&lt;br /&gt;New Preston, CT 06777 &lt;br /&gt;Camping (860) 868-0220 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/lakewaramaug.htm"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HIKING #1:&lt;br /&gt;Macedonia Brook State Park&lt;br /&gt;159 Macedonia Brook Road&lt;br /&gt;Kent, CT 06757 &lt;br /&gt;(860) 927-323&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/macedonia.htm"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HIKING #2:&lt;br /&gt;(No good map)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAVING:&lt;br /&gt;(Conservation prevents publishing location)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/lakewaramaug.htm"&gt;&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/lakewaramaug.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540229000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1146846110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping, Hiking, and caving in Western CT for Weekend</name><id>4924276</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1150498800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4924276/</event_url></item>