<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>route 165</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02822</zip><lat>41.576874</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Arcadia Management Area</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1305681</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.702774</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/c/2/event_142093762.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We all know of the Yeti, the Sasquatch, and the Loch Ness, of Huffalumps and Woozles, and Jabberwocks and Chupacabras… but do we all know of the most diabolically evasive creature to ever exist? Well, join me, join us, as I, as we head out into our own Hundred Acre Wood in search of the most elusive of all mythical creatures: My Fitness (and perhaps yours).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/1/4/event_142094612.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Here we can meander with mazy motion and banter back and back, and forth and forth in our pursuit. And should we find, and should we slay &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; most elusive beast Fitness, we can return to our cars, with lungs in tack, chortling our triumphilious conquest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Ride:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We’ll start by meeting at the J B Hudson Trail parking area (east, just up the street from the white church &amp;amp; Frosty Hollow Rd). We’ll saddle our tubular steeds and ride north following the J B Hudson (or whatever unrestricted trail or road we find) to Breakheart Pond. From there we’ll ride around the eastern side of the pond, picking up the Breakheart Trail as it leads us west towards the Shelter Trail and Austin Farm Rd.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/0/a/event_142127882.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The plan is to ride a loop that will keep us out in the woods for up to an hour and a half, or two hours. Should any of us find that darkness is settling in, or that our legs are giving out, we’ll take advantage of the trails or fire roads that will return us to our cars in the shortest amount of time and/or the least amount of effort. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;On trail you can expect to experience a combination of fire roads and single-track, passing through forests and fields, over varied terrain, from smooth to rough, over rocks and roots, gravel and dirt which will require a bit of technical skill. But no worries, because we will be following the Primary Rules of Mountain Biking: 1. We ride as a group; 2. We hike what we cannot ride; and 3. We wait at all major trailheads. Our pace will be moderate and accommodating (no speedsters here), but, you should know that the ride is filled with a number of short steep ups and downs, and I ask that you believe yourself to be an intermediately skilled rider, or a fit beginner/intermediate rider willing to be challenged by the terrain. I will be riding a rigid single-speed (no shocks) w/ flat pedals, so my pace will not be blazing, nor will I be riding up every climb; that my friends is for another time.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;From the intersection of Rt 3 and Rt 165, follow Rt 165 east for approximately 2.5 miles. Turn right into a small parking area hidden from obvious view (about 400’ before Frosty Hollow Rd &amp;amp; the white church). Should you find yourself at the church… no worries, turn around, go back and turn left at the first drive you see.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Google Maps: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=@41.576874,-71.702774"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=@41.576874,-71.702774"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Coordinates: 41.576874, -71.702774&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you reach Frosty Hollow Rd &amp; the white church, you've gone too far - we're 400' east, back up the road; call if you can't find us. Cell: 860-460-1500</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>11024921</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343334302000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343076849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike Arcadia: To Breakheart Pond, Beyond &amp; Back</name><id>74588882</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343252700000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/74588882/</event_url></item>