<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>65 Thornton Ferry Road II</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03031</zip><lat>42.842518</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Souhegan Woods Golf Club‎</name><city>Amherst</city><id>2239681</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.568413</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>United We Stand for Jason (UWSFJ) will host our 7th annual golf tournament on Monday, July 18th at Soughegan Woods Golf Course, Amherst, NH at 7:30 a.m. The tournament benefits the lives of those inflicted with Huntington's Disease and in honor of our dear friend, Jason Hilton who lost his battle with the terrible disease this past year. Our goal this year is to raise $15,000. The tournament will include a round of golf, lunch, live auction, silent auction and raffle prizes. Please visit our website (www.unitedwestandforjason.org) for more information, sponsor signup sheets and registration signup sheets. The deadline for registration is June 27, 2011. United We Stand for Jason is a non-profit charity that is dedicated to educating people about Huntington&amp;#146;s Disease (HD), funding research for a cure and improving the lives of people living with HD. United is 100% staffed by countless volunteers and board members who dedicate themselves to United&amp;#146;s mission. We are proud that over 90% of the proceeds raised by United went directly to our mission last year. Huntington&amp;#146;s Disease is a neurodegenerative disease in the same family as Alzheimer&amp;#146;s and Parkinson&amp;#146;s Disease. Huntington's Disease results from genetically programmed degeneration of cells in certain areas of the brain. It causes uncontrolled movements, loss of intellectual faculties, and emotional disturbance. Over time, concentration on intellectual tasks becomes increasingly difficult and the patient may have difficulty eating and swallowing. The rate at which the disease progresses and the age of onset varies. At this time there is no way to stop or reverse the course of Huntington's Disease.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310993039000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Millionaires</urlname><id>1477459</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Millionaires</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308579296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Play golf in a non-profit golf tournament which also has raffle prizes.</name><id>22829391</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310988600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Millionaires/events/22829391/</event_url></item>