<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>623 Trapelo Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.404760</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John M. Sullivan Post #10334 - VFW</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1114517</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.217073</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Cost: $10 early bird price paid before Sept 1st.  $12 paid between Sept 1st and Sept 23rd.  $15 at the door&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you remember flower power, Bel Air automobiles, or cigarette ads on TV--or even if you don't--come to the BBTC's fall Sixties Dance!  Greet your fellow Beanstalks and members of the public while&lt;br /&gt;dancing to great tunes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear your best 1960s gear and styles for a chance to win the costume contest.  Dig out your go-go boots, wide belts, skinny ties, Bryl Creem, hot pink lipstick, bellbottoms, etc. If you tossed them, go to a vintage clothing store! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special prize for the Best Jimi Hendrix!  (of any race)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember: We're going for the LOOK, not the actual sex, drugs, and rock 'n' roll! Well, OK, we WILL have the rock 'n' roll part.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This brand-new, beautifully appointed hall has hardwood floors throughout for dancing, a full bar, and plenty of parking. It has the distinction of being the first VFW post in Massachusetts to be named for a Vietnam veteran. Their bartender will take care of all your beverage needs, there will be plenty of munchies, and a DJ will provide tunes to keep your feet happy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tell a friend--bring a friend--and BE THERE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register in advance and pay via Paypal via the option when you RSVP to this posting, and enter your payment as a &amp;quot;donation&amp;quot; along with your credit card information. (It’s not really a donation, but that’s the language Paypal uses, so we humor them.)  Bring your e-mail receipt with you when you come to the dance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 95: Take exit 28, Trapelo Road, east toward Waltham/Belmont. Continue eastward on Trapelo. The building is on the corner of Trapelo Road and Marguerite Ave. Parking is behind the building as well as on Marguerite Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2: Take exit 54, Waltham Street, and follow southward, crossing Route 2. Waltham Street will change to Lexington Street. At junction with Trapelo Road, turn left and continue on Trapelo. The building is on the corner of Trapelo Road and Marguerite Ave. Parking is behind the building as well as on Marguerite Ave.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285524992000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281667700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sixties Dance</name><id>14409059</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285457400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/14409059/</event_url></item>