<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;For those who've seen the film and are dying (pun intended) to talk about it, or for those who haven't but are dying to see it, even for those who've seen it and wonder what all the fuss about Wes Anderson is about,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the new comedy from director/co-writer Wes Anderson (The Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou, The Royal Tenenbaums), three American brothers who have not spoken to each other in a year (Owen Wilson, Adrien Brody and Jason Schwartzman) set off on a train voyage across India with a plan to find themselves and bond with each other?to become brothers again like they used to be. Their &amp;quot;spiritual quest,&amp;quot; however, veers rapidly off-course, and they eventually find themselves stranded alone in the middle of the desert with eleven suitcases, a printer and a laminating machine. At this moment, a new, unplanned journey suddenly begins. BONUS! All screenings are now preceded by Anderson's Hotel Chevalier, a short companion piece starring Schwartzman and Natalie Portman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Caution:  This film is currently playing at Kendall Square, but as it has been out for a long time, there is no guarantee that it will still be playing, or at this posted time, on December 1.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, unlike my historic Blade Runner snafu, I will update this posting during the week for exact times (and possibly theater)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, we will go to a local restaurant for scintillating discussion.  John will hold up a Meetup sign in english at the front of the theater.  If you've never come to one of this group's meetups, start your New Year's resolutions early with a trip to India and some pretty neat fellow travellers.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196787701000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196000001000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Darjeeling Limited</name><id>6799241</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196544600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6799241/</event_url></item>