<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>472 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363930</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-866-777-8932</phone><name>The Middle East Restaurant and Nightclub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669146</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101230</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Gah, one of my favorite Southern bands is Royal Bangs. And low and behold they are a favorite on Woxy too. A drum beating and hip shaking slightly emo, highly garage band rockin band, they ALWAYS put on a great show. And We Were Promised Jetpacks in addition? Guaranteed AMAZING night. So let's PBR it preshow style and then enjoy the show. Yes, it is Valentines Day and yes it is a Sunday. But there is more than one kind of love and there is no love like that of good music. Doors open at 8:00. I will be there around 7:00 and maybe do some dinner and predrinks. Come early and share or meet us later, but either or you should come!&lt;br /&gt;$12 pre, $14 @ the door   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lala.com/zwdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Wiki: &lt;br /&gt;Royal Bangs: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Royal Bangs are an American rock group from Knoxville, TN. Formed in 2005, the quintet is composed of Henry Gibson (bass guitar), Chris Rusk (drums), Ryan Schaefer (keyboard, vocals, beats), Brandon Biondo (guitar), and Sam Stratton (guitar).[1] Royal Bangs released their debut LP We Breed Champions in 2008 through Audio Eagle Records, an independent record label founded and run by Patrick Carney of The Black Keys.[2] The following year, German label City Slang released the album in Europe where British music publication Uncut (magazine) described the record as &amp;quot;belting garage rock, quirky indie rock and bamboozling electronica, all served up in one smart and super-confident package, rather like a chirpier, younger, less navel-gazing Radiohead.&amp;quot;[3][4] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Royal Bangs played at Bonnaroo in 2008 [5] when Danny Sale and Jason Campbell were still in the band. Royal Bangs also played at the 1st annual KahBang Indie Music Festival in Bangor, Maine on August 15, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From FatCat Records: &lt;br /&gt;We Were Promised Jetpacks: &lt;br /&gt;Following closely in the footsteps of The Twilight Sad and Frightened Rabbit, We Were Promised Jetpacks are yet another hugely talented young Scottish band added to the FatCat roster. The 4-piece came to our attention when listening to some of the friends on the Frightened Rabbit Myspace page. Though recent months has seen the band tour the UK with their aforementioned friends, the four preceding years have consisted of local gigs in and around Glasgow and Edinburgh, allowing WWPJ to find their sound and hone their live performance.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Assembled in Edinburgh as high school friends in 2003, their first ever gig saw them winning their school's battle of the bands competition. Proceeding shows were after school performances around the city of Edinburgh which were well attended and fuelled the band with a hunger and ambition. If the nascent WWPJ aural template embraced light-footed compositions – few effects pedals, traditional song structures, clear-cut guitars - succeeding years have seen WWPJ soar aural heights and mine emotional depths in every sense: the band you will encounter now are a cacophonous tour de force: louder, wilder, avidly literate; fiercely melodic, yet eagerly restrained. Lyrics and vocal melodies come courtesy of Adam Thompson, everything else arises from the full group; Adam Thompson (Guitar/Vocals), Michael Palmer (Guitar), Sean Smith (Bass) and Darren Lackie (Drums). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jenn</member_name><member_id>10142965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267493671000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263599165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Royal Bangs and We Were Promised Jetpacks @ the Middle East </name><id>12332092</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266195600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/12332092/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/e/global_12632670.jpeg</photo_url></item>