<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S5QErPDNcj4"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S5QErPDNcj4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Turn up the volume&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;WARNING CONTENT AND LANGUAGE &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5PsnxDQvQpw"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5PsnxDQvQpw&lt;/a&gt;WARNING CONTENT AND LANGUAGE!!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What is normal?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ellyn Satter, an expert on eating and feeding. writes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Normal eating is going to the table hungry and eating until you are satisfied. It is being able to choose food you like and eat it and truly get enough of it—not just stop eating because you think you should. Normal eating is being able to give some thought to your food selection so you get nutritious food, but not being so wary and restrictive that you miss out on enjoyable food. Normal eating is giving yourself permission to eat sometimes because you are happy, sad or bored, or just because it feels good. Normal eating is mostly three meals a day, or four or five, or it can be choosing to munch along the way. It is leaving some cookies on the plate because you know you can have some again tomorrow, or it is eating more now because they taste so wonderful. Normal eating is overeating at times, feeling stuffed and uncomfortable. And it can be undereating at times and wishing you had more. Normal eating is trusting your body to make up for your mistakes in eating. Normal eating takes up some of your time and attention, but keeps its place as only one important area of your life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In short, normal eating is flexible. It varies in response to your hunger, your schedule, your proximity to food and your feelings.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I think normal life, normal anything might fit this definition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I want to go to the table of life hungry and consume all the wonders life has to offer until I am satisfied. I want to choose the work and the play I like, and then do it until I've gotten enough from my work and my play - not work until I drop or play with no regard for contribution or well-being. Normal living is being able to give yourself permission to live sometimes as happy, sad, or bored because life is all those things and sometimes it feels good and sometimes it doesn't but you should feel all of it. Normal is living life by choosing every day or several times a day or in constant review how you want to react to stimuli, what direction you wish to move in this living, and who you want on the journey with you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is leaving some experiences on the plate because anticipation is a wonderful thing and you can choose to come back to that experience. It is also taking everything offered and throwing caution to the wind, it is bungee cords, parachutes, and roller coasters. Normal is quite meditation and solitude. It can be sitting alone, accepting the feelings that accompany loneliness, and finding hope or humor in moments of silent desperation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Normal life is feeling all there is to feel, experiencing what gifts you are offered or have to offer, and trusting yourself to learn from your mistakes and your successes. Normal hugs everything and waits to see what hugs back. A life lived full of normal requires your time and attention. Life with all its moods, shades, and geography insists on, demands to be a priority.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Life in the normal is ultimately flexible; it varies according to your choices, the environment, the resources you can pull together and your acceptance and celebration of your feelings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lots of fun and lots of food and drink. It is perfectly normal! Remember there are no rules. Caryl will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>back at Caryl's place, I'll send the location email out the Wednesday before the dinner</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347720543000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344628692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Try Something Normal</name><id>qxhmlcyqmbsb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347663600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/77213102/</event_url></item>