<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A single mom and her slacker sister find an unexpected way to turn their lives around in the off-beat dramatic comedy Sunshine Cleaning. Directed by Christine Jeffs (Rain, Sylvia), this uplifting film about an average family that finds the path to its dreams in an unlikely setting screened in competition at the 2008 Sundance Film Festival. Once the high school cheerleading captain who dated the quarterback, Rose Lorkowski (Amy Adams) now finds herself a thirty something single mother working as a maid. Her sister Norah, (Emily Blunt), is still living at home with their dad Joe (Alan Arkin), a salesman with a lifelong history of ill-fated get rich quick schemes. Desperate to get her son into a better school, Rose persuades Norah to go into the crime scene clean-up business with her to make some quick cash. In no time, the girls are up to their elbows in murders, suicides and other…specialized situations. As they climb the ranks in a dirty job, the sisters find respect for one another. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Amy Adams, Emily Blunt, Alan Arkin, Jason Spevack, Steve Zahn &lt;br /&gt;Director: Christine Jeffs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like the other movie meetup group (Beyond the Multiplex - Indie ...)   is going this night too so hopefully we'll get a good crowd.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby.  The movie starts at 7:30 but let's meet by 7:15.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240532410000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238692868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunshine Cleaning</name><id>10098647</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239232500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10098647/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/4/global_7947476.jpeg</photo_url></item>