<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Jamaica Pond 507 Jamaicaway Jamaica Plain, MA 02130</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.319700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jamaica Pond</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>694523</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.spontaneouscelebrations.org/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;POSTPONED DUE TO WEATHER&lt;/a&gt; - JOIN US ON SUNDAY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you been searching for &lt;i&gt;cool progressives&lt;/i&gt; to hang with in Boston? Want to &lt;i&gt;cross-promote your campaigns&lt;/i&gt; under the candle-light? Are you &lt;i&gt;new to the area&lt;/i&gt; and looking for something fun to do? Then join &lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice&lt;/b&gt; (SoJust) on SUNDAY, OCTOBER 26 for the&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt; &lt;b&gt;Lantern Parade for Justice!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For 25 years, the ritual of the Jamaica Pond Lantern Parade has been a loved tradition. Each year, thousands of people gather with friends and family to make a journey with their candle-lit lanterns around the Jamaica Pond. Each lantern is hand made from recycled soda bottles and is decorated with beautiful, colorful tissue paper. Make your own or purchase one the night of the parade! The parade proceeds around the pond, bringing a trail of bouncing lights into the darkness that can be seen from all directions. This beautiful autumn evening ceremony has become an annual tradition in the Jamaica Plain community in October. &lt;b&gt;Come for fun, friends, conversation, and even some Halloween costumes!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at 6:30 PM in front of the Boathouse&lt;/b&gt; (across from Pond Street at the intersection of Jamaicaway) to meet-up and parade with like-minded people. We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have. At SoJust events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come bask in the warmth, love and light with people who share your vision of building a more just world&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;newcomers always welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: $2 to cover group expenses + Lanterns are on sale at the event (sales benefit Spontaneous Celebrations)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is put on by Spontaneous Celebrations. Check their website for more event details and information on hosting your own lantern making party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.spontaneouscelebrations.org/happening.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.spontaneou...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hilary</member_name><member_id>3092728</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caitlin Gury</member_name><member_id>7596710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227142918000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224696324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lantern Parade for Justice!</name><id>9011391</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225060200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/9011391/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/c/global_5983772.jpeg</photo_url></item>