<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 8:00, so we'll meet right inside the theater doors (or right outside if it's nice out) at 7:30. Please call me if you're going to be late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, please keep your RSVP up to date, so I know who to expect and wait for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks and see you Wednesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;It's been a while... I've been terribly busy (both good and bad stuff), but I wanna go see the early summer blockbusters, so I'm off my duff and scheduling away! (Didja miss me? Can you pretend that you noticed I was dark for a while? &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's see how the tough guy with a big heart got his metallic skeleton -- &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1808665084/info" target="_blank"&gt;Wolverine&lt;/a&gt;, both scary and kind of a heartthrob.  X-Men Origins is a series (rumor has it they're making or have just finished making one about Magneto....ooooo!) that predates (chronologically per the story) the X-Men trilogy we all know and love. We all do know and love it, right? Right?! I don't think you need to have seen the trilogy to love this one, but it will probably help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&amp;quot;X-Men Origins: Wolverine&amp;quot; tells the story of Wolverine's epically violent and romantic past, his complex relationship with Victor Creed, and the ominous Weapon X program. Along the way, Wolverine encounters many mutants, both familiar and new, including surprise appearances by several legends of the X-Men universe.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for X-Men Origins: Wolverine!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242515963000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241577403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>X-Men Origins: Wolverine</name><id>10348030</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242255600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10348030/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>