<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Our &amp;quot;chefess&amp;quot;/hostess extraordinaire will guide us in preparing and cooking Mexican cuisine (you may want to dust off and bring your aprons as everyone will be helping out) .  There will be a nominal charge (divided evenly among all attendees - approximately $12 to $15 per person) to pay for the food that our hostess will purchase prior to the event.. This is a BYOB (Mexican, Spanish, or South American wine/beer would be good choices - only bring one) event, which we'll share with each other.   &lt;br /&gt;                                                                       &lt;br /&gt;The hostess sent me to following info about what will be on the menu:  &lt;br /&gt;                                                                                            &lt;br /&gt;The menu is as follows: &lt;br /&gt;                                                                                        &lt;br /&gt;Wine &amp;amp; Beer: Your choice (only bring one). Mexican, Spanish or South American preferred (if you can't find one of these, just do your best) &lt;br /&gt;Appetizers:  quesadellas, tortilla chips with guacamole, black bean and corn salsa &lt;br /&gt;Beef Chili with cornbread &lt;br /&gt;Desert: Tres Leches cake (and possibly Kahlua chocolate mousse &amp;lt;- yummy, this sounds good!)  &lt;br /&gt;                                      &lt;br /&gt;This should definitely produce endorphins. If not, you'll just have to engorge yourself with more wine or beer.    &lt;br /&gt;                                                                           &lt;br /&gt;I will send out a follow-up email with more information (directions, etc.) on Thursday, November 18th, to those who have been responded &lt;b&gt;Yes&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290354192000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289775901000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reminder: Wine, Beer, &amp; Cooking Event, Wethersfield, Nov 20  @ 6:00 PM</name><id>15446084</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290294000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/15446084/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>