<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Arrow St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.868.2033</phone><name>Pierre Menard Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>347668</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lame Duck Books and Pierre Menard Gallery are proud to announce a reading by the extraordinary novelist and poet Rikki Ducornet beginning at 7 PM on Monday 12 October at Pierre Menard Gallery, 10 Arrow Street, Cambridge, MA.  Ms. Ducornet will read from her new book of stories, THE ONE MARVELOUS THING, published by Dalkey Archive Press.  A reception and signing will take place after the reading.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rikki Ducornet had already illustrated books by Jorge Luis Borges and Robert Coover, published two children’s books of her own, as well as four volumes of poetry and a collection of stories, The Butcher’s Tales, before her first novel, The Stain, came out in 1984, which Angela Carter praised as a “A riotous extravaganza, comic, melodramatic and touching, that goes over the top time and time again but never loses its antic grace” and The Guardian called “the most brilliant first novel in years.”  Seven novels and several collections of short fictions have followed, including The Fountains of Neptune (“extraordinary”—Oliver Sacks), The Complete Butcher’s Tales, Phosphor in Dreamland (“astonishing, a complex fantasia redolent of Swift and Borges, but stranger than both”—The Times, London), and The Fan-Maker’s Inquisition (“an exquisitely crafted work of art, a treasure”—Robert Coover).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ducornet’s work draws upon the surreal, satirical, erotic, comic, and visionary, and is viewed by many as being a crucial contemporary voice in the fantastic tradition of H.P. Lovecraft, Bruno Schulz, Borges, and Carter.  She is an accomplished visual artist, as well, whose lithographs, drawings and paintings have been exhibited widely, including museums in West Berlin, Ixelles, Coimbra, Mexico City, and Lille, as well as the Biblioteque Nationale.  Her most recent show took place at the Museo de la Solidaridad in Santiago, Chile.  She has won numerous awards for her writing, The Jade Cabinet being a finalist for the National Book Critics Circle Award, The Fan-Maker’s Inquisition named an Los Angeles Times Book of the Year. She has received a Lannan Fellowship and a Lannan Literary Award for fiction and an Academy Award from the American Academy of Arts and Letters.  She is currently Visiting Hurst Professor at Washington University.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255647911000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255104128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading: Rikki Ducornet at Pierre Menard</name><id>11589014</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255388400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/11589014/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/4/global_8983348.jpeg</photo_url></item>