<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>CGIS South Building Tsai Auditorium</address_2><address_1>1730 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375269</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tsai Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>748933</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112774</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am extremely grateful to Joana for bringing this free film series to our attention. If you are able to join us for the final film, please meet me (Tonya) at &lt;b&gt;5:30 PM&lt;/b&gt; for FREE pizza and conversation before the FREE film. There are vending machines nearby to purchase beverages. I'll be seated downstairs at the high tables outside of the auditorium wearing an orange beret. Look for the table with a gold star and Portuguese sign. If you aren't able to find us, call or text me (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Tuesday, November 18, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;Movie Time: 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address: 1730 Cambridge Street, Cambridge, MA 02138 (above is photo of building)&lt;br /&gt;Building: Center for Government and International Studies (CGIS South)&lt;br /&gt;Room: Tsai Auditorium is downstairs from entrance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route. Less ten (10) minute walk from Harvard Station stop on Red Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your driving route&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;Very limited parking at meters on Oxford and Cambridge Streets, as well as non metered parking on Beacon Street, which is two blocks away.&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Square Public Parking&lt;/a&gt; for garages and lots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by The Brazil Studies Program at David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies (DRCLAS) and The Harvard Brazilian Organization&lt;br /&gt;This event is made possible by the generous support of the Jorge Paulo Lemann Fund.&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Marcio Siwi (msiwi@fas.harvard.edu)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.drclas.harvard.edu/brazil/events/brasileirinho" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.drclas.har...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sound of Brazil: Brasileirinho&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Mika Kaurismäki, 2005 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mika Kaurismäki's toe-tapping, finger-snapping documentary reveals the vibrant sounds of Brazil's old-style Choro music, a blend of native Indian, European and African styles that forms the foundation of modern musical styles including Bossa Nova and Samba. This musical documentary shows the history and the vitality of Choro, one of the first genuinely Brazilian urban musical style. Choro was created around 1870 when new music groups in Rio de Janeiro started mixing European music with Afro-Brazilian rhythms and melancholic music of Brazilian Indians. After being overshadowed by the Samba in the 1920s and later by the Bossa Nova, Choro is now livelier than ever before in the bars and concert halls. Brasileirinho focuses on the musicians from &amp;quot;Trio Madeira Brasil&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Sitting at the high tables outside the the auditorium wearing an orange beret</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259017933000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221526545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brazil Movie Series: The Sound of Brazil: Brasileirinho - FREE PIZZA &amp; A MOVIE</name><id>8764958</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227047400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/8764958/</event_url></item>