<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Amherst Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6177232226</phone><name>New MIT Media Lab</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1415046</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.087191</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consent of the Networked&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Worldwide Struggle for Internet Freedom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thursday, February 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time and Venue TBA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free and Open to the Public&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP required for those attending in person&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP &lt;a href="http://cyber.law.harvard.edu/events/2012/02/mackinnon"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remember: The CMF Meet-Ups are &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;member-driven&lt;/span&gt;; that is, if you would like to meet up with other members, it is up to you, as a member, to post your plans on the event message board. I am not able to attend every event, so if no one posts plans, then no one meets up.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Co-hosted by the MIT Center for Civic Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A global struggle for control of the Internet is now underway.&amp;nbsp; At stake are no less than civil liberties, privacy and even the character of democracy in the 21st century. Many commentators have debated whether the Internet is ultimately a force for freedom of expression and political liberation, or for alienation, and repression. It is time to stop arguing over whether the Internet empowers individuals and societies, and address the more fundamental and urgent question of how technology should be structured and governed to support the rights and liberties of all the world&amp;rsquo;s Internet users. In her timely book, Rebecca MacKinnon warns that a convergence of unchecked government actions and unaccountable company practices is threatening the future of democracy and human rights around the world. Consent of the Networked is a call to action: Our freedom in the Internet age depends on whether we defend our rights on digital platforms and networks in the same way that people fight for their rights and accountable governance in physical communities and nations. It is time to stop thinking of ourselves as passive &amp;ldquo;users&amp;rdquo; of technology and instead act like citizens of the Internet &amp;ndash; as netizens &amp;ndash; and take ownership and responsibility for our digital future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Rebecca&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Rebecca MacKinnon is a Bernard L. Schwartz Senior Fellow at the New America Foundation, where she conducts research, writing and advocacy on global Internet policy, free expression, and the impact of digital technologies on human rights. She is cofounder of Global Voices, an international citizen media network. She also serves on the Boards of Directors of the Committee to Protect Journalists and the Global Network Initiative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fluent in Mandarin Chinese, MacKinnon worked as a journalist for CNN in Beijing for nine years and was Beijing Bureau Chief and Correspondent from 1998-2001, then served as CNN&amp;rsquo;s Tokyo Bureau Chief and Correspondent from 2001-03. From 2004-06 she was a Research Fellow at Harvard&amp;rsquo;s Berkman Center for Internet and Society, where she began her ongoing research and writing about the Chinese Internet in addition to launching Global Voices with colleague Ethan Zuckerman. In 2007-08 she taught online journalism at the University of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Journalism and Media Studies Centre. In 2009 she conducted research and writing as an Open Society Fellow, and in the Spring of 2010 she was a Visiting Fellow at Princeton&amp;rsquo;s Center or Information Technology Policy. MacKinnon received her AB magna cum laude from Harvard College and was a Fullbright scholar in Taiwan in 1991-92.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/"&gt;Consent of the Networked website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328207078000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322782671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Consent of the Networked</name><id>43090052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328202000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/43090052/</event_url></item>