<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Railroad Ave &amp; 1A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01969</zip><lat>42.725187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-921-2272</phone><name>American BBQ</name><city>Rowley</city><id>1144374</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.865423</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Yes you read it right, we are bringing back Conversation night. We have had many requests from members who attended last year, those who have heard about last years but did not attend. So we have decided to go back to our favorite venue for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;2.20.11 UPDATE:&amp;nbsp; For these of you with Dietary concerns we have called American BBQ to double check and they have a Gluten free menu and also vegetarian items.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who did not attend, we talked about dating &amp;amp; relationships and also learned a little bit about each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We try to make this a fun, non-stressful night because some questions are hard to ask, we provide paper and a basket at the door. When arriving you will be asked to write your question on the paper and drop it in the basket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;American BBQ provides us with a very private room and are extremely accommodating. So come on down and socialize and join in the conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will begin the night by having dinner in a mix n mingle format. Once everyone has eaten we will then open up the conversation to the questions that were left in the basket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come on down to American BBQ and have some fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there  &lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Organizers in the private room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298914730000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294015669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BACK BY POPULAR DEMAND:  Conversation night at American BBQ in Rowley</name><id>15889928</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298754000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/15889928/</event_url></item>