<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rte. 138</address_2><address_1>217 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02072</zip><lat>42.139900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781)344-1800</phone><name>X &amp; O RESTAURANT</name><city>Stoughton</city><id>1262956</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103500</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group and their Guests for a Mediterranean treat for lunch at X &amp;amp; O on Route 138 in Stoughton. Save your appetite for some delicious baklava after lunch!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience the difference of X &amp;amp; O, where rich family traditions are balanced perfectly by an understanding of modern trends.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gregoriades’ passion for fine food and hospitality is generations old and a tradition that traces back to the villages of northern Greece, when meals were a time to come together in celebration, for business, or simply to enjoy each other’s company.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While many miles and many years have passed, one thing has not – today, the Gregoriades' family recipe for an X and O experience includes homemade Greek, Italian and American cuisine, an inviting atmosphere, and an opportunity to connect with family and friends.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrees range from $8-$13. Salads and Appetizers range from $4-$11 (option of additional toppings for an additional cost). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday Lunch @ X &amp;amp; O &lt;br /&gt;Sunday September 19th @ 12:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;217 Washington St &lt;br /&gt;Stoughton, MA 02072 &lt;br /&gt;781-344-1800&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://xoonline.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://xoonline.net...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: Inside the lobby. We will then be seated as a Group.  If you arrive after we are seated the reservation is under &amp;quot;Alison&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Alison  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 4 people 48 hours in advance. Max of 12 people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per Member &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: Current Annual Members - FREE, Group Members - $2, Guests - $2. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 6pm on Saturday, September 18th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page. Please Note: The restaurant has requested we call in our final RSVP on Saturday. (A quick note about the RSVP Deadline, you can only RSVP up until 10am the day of the event. After that time you will not be able to RSVP. While the Group's RSVP Deadline is Saturday evening, this will allow anyone to join us Sunday morning if a spot opens up if someone is unable to make it between Saturday's deadline and Sunday's cutoff. You can't RSVP on the site after 10am on Sunday. Our No-Show policy remains the same; any changes from Yes to No after the deadline and/or anyone who is a Yes at the deadline who does not attend is considered a No-Show. Our updated RSVP policy still allows for one excused No-Show per 12 month period from the previous excused N/S.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the wait staff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Event takes place rain or shine.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These directions are directly from the X &amp;amp; O website, but feel free to use your GPS or Google maps if you prefer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North &amp;amp; West From MASS PIKE, or Rte 2, or Rte 3 &lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 S / Rte 128 S. Merge LEFT onto I-93 N. Take Rte 138 S (EXIT 2A). Continue on Rte 138 for about 4.5 miles; X &amp;amp; O is on the RIGHT.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From South-East Mass &lt;br /&gt;From I-495 NB take Rte 24 N. Exit at Central St (head WEST, toward Stoughton). Continue on Central St about 2 miles; turn RIGHT onto Rte 138 / Washington St. X &amp;amp; O is on the LEFT.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rhode Island &amp;amp; the South &lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 N to town of Sharon (EXIT 8). Continue about 5 miles (thru Sharon Center and thru Cobb’s Corner - the road becomes Rte 27). Follow Rte 27 up to fork; veer LEFT onto Central St. at fork. Continue on Central St.; turn LEFT onto Rte 138 / Washington St. X &amp;amp; O is on the LEFT.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Neighboring Towns &lt;br /&gt;- Join Rte 27; then follow directions From Rhode Island.  &lt;br /&gt;- Follow Rte 139 to Rte 138 / Washington Street; then follow directions From S.E. Mass.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture and will wait in the entry way / lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285034099000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283224499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"X" Marks the Spot (X &amp; O that is)........</name><id>14600137</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284913800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/14600137/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/6/global_16657014.jpeg</photo_url></item>