<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;ROBERT DARNTON&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;explains&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Case for Books:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Past, Present, and Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is delighted to host a conversation about the importance of the printed word with Harvard University Library director ROBERT DARNTON.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The invention of writing was one of the most important technological, cultural, and sociological breakthroughs in human history. With the printed book, information and ideas could disseminate more widely and effectively than ever before—and in some cases, affect and redirect the sway of history. Today, nearly one million books are published each year. But is the era of the book as we know it—a codex of bound pages—coming to an end? And if it is, should we celebrate its demise and the creation of a democratic digital future, or mourn an irreplaceable loss? The digital age is revolutionizing the information landscape. Already, more books have been scanned and digitized than were housed in the great library in Alexandria, making available millions of texts for a curious reader at the click of a button, and electronic book sales are growing exponentially. Will this revolution in the delivery of information and entertainment make for more transparent and far-reaching dissemination or create a monopolistic stranglehold? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In The Case for Books, Robert Darnton, an intellectual pioneer in the field of the history of the book and director of Harvard University's Library, offers an in-depth examination of the book from its earliest beginnings to its shifting role today in popular culture, commerce, and the academy. As an author, editorial advisor, and publishing entrepreneur, Darnton is a unique authority on the life and role of the book in society. This book is a wise work of scholarship—one that requires readers to carefully consider how the digital revolution will broadly affect the marketplace of ideas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;CONTACT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Info:&lt;br /&gt;617.661.1515&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Media:&lt;br /&gt;617.661.1424 ex.1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email:&lt;br /&gt;rbcass@harvard.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Event Information&lt;br /&gt;DATE: Wednesday, February 3rd &lt;br /&gt;TIME: 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: Harvard Book Store &lt;br /&gt;1256 Massachusetts Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge  &lt;br /&gt;TICKETS: This event is free; no tickets are required &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Robert Darnton is a former professor of European History at Princeton University, and current Carl H. Pforzheimer University Professor and director of the Harvard University Library. The founder of the Gutenberg-e program, he is the author of many books, including most recently George Washington's False Teeth: An Unconventional Guide to the Eighteenth Century, as well as the 1995 National Book Critics Circle Award–winning The Forbidden Best-Sellers of Prerevolutionary France. He lives in Cambridge, Massachusetts.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present. See message board below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265415250000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262376015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Case for Books</name><id>12191315</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265241600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12191315/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/a/global_6571242.jpeg</photo_url></item>