<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Here's our chance to view and swap cards! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've got cards you'd like to exchange, bring 'em along. If you've got cards you'd just like to show off, bring those, too. And also bring any books, supplies or materials that you're willing to lend, swap or just give away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't have any cards yet, come anyway. You'll meet other ATC enthusiasts and go home inspired to start making cards of your own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's no charge for this meetup except for your own (optional) lunch costs. We'll only be yakking and trading this time, not actually making cards (but we have a hands-on session coming up in September, so you won't have to wait too long to create again).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who'd like to have lunch should arrive by 1 p.m. Those who just want to trade should arrive by 2. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be in a private dining room with a big conference table with plenty of space for us to do our show-and-tell (and swap). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---The restaurant's lunch menu is here: &lt;a href="http://www.jimbossteakandfin.com/menus&amp;amp;events/lunchmenu.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jimbosstea...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Directions are here: &lt;a href="http://www.jimbossteakandfin.com/Directions.html?a=u&amp;amp;b=FFFFFF&amp;amp;c=0&amp;amp;d=1&amp;amp;e=&amp;amp;f=&amp;amp;g=&amp;amp;h=&amp;amp;i=" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jimbosstea...&lt;/a&gt; (if the link doesn't work, just use the &amp;quot;directions&amp;quot; tab on the Web site.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP ASAP -- and please plan to attend our Sept. 15 all-day hands-on session in Natick! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188234158000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185630628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England ATC Meetup Summer Lunch &amp; Swap</name><id>6089419</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188061200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/6089419/</event_url></item>