<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bio-IT World Conference &amp;amp; Expo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;When: April 24-26, 2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Where: World Trade Center, Boston, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Register: &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;www.bio-itworldexpo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Keynote Speakers: Eric D. Perakslis, Ph.D., the newly appointed CIO and Chief Scientist of Informatics, U.S. Food and Drug Administration; Martin Leach, Ph.D., CIO, Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard; and Jill P. Mesirov, Ph.D., Associate Director and Chief Informatics Officer, Director, Computational Biology and Bioinformatics, Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Join us for the 10th anniversary celebration of the Bio-IT World Conference &amp;amp; Expo. The 2012 Expo plans to unite 2,000+ life sciences, pharmaceutical, clinical, healthcare, and IT professionals from 30+ countries. The Expo provides the perfect venue to share information and discuss enabling technologies that are driving biomedical research and the drug development process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;Since its debut in 2002, the annual Bio-IT World Conference &amp;amp; Expo has established itself as a premier event showcasing the myriad applications of IT and informatics to biomedical research and the drug discovery enterprise. Marking our 10th anniversary, the 2012 program will feature compelling talks from industry and academia on new trends in data generation, knowledge management, and information technology in life sciences and drug development. Bio-IT World Conference &amp;amp; Expo continues to expand with the addition of three new Tracks: Molecular Diagnostics Informatics, Open Source Solutions, and Cancer Informatics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #704525"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #704525"&gt;In addition, the conference will feature a plenary panel discussion on advances in cancer diagnostics, informatics and therapeutics, in which a distinguished group of some of the most innovative and renowned cancer researchers will discuss the current state of cancer research, diagnostics, genome analysis and clinical trials. Panelists include Julian Adams (Infinity Pharmaceuticals), Jose Baselga (Massachusetts General Hospital), Sir John Burn (Newcastle University, UK), and John Quackenbush (Dana- Farber Cancer Institute).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335273689000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334109487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bio-IT World Conference &amp; Expo</name><id>60071022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335268800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/60071022/</event_url></item>