<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello. I am the assistant organizer to George for this club. I would like to schedule some books that are light and quick and fun to read. A few I would like to read are books by Emily Giffin, John Grisham,  and Charlaine Harris. Just some ideas.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's start the first book with the Girl with the Dragon Tattoo. I hear it is a great book and it is now a movie. If you have ANY other suggestions, I would love to hear them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out for a night of meeting new people and fun conversation!!  Look forward to meeting you.  Kim&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo&lt;/i&gt; by Stieg Larsson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cases rarely come much colder than the decades-old disappearance of teen heiress Harriet Vanger from her family's remote island retreat north of Stockholm, nor do fiction debuts hotter than this European bestseller by muckraking Swedish journalist Larsson. At once a strikingly original thriller and a vivisection of Sweden's dirty not-so-little secrets (as suggested by its original title, Men Who Hate Women), this first of a trilogy introduces a provocatively odd couple: disgraced financial journalist Mikael Blomkvist, freshly sentenced to jail for libeling a shady businessman, and the multipierced and tattooed Lisbeth Salander, a feral but vulnerable superhacker. Hired by octogenarian industrialist Henrik Vanger, who wants to find out what happened to his beloved great-niece before he dies, the duo gradually uncover a festering morass of familial corruption—at the same time, Larsson skillfully bares some of the similar horrors that have left Salander such a marked woman. Larsson died in 2004, shortly after handing in the manuscripts for what will be his legacy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publishers Weekly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a name tent with my name on it for this meeting.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285286857000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279369296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo</name><id>14128338</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281999600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/14128338/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/6/global_16522246.jpeg</photo_url></item>