<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>575 Congress Ave.</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.654754</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207-552-0426 Spencer Albee</phone><name>Empire Dine and Dance</name><city>Portland</city><id>1084834</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.262381</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Get Local &amp;amp; Get Happy!  Permaculture &amp;amp; local food advocates are invited to take over Empire Dine and Dance for a couple of hours on Friday!  &lt;em&gt;Entrance is free with a business card, email address or student ID.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-snc4/373215_271597892946636_1609279835_n.jpg" alt="Frugal Fridays - The Substitutes @Empire Dine &amp;amp; Dance" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We are honored to have been invited (along with the &lt;a href="http://eatmainefoods.ning.com/page/about-the-eat-local-foods"&gt;Eat Local Foods Coalition&lt;/a&gt;) to take the floor this Friday for the new Frugal Fridays Happy Hour at Empire Dine and Dance, to talk about local food, growing your own, resilience-building and more.  This is a great opportunity to get together informally and reach beyond our normal circles to share what permaculture and resilience have to offer our local communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are in and around Portland at the end of the day Friday, grab a friend and join us for a social gathering, enjoy a local beverage and spread the Permaculture &amp;amp; local food fun.&lt;/strong&gt; I'll be making a few comments from the mic, but I would welcome any and all to join in and share their stories either at the mic or just by chatting on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More details about this series from the organizers:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Portland Pirates are building community beyond the ice rink. The Pirates have partnered with Empire Dine &amp;amp; Dance and local rockers, The Substitutes, to create “Frugal Fridays”, which is slated as an “eco-tainment happier hour” and kicks off Friday, August 3 at 5:00pm. The goal of the weekly event series is to raise awareness of local environmental, sustainability, and community initiatives. Frugal Fridays is designed to inspire Maine’s community to connect with key organizations and community leaders in the casual setting of a ‘rock ‘n’ roll happy hour’. The Natural Resources Council of Maine will present the inaugural Frugal Friday. Empire will offer local beer and locally raised menu specials while organizations present their initiatives and The Substitutes serve up a set of “vintage Woodstock-era” rock. Admission to Frugal Fridays requires only a business card or email address, and everyone in attendance qualifies for Portland Pirates ticket giveaway drawings. Frugal Fridays - Get local and get happy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351282466000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345574124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Permaculture &amp; Local Food at Frugal Fridays Happy Hour (Empire Dine &amp; Dance)</name><id>78725922</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345842000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/78725922/</event_url></item>