<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;pre&gt;
Trail: Mt. Pemigewasset Trail
Mountains: Mt. Pemigewasset (2557 ft.)
Rating: Easy/Moderate
Total: 3.6 miles (round trip), approximate time 3-3:30 hrs.
Elevation Gain: 1150 feet
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
Date: Saturday, October 6th, 2012

Location: 11:30am Flume Visitor Center North Parking lot.

We will leave promptly at 11:45 so don't be late!
&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time for our Annual Fall Foliage hiking trip. This is a relatively easy hike and we've done this one before. Last time some people ended up taking the flume gorge tour by mistake instead of hiking. This hike is FREE and starts in the parking lot, so if you're in the visitor's center, and they ask you to pay, you're on the WRONG trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some excerpts from the AMC White Mountain Guide: This trail runs from the Flume Visitor Center parking area to the summit of Mt. Pemigewasset (Indian Head), where excellent views can be obtained with modest effort. Grades and footing are mostly easy. The trail reaches the vertical summit cliffs very abruptly, so care should be exercised. The trail follows the bike path north from the parking lot for 150 yd., turns left on a gravel path and passes under old US 3 in a tunnel, then turns left and crosses a brook on a bridge. It goes over a small rise, then turns sharp right and ascends under both lanes of the Franconia Notch Parkway. It enters the woods at .4 mi. and crosses several small brooks on log bridges, then turns right and then left along a small brook, climbing moderately. At 1.3 mi it squeezes around a large boulder and swings left uphill, climbing a bit more steeply to the ridgecrest, which it follows to the left (south). It passes the junction with the Indian Head trail on the right at 1.7 mi. and reaches the summit ledges at 1.8 mi. At the true summit which is just beyond the first ledges and a bit to the left there is a fine northeast view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;
Driving Directions
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
I-93 to Exit 34A to the Flume Gorge Visitor's Center
Parking lot. Driving time is approx. 2.5-3 hours from 
Boston without stops.
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transportation is the responsibility of the individual&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, our members are good about offering carpools. Please note if you need a ride, what town you are coming from and/or what T stop you can meet at. Same for those that can provide a ride. Since it is quite a bit of a drive we will have a carpool fee of $13 - payable to the driver. This will help towards gas &amp;amp; tolls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stuff to bring: backpack, lunch, water (2 liters), hiking boots, extra layers of clothing if it is cold, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the Flume Gorge North Parking Lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Henry</member_name><member_id>7346155</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349697730000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348610241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Hike - Mount Pemigewasset</name><id>84069692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349537400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/84069692/</event_url></item>