<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10253922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/b/8/a/event_218036202.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Laurie's was packed the last two weekends with live performances after dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join the Red Sox Natives and other invited groups for The Bucket of Blues as they perform for the first time at Laurie's 9:09 on Saturday, March 30 at 9:00pm. They are a Rockin Blues Band that plays a mix of Rock, Soul, Funk and Rockin Blues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the Band go to &lt;a href="http://www.onionlove.net/home.html"&gt;http://www.bucketofblues.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be gathering near both the Penny Lane and Trackside Bars at Laurie's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early as Laurie's will be packed with it's dinner crowd. The live performance will begin at approximately 9:09pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for appetizers, dinner, a cocktail or two or three, socializing and more. If you have a group of people that want a table reservation for dinner please call Laurie's at 781-246-1909 and make a reservation. For information on Laurie's 909 and the menu go to &lt;a href="http://www.lauries.com/"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get there when you can and stay as long as you are able. You are more than welcome to show up for all or just part of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this will be your first time meeting the Red Sox Natives Crew and the other groups check out the photos of those who RSVP Yes so you can find the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay as you order and tip your servers. However, if you sit at a group table a group bill may be provided so please communicate with your server when ordering. Credit Cards will be held by the servers at Laurie's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar is Wakefield's newest restaurant and Bar with live entertainment several nights per week and Tuesday night Trivia with Morgan White Jr. from WBZ Radio. Laurie's is located at the Wakefield Commuter Rail Train Station in Wakefield. The Reading and Haverhill Commuter Rail trains stop at Laurie's. Laurie's is easily accessible within 10 minutes from Routes 128, 93, 28 and 1. Free parking is available in two lots on Tuttle Street, in the Church parking lot if there are no activities there, and on street after 5:30pm. Check out the MBTA or Hop Stop for additional public transit options including the less reliable/frequent 136 and 137 bus lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information at http://&lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask Bob or the bartenders for the Wakefield, Red Sox and other groups in the bar area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364745712000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364257324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bucket of Blues First Time Performance at Lauries 909 Steakhouse &amp; Raw Bar</name><id>111049712</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364691600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/111049712/</event_url></item>