<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Elm St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.990097</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>abi Innovation Hub</name><city>Manchester</city><id>10651362</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, everyone! It has been quite some time since this group has been active. Let's ring in the New Year in WordPress right, and start meeting again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before we get into the details of the agenda, note that the new organizers of the meeting (Amanda and Jonathan) would like to &lt;strong&gt;expand&lt;/strong&gt; the audience for this group to include not just WordPress "&lt;strong&gt;developers&lt;/strong&gt;" (people who know how to customize WordPress with code), but also regular ol' WordPress &lt;strong&gt;users&lt;/strong&gt; (people who mostly configure Wordpress, but generally do not code). We also want to welcome folks will ALL levels of WordPress experience: experts, rank beginners, and anyone in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the proposed agenda...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome and Introductions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll ask everyone to introduce themselves: where do you hail from, what do you do in life, how do you use WordPress (or how would you LIKE to use it) and, well, anything else you want to share about yourself in about 30 seconds or less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reset and Re-launch Discussion:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the main topic of the night: How we want to run the group going forward: What should be the GOALS of the group and what are we interested in meeting ABOUT? Solution sharing? Career networking? Just plain socializing? All of the above? We also need to find out who might want to contribute topics to the agenda, and figure out how often and when we want to meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Favorite Themes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just to get the techno juices flowing a bit...do you have a particular theme or two that you have had good luck using? Or, perhaps you have created your own theme and want to show off your wares. We'll have a computer with Internet access and a large screen TV where you can do a brief demo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shout-Out Time:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is your company looking to hire some WordPress talent? Do have information you'd like to share about an upcoming event? Is there a great new book we should know about? Or...anything else on your mind concerning the World of WordPress? Now will be the time to shout it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hang-Out Time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll use whatever time is leftover to network and just get to know one another a bit better. Bring your business cards! Also, if you like, BYOR, where "R" is for "Refreshments". The abi Innovation Hub has said we can bring whatever food/drink we like, as long as we: 1) CLEAN UP after ourselves, and 2) we RECYCLE anything we bring into the facility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it folks. Let's have a great turnout for the first meeting of 2013 -- and set the stage for an active year going forward! If you have any suggestions/comments, please share!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>278258</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan May</member_name><member_id>41095902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359684720000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WordPressDevNH</urlname><id>1488811</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Manchester, NH WordPress Developers and Users</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354916371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reset and Re-launch this Meetup!</name><id>94504002</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359676800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WordPressDevNH/events/94504002/</event_url></item>