<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello and happy 4th of July!&lt;br /&gt;I want to try and send you this link. This is the world music calendar compiled and Published by Martin Pillsbury, Email:   RhythmNet@aol.com, &lt;br /&gt;MAIL:    WORLD RHYTHM&lt;br /&gt;             PO BOX 120502 &lt;br /&gt;             Boston, MA 02112-0502&lt;br /&gt;Martin is very knowlagable and does an amazing job with his calendar. You can subscribe to it or just see it on line at the web-address below.&lt;br /&gt; He is also an outstanding world-music DJ if you ever need one for a party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://campaign.constantcontact.com/render?v=0013dcFqZEsrWm382-8bq6VaRyGzOr_Tql7F7zN9A3Vd33TkFIGk5THX5vtwR9Y-i5MowNkr5YvwdTU54TKkkp51uvXhFQrTBGlk9EOc5RS2q7MKkU4TDowOQ%3D%3D" target="_blank"&gt;WORD RHYTHM CALENDAR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The featured artist this month is Sarazino and I am setting -up a meet-up to go see him this Thrusday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THUR, July 8, 7:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;SARAZINO (Reggae/Latin) @ 7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Johnny D's&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;17 Holland St.&lt;br /&gt;Davis Square, Somerville&lt;br /&gt;617-776-2004&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope that you can make it and to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jacques&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sarazino is the brainchild of Lamine Fellah, a musician, songwriter and producer whose nomadic life is reflected in the multicultural influences in his songs. Fellah is a true child of a globalized world and Sarazino's music draws on reggae, Latin and African grooves, Arabic music and catchy, international pop to create an upbeat celebration of the diverse world we all share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fellah formed the original incarnation of Sarazino in Montréal in 1995, and the project's first album was released in 1997. While all of the songs on Et Puis Voila were in French, the music fused African, Algerian and French influences. The album was well received, but it was not a huge commercial success, and Fellah decided to focus on traveling and exploring the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On a trip to Ecuador in 1996, Fellah fell in love with Latin America and Latin music. He decided to move to Quito, where he now has an active music production business. In 2003, the second Sarazino album, Mundo Babilón, was released by Ecuadorian label MTM, and the Latin American influence on the project's music was already apparent. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On Sarazino's newest album Ya Foy! (which means &amp;quot;no problem&amp;quot; in the Dioula language of West Africa), Sarazino presents a musical melting pot of roots reggae and Latin grooves with Arabic and West African flavors spicing up the mix. Many songs feature the inspired vocals of Revelino Aguidissou, a native of Benin, Africa, who also ended up settling in the Andean metropolis of Quito. Ecuadorian guitarist Pablo Estrella adds tasty riffs, backing up a selection of guest artists ranging from reggae legend Toots Hibbert of Toots and the Maytals to Latin toaster Blanquito Man from the ska-rock band King Chango. The result of this musical mélange is a savory stew of catchy, accessible songs that offer a soundtrack for a true world party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarazino is on their first US national tour, and their only Boston area appearance will be at Johnny D's on July 8. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279159985000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278286882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SARAZINO (Reggae/Latin)</name><id>14001956</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278631800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/14001956/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/7/global_16188343.jpeg</photo_url></item>