<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;"But Thanksgiving is more than eating, Chuck. You heard what Linus was saying out there. Those early Pilgrims were thankful for what had happened to them, and we should be thankful, too. We should just be thankful for being together. I think that's what they mean by 'Thanksgiving,' Charlie Brown."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;-Marcie,&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;A Charlie Brown Thanksgiving&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that time of year approaching where we all come together to recreate the bonds of family and community (and try not to kill each other), today we will use the play of cooperative games to strengthen our little group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooperative games are rare, but do something important. &amp;nbsp;Everyone works together, finds ways to communicate without manipulation and generally gets to know each other in order to use everyone's talents. &amp;nbsp;Unlike most board and card games, there are no individual winners or losers. &amp;nbsp;The group plays against the "game" and we either succeed as a group or fail as a group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saving the world against an epic disease&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excavating the lost treasure from a hostile island&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working together to keep a ship from sinking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solving picture and word problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what do you say about putting aside the Anomia competitiveness and Snatch-It&amp;nbsp;animosity and working towards a common goal?&amp;nbsp;What better way to give thanks, then to appreciate what each of us brings to the table. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll have some cooperative games ready to go, but if you have one please bring it as they are rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, hope to see you. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;. Anyone can sign up, but I would please ask that you&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;allow new or previously inactive members get a slot if they are on the waiting list since there is limited seating. &amp;nbsp;Thanks.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;See this&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food theme:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme for this event will be "your speciality or abundance". Please bring a food item that is a reflection of what you enjoy the most or something of which you have a lot of to share. &amp;nbsp;I will try to have also generic, healthy snacks on hand for all diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the location:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 This event will be hosted at a private residence,&amp;nbsp;conveniently&amp;nbsp;located at the intersections of Route 1 and Route 95. &amp;nbsp;If you need directions, just ask. &amp;nbsp;This is a housing complex, so please do NOT park in any numbered spaces. &amp;nbsp;There are no animals on the premises and the property should be child friendly. &amp;nbsp;Look for Unit 901 since Meetup doesn't display addresses correctly! :-(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unit 901</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321847524000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319422467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: A Community of Gamers</name><id>38454242</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321729200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/38454242/</event_url></item>