<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Manchester Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03038</zip><lat>42.896767</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pinkerton Tavern</name><city>Derry</city><id>852939</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.330231</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope everyone had a fantastic summer and I apologize for not posting a meetup sooner, but mine has been pretty jam packed and crazy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, now that the air is cooling and the leaves are turning, let's get back to reading.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've decided to include two books for this particular meetup, which is something I usually don't do. However, one of our members, Jaimee, sent a recommendation which sounds really interesting, plus I have a book that looks like it could be very good as well. In addition, there's about seven weeks between now and Oct 27 so it is possible to read both in that time, if you so desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first is Jaimee's recommendation which is called Packing for Mars by Mary Roach. It's a very witty and unique look at what it takes to get a crew into orbit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second book is something I saw at Barnes and Noble a week ago which looked really good. It's called The Art of Racing in the Rain by Garth Stein. It's a book about all the absurdities and joys of life....from the perspective of a dog.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, there is no requirement to finish both books for the meeting, hence my title. If one grabs your interest more than the other, read it. If both look good and you have the time, then read both.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given that we'll have two books to discuss, I'm opting for a quieter venue, which is also a place we're familiar with as a group. We'll meet at the Pinkerton Tavern in Derry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12 person cap will apply as usual although I may give some leeway for newer members since we haven't had a meeting in while. So, RSVP quickly and I hope to see a lot of you in Oct.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take care,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason Lambert</member_name><member_id>3148632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1288283434000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club</urlname><id>1332912</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>The Southern NH Books and Brew Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284597715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Two books. Take your pick or read both.</name><id>14786407</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288220400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club/events/14786407/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/a/global_6582442.jpeg</photo_url></item>