<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>545 Hooksett Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>43.014860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 628-6899</phone><name>La Carreta</name><city>Manchester</city><id>943759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.451859</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everybody,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the delay in posting this, but getting engaged tends to be a little distracting. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We decided to take August off since it's a prime summer vacation month, but we'll be back for September. So here's the post for the Sept Meetup. We'll be reading The Shadow of the Wind by&amp;nbsp; Carlos Ruiz Zafon. I've only just started it, but it's already intriguing me. Imagine a place where books are preserved and kept safe especially after people have stopped loving them. Now imagine that you are allowed to take one book for your own, but the condition is this: you must protect that book and preserve it for the rest of your life. However, what do you do when you learn that all the copies of the book you have and all other works by the author are being systematically destroyed? Sounds pretty intriguing, doesn't it? Well that's the book we're reading for Sept.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at La Carreta in Manchester in their original location up on Route 3 instead of the new location on South Willow Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll make it a 14 person cap this time so RSVP as soon as you can. And if you need to cancel please update your RSVP asap so another person can attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy your summer and see you in September.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason Lambert</member_name><member_id>3148632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1316662703000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club</urlname><id>1332912</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>The Southern NH Books and Brew Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313165019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discuss The Shadow of the Wind</name><id>29249251</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316646000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club/events/29249251/</event_url></item>