<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374275</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Harvard Extension School</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>465494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121765</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>700.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Note: This is not a MeetUp Event, just a reminder that the Harvard Extension School is now registering students for the spring semester. It is a wonderful program.&lt;br /&gt;S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get in the game!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.extension.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Extension School&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are numerous paths to personal enrichment and professional development at Harvard Extension School. Their open-enrollment courses and academic programs offer nontraditional students a challenging academic experience at tuition rates that rank among the lowest in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Courses and Programs&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Explore a subject that interests you. Build skills to advance your career. Enroll in a degree or certificate program. With 620 courses, the Extension School offers a range of possibility. Vital subject areas such as environmental management, information technology, and biotechnology. Professional graduate certificate and degree programs. Career and study skills workshops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Faculty&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you study biology or music, you learn from experts; Harvard professors offering their Harvard College courses at the Extension School; leading faculty from local universities; community and business leaders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Students and Alumni&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The population of nearly 13,000 students is diverse. All students share a common goal to challenge themselves and satisfy their intellectual curiosity. Alumni have gone on to attend prestigious graduate programs and become leaders in fields such as business, medicine, education, and law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Students range in age from early teens to 80s; average age is 33. &lt;br /&gt;- They come from 118 countries and 46 US states. &lt;br /&gt;- Seventy-five percent have bachelor's degrees; 25 percent have graduate degrees.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201183506000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199313782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Continuing Education at Harvard </name><id>7015796</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201010400000</time><rsvp_limit>340</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/7015796/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/8/global_2898824.jpeg</photo_url></item>