<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01247</zip><lat>53.959106</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Your home or work</name><city>Your city</city><id>1192498</id><country>us</country><lon>-1.079194</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>95.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Join this 7 week teleclass series to release self-sabotaging patterns and access your inherent power.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each Chakra stores the collection of our core beliefs, emotions and experiences in correlation to seven fundamental themes in our life: survival, creativity, power, love, self-expression, wisdom, and divine connection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will focus on one chakra a week:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Clear negative accumulations and blockages. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Activate the positive attributes and potentialities of each vital energy center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Through the guided meditations and exercises you will learn to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Feel Safe in the World&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Release Pain, Shame, Guilt, Anger and Fear&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Expand your Ability to Experience Pleasure&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Access your Core Power &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Take Effective Action in the World&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Open your Heart to Love &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Express your Truth&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Trust your Inner Guidance and Wisdom&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Tap into Abundance Consciousness&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Experience Oneness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During &lt;b&gt;each teleclass&lt;/b&gt; in the series you will be presented with &lt;b&gt;step-by-step guidance on fundamental techniques&lt;/b&gt;. Each call will include &lt;b&gt;new instruction&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;guided meditations&lt;/b&gt;, plus time to &lt;b&gt;have your questions answered.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The calls will be &lt;b&gt;recorded&lt;/b&gt; and available for &lt;b&gt;free download&lt;/b&gt;. It will be particularly useful to use the &lt;b&gt;guided meditations for your home practice&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional &lt;b&gt;support between calls&lt;/b&gt;, you are encouraged to make use of the &lt;b&gt;community board&lt;/b&gt; to ask questions that arise, and share your experience with others on the path. This will help build a sense of community as well as offer inspiration and motivation to keep going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dates:   Wednesdays, May 5, 12, 19, 26, June 2, 9, 16 &lt;br /&gt;Time:   7-8pm&lt;br /&gt;Location:   The privacy and comfort of your own home&lt;br /&gt;Investment: $95 early registration discount by May 12, $125 thereafter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Tuition includes seven classes, free downloads of instruction, guided meditation and Q&amp;amp;A, and online support via message board and email. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*You do not have to be present on the calls to receive the downloads and participate fully in the course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*You may register at any time during the series, and have access to download any calls you have missed.&lt;/b&gt; (Only register once for the first week you plan to attend)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to email me directly (organizer) or call me at 415-244-1652 if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Service,&lt;br /&gt;Brynn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Tantra Educator and Intimacy Coach. She has been studying and practicing in the fields of Somatics and Consciousness since 1988. Brynn guides individuals and couples in clearing emotional blocks, and awakening and harnessing their Vital Energy to experience the fullest range of Pleasure in their sexuality, Intimacy in their relationships, and Purpose and Passion in their lives. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The conference call number will be emailed to confirmed registrants</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274757259000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267564731000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantric Empowerment 7 Week Teleclass Series</name><id>vrdmnynhbhb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273100400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/12760668/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/3/global_10606195.jpeg</photo_url></item>