<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Activity Description / Brunch price and 2 hour Cruise $35.00  &amp;quot;Its A Steal&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy brunch in a new unique way. Experience the savory flavors provided by The Greek Olive Restaurant while taking in the delightful views of New Haven Harbor. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Our brunch Includes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coffee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Juice&lt;br /&gt;Bagels&lt;br /&gt;Muffins&lt;br /&gt;Danish&lt;br /&gt;Croissants&lt;br /&gt;Egg Sandwiches&lt;br /&gt;Burritos&lt;br /&gt;Fruit&lt;br /&gt;Quiche &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the sites you'll see are: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Historical Fort Nathan Hale - this fort played a role in the American Revolution, the War of 1812 and the Civil War, and was the first site in New Haven to be recognized as a Landmark and Historic site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Picturesque Lighthouse Point - the lighthouse is also known as the Five Mile Point Light as it sits on a point of land five miles from the center of New Haven. &lt;br /&gt;An incredible view of Long Island Sound - the Sound features a diversity of plant and animal life and was designated a National Estuary in 1987. &lt;br /&gt;Work up your appetite by helping raise sail or just sit back and relax while you enjoy your coffee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll come for the food, you'll stay for the experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What Is Not Included? &lt;br /&gt;Alcohol is not served on board. If you enjoy a Mimosa or Bloody Mary with your brunch, you are more than welcome to bring your own. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Gratuity is not included in the price of your sail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: &lt;br /&gt;Long Wharf Pier (New Haven, CT) &lt;br /&gt;(Exact meeting location details will be provided immediately upon purchase of tickets.) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Lets get together and bring our own Mimosa for the Cruise :-) Go on line to purchase tickets &lt;a href="http://www.zerve.com/SchoonerInc" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.zerve.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283377353000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281622725000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Brunch " Harbor Cruise"</name><id>14401171</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283094000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/14401171/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/d/global_2165245.jpeg</photo_url></item>