<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come join us for our first annual Yule Celebration to be held this year in Warren Mass!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start the celebration with the Battle of the Oak and Holly King&lt;br /&gt;as we go from the Dark half of the year into the Light half of the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be an informative Yule discussion on where, and how our Christmas customs originated from earlier pagan ones, what the Sabbat is all about, and ways to celebrate Yule in style!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a pot luck feast with homemade lasanga, garden salad, and garlic bread, and more, &lt;br /&gt;along with yummy desserts!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be doing &amp;quot;pagan&amp;quot; Yankee swap, after the feast,  along with the carving or wishes in a traditional yule log that will be burned on Yule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pot luck sign up will be put up on the list before the meet up-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a meet-up that will prove to be tons of fun, and a good way to bring in the light&lt;br /&gt;to celebrate the Winter Solstice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, if you are on the Pagan Learning Center Meet up group also, please rsvp on one site only for an accurate count of people :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;House phone: 413-436-0191&lt;br /&gt;cell phone; 978-852-1478&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions on mapquest.com are accurate. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The house is a big white house, black roof with a red door and a &amp;quot;for sale&amp;quot; sign in the front of the house.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions to come :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232207849000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214115739000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yule Celebration</name><id>8189483</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228593600000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/8189483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/f/global_3694063.jpeg</photo_url></item>