<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.384979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Waltham</name><city>Waltham</city><id>561766</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.216743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dinner Speaker Series features Judith Kravitz - Transformational Breathing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date : 19 May 2009 (Tuesday)       From : 05:30   To : 09:30 &lt;br /&gt;Category : General &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Description : &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our speaker this month will be Judith Kravitz - Transformational Breathing, more information to follow. Please check out her website: www.transformationalbreathing.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gourmet Raw Potluck 6 - 7pm, bring a dish to share for eight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $10.00 plus food or $20 without&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call Betsy Bragg if you have any questions: 781-899-6664 or cell 617-835-2913 or email at address below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;U Mass Waltham Center and the Waltham Fields Community Farm 240 Beaver Street, Waltham, MA 02452 Sign out front says &amp;quot;Waltham Fields Community Farm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge/Harvard Square: Take the 73 Bus to the final stop at Waverly Oaks Square in Belmont. From Waverly Oaks you can make a connection to the 554 Bus, which goes to Waltham, and runs directly past the farm. The bus stop is located on Trapelo Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternately you can take the 70 Bus from Central Square, Cambridge toward Waltham. Ask to get off at the intersection of Routes 20 and 60. Follow Route 60 away from Main Street, all the way until you get to Beaver Street. Take a left onto Beaver Street; the farm and building will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Waltham Center: Take the 554 Bus which runs directly past the farm on Beaver Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Commuter Rail: Take the Fitchburg line to Waltham Center and follow directions above. The Fitchburg line also stops at Waverly Square where you can catch the 554 Bus to the farm (not all trains stop at Waverly though so check schedule)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge: Take Mount Auburn Street past the cemetery and bear right onto Belmont Street (this is just past the Star Market). Travel on Belmont Street (this becomes Trapelo Road) to the intersection with Route 60, about 3 miles. Turn left onto Route 60. Follow Arlington/Belmont directions below. Alternately take Route 2 to Route 60 and follow Arlington/Belmont directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Arlington or Belmont: Take Route 60 West to Beaver Street. Take a right onto Beaver Street. The UMass Field Station is about 100 yards up on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Waltham or Watertown: Take Route 60 East from Main Street Waltham (Route 20). Beaver Street will be the first traffic light, turn left onto Beaver Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128: Take the Trapelo Road exit (one exit south of Route 2) east toward Belmont. Route 60 is about 3 to 4 miles down the road. Turn right onto Route 60, then follow Arlington/Belmont directions above. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email : betsy@rawnenglandcommunity.com &lt;br /&gt;More info : &lt;a href="http://www.transformationalbreathing.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.transforma...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243213662000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240641586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Potluck &amp; Lecture - Judith Kravitz</name><id>10263620</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242768600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/10263620/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/5/e/global_8470190.jpeg</photo_url></item>