<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>'We're going to need a bigger boat'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When a leviathan of a Great White begins making snacks out of the good people of Amity Island, it's up to police Chief Brody, the grizzled fisherman Quint, and Richard Dreyfuss to embark on one of the greatest fish stories ever told. The physical scars these men boast and brandish in the cabin of the Orca seem like paper cuts when compared to the carnage inflicted by the teeth of their intended prey. Will these men have what it takes to reel in the horror that awaits them beneath the waves? One thing is for certain; they're going to need a bigger boat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Very few films have the ability to instill deep rooted phobias in those who sit down to watch them. Steven Spielberg's 1975 classic terrified moviegoers to a point that almost crippled the shoreline tourism trade at the time of its release. Thirty-five years later, the thought of a wide-open and sharp-toothed abyss lurking just beneath the surface is still very present in the minds of any swimmer whose feet leave the safety of the sea-floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Steven Spielberg w/ Roy Scheider, Richard Dreyfuss, Robert Shaw 2h4m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday Classics at the Coolidge Sell Out.  Please purchase your ticket when you RSVP:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes" target="_blank"&gt;Jaws Tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will gather before the film across the street at Panera Bread starting at 6:00 to have a little seafood, make beach plans, and talk about where we were when first we watched Scheider, Dreyfuss, and the incredible performance by Robert Shaw.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You follow?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283133219000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JAWS: 35th Anniversary Screening </name><id>14585549</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284418800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14585549/</event_url></item>