<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Although Smarty is known as a &amp;quot;Template Engine&amp;quot;, it would be more accurately described as a &amp;quot;Template/Presentation Framework.&amp;quot; That is, it provides the programmer and template designer with a wealth of tools to automate tasks commonly dealt with at the presentation layer of an application. I stress the word Framework because Smarty is not a simple tag-replacing template engine. Although it can be used for such a simple purpose, its focus is on quick and painless development and deployment of your application, while maintaining high-performance, scalability, security and future growth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join BostonPHP and Michael Bourque as he takes you through the Smarty Framework. This will be an interactive session where Michael will write code and demonstrate throughout the session. You will leave with the tools and information to apply Smarty to your next project:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is Smarty? Learn why it is good to separate the presentation code from the business logic of your application&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Smarty syntax and functions&lt;br /&gt;    * Best practices and demos&lt;br /&gt;    * How to use a terminology property file to make it easier to control application terminology and software strings outside of your code.&lt;br /&gt;    * Learn how to offer multiple language support and switching in your application&lt;br /&gt;    * Plenty of time for your questions and answers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See why so many others love using Smarty in their projects. You will too and I will show you how. Invite your PHP friends, your CSS/Design team - you don't want to miss this one.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244069602000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235581815000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Get Smart - Use Smarty!</name><id>9821182</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241649000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/9821182/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/1/global_7457329.jpeg</photo_url></item>