<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>route 165</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02822</zip><lat>41.587738</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Arcadia Management Area</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1305681</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.709100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Before we move on to Big River,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;we’ll return to the familiar setting we know as Arcadia Wildlife Management Area and once again stake our claim to the gems we know as the Shelter and Breakheart Trails. A ride featuring a couple of paths that when combined, amount to what could arguably be considered the Crown Jewel of Arcadian Cross-Country MTB.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Ridden clock-wise, we'll begin with a short, &lt;em&gt;moderately&lt;/em&gt; technical introduction known as the Shelter Trail. For 10 to 15 minutes, we'll roll over root, rock and road (abandoned road... fire road that is) before we spend the next 5 minutes catching our breath and "chatting-it-up" on our way to the Breakheart Trail's western most trailhead. Turning right, we'll climb... but not for long. For the next hour plus, we'll spend our time climbing and descending, hiking and biking over roller coaster trails, speeding (figuratively speaking of course) thru pine and hard wood forest, around bermed turns and smooth single track as we make our way back to our cars via the northern section of the Shelter Trail... hopefully before we fall, and/or night falls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;In the woods, you can expect to experience a combination of fire roads and single-track, passing through forests and fields, over varied terrain, from smooth to rough, over rocks and roots, gravel and dirt which will require a bit of technical skill. But no worries, because we &lt;br /&gt;

 will be following The Unwritten Primary Rules of Mountain Biking: 1. We ride as a group; 2. We hike what we cannot ride; and 3. We wait at all major trailheads.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Our pace will be moderate and accommodating (no speedsters here), but you should know that the ride is filled with a number of short steep up and downs, and I ask that you believe yourself to be an intermediately skilled rider, or a fit beginner/intermediate rider willing to be challenged by the terrain. I will be riding a rigid single-speed (no shocks) w/ flat pedals, so my pace will not be blazing, nor will I be riding up every climb (I blame the single-speed); that my friends is for another time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : small"&gt;PS: Please take note of the time change. Plan to meet at 5:15 so that we can begin our ride close to 5:30; this will hopefully keep us from riding out in the dark.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We'll meet at the Frosty Hollow Pond parking area (a 3/4 mile drive up Frosty Hollow Rd from the intersection of Rt 165).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;From the intersection of Rt 3 and Rt 165, follow Rt 165 east for approximately 2.75 miles. Turn right into Frosty Hollow Rd &lt;em&gt;(dirt road @ the white church)&lt;/em&gt; and continue for .75 miles, turning right into a small parking area just after the small fishing pond.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Google Maps: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=41.587755,+-71.709374&amp;amp;daddr=41.587755,+-71.709374&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=41.587748,-71.709352&amp;amp;spn=0.004646,0.009162&amp;amp;sll=41.587716,-71.700554&amp;amp;sspn=0.148678,0.293198&amp;amp;geocode=FSuUegIdQs25-w%3BFSuUegIdQs25-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=17"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=@41.576874,-71.702774"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Coordinates: 41.587755, -71.709374&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Frosty Hollow Pond parking area (3/4 of a mile North of Rt 165 &amp; the white church); call if you can't find us. Cell: 860-460-1500</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>11024921</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346286303000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346175893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike Arcadia: Because I missed you last week</name><id>79751652</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346274900000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/79751652/</event_url></item>