<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>297-2053</phone><name>Trinity College Life Sciences Center Auditorium</name><city>Hartford</city><id>440540</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join international film buffs as well as Spanish language speakers and learners at Trinity College's free weekly showings of Iberian and Latin American films.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's film is THE YEAR MY PARENTS WENT ON VACATION, directed by Cao Hamburger (Brazil, 2006)&lt;br /&gt;In 1970, near the World Cup, Daniel Stern and his wife Miriam leaves Belo Horizonte in a hurry and scared with their ten years old son Mauro in their Volkswagen. While traveling to São Paulo, the couple explains Mauro that they will travel on vacation and will leave Mauro with his grandfather Mótel. Daniel promises to return before the first game of the Brazilian National Soccer Team in the Cup. The boy is left in Bom Retiro, a Jewish and Italian neighborhood, and waits for Mótel in front of his apartment. When the next door neighbor Shlomo arrives, he tells the boy that Mótel had just had a heart attack and died. Alone and without knowing where his parents are, the boy is lodged by Shlomo and the Jewish community. Through the young neighbor Hanna, Mauro makes new friends, cheers for the Brazilian team and sees the movement of the police and militaries on the streets while waiting for his parents. &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0857355/plotsummary" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Manuella Meyer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Films start at 7:00 in the Life Sciences Building. &lt;br /&gt;For directions to Trinity, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/AboutTrinity/VisitingTrinity/DirectionsToTrinity.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Or call (860) 297-2053.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/NR/rdonlyres/92062DC6-138A-430E-9ADA-5A209B506787/0/campusmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can come earlier than 6:45, please join me for supper in the Cave cafeteria (basement of Mather Hall, no id required). Prices are reasonable and the food is quite good. I usually get there by 5:15.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll display a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret Vincent</member_name><member_id>1777042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241048858000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233946120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film: The Year My Parents Went on Vacation</name><id>9688335</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240441200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/9688335/</event_url></item>