<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>/person ($5 if WRNEC mem)</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Special RSVP instructions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To RSVP to this event, you must use &lt;b&gt;BOTH&lt;/b&gt; the Meetup system &lt;b&gt;AND&lt;/b&gt; prepay for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prepaid Reservations only:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;New policy due to popularity of Victoras Kulvinskas, fire law limit of 150 people and 30% no shows at the last 3 events. Mail check payable to &amp;quot;Waltham Raw New England Community&amp;quot; for $30 ($25 for annual dues March 2008-February 2009 and $5 for the speaker) or if you want to remain a non-member, send $10 ($5 entry fee and $5 for the speaker).  Mail checks to Joseph Gerber, 21 Manning St. Needham, MA 02494.  When we have 150 reservatons, we will send out a newsletter stating that we are sold out and no more reservatons will be accepted.  Be sure your postal address, phone number and email address are on the check.  If you have any questions,  call Betsy Bragg at 781-899-6664 or email her at betsy@rawnewenglandcommunity.com. If there are seats available at the time of the event, the cost will be $5 for members and $15 for non-members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you only use the Meetup RSVP system, then you won't be registered. If you only contact Betsy and don't use Meetup, your Meetup member stats and our group's Meetup stats won't be correct.&lt;/b&gt; Thank you for understanding. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Victoras Kulvinskas Talk at Waltham UMass Center&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raw Foods is Popular and Well-Researched Thanks to pioneers in Healing and Raw food Research Like Viktoras&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When:&lt;/b&gt;  Tuesday, March 25, 6-9 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; UMass Waltham, 240 Beaver St, Waltham&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who:&lt;/b&gt;  Victoras Kulvinskas, now living in Costa Rica, is the father of the modern day living foods diet that is gaining scientific support in the medical community.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raw Luck 6-7 PM &lt;br /&gt;Speaker 7:00 PM to 9:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We see in Victoras one of the most eminent geniuses in the history of the wellness community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Viktoras has been a practitioner in the Holistic field for over 35 years and has assisted tens of thousands through his lifestyle consultation services. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Co-founder with Ann Wigmore of the Hippocrates Health Institute - presently rated as the top health resort by the International Spa Industry. Spent seven years in developing the HHI Live Food program - which has been adopted worldwide, affecting millions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Author of the best-seller &lt;i&gt;Survival In the 21st Century&lt;/i&gt; plus six other books, with over 500,000 copies sold. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Co-founder of Dick Gregory's Obesity and Substance Abuse Resort - nutritional and educational director for two years both in Bahamas and Florida. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Lecturer - Internationally for over 20,000 hours in the field of health &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Chef - served gourmet raw life food vegetarian feasts to over half a million &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All those attending are requested to bring a raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based (vegan with no honey) ready- to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people.  Please bring serving utensils labeled with your name on them. Bring a typed or neatly printed recipe to display next to your dish.  For recipe ideas, go to &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawnewengl...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here are some ideas to help you find something raw to bring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. you could bring an organic salad;&lt;br /&gt;2. there is a source for raw recipes listed in the invitation at &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawnewengl...&lt;/a&gt; ;&lt;br /&gt;3. there are plenty of raw recipes available online&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.living-foods.com/recipes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.living-foo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://goneraw.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://goneraw.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawsacramento.net/recipes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawsacrame...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawfoodlife.com/raw_food_recipes.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawfoodlif...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shazzie.com/raw/recipes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.shazzie.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.healthfree.com/raw_food_recipes.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.healthfree...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawganique.com/recipes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawganique...&lt;/a&gt; ; &lt;br /&gt;4. most raw food books have raw recipes; and&lt;br /&gt;5. organic fruit or fruit salad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For other raw food events in New England:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.RawNewEnglandCommunity.com/newsletterarchive.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.RawNewEngl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click on most the most recent Newsletter.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278898780000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201374087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Victoras Kulvinskas Talk at Waltham UMass Center</name><id>7200743</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206482400000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/7200743/</event_url></item>