<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61 Harvard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.272099</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-769-6113</phone><name>Visions By Baker</name><city>Worcester</city><id>415038</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.801903</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A Tour of iPhoto ’09&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So you are looking for a basic digital workflow, to organize your photo libraries, improve your images, and share them with friends and family by publishing them on the web, in a book, or on a card, but can’t justify the cost of Apple® Aperture® or Adobe® Lightroom® just yet? If you own a Mac, then iPhoto just may be the answer for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll take you on a tour of Apple iPhoto ’09 (part of the iLife ’09 suite of products), their affordable consumer level photo management software, that allows you to organize, improve, enjoy, share on the web and in print (i.e., books, cards, etc.). We’ll show you how to: import photos from your camera, organize them into events (into albums and smart albums), edit (i.e., rotate, crop, straighten, enhance, eliminate red-eye, retouch, add effects, and adjust), flag, hide, keyword, and share (i.e., create a slideshow, book, calendar, card).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you own a MacBook or MacBook Pro, please feel free to bring it along with you. This will be a tour of iPhoto ’09 (the latest version of the iLife suite), but we’ll have some breaks that you can feel free to explore what you’ve learned. Bring a notepad and pen to take notes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is a free learning session offered to Photo MeetUp Members - we ask that you please bring your favorite chips, dips, other munchies and beverages to share with the group or give a $ donation to cover costs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This tour is being presented by Steve Stearns, a Worcester Photography MeetUp member, and former Apple Creative (or Trainer), who was trained at Apple headquarters in Cupertino, CA and has taught a multitude of One to One classes and workshops on a wide variety of subjects for Apple customers. He previously taught the Digital Asset Management (DAM) workshop with Scott Erb and Steve Iadarola for the Worcester Photography MeetUp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is limited to the first 15 who RSVP, so please register today. We’ll activate the waiting list feature, just in case any of the first 15 are unable to attend. If you register and find you are unable to attend, please change your RSVP from Yes to No as soon as possible, so others can attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visions By Baker&lt;br /&gt;61 Harvard Street (in the parking lot across from 37 Highland Street)&lt;br /&gt;Worcester, MA 01609&lt;br /&gt;877-901-7468&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 26, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Beginning at 11:00 AM and finishing up at around 1:30 PM (includes 0:15 breaks)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254502940000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251150502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Tour of iPhoto ’09</name><id>11189893</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253977200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11189893/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/6/b/global_10373483.jpeg</photo_url></item>