<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364744</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-1580</phone><name>Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1019999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;When Paul Auster was asked by &lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt; to write a Christmas story for the Op-Ed page, the result, "Auggie Wren's Christmas Story," led to Auster's collaboration on a film adaptation, &lt;em&gt;Smoke&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It begins with a writer's dilemma: he's been asked by &lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt; to write a story that will appear in the paper on Christmas morning. The writer agrees, but he has a problem: How to write an unsentimental Christmas story? He unburdens himself to his friend at his local cigar shop, a colorful character named Auggie Wren. "A Christmas story? Is that all?" Auggie counters. "If you buy me lunch, my friend, I'll tell you the best Christmas story you ever heard. And I guarantee every word of it is true." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

And an unconventional story it is, involving a lost wallet, a blind woman, and a Christmas dinner. Everything gets turned upside down. What's stealing? What's giving? What's a lie? What's the truth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, if any of you would like to bring any literary "gifts" to share with the group, please do.&amp;nbsp; Just let me know and be sure to bring enough copies for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328486164000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322934652000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Auster: Auggie Wren's Christmas Story</name><id>43266102</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324249200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/43266102/</event_url></item>