<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>154 Tedesco Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.485847</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tedesco Country Club</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>701864</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.893494</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Looks like around 150 for the June 14 dance!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Checkout our original website, Northof40Singles.com, where most of our dancers register.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;We had more women then men the last dance and I'm working hard to balance that off. Help me create something special for over 40 singles north of Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With summer approaching we have changed to &amp;quot;Business-Casual&amp;quot; attire. Men must wear collared shirts, no dungarees or shorts. Women...you know what to wear! We will have theme dances soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many dancers are members of local golf, yacht &amp;amp; dance clubs. Please remember to invite your friends, they need to dance, party and socialize with the interactive people of the North Shore, and beyond! You, and they, will make lots of new friends, meet great guys and gals, and maybe find a soulmate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 ADMISSION INCLUDES:&lt;br /&gt;• Group Dance Lesson 7:30-8&lt;br /&gt;• Dancing to 11PM&lt;br /&gt;• Tasty chef-prepared hors d'oeuvres&lt;br /&gt;• Yummy veggie platter&lt;br /&gt;• Dessert for your sweet tooth&lt;br /&gt;• Door prize gift certificates&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dance in the grand ballroom, watch sports on the Grill Room flat-screen TV, or cool off on the romantic patio overlooking the 18-hole golf course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cash bar will have a variety of beer, mixed drinks, wine, soda &amp;amp; bottled water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be polite when someone asks you to dance...be friendly and dance at least once, even if that person isn't your dreamboat...they might be very interesting, funny, or even a future friend. Everyone hates rejection, so lets lighten the heart, lift some spirits and leave our inhibitions at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may pay cash at the door or send a check for $20 per person to:&lt;br /&gt;North of 40 Singles, 20 Tidd Street, Swampscott, MA 01907.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mention your name at the door and my sister Nancy will check it off the list.&lt;br /&gt;Come early so you don't miss out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Check out my original website Northof40Singles.com where most of the dancers respond too.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you are interested in: Theme Dances, Golf Outings, Night Cruises, Singles Vacations, Weekend Trips, Fashion Shows, 40 Diners (20 men/20 women), Other Singles Events?&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be greeting you at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Richard P.</member_name><member_id>9495023</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248582782000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>dancers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Over-40-Singles</urlname><id>1455951</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North of 40 Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243223379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North of 40 Singles </name><id>10485494</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245022200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Over-40-Singles/events/10485494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/7/f/global_8623407.jpeg</photo_url></item>