<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Never released in the US, a Hartford Premiere! Jean-Paul Belmondo stars in&lt;br /&gt;this 1961 Nouvelle vague film directed by Jean-Pierre Melville with director of photography Henri Cecae (also of Les 400 coups)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(France, 1961) Written and directed by Jean-Pierre Melville, based on the novel by Béatrix Beck. Director of photography, Henri Decaë. Cast: Emmanuelle Riva, Jean-Paul Belmondo, Irene Tunc, Nicole Mirel. Every so often moviegoers get the chance to see a great film by a major director that was never released in the States. The cinematic surprise of this season is the new release of a 1961 film starring Jean-Paul Belmondo (Breathless) and Emmanuelle Riva (Hiroshima Mon Amour), complete with newly translated subtitles. Director Jean-Pierre Melville made Léon Morin Prêtre in between Bob Le Flambeur and Army of Shadows, and it is an evocative story of a woman who is a Jewish communist in Nazi-occupied France, based on the novel by Béatrix Beck. Her attempts to find solace with a (gorgeous) man who happens to be a local priest is a masterpiece that can now be added to the glories of the French New Wave. &amp;quot;...a fascinating, unexpected movie that fans of French film in general, and Melville in particular, will not want to miss!&amp;quot; - Kenneth Turan, Los Angeles Times. 117 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket prices are $8;  $7 for students, educators,seniors, and French group members&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265744405000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French</urlname><id>459167</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Groupe de French</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263409645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French film "Leon Morin, Pretre" at Cinestudio</name><id>12310016</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265571000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French/events/12310016/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/7/global_1365207.jpeg</photo_url></item>