<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810067275/info" target="_blank"&gt;The Book of Eli&lt;/a&gt; promises to be a thrill ride meets religiouso kind of like DaVinci Code, but darker. And futuristic. Hell, Denzel Washington. Need I say more?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:10, so let's meet at 6:40 right inside the theater ticket lobby doors. Then I'll buy us all cheap tickets ($8 for FMM members and their guests) and we can go buy cheap snacks ($3 for small popcorn and $3 for small soda) and we can hang out and enjoy our movie. Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, let's head to Uno's and chat it up, eat, drink and be merry. (I'm a bit tired of Friday's, so trying to change it up a bit.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the not-too-distant future, some 30 years after the final war, a solitary man walks across the wasteland that was once America. Empty cities, broken highways, seared earth--all around him, the marks of catastrophic destruction. There is no civilization here, no law. The roads belong to gangs that would murder a man for his shoes, an ounce of water... or for nothing at all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But they're no match for this traveler.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A warrior not by choice but necessity, Eli seeks only peace but, if challenged, will cut his attackers down before they realize their fatal mistake. It's not his life he guards so fiercely but his hope for the future; a hope he has carried and protected for 30 years and is determined to realize. Driven by this commitment and guided by his belief in something greater than himself, Eli does what he must to survive--and continue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only one other man in this ruined world understands the power Eli holds, and is determined to make it his own: Carnegie, the self-appointed despot of a makeshift town of thieves and gunmen. Meanwhile, Carnegie's adopted daughter Solara is fascinated by Eli for another reason: the glimpse he offers of what may exist beyond her stepfather's domain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But neither will find it easy to deter him. Nothing--and no one--can stand in his way. Eli must keep moving to fulfill his destiny and bring help to a ravaged humanity.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Book of Eli this Wednesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265413062000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264963159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book of Eli</name><id>12474854</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265239800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12474854/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>