<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 State St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076996</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-9715</phone><name>The Rosa Restaurant</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>260717</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.754150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/e/f/event_23988111.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Our June book club pick is &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Never Let me Go&lt;/span&gt; by Kazuo Ishiguro.&amp;nbsp; Here is a brief synopsis of &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Never Let Me Go&lt;/span&gt; from Amazon.com :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All children should believe they are special. But the students of Hailsham, an elite school in the English countryside, are so special that visitors shun them, and only by rumor and the occasional fleeting remark by a teacher do they discover their unconventional origins and strange destiny. Kazuo Ishiguro's sixth novel, Never Let Me Go, is a masterpiece of indirection. Like the students of Hailsham, readers are "told but not told" what is going on and should be allowed to discover the secrets of Hailsham and the truth about these children on their own. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offsetting the bizarreness of these revelations is the placid, measured voice of the narrator, Kathy H., a 31-year-old Hailsham alumna who, at the close of the 1990s, is consciously ending one phase of her life and beginning another. She is in a reflective mood, and recounts not only her childhood memories, but her quest in adulthood to find out more about Hailsham and the idealistic women who ran it. Although often poignant, Kathy's matter-of-fact narration blunts the sharper emotional effects you might expect in a novel that deals with illness, self-sacrifice, and the severe restriction of personal freedoms. As in Ishiguro's best-known work, &lt;a&gt;The Remains of the Day&lt;/a&gt;, only after closing the book do you absorb the magnitude of what his characters endure.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308350994000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299638953000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club June Meetup - Never Let Me Go</name><id>mbhqqypjbsb</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308092400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/17415285/</event_url></item>