<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61 Exeter St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02216</zip><lat>42.349170</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Solas in Lennox Hotel</name><city>Boston</city><id>503355</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Solas is in the Lennox Hotel. &lt;br /&gt;The Barflies will be playing on the Second floor of the Solas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lenoxhotel.com/boston-restaurants.html" target="_blank"&gt;Solas/Lennox Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They list on the &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/mikehermans" target="_blank"&gt;Mike's Myspace&lt;/a&gt; Website that they start about 8pm, But when I called there I was told they start playing at 9pm. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The barflies are typically a duo featuring Mike Hermans on Guitar, George Chinaglia on Bass. &lt;br /&gt;They do have a female vocalist sit in for some portion of the songs when they play too. &lt;br /&gt;They play primarily top 40 rock and blues tunes from artists like U2, Toto, Stevie Wonder, Lou Reed, Asia, the Beatles and the Police for example.  &lt;br /&gt;Stop in for a drink and relax  for awhile at the Solas on a Tuesday night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested the Solas serves food till at least 11pm I believe, not a bad place to get a bite to eat before the show. There is also good Mexican food, and other dinning choices close by.&lt;br /&gt;If there is enough interest we could make plans to get something to eat either at the Solas or elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me if your interested in gettting something to eat before the show.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to Meetup with some of you there. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;E-mail me if you have any questions...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Solas is a small venue. I will be upstairs at  the second floor bar where the Barflies will be playing.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg D</member_name><member_id>4879355</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204251092000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Mike and George usually play some good tunes and have established a Tuesday night residency now at the Solas.  They play almost every Tuesday night. Come out, stop in for a few drinks or a bite to eat and see this Free Show.</why><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203294812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Barflies @ the Solas</name><id>7351671</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204077600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/7351671/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/3/global_3151347.jpeg</photo_url></item>