<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Administrative Fee </label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>As promised, I'm rescheduling this event.  The bevy of beautiful bovines still awaits us and are still ready for their close-ups!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dunajski Dairy is a functioning dairy farm which has been in business since the early 1900's. Founded by an immigrant from Poland, the farm has been in the family for three generations.  The dairy is home to 140 dairy cows and about 24 calves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tracy Dunajski will get us started on our tour of the barn and then we'll be on our own to get to know the girls. We will have access to every one of them. They are all quite sweet and interested in having their picture taken.  The babies are adorable and have personalities - some frisky, some quite shy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The farm itself has a field where some of the older cows hang out. We will have access to the barn, field and the milk plant (note: the plant won't be functioning on Sunday but there are some interesting things to photograph like machinery and other rustic items. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ONE NOTE: The main barn where the cows are sheltered has a pungent smell of hay and &amp;quot;cow pies&amp;quot;. It's not overpowering and is easily gotten used to. (For those who went to the Franklin Park Zoo primate house last year, it's NOT anywhere near that level). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've ever been in a horse stable, the smell is equivalent. The floors will have been swept clean but could be wet.  The fields may be dryer but in both cases, you should wear appropriate footwear so you don't ruin any good shoes.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The barn provides some shelter so we'll keep the date if it's a little bit misty or rainy.  Torrential rain will cancel the event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll post directions and a map the week before the shoot.  We'll meet at a North Shore Mall location (TBA) and then head over to the farm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have access to the cows for 2 hours. At 3:00 PM, they go into the milking house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the shoot, there are a couple of options in the area for lunch for anyone interested in gathering after for a bite and conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you'll join me. The cows are all very sweet and once you look at each individual face, you start to see complete individuality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!... Dianne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: CAPE Group charges $1 per meeting/per photographer in order to cover the cost of our Meetup.com website.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>North Shore Mall parking lot  (location TBA)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>5274985</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245512768000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239891988000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dunajski Dairy Cows</name><id>10198105</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244394000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/10198105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/0/5/global_8177893.jpeg</photo_url></item>