<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>119 Hope Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02809</zip><lat>41.661620</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-253-9100</phone><name>The Lobster Pot</name><city>Bristol</city><id>969795</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.271183</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I figured the final event of summer ought to include seafood, so I picked The Lobster Pot in Bristol, Rhode Island.  The other reason I picked this restaurant is we have not been too far East of Providence yet, so I thought those members ought to get a chance and try a restaurant closer to home.   The menu and information about the The Lobster Pot can be viewed on their website &lt;a href="http://www.lobsterpotri.com/" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  Although the prices were not quoted in the website, I was informed most meals range in the $17-$21 range, with 1 pound lobsters $25.95.  All meal items come with a vegetable and a potato side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have one bill for food, which will be divided equally among members then a second bill for beverages and alcohol. This way we can order appetizers as a table and everyone can enjoy with minimal confusion and the ones who choose not to indulge in &amp;quot;adult beverages&amp;quot; won't have to worry about paying extra when just enjoying non-alcoholic drinks. Please let me know if this is a problem for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should we fill up and you are still interested in attending, please enter a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP and put a note stating that you want to be wait-listed. If spots open up, I will contact you in order of RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has not attended previous events, please plan on bringing a dollar to help me defray the cost of posting on meetup. For everyone who has attended, I only ask that you contribute every other event. This would be such a big help to me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please see my piccy.  I am the one with the red hair ;-).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223503060000</updated><rating><average>3.79999995232</average><count>5</count></rating><why>We are a great group of people who love to dine out.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211941099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Dining Out August Meetup- The Lobster Pot</name><id>8024119</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220050800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/8024119/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/7/global_4283959.jpeg</photo_url></item>