<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>cross street is Washington Street in Dudley Station</address_2><address_1>12 Dade Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02119</zip><lat>42.331779</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 445-0900</phone><name>Haley House Cafe</name><city>Roxbury </city><id>1088485</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081993</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coloroffilm.com/"&gt;The Color of Film Collaborative&lt;/a&gt; in partnership with the &lt;a href="http://www.haleyhouse.org/calendar"&gt;Haley House&lt;/a&gt; periodically present documentaries and narrative films via Dinner and a Movie. The next offering Soul Food Junkies is scheduled for Friday November 30, 2012. This is another great time to get together to enjoy each others company a meal and food for thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members of the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonOnyxbirds/events/91821792/"&gt;Onyxbirds Meetup&lt;/a&gt; will be joining us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchase tickets for $21.69 (includes dinner and movie but not beverages) at &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/293001"&gt;http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/293001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the menu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mills' Award-Winning Spicy Jerk Chicken &lt;br /&gt;

 Haley House Vegan Collards &lt;br /&gt;

 Organic Brown Rice &lt;br /&gt;

 HH Cornbread &lt;br /&gt;

 Sweet Potato Pie &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Vegetarians (or those afraid of heat) can get a Vegetarian Cutlet instead of chicken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beer, wine and non-alcoholic beverages will be available for purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A film about food traditions that are hard to change, especially when they're passed on from generation to generation. In this PBS documentary, award-winning filmmaker Byron Hurt shares his journey to learn more about the African American cuisine known as soul food&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baffled by his dad's unwillingness to change his traditional soul food diet in the face of a health crisis, Hurt sets out to learn more about this rich culinary tradition and its relevance to black cultural identity. He discovers that the love affair that his dad and his community have with soul food is deep-rooted, complex, and in some tragic cases, deadly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through candid interviews with soul food cooks, historians, and scholars, as well as doctors, family members, and everyday people, Soul Food Junkies blends history, humor, and heartwarming stories to place this culinary tradition under the microscope. Both the consequences and the benefits of soul food are carefully addressed. So too is the issue of low access to quality food in black communities, which makes it difficult for some black people to eat healthy. In the end, Hurt determines whether or not black people are addicted to this food tradition that has its origins in West Africa and the black south, yet is loved all over the world. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 After the film, time is planned for folks to share a 5 minute or less food story with a chance to win a prize. You're also welcome to sit back and listen to the great stories and participate as a voter to help decide the winner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Transit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. &lt;br /&gt;

 Orange Line subway to Ruggles Station then any bus to Dudley Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to arrange your driving directions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking lot on Dade Street as well as along Washington Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/a/9/event_16789577.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would also like you to know the &lt;a href="http://www.roxburyfilmfestival.org/index.php"&gt;Roxbury International Film Festival&lt;/a&gt; (RIFF) showcases and honors the work of emerging and established filmmakers of color as well as films important to our community. It has become the largest festival in New England dedicated to celebrating this genre. This is always a great time with fascinating people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Run time for the 15th annual RIFF is Thursday June 14th through Sunday June 17th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354327299000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353189353000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and A Movie at Haley House on Friday November 30th</name><id>91825182</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354316400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/91825182/</event_url></item>