<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you had this conversation with yourself and/or with others?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I  know what I want. I use LOA principles diligently.  I'm great at manifesting the little things &amp;amp; some bigger ones. However, with some of the bigger issues &amp;amp; dreams I have…well, when I notice what I want is not showing up yet, I get frustrated, I feel bummed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know I shouldn't focus on the lack.  Yes, I know I need to let go &amp;amp; not be too detached to the outcome.  Yet I can't seem to be able to let go completely or feel less frustrated.  What if I can't or have a difficult time letting go?  What if I continuously feel bummed out?  Does this mean I'll just never attract what I want?  Maybe it's not meant to be.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Yuliya Cohen, BostonLOA member and Energy Healer,&lt;/b&gt; assures us that the difficulties we experience with the process of letting go are not our fault.  You can still get what you want, &lt;b&gt;without having to let go &amp;amp; detach&lt;/b&gt; from your &amp;quot;low energy&amp;quot; feelings, limiting beliefs &amp;amp; your desired outcome.  She'll share with you how you can &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;recycle&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; the negative or stuck feelings you have &amp;amp; still come out a winner! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hmm....doesn't this contradict the principles of the Law Of Attraction?  Join us to find out.  Take your practice of the Law OF Attraction to a new level as we explore the nature of duality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&amp;quot; Duality is the nature of any quality.&lt;br /&gt;Opposites complement each other &lt;br /&gt;instead of competing with each other&lt;br /&gt;— they are two faces of the same coin — &lt;br /&gt;one cannot exist without the other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you perceive that no quality in itself is good or bad,&lt;br /&gt;the right and wrong game in your mind will wind down&lt;br /&gt;and you will enter an inner world of peace and balance. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Taoist teachings&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Yuliya Cohen:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.yuliyacohen.com&lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Yuliya Cohen&lt;/b&gt; is a trained energy healer, medical intuitive and therapist, and the creator of the Energy Restructuring™ System.  She received her training from the HLCC &amp;quot;Crucible&amp;quot; program, directed by Rev. Rosalyn Bruyere, a world-renowned healer, scholar &amp;amp; researcher in the field of Energy Healing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya was formerly an engineer &amp;amp; computer science researcher (including work at Siemens Research and Technology Laboratories) and holds degrees in Civil Engineering from the Kiev School of Civil Engineering &amp;amp; in Computer Science from Brandeis University.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224638154000</updated><rating><average>3.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>70</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220439833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction October Meetup</name><id>8677722</id><headcount>71</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223420400000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/8677722/</event_url></item>