<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>701 Centre Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.311574</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 522-2195 </phone><name>Bukhara Restaurant</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>918425</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114632</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lunch location: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=475%20Moody%20St%2C%20Waltham%2C%20MA" target="_blank"&gt;Bukhara,&lt;/a&gt; 701 Centre Street, Jamaica Plain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate cost: $20 (includes lunch, tax, tip, and $1 to support the meetup). May be a little less depending on location. Additional cost for anything you add from the menu (breads, beverages, chai).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;GOODREADS - A contemporary story of adventure, history, and identity by acclaimed author Amitav Ghosh. Off the easternmost corner of India, in the Bay of Bengal, lies the immense labyrinth of tiny islands known as the Sundarbans, where settlers live in fear of drowning tides and man-eating tigers. Piya Roy, a young American marine biologist of Indian descent, arrives in this lush, treacherous landscape in search of a rare species of river dolphin and enlists the aid of a local fisherman and a translator. Together the three of them launch into the elaborate backwaters, drawn unawares into the powerful political undercurrents of this isolated corner of the world that exact a personal toll as fierce as the tides.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AMAZON - The Hungry Tide is a very contemporary story of adventure and unlikely love, identity and history, set in one of the most fascinating regions on the earth. Off the easternmost coast of India, in the Bay of Bengal, lies the immense labyrinth of tiny islands known as the Sundarbans. For settlers here, life is extremely precarious. Attacks by deadly tigers are common. Unrest and eviction are constant threats. Without warning, at any time, tidal floods rise and surge over the land, leaving devastation in their wake. In this place of vengeful beauty, the lives of three people from different worlds collide. Piya Roy is a young marine biologist, of Indian descent but stubbornly American, in search of a rare, endangered river dolphin. Her journey begins with a disaster, when she is thrown from a boat into crocodile-infested waters. Rescue comes in the form of a young, illiterate fisherman, Fokir. Although they have no language between them, Piya and Fokir are powerfully drawn to each other, sharing an uncanny instinct for the ways of the sea. Piya engages Fokir to help with her research and finds a translator in Kanai Dutt, a businessman from Delhi whose idealistic aunt and uncle are longtime settlers in the Sundarbans. As the three of them launch into the elaborate backwaters, they are drawn unawares into the hidden undercurrents of this isolated world, where political turmoil exacts a personal toll that is every bit as powerful as the ravaging tide. Already an international success, The Hungry Tide is a prophetic novel of remarkable insight, beauty, and humanity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Books on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>6571667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337534240000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333326595000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May 2012 - The Hungry Tide by Amitav Ghosh</name><id>58832542</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337443200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/58832542/</event_url></item>