<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Exit 5 West from Route 3</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.759998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rt. 111</name><city>Nashua</city><id>347799</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.470001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's rally our Meetup troops to show Dr. Paul a warm and supportive welcome to the GOP BBQ and show all those attending that the Ron Paul campaign is made up of enthusiastic supporters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An hour prior to the GOP BBQ, we will meet to line Route 111 (West Hollis St.)  with Ron Paul supporters holding campaign signs and Revolution Banners. Route 111 (at Exit 5 off Rt. 3, Everett Turnpike), leads to the GOP event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring signs if you have them, but don't worry if you don't have signs or banners. The Nashua Meetup Group will supply 35, 3 x 9 foot banners that we've made for this purpose. We have more events planned with these banners, so be sure to return them after the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Location...&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 5W off the Everett Turnike (Rte. 3). We will plan to meet at the little island in front of the Police Station across from the Greek Church. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For parking...&lt;br /&gt;Take a right at the light at the end of the exit ramp onto 111. Then take your first right onto the little street where you see the sign that says &amp;quot;no thru traffic&amp;quot;. Then take a fast right onto the street that runs along the cemetary parimeter. Park there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187709013000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186674979000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre BBQ Banner Blitz and Sign Wave</name><id>6152001</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187535600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6152001/</event_url></item>