<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;The start time is 7:25. &lt;br /&gt;Blame it on Fidel! screened once at this year's MFA French Film Festival and we had a small group who attended  with a very enthusiastic response. I think &amp;quot;charming&amp;quot; was the word used most by group members . Afterward, I hoped that this first time feature by Julie Gravas, daughter of the legenday Greek director Costa-Gavras (Z, State of Siege) would get a larger US release and lo and behold, it is getting a week run at the Kendall!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set in 1970, nine-year old Anna (Nina Kervel) leads a happy life with her well-to-do Spanish lawyer dad, Fernando (Stephano Accorsi), and French glam magazine writer mom, Marie (Julie Depardieu). But, this stable world is about to turn upside down when her parents are bitten by the bug to right the world's wrongs and Anna will &amp;quot;Blame It on Fidel.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of those rare films that maintain unwavering fidelity to a child?s view of the world&amp;quot; Time Out New York &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Unforced in its tenderness and wit, the film lightly addresses the era's incendiary revolutions through the girl's developing filters without oversimplifying the complex politics. &amp;quot; Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Playing the type of young girl who simply must come out on top in school, young Nina Kervel-Bey could so easily have become unpleasant with her baby fat pout, but the perplexing state of affairs she finds herself in bring on a maturity that is fascinating to watch.  Gavras's direction of the child as adult and the adults often childish is pitch perfect.  Hands down, of the half films previewed for the MFA's 12th Boston French Film Festival, &amp;quot;Blame it on Fidel&amp;quot; is the best discovery.  It's also one of the best films of the year.&amp;quot; ReelingReviews&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is The New York Times  complete review: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2007/08/03/movies/03fide.html?ex=1217736000&amp;amp;en=48efb178f28e8525&amp;amp;ei=5083&amp;amp;partner=Rotten%20Tomatoes" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meet-Up sign near the front row at the movie's conclusion and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. Yes, I think its one of the best movies I've seen this year, and if you wind up disagreeing, I hope you don't Blame it on Tom!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187651990000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186191480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blame it on Fidel! One Mo' Time!</name><id>6122881</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187478900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6122881/</event_url></item>