<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>68 Howe St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.309635</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-777-9760</phone><name>Miya's Sushi</name><city>New Haven</city><id>249886</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.935280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miya's Sushi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By special request (you know who you are), the NHC scored a very special HH.&lt;br /&gt;Many of you are extremely familiar with Miya's but for those who aren't, Bun, the owner would like me to share the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Miya's Sushi is a 2 time winner in Taste of the Nation!&lt;br /&gt;***Only CT restaurant 2 times in a row to be reviewed in the NY times in subsequent years. &lt;br /&gt;***Will be featured this season on A&amp;amp;E...Flip This House&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please visit their My Space account at: www.myspace.com/miyassushi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bun is being extremely generous and offering The NHC the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5.75 for ALL drinks-this includes beer, wine and his 7 different homemade Saki's, and much more&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HH food:&lt;br /&gt;FREE -  award winning original Sushi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have our own room in the bar area. Bun said feel free to bring your IPODs to plug into his stereo sytem. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is so happy to have us and is asking in return we promote his restaurant  by telling friends and family about his amazing food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The catch: They only hold 80 people. So he asked us to cap at 40 to leave room for his regulars. Don't know if NHC ever had 40 attend a HH but just in case....I'm capping! However...who would stop you if you just happen to be in the area and want to say hello?   hint hint&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**There is NO ONSITE PARKING. See Eric's comment below for suggested parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to see you there!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... &lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post-party location TBD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact:&lt;br /&gt;Robyn-Allise - 203 823 5302&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175119706000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174443230000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour- MIYA'S SUSHI!!</name><id>5589382</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174946400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5589382/</event_url></item>