<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03442</zip><lat>43.000154</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Pinkham Notch Camp</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>832702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.922233</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizers: Karine &amp;amp; Spruce&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/strong&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared,  you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a group of adventurous hikers who aren't afraid of &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;lots of extra climbing&lt;/span&gt; to hike Mt. Isolation. We are not fans of the Rocky Branch trail, so will be taking a different route. This is not a peak-bagging trip - if you need this peak, there is a much easier way to get it! Our proposed route has &lt;strong&gt;3,000 EXTRA feet of climbing&lt;/strong&gt; vs the traditional route (that's almost twice the elevation!). This hike will also take us up Huntington Ravine - known as one of the most difficult trails in the Whites, due to the steep &amp;amp; exposed climb up slabs of rock that require scrambling and using hand/footholds. This route is not for anyone who is afraid of heights or exposure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this challenging &lt;strong&gt;fast-paced&lt;/strong&gt; loop hike we will&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;hike 16 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 6,400 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. Book time is about 11 hours - but our plan/goal is to hike faster than book time and finish in less than 10 hours. This trip is considered &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain&lt;/strong&gt;. You should be a strong and steady climber (1.5-2mph while ascending) and able to climb all day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We plan to hike up &lt;strong&gt;Hungtington Ravine&lt;/strong&gt; from Pinkham Notch, across the &lt;strong&gt;Alpine Garden&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Boott Spur&lt;/strong&gt; (5,500 ft - not an official 4K), then descend the Davis Path along the Montalban ridge down to &lt;strong&gt;Mt. Isolation&lt;/strong&gt; (4,003 ft - #46 on the NH48). Then, we'll climb BACK UP the Davis Path to the junction with the Glen Boulder trail and descend over &lt;strong&gt;Slide Peak&lt;/strong&gt; (4,806 ft - not an official 4K) and past &lt;strong&gt;Glen Boulder&lt;/strong&gt; back to the trailhead. Notice that we will be climbing several peaks that are NOT official 4Ks that are significantly taller than Mt. Isolation. One of these will be scaled on the way back - so you will need to climb strong late in the day. This route will spend plenty of time above treeline and give us beautiful views. Note that we will NOT be summitting Mt. Washington (the typical destination of the Huntington Ravine Trail). Also, &lt;strong&gt;our trip is weather dependent.&lt;/strong&gt; If there was recent rain and Huntington Ravine is possibly wet - we will not take this route - and will climb directly up to Boott Spur instead. Due to the time above tree-line, we will cancel this trip if there is threat of thunderstorms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we have visited these peaks and some of these trails before, a few parts of this route are new to us. We expect all participants to bring a map, and be familiar with the route. We researched this trail via the AMC White Mountain Guide, online resources, and with maps - and we expect you to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who should sign up?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To sign up for this hike, you should be an experienced hiker who has recently completed trips of similar distance and elevation - faster than book time. Please answer all RSVP questions - if we haven't hiked with you before, you may also be contacted by meet up organizers to further elaborate on your preparation/experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event. If there was recent rain and Huntington Ravine is possibly wet - we will not take this route - and will climb directly up to Boott Spur instead. Due to the time above tree-line, we will cancel this trip if there is threat of thunderstorms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Footwear: Sturdy hiking boots/trail runners with good traction on slabby rock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON. It can be very chilly above 5,000 feet - bring hat and gloves as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip (3 Liters recommended).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Bug Spray. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will meet at Pinkham Notch Visitor Center on Route 16, north of Jackson, NH and south of Gorham, NH.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Google maps indicates this location is about 160 miles and 3 hours 15 minutes from Boston.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=Pinkham+Notch,+Coos,+NH&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=43.309191,-71.021118&amp;amp;spn=2.174446,5.333862&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFTVgowIdm9TA-yEz_vuuYdAtpw&amp;amp;oq=Pinkham+Notch+&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;doflg=ptm&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Here for Directions&lt;/a&gt; - change your starting location from Boston, to your address.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1344284221000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338950144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K: Mt. Isolation via Huntington Ravine/Alpine Garden/Boott Spur (Advanced)</name><id>67942712</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344168000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/67942712/</event_url></item>