<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you are having trouble reading this email, go to iacboston.org/mckinneyboston.html to view it. Facebook Twitter More... Please Post Widely International Action Center - iacenter.org iacboston.org About the IAC | Donate | IAC Books &amp;amp; Resources | Contact Us Send a copy of this message to a friend with this link. Come to a Meeting AUGUST 6 &amp;#149; SAT &amp;#149; 4 pm AT ST. KATHERINE DREXEL CHURCH 175 Ruggles St., Roxbury, MA Report from Libya: - U.S. war in Africa Hear former U.S. Congressperson Cynthia McKinney, recently returned from leading a delegation to Libya during the U.S. bombing Report on Millions Marching in Harlem &amp;#149; Sat &amp;#149; AUG &amp;#149;13 ASSEMBLING ON MALCOLM X BLVD AT 110TH STREET, HARLEM, NEW YORK More than 120 days of U.S./NATO bombing of Libya 1 cruise missile could pay 10 teachers for a year. We need jobs, health care &amp;amp; education, not budget cuts, prisons and war. The national 15-city educational &amp;amp; fundraising Report from LIBYA tour with Cynthia McKinney is organized by International Action Center, www.IACenter.org in coordination with many antiwar and community organizations from July 7 to August 24, 2011. Boston program is in cosponsored by the International Action Center; Fanmi Lavalas Boston; Boston United National Antiwar Commitee; Minister Don Mohammad, Temple 11, Nation of Islam*;Veterans for Peace, Chapter 9, Smedley Butler Brigade; Chelsea Uniting Against the War; Women's Fightback Network, SistaCipher; Politicin' with the Sistas; United American Indians of New England, Bishop Filipe Teixeira, OFSJC, Diocese of St Francis of Assisi, CCA; Steve Gillis, VP,USW 8751 Boston School Bus Union; Ed Childs, Chief Shop Steward, UNITE-HERE local 26*, N'COBRA (Reparations), Manchester NH (*= for id only) (list in formation - to cosponsor call 617-522-6626). STOP U.S./NATO WAR ON LIBYA For information in Boston call: 617-522-6626 or go to www.iacboston.org For more information and a complete list of cities or to help donate for the tour expenses see: www.IACenter.org or call: 212-633-6646 Labor donated 7/11 Donate at iacenter.org/africa/donatemckinneylibyatour Download pdf flyers: Color Poster / Color Flyer / B&amp;amp;W Flyer Part of 15 City Tour coordinated by the International Action Center. For listing of full tour go to &lt;a href="http://www.iacenter.org/africa/libya-mckinney-tour070911/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.iacenter.o...&lt;/a&gt; Donate at iacenter.org/africa/donatemckinneylibyatour Download pdf flyers: Color Poster / Color Flyer / B&amp;amp;W Flyer About the IAC | Donate | IAC Books &amp;amp; Resources | Contact Us International Action Center National Office: c/o Solidarity Center 55 W 17th St Suite 5C New York, NY 10011 212-633-6646 iacenter@iacenter.org www.iacenter.org Boston Office: c/o Action Center 284 Amory St Jamaica Plain, MA 02130 617-522-6626 iacboston@iacboston.org www.iacboston.org Facebook Twitter More... Please post widely!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312665579000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311971172000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>8/6 4pm Report from Libya: US war in Africa w/former US Cong. Cynthia McKinney</name><id>27528131</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312660800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/27528131/</event_url></item>