<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Water Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06355</zip><lat>41.353578</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-536-5059</phone><name>Courtyard Art Gallery</name><city>Mystic</city><id>1285975</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.972302</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/f/6/event_216157622.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Poetry at Courtyard Art Gallery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;with Joanie DiMartino&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time to make our trip back to Mytic!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our friend Fran Harkins has invited us back for a private gathering at her wonderful art gallery in beautiful Mystic! This is a visit we make a couple of times a year and it is always one of our favorites! Fran is sponsoring a few poetry venues this year, and as we tend to take over her place when we show up, has graciously offered to do this event privately for all of us. We will have the opportunity to look through her art gallery, meet some of the artists, (all of which are amazing), have a glass of wine, and light dessert and hear some poetry.&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/f/0/event_223237872.jpeg" width="124" height="159" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Poet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"I desire only ink for wine, only stanzas for bread." -Joanie DiMartino &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Joanie DiMartino has work published in many literary journals and anthologies, including &lt;em&gt;Modern Haiku, Alimentum, Calyx, &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt;Amethyst Arsenic.&lt;/em&gt; Her first chapbook, &lt;em&gt;Licking the Spoon&lt;/em&gt;, was published with Finishing Line Press in 2007. She is a past winner of the Betty Gabehart Award for poetry from the Women Writers Conference, Kentucky, and was a finalist in the Cultural Center of Cape Cod poetry competition. Her first full-length collection, &lt;em&gt;Strange Girls&lt;/em&gt; was published in June, 2010 by Little Red Tree Publishing, and the poem “A Treatise on Handling Snakes” from that collection received a nomination for a Pushcart Prize. &lt;em&gt;Strange Girls&lt;/em&gt; was nominated for the 2011 Connecticut Book Award.  &lt;em&gt;Strange Girls &lt;/em&gt;is presently being developed for a stage performance by director Steve Rotolo for the Salem Theater Company in Salem, MA. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Her poems have been featured in several art exhibits in Lexington, Kentucky, including &lt;em&gt;Sideshow&lt;/em&gt;, a collaborative project with the Women Artists Group; &lt;em&gt;Collaborations + Catalysts&lt;/em&gt;, an exhibit highlighting combined mediums; and &lt;em&gt;Connections--We Are All One&lt;/em&gt;, an interfaith exhibit, where her poem, “The Monks,” an experimental piece incorporating Gregorian Chant throughout the poem, was performed. DiMartino has had several poems presented by the East Haddam Plays &amp;amp; Players as part of their &lt;em&gt;Plays &amp;amp; Poetry&lt;/em&gt; performance in selected locations throughout Connecticut. She was most recently featured in the exhibit &lt;em&gt;Women in the Arts&lt;/em&gt;, a show by local artist Deborah Curtis, where her portrait and poem, “Self-Portrait,” were on display at ArtWorks in Norwich, Connecticut.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

She is currently at work on several projects, including a collection of poems about the 19th-century whaling industry, highlighting the career of the &lt;em&gt;Charles W. Morgan &lt;/em&gt;whaling bark; a collection of persona poems from the perspective of militant suffragist Alice Paul; a haiku sequence collaboration with visual artist Deborah Curtis; and a haibun children’s book with musician and illustrator Don Sineti.  She is also editing an anthology about the Jersey Shore for Jersey publisher unbound CONTENT, to raise funds for restoration from Hurricane Sandy damage.  Her work is being translated into Bulgarian and Spanish. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

DiMartino holds an MA in public history from Rutgers University. She worked in the history museum field for over fifteen years, and her poetry often addresses history with a feminist perspective. She was a founding member of the now-defunct women’s poetry group Mosaic, in Lexington, Kentucky, and is currently a member of Poets &amp;amp; Writers Consortium East in Groton, CT. She hosts Soup &amp;amp; Sonnets, a monthly literary salon for women, and directs the Hidden Treasures Poetry Series in partnership with the William Meredith Foundation.  Along with performing poetry, she reviews books and leads workshops and discussion groups. Raised in southern New Jersey, DiMartino has lived in Lexington, Kentucky, and now resides with her son in Mystic, CT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the gallery</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367626381000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363825150000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poetry at Courtyard Art Gallery</name><id>110262962</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367175600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/110262962/</event_url></item>