<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me for Clint Eastwood’s &lt;i&gt;Gran Torino&lt;/i&gt;.  Please note that the time listed above is incorrect; the film is scheduled to begin at 1:20.  As this film will be in its opening weekend, I suggest you buy your tickets ahead of time by visiting the Embassy’s &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=249" target="_blank"&gt;site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Decades after the Korean War has ended, ageing veteran Walt Kowalski (Clint Eastwood) is still haunted by the horrors he witnessed on the battlefield. The two objects that matter most to Kowalski in life are the classic Gran Torino that represents his happier days working in a Ford assembly plant, and the M-1 rifle that saved his life countless times during combat. When Kowalski's teenage neighbor (Bee Vang) attempts to steal his Gran Torino as part of a gang initiation rite, the old man manages to catch the aspiring thief at the business end of his well-maintained semi-automatic rifle. Later, due to the pride of the Asian group, the boy is forced to return to Kowalski's house and perform an act of penance. Despite the fact that Kowalski wants nothing to do with the young troublemaker, he realizes that the quickest way out of the situation is to simply cooperate. In an effort to set the teen on the right path in life and toughen him up, the reluctant vet sets him up with an old crony who now works in construction. In the process, Kowalski discovers that the only way to lay his many painful memories to rest is to finally face his own blinding prejudice head-on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A New York Times Critics’ Pick: Manohla Dargis says: “Twice in the last decade, just as the holiday movie season has begun to sag under the weight of its own bloat, full of noise and nonsense signifying nothing, Clint Eastwood has slipped another film into theaters and shown everyone how it’s done. This year’s model is &lt;i&gt;Gran Torino&lt;/i&gt;, a sleek, muscle car of a movie Made in the U.S.A., in that industrial graveyard called Detroit. I’m not sure how he does it, but I don’t want him to stop. Not because every film is great — though, damn, many are — but because even the misfires show an urgent engagement with the tougher, messier, bigger questions of American life.”  Read the complete review &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2008/12/12/movies/12tori.html" target="_blank"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it’s off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230996530000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gran Torino</name><id>9433145</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231697700000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9433145/</event_url></item>