<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Please note the early start time.  As the film is over two hours long, it would have been too late to go to a later start time.  I will try to make reservations at Zaftigs for 8:00 pm.  PLEASE change your RSVP if you cannot attend.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FROZEN RIVER&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;is the story of Ray Eddy (Melissa Leo), an upstate New York trailer mom who is lured into the world of illegal immigrant smuggling when she meets a Mohawk girl who lives on a reservation that straddles the US-Canadian border. Broke after her husband takes off with the down payment for their new doublewide, Ray reluctantly teams up with Lila, a smuggler, and the two begin making runs across the frozen St. Lawrence River carrying illegal Chinese and Pakistani immigrants in the trunk of Ray's Dodge Spirit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Courtney Hunt, w/ Leo, Misty Upham, Charlie McDermott, and Mark Boone, Jr., 1h37m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Stephen Holden of the New York Times:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s Not a Wonderful Life&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venturing deep into the trenches where hard-working Americans struggle to put food on the table, Courtney Hunt’s somber film “Frozen River” evokes a perfect storm of present-day woes: illegal immigration, ethnic tension, depressed real estate, high gas prices and dire poverty. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film’s setting, in upstate New York at the Canadian border, is a gray wintry landscape of mud and slush dotted with trailers and discount stores. Although it is days before Christmas, there is no joy here, and as the movie goes along, its chill begins to seep into your bones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clearly, we are in for a fun, fun time as we watch this Sundance Film Festival Indie hit!  However, grim as the film may appear, the underlying themes of redemption may be well worth the effort:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If “Frozen River” has all the ingredients for a weepy Christmas story in the tradition of “It’s a Wonderful Life,” it is almost the opposite of that. It is grim reality. But because Ray refuses to give up, she lends the movie nobility. &lt;i&gt;Ms. Leo’s magnificent portrayal of a woman of indomitable grit and not an iota of self-pity makes “Frozen River” a compelling study of individual courage.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for me in the theater during the closing credits holding a meetup sign and weeping in my popcorn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, I will look to make reservations at Zaftigs for us to discuss the film over banana stuffed french toast and knish, or to sit outside at Panera Bread sipping soup and ice tea.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be standing like a frozen statute with a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219613769000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218561692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FROZEN RIVER</name><id>8528858</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219440600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8528858/</event_url></item>