<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Westledge Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06092</zip><lat>41.878990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>West Mountain Trails</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>1785191</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.866302</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/4/a/event_6578986.jpeg" width="201" height="288" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This is a loop in Simsbury at the Simsbury Land Trust. It is a 5ish mile loop that will take us through the Masters School area and out to a pretty good lookout. There are some challenging areas to this trail so be forwarned. The challenges include rocky terrain and steep slopes. I would call this a moderate hike.  We will make a detour to check out the waterfall (water not guaranteed).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will head out the red trail until it ends at the lookout. Our return promises a flatter contour on the white to blue route. The terrain is woods so be prepared to really hike. We should be done in four hours but we are only as fast as our slowest hiker. We do hike as a group so if that does not appeal to you, this is not your crew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring lots of water, food since we will have a lunch break on the trail, sun screen, bug spray, camera, hiking boots, and a small pack to keep all your stuff in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking area is limited so we will have to pack them in.  We can work to find road spots or park at the Master's School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am hoping we can head down the road to Tulmeadow Farm ice cream after we stummble out of the wilderness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please, no dogs or children. Thats how I roll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not be affraid of the elevations on this map.....it is compressed and does not really look like the Himalyas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.simsburylandtrust.org/pdf_files/w_mtns_trailguide.pdf"&gt;http://www.simsburylandtrust.org/pdf_files/w_mtns_trailguide.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information about the land trust and another map link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.simsburylandtrust.org/westledge.shtml"&gt;http://www.simsburylandtrust.org/westledge.shtml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;

By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1336351755000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330913506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking West Mountain Trails Simsbury, CT</name><id>54989492</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336226400000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/54989492/</event_url></item>