<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Danvers NorthShore Network Marketing Support Meetup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Everyone, (If you are in a MLM, Network Marketing, Product Driven, Home Based Business READ THIS!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My name is Anthony Pasquale. I am forming this group for the purpose of education and support in the field of Direct Sales, MLM, Network Sales, Network Marketing and all Home Based Businesses that are in need of the ART OF THE APPROACH. Yes, this is a skill! How many times have you been approached by someone who has no idea how to win someone's trust or to start a conversation, they are annoying, they show no care for the person they are speaking to, they come across as rude, disrespectful, pushy and no finesse. You might be one of these people! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is an art to speaking, gaining trust, building teams that will help you create wealth. There are MLM's and Direct Sales Companies and Network Marketing Programs that will pay you well but if you STINK at the approach or creating a team or being organized to follow up, well you will loose money, interest, friends and great connections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop it! Stop trying to do it yourself. Invest in your self for a short time and you will be amazed at what you will be able to create. A life with meaningful income and relationships. Look, instead of buying another book, listening to another CD or doing another seminar here is a place to PRACTICE FIRST! This will be a safe haven for you to make your mistakes, fall flat on your face, stumble and bumble and you will LEARN FIRST.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me tell you what this group is NOT, Don't come here to pitch your company, your product or your services. This is where you will come to study how to create the best list of people you can approach, how to form a WINNING TEAM for your goals. How to learn the trade of the invitation script, How to find the right prospect, how to leverage your time better. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In other words: this is where we will learn how to do this right! How many times have you been frustrated with yourself for not following up with someone and then finding out they did something else. Well now this is your chance to study what needs to be done like a PROFESSIONAL!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will bring in special guest to speaker, from many different organizations, the best of the best! So you will be amazing at what you do! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am going accept only 20 people in this core group and then close it off. This will be your Master Mind Group for success in this field. Each one of you who does join will need to learn and teach a subject in your weakest area down the road. First let's learn. We will meet the first Monday of the month then as the group grows we will open it to twice a month. Yes there is a charge per month of $12.00. (This way we have only the serious attending)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you are ready to learn, it will be first come first serve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Pasquale &lt;br /&gt;AJP Enterprise Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pasquale and Hurley Assoc.&lt;br /&gt;United Martial Arts Center&lt;br /&gt;Osanna Seminars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Live with purpose and passion everyday&amp;quot; ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.umachealth.com &lt;br /&gt;www.danversmartialarts.com&lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street, Suite 100 &lt;br /&gt;Danvers MA 01923 &lt;br /&gt;(978) 836-6501 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain &amp;quot;average&amp;quot;. These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will introduce myself.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241885587000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236002837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Danvers &amp; NorthShore Network Marketing Support April Meetup</name><id>9859008</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240059600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/9859008/</event_url></item>