<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I had tickets to see Harry Chapin at the Hampton Casino on July 17, 1981.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The night before the concert, Harry died on the Long Island Expressway when he suffered a massive heart attack, lost control of the wheel, and drifted into the path of an 18 wheeler. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He was on his way to a benefit concert.  More than half of Harry's concert's were benefit concerts.  He figured he'd do one for himself and one for the other guy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'If a man tried&lt;br /&gt;to take his time on earth&lt;br /&gt;and prove before he died&lt;br /&gt;what one man's life could be worth&lt;br /&gt;Well, I wonder what could happen to this earth?'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raiders of the Lost Ark opened in theaters on July 17, 1981.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Indy shakes his head, forgets about the whip, pulls out the gun, and shoots sword master - in that moment - I burst out laughing and transitioned from tragedy to cinematic history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And transitioned into Boston history.  John Williams composed the score to Raiders and conducted the Boston Pops on July 4 at the Esplanade, where he premiered his newest score each year.  In 1980, the hostages were held in Iran, and Williams premiered the 'Darth Vader Theme' to half a million people who waved American flags in time to the music.  The 'woosh' and emotion was so profound that Williams turned and stopped conducting as his jaw dropped at the site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Williams conducted 'Star Wars' and a 16 minute medley from 'ET' without using a score.  He premiered the Liberty Fanfare and 1984 Olympics Theme at the Esplanade. The privilege of hearing the Pops premier the most popular film music ever recorded has never been matched.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Much like a Harry Chapin concert.  Word was, if you weren't impressed with the number of people at a Chapin concert, come back next time he's in town because it will be sold out.  And they were.  His concerts have never been matched.  And they were always for the other guy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be at Panera Bread as early as 5:45 to tell Harry stories, and remember the golden age of John Williams conducting the Boston Pops.  Join me for a film when they (and we) were young, and film transitioned to the age of Spielberg and Lucas.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Indy pulls out his whip, we'll witness cinema classic.  When he pulls out the gun, I'll be in tears.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277167213000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Big Screen Classics: RAIDERS OF THE LOST ARK</name><id>13869890</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278975600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13869890/</event_url></item>