<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, it's another Men in Black movie. I loved the first, and while the second film was not as strong it did have some funny moments, and I have a soft spot for the characters. The trailer has made me curious, so come on out with me and see if Sony/Columbia spent enough money on the script!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I now know the time of the movie - we will be seeing the &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;6:15 show&lt;/span&gt;. I will be at the lobby close to an hour before and I will be wearing a red trucker hat with the meetup logo. Here are the instructions on where the group is meeting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- if there is a ticketholder line to get into this movie, you should look for me and the group in the line &lt;br /&gt;

- if there is no line and the movie is upstairs, the group will gather in the 2nd floor lobby where the tables and chairs are, near the giant window &lt;br /&gt;

- if there is no line and the movie is downstairs, the group will meet in the 1st floor lobby near the refreshment stand&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry if that's complicated, but trust me it'll work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/4/6/event_112745702.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We'll head into the theater 20 minutes before showtime. Yes I know that's awfully early when you add it to the 10 to 20 minutes of previews, but hey, it'll give you a chance to talk to your neighbor!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I strongly advise buying tickets ahead of time on fandango.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, we gather outside the theater showing the film after the film ends. And then we go out for a discussion 'n' food 'n' beer. Or wine, or cocktails, according to your preference. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synopsis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In "Men in Black 3," Agents J (Will Smith) and K (Tommy Lee Jones) are back... in time. J has seen some inexplicable things in his 15 years with the Men in Black, but nothing, not even aliens, perplexes him as much as his wry, reticent partner. But when K's life and the fate of the planet are put at stake, Agent J will have to travel back in time to put things right. J discovers that there are secrets to the universe that K never told him -- secrets that will reveal themselves as he teams up with the young Agent K (Josh Brolin) to save his partner, the agency, and the future of humankind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailers 'n' Stuff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=54148"&gt;http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=54148&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See meetup description for how to find the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338169129000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335135488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Men In Black 3</name><id>61682522</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338067800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/61682522/</event_url></item>