<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>257 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 629 8717</phone><name>Diesel Cafe</name><city>Somerville</city><id>705077</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"The upper 1 percent of Americans are now taking in nearly a quarter of the nation’s income every year. In terms of wealth rather than income, the top 1 percent control 40 percent. Their lot in life has improved considerably."  -- Of the 1%, by the 1%, for the 1%, Vanity Fair&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;

"Well, an angry population and an angry populace could just as easily turn their anger toward the very rich. Again, it is in the interest of the people at the top to actually call for a more equitable distribution of the gains of economic growth and a better tax system: a tax system that is fair.". -Robert Reich, former secretary of labor.  &lt;br /&gt; 

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Is income inequality a problem?    What is fair? &lt;p&gt;How much should the rich be paying in taxes?  Do they pay their fair share?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What limits on the top income earners, is proper role for the federal gov't?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Should taxes be used solely to pay the cost of gov't, or should they also used to enact social policy related to income inequality issues?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;"We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable Rights, that among these are Life, Liberty and the pursuit of Happiness.".  -- U.S. Declaration of Independence.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Is one's pursuit of happiness diminished by how rich someone else is?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join us for a lively discussion of the super rich, taxation and fairness.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[event date subject to change]&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us at the large table in back</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1306078184000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304265411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Income inequality &amp; the pursuit of happiness</name><id>17498891</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305932400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/17498891/</event_url></item>