<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Across from Copley Sq.</address_2><address_1>545 Boylston St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>627-638-9699</phone><name>Vlora</name><city>Boston</city><id>895794</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Authentic Mediterranean cuisine - a cool place with superb food, a great wine list, all in a great atmosphere with excellent service.   Check out their website.  I had dinner here with another Meet-Up group a few months ago and was very impressed with Vlora.  This is truly a hidden gem.  You will not be disappointed.  Let's get togegther and enjoy a wonderful, moderately priced meal in a beautiful setting and celebrate the coming of spring with some fresh, clean tasting healthy food!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The chef will also be serving our group complimentary appetizers for our dinner on the 16th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“EAT BETTER, LIVE BETTER.” In the heart of Boston’s Back Bay, lives the soul of authentic Mediterranean cuisine. Vlora, named after Chef/Owner Aldo Velaj’s hometown in Albania, opened to the public in Fall 2007. With a menu brimming with old family recipes and unique versions of traditional favorites, Vlora embraces the true Mediterranean lifestyle. The dishes reflect the age-old adage of “eat better and live better.” Believing that food should taste like food, the natural tastes and flavors of the freshest ingredients are enhanced primarily with olive oil and fresh herbs. With an emphasis on freshness and a minimalist cooking style, the naturally healthy menu covers tastes from the Northern Mediterranean region encompassing Southern Italy, Greece, and Albania. The menu and wine list are an extension of the flavors and dishes served in Aldo’s own home, including exclusive hand-picked wines and lovingly prepared signature dishes that are unmatched in the city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there! &lt;a href="http://www.vloraboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vlorabosto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Private Dining room on first floor</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240144453000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Baby Boomers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun</urlname><id>1347228</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Baby Boomers Meetup Group-Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237855403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fabulous dinner at Vlora Boston         http://www.vloraboston.com</name><id>10020352</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239922800000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun/events/10020352/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/5/global_6792485.jpeg</photo_url></item>