<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ITS LOOKING REALLY FINE FOR THIS TRIP !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today: Mostly sunny, with a high near 74. West wind between 8 and 16 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight: Mostly cloudy, with a low around 43. West wind around 6 mph becoming calm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't Contacted Crabby Appelton at 1-800-553-RAFT(7238) i dont know if there is any openings left, Im paid up and a few others have, so those that are ready...See ya soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obviously this event WAS listed a few DAYS in advance but its one of the more unique events we will do this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes its the most costliest event i will ever list, but look at it this way..its only once every two years..&lt;br /&gt;so thats about 5 bucks a month in the SQUEEL LIKE A PYGGY BANK.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides we don't white water kayak, yet here we will enjoy the thrill of if and have a party after the event very simillar to  my events but its included in the total price.  The Barbie-Q will be held at the Ski Lodge afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Crabappel they are listing about 20 of us from meetup ???, some may be from another group but i didn't want to bug the people for the exact names and stuff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We figure out that later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK ITS TIME TO BOOK YOUR TRIP !!!!!  Call Crabby Appleton with the details below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TO BE WITH THE GROUP PLEASE MENTION YOU ARE WITH THE &amp;quot;REIGINS&amp;quot; GROUP.&lt;br /&gt;or thay stick you in any random boat, maybe with some toothless hillbillies hooten and hollerin for a Miss Piggy..&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; I CHOSE THE AFTERNOON TRIP (12:30 PM BUS to LEAVE to take  us to &amp;quot;DELIVERANCE RIVER&amp;quot; after our quick training lecture) *YOU MUST SIGN IN BEFORE THAT TIME OR THE BUS LEAVES you in the parking lot and you are left to paddle your own ass in shame*   Watch out for the guys with missing teeth, suspenders and shotguns waiting for the late Green Paddlers they will  focus on helping you in ways you don't want.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REMEBER: A GREAT &amp;quot;HILLBILLY&amp;quot;  (the kind you can eat with many missing teeth) MEAL IS INCLUDED AT THE END AND THEY HAVE SOME SNACKS ALONG THE WAY FOR US ALSO..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REMEMBER , This particular trip only happens on this one particular day at location once per year so its pretty well set unless there is no dam release. (Rain or Shine) You are going to get a little wet anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To me this is one of the most exciting active events i list for us and as you look back on the pics if you join us, you will remember your trip, i sure do with good memories.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the members of our boat from the last time:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/9/b/event_5709371.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event does fill up about  ONE  to TWO months in advance so keep that in mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will pay them directly (as i will and have) and they will send you confirmation info back via e mail and other info..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be the first to pay and reserve sometime in JULY to get things moving. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Over the past 3-4 years we have been going with Crabappel on these trips, this has been the more popular LOCATION and Rafting event (Vermont trip) than the previous trips i listed of the other local rafting trips in Mass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For pics of our last event here check out this link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CT-Recreational-Sea-Kayakers/photos/449036/5709375/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How do I make reservations?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speak with our friendly reservation staff at 1-800-553-RAFT(7238). The office is coordinated by Sharyn and Carrie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info will be posted closer to the necessary time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The sound of the Banjos AND GUYS THAT LOOK LIKE THEY ARE STILL IN THE DILLIVERANCE MOVIE SMILING IN WAITING along the river will keep you &amp;quot;paddling  faster&amp;quot; are you ready ???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}}&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;West River White Water Rafting in Vermont.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We raft the West River on scheduled dam releases provided by the Army Corpse* of Engineers.&lt;br /&gt;(* pronounciation taken from Obama's Teleprompter.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is an exciting trip not only in seeing the immense dam and its views of the landscape on both sides, but seeing the dam opening releasing our liquid highway of delight and frothing in raging fury for the trip down stream is exciting also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The West River offers a unique trip combining eight HUNDRED miles of continuous Class III intermediate action with some bigger whitewater in rapids such as &amp;quot;Tumbling Boulder Landslide&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The CHICKEN Dumplings&amp;quot; along the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We meet at our base camp for our trip at the Mount Snow Ski Resort (directions supplied in your reservation) and additional info if car pooling closer to the event week..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; At the end the Rafting trip on the river there will be a delicious cookout to talk and laugh about the enjoyable day and a slide show of the day's raft trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting Ready:&lt;br /&gt;We begin our trip by walking to the top of Ball Bearing Boulder Mountain Man Dam. Views from atop the dam are breathtaking and may make you wet your pants instantly as we look down at the first gut churning rapid and back across the full and rapidly draining reservoir at Stratton Mountain Ski Area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We then descend down to the river of the churning an deafening sound of frothing and boiling liquid hell, we will practice paddling for the upcoming action  in the practice area right before we enter The TUBE of Doom). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first half of the trip runs through beautiful Jamaica State Park (Rosta Farian Park) and includes a half-mile rapid called &amp;quot;Tumbling Boulder Landslide Splash&amp;quot; and the feature rapid of the day, &amp;quot;The Chicken Dumplings&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Chicken Dumplings&amp;quot; will make you dump out anything you ate 3 days before LOL..its is a tight S-turn where strong team paddling is necessary to avoid giant boulders the size of Crashed Grey Hound Busses with jagged sharp edges ready to rip off your face and pierce you guts spilling then into the piranha filled water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its like being on the super highway going 70 miles per hour avoiding things  BOULDERS the size of trailer trucks and greyhound busses BUT hitting the biggest waves you ever seen maybe even going over the top of them too if you didn't paddle hard enough to avoid em. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dilliverance Men are waiting on the shore here and mostly along the way with lassos (im sure to help you) , whatever you do ..don't make any oinking sounds .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a quick snack on what we find uneaten in the water or river bank, (usually some mangled body parts) the second half of the trip has several more Class II-III rapids like &amp;quot;Tornado Gut Rip and Fling em on the bank Alley&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;The Naked Beach Ledges&amp;quot; and works back toward our base camp at Mount Snow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wild Wild West River has an unbeatable combination of action and scenery which is universally loved by both veteran and new rafters. Check out the Photo Gallery on the Crabby Appleton website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Trip Overview:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miles: 8&lt;br /&gt;Trip time: Full day&lt;br /&gt;Minimum Age: 12   &amp;lt;~~~~~~~~ if its ok for snot faced kids its ok for you...&lt;br /&gt;Food: Cookout at base after trip&lt;br /&gt;No. of people per boat: 6 - 8&lt;br /&gt;Rapid Classification: Class II-IV&lt;br /&gt;Digital Slide Presentation from &amp;quot;Falling Boulder Landslide&amp;quot; rapid&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;West River Prices and Schedule:  OK NOT THE CHEAP STUFF I TRY TO ALWAYS post..BUT ITS ONCE EVERY OTHER YEAR OR SO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rafting Price:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adults $100pp &lt;br /&gt;Children 12-15 $83pp&lt;br /&gt;Group Rates  for groups of 12 or more&lt;br /&gt;Schedule:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 25, 2010        APX. 12:OO PM MEET  IN THE LODGE, 12:30 MAKE SURE YOU ARE CHECKED IN.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event includes a Pre-trip safety instruction of paddling techniques, safety procedures, professional guide, ( Maybe even one of the Owners)  a proper PFD and helmet are supplied.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update you on if you need any other PADDLING clothes based on water conditions, (HAVE A NICE SET OF dry COMFORT CLOTHES FOR THE BARBIE-Q LATER) but last year it was warm so only a simple wetsuit was all that was needed and they rent those to you if you need it, they also have the latest data and will recommend or simply indicate ya don't need it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(last time i had short sleeve shirt  on and hiking pants)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The transportation to and from river PUT IN AND TAKE OUT, ENDING WITH A cookout at Mt Snow after trip (chicken, fish or vegetarian option), photo presentation of your adventure are also included in the package Deal. (yeah ya have to buy the pics if ya want them but we dont buy em ---- we may take our own)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR EXTRA INFO FROM THE SOURCE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crabapplewhitewater.com/vermont/index.shtml"&gt;http://www.crabapplew...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS: use Mount Snow Sundance Base Lodge at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; x Pisgah Rd; West Dover VT 05356&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;Follow I-91 North to Exit #2 in VERMONT. &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 West for 20 miles to Wilmington, VT. &lt;br /&gt;Turn right at the stoplight on to Route 100 North. &lt;br /&gt;Go Nine miles to Mount Snow/Haystack area. &lt;br /&gt;Turn left into Mount Snow Resort. &lt;br /&gt;Follow the signs to Sundance Base Lodge and Crab Apple Whitewater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its apx 100 miles @ apx 2 hours drive time depending on your particular route or speed.&lt;br /&gt;Hit the road about 10:00, go slow, and get something to eat on the way, we were early last time.&lt;br /&gt;Rather be early than late...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I AM PAID UP SO THE RESERVATIONS ARE UP TO YOU INDIVIDUALLY TO PAY UP..ETC..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Al-r &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crab Apple Whitewater, Inc. &lt;br /&gt;1-800-553-RAFT(7238) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activities FROM DATE TO DATE ACTIVITY DESCRIPTION CHARGES &lt;br /&gt;09/25/2010  WEST RIVER  VERMONT&lt;br /&gt;12:30PM&lt;br /&gt;Includes HOT BUFF-A  LUNCH   with the Dilliverance men Porking around back and doing the cooking..after the paddling event on 09/25/2010 --- 2 ADULT @ 100.00  = 200.00 &lt;br /&gt; Activities Total 200.00 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok see ya soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the staff at the check in desk for the Reigins Party or look for the ORANGE hunting Hat...in the Mt Snow Ski Lodge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285538213000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262536514000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SEPT 25 --&gt; PADDLE FASTER - I HEAR BANJOS on the DELIVERANCE  RIVER Expedition </name><id>12205657</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285430400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/12205657/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/c/global_3264476.jpeg</photo_url></item>