<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a movie for all of us who are interested in (or obsessed with) food.  It's  Pennebaker documentary, so it's sure to be intriguing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It starts at 3:10 at the Coolidge.  I'll be outside the theater (or inside, depending on the weather) from 2:50 to 3:00 - then I'll be in the theater making sure we have good seats in the center.  It's the only time on Sunday the movie is showing and it's supposed to be a windy day, so get your tickets in advance as it may sell out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we'll go to the restaurant of our choice.  Who knows what we'll feel like eating after the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Imagine a scene never before witnessed: Sixteen French pastry chefs gathered in Lyon for three intense days of mixing, piping and sculpting everything from delicate chocolates to six-foot sugar sculptures in hopes of being declared by President Nicolas Sarkozy one of the best. This is the prestigious Meilleurs Ouvriers de France competition (Best Craftsmen in France). The blue, white and red striped collar worn&lt;br /&gt;on the jackets of the winners is more than the&lt;br /&gt;ultimate recognition for every pastry chef –&lt;br /&gt;it is a dream and an obsession.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Filmmakers D A Pennebaker and Chris Hegedus secured exclusive access to shoot this epic, never-before-filmed test of France’s finest artisans. The film follows chef Jacquy Pfeiffer, co-founder of Chicago’s French Pastry School, as he journeys back to his childhood home of Alsace to practice for the contest. Two other finalists are profiled in the film — chef Regis Lazard, who was competing for the second time (he dropped his sugar sculpture the first time), and chef Philippe Rigollot, from Maison Pic, France’s only three-star restaurant owned by a woman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   During the grueling final competition, chefs work under constant scrutiny by master judges and the critical palates of some of the world’s most renowned chefs evaluate their elaborate pastries. Finally, these pastry marathoners racing the clock must hand carry all their creations including their fragile sugar sculptures through a series of rooms to a final buffet area without shattering them. The film captures the high-stakes drama of the competition – passion, sacrifice, disappointment, and joy – in the quest to become one of the KINGS OF PASTRY.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside from 2:50 - 3:00 - then in the theater</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287070188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kings of Pastry at the Coolidge at 3:10 pm</name><id>15108355</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287342000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15108355/</event_url></item>