<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Brattle is doing their annual pre-Valentine screening of romantic movies and two Audrey Hepburn classics are being featured. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Roman Holiday begins at 1, followed by Sabrina at 3:30. Please note which films you plan to attend when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, we'll head off to a local eatery for dinner and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Roman Holiday:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Mr. Wyler and his associates have fashioned a natural, tender, and amusing yarn about the heiress to the throne of a mythical kingdom who is sick unto death of an unending schedule of speeches, greetings, and interviews attendant on her goodwill tour...&amp;quot; - A.H. Weiler, New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The film itself is a classic of romantic wish fulfillment, exactly the sort of beautiful lie that Hollywood specialized in.&amp;quot; - Ty Burr&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This was the first major film starring Audrey Hepburn, the film that made her a star, an Oscar winner and (for many) a cultural icon. Gregory Peck, however, is also great in his role as an American journalist who discovers a princess-in-hiding (played by Hepburn). This film has a 98% rating on Rotten Tomatoes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sabrina&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It is a story as light as a feather and as old as yesterday's news, as transparent as a society column item and as smug as a foreign-made car. But Mr. Wilder...has made it into a commentary as crisp as a screed in a smart magazine.&amp;quot; - Bosley Crowther, New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Billy Wilder directed film (not the Harrison Ford rip-off) depicts a love triangle between a chauffeur's daughter and two wealthy brothers (played by Humphrey Bogart and William Holden). This film has a 93% rating on Rotten Tomatoes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a sign in front of the theater at the end of the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233017568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Audrey Hepburn Double Feature: Sabrina &amp; Roman Holiday</name><id>9607912</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234116000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9607912/</event_url></item>