<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Duck! Fried rice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh, wait... Sorry, false alarm, everybody. It says &amp;quot;duck fried rice&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's that? You've never heard of duck fried rice? Well, how about salmon terriyaki? Maybe Mango with Sticky Rice for dessert?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If all of these exotic names leave you feeling a bit at sea, don't worry - there's help! It's called &amp;quot;Ingestion Therapy&amp;quot;; sometimes described simply as &amp;quot;Try it! You'll like it!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be doing just that at Wild Ginger in Norwell at 5:30 PM on Sunday, July 12th. Located a stone's throw from Queen Anne's Corner in the space formerly occupied by Cherrywoods Barbeque, Wild Ginger opened last year to enthusiastic reviews (including one for the Patriot Ledger by &lt;a href="http://www.wildgingerthai.net/" target="_blank"&gt;Christine Ordway&lt;/a&gt;) and has also been highly recommended to Mike by trusted dining friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this Thai restaurant occupies a small space and we are limiting attendance to 10 diners. We are anticipating a fun, intimate evening of shared conversation and more than likely some shared food as we explore a largely unfamiliar cuisine. Please take a look at the review linked above, as well as the online menu on their website, then plan to join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wild Ginger&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;124 Washington St. (Route 53), Norwell&lt;br /&gt;(781) 347-4702&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wildgingerthai.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wildginger...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maximum number of attendees:&lt;/b&gt; 10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Moderate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; No Event Fee for current Annual Members. Other Members and Guests: $2.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Saturday, July 11 @ 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Wild Ginger is on Washington Street (Route 53) in Norwell, just south of Queen Anne's Corner. To reach it from Route 3, get off at Exit 14 (Route 228) and head North on Rt 228 towards Hingham/Nantasket and Route 53.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will bring you to a busy intersection at a traffic light (Queen Anne's Corner). Go right (south) onto Route 53, keeping the mall where Hannaford's Supermarket is located to your right. You will quickly pass the now-closed 53 South (another restaurant) on your right, and shortly thereafter Hight St will bear off to the right, at which point you need to be careful to keep going straight and remain on Route 53. Just after High St you will pass Marsh's Liquor Store on your right. The next businesses on your right are in a small strip mall. Wild Ginger is in the building farthest to the left in this mall.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Small restaurant - you'll probably see us! Or just ask for the Meetup table!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248907379000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246333445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wild Ginger! Let's Thai it!</name><id>10766831</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247434200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10766831/</event_url></item>