<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hike Mount Greylock – Saturday, May 4th, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 Rain Date – Saturday, May 11th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: There is a campground located 2.2 miles along the trail.  People who want to try the hike, but feel they may not make the summit, can rest/eat at the campground and either return to the parking lot or wait for those who continue for the trip back to the cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join a group of people – some you may know, some not – hiking Mt. Greylock on Saturday, May 4th, leaving the Worcester area at 7 a.m. in order to start the hike at 9 a.m. leaving from the base on Hopper Road. This hike is being coordinated by Lothar Franke – he can be reached at RJLark@aol.com. He can take two additional passengers and will try to coordinate rides.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be hiking the Hopper trail to the summit. It’s an 8 mile round trip and takes ~ 6 hours. We will stop for lunch on the summit and return to the base at ~ 4 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website describes the trail as strenuous, although Lothar would describe it more as moderate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather is extremely variable from year to year. In the past there has been snow/ice on the trail and windy/cold at the summit; another time it was so hot that we wanted shorts. We will be checking the forecast towards the end of the week to determine if there is a significant chance of rain – if so, we will need to change the date to May 11th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need: &lt;br /&gt;

 Cold weather clothing – hats, gloves, windbreaker, hiking boots. YakTrax or Microspikes if you have them – ice is usually minimal. &lt;br /&gt;

 Trail Map – can be printed from the website &lt;br /&gt;

 Food &amp;amp; Water &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunscreen – in the past, the leaves are not out on the trees and the sun can be intense&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to The Mount Greylock website, which has maps and trail lengths as well as a weather link: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/mtGreylock/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/mtGreylock/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn Franke</member_name><member_id>10837891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367699693000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367074387000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mount Greylock - Saturday May 4th</name><id>116464412</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>34200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367665200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/116464412/</event_url></item>