<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Fun&amp;quot; isn't a word you hear applied to most documentaries. Usually it's a category reserved for comedies, but after watching the preview for this film before Army of Shadows, a lot of group members were smiling and laughing at the promo. Hopefully, that's the preview is an indicator of how good this film will be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, April 22&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Area Theatrical Premiere!&lt;br /&gt;Air Guitar Nation at 3:30, 5:30, 7:30, 9:30&lt;br /&gt;(2006) dir Alexandra Lipsitz [81 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A battle of naked ambition played out on the national and, ultimately, world stage, AIR GUITAR NATION chronicles the birth of the U.S. Air Guitar Championships as legions of aspiring rock stars live out their dreams on a quest to become the world champion in a strange world where musical ability plays second fiddle to virtual virtuosity. As the film un-reels, two aspiring rock legends strum and strut their way towards glory and the coveted national title. C. Diddy , a samurai warrior clad in a Hello Kitty breastplate and red kimono, emerges as an early favorite. But his arch nemesis from the Lower East Side, Björn Türoque, is not far behind. While C. Diddy threatens to unleash his self-professed &amp;quot;Asian Fury'' on his competitors, Björn vows to take Diddy down. As the film reaches its climax, the future of Air hangs in the balance; will Björn's technical prowess, stage presence, and ?airness' be enough to take him to the top, or will C. Diddy conquer all to become America's first supreme being of Air Guitar? Full of triumph and disappointment, patriotic spirit and political tension - and, of course, invisible guitars - AIR GUITAR NATION take audiences on an inspiring, exhilarating, and ultimately hilarious journey that delves deep to find out what it truly takes to become the best in the world and find the inner meaning of the chant, &amp;quot;Make Air, Not War.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner, Audience Award, SXSW Film Festival &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of the most fun documentaries I suspect will ever be seen.&amp;quot; - Ain't It Cool News &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film will be hosted by Nicole, your friendly Meetup Assistant organizer, who will be holding a Meetup sign at the front of the Brattle after the film gets out. Afterward, we will go to a local cafe restaurant for dinner and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177419996000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176650053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Funnest Documentary You'll Ever See? - Air Guitar Nation</name><id>5672126</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177183800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5672126/</event_url></item>