<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>coliseum ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.762794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>mine falls </name><city>Nashua</city><id>1497739</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.497437</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Easy Hike Mine Falls&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday Dec. 2nd. 1 pm. to 3ish pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mine Falls Coliseum Ave. Nashua, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962  ob@tds.net &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT!   THIS IS A DOG &amp;amp; CHILD FRIENDLY EVENT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at anytime. If you can make it at 1 pm.?  I will have my phone on, and the trails crisscross each other. This it an easy hike on the trails at Mine Falls Park in Nashua. Please &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/b/6/event_183692182.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/0/8/event_164046152.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;know this is not a race. My intent is to enjoy the views of the area, and to chat along the way. This event is meant more to have fun than to get a good workout. I thought that we would enjoy nature for about two or three hours, with a few breaks/stops along the trail. This park is just full of beautiful views and history. So, come and enjoy some fresh air, beautiful views, and all this while in good company of new and old friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 1:00 pm in the lot at the end of Coliseum Ave, which is off of Rte 130 in Nashua. Steve Ob1. will be doing the introductions at that time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: Take exit 6 from Route 3 (Route 130) and go west towards Brookline, take the second entrance to the shopping center area (Colliseum Ave), go all the way to the end of the road for the parking lot. Look for the meetup sign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring plenty of fluids and to dress in layers so that you will be comfortable the whole time we are out on the trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone cares to, we can then go grab a bite to eat or enjoy a drink or hot chocolate, at a nearby restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354482668000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354217925000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Hiking Mine Falls</name><id>93367232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354471200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/93367232/</event_url></item>