<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a dance movie, about choreographer Pina Bausch.&amp;nbsp; The movie has won many, many European awards and I'm delighted it will be shown here.&amp;nbsp; The movie begins at 5:25.&amp;nbsp; I'll be waiting by the ticket booth from 4:45 until 4:55.&amp;nbsp; At 4:55 I will go in.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Will meet you after directly outside the doors of the theater where Pina is showing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is one of the reviews:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens when a celebration is transformed, by awful necessity, into a memorial?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://artsfuse.org/?attachment_id=48278"&gt;&lt;img src="http://artsfuse.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/pina-1.jpg" width="350" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A scene from PINA, a documentary directed by Wim Wenders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;German filmmaker Wim Wenders had been discussing a collaborative project with his friend, choreographer Pina Bausch, for&amp;nbsp;20 years. She regularly teased him about how procrastination and competing offers were burying his good intentions. It was one of those &amp;ldquo;one day we&amp;rsquo;ll do it&amp;rdquo; dreams&amp;mdash;we all have them&amp;mdash;that never seemed to get off the ground.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, in 2007, Wenders caught a screening of the 3-D concert &lt;a href="http://www.u23dmovie.com/"&gt;film&lt;/a&gt; made by the rock band U2. Wenders would later say that he was elated. Finally, here were the tools he felt he needed to do justice to Bausch&amp;rsquo;s work. The two artists mapped out a proposed repertory and scouted for locations&amp;mdash;German theaters, windowed galleries, urban traffic circles shadowed by monorail lines, the edge of an open pit with a long view to the horizon&amp;mdash;and scheduled a shoot featuring the dancers of Tanztheater Wuppertal, which Bausch had led since 1973.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just two days before the rehearsal shoot, the 68-year-old Bausch was told by her doctors she had cancer. Five days later, she was dead. Wenders&amp;rsquo;s first impulse was to scrap the project until, encouraged by her family and her dancers, he reversed his decision. Dance and film lovers alike can be glad he did.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1440266/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pina&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; depicts not merely the repertory of one of Europe&amp;rsquo;s most important dance artists but a provocative, influential, and still-controversial sensibility. Standing at the crossroads of &amp;ldquo;raw,&amp;rdquo; lived experience and Bausch&amp;rsquo;s artful exhibitionism, Wenders has been able to expose how Bausch transmuted soil, water, and the sweat of both young and aging bodies into a series of unrelenting metaphors for desire, despair, and most often, the type of loss that renders a human being shell-shocked.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There are moments,&amp;rdquo; Victor Hugo wrote in &lt;em&gt;Les Miserables&lt;/em&gt;, &amp;ldquo;when, whatever the posture of the body, the soul is on its knees.&amp;rdquo; Pina Bausch&amp;rsquo;s dance articulates its dystopian language from that spiritually abject position. To me, her expressionism carries within it the erotics of the Austrian painter Egon Schiele, clinical in its voyeuristic empiricism while defaulting to passivity in the face of molestation and social demands.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a dancer, Pina Bausch was the presiding spirit of speechlessness. She had the macabre body of an anorexic, but her matchstick arms communicated entire inner worlds. &lt;em&gt;Caf&amp;eacute; Muller&lt;/em&gt;, the bleak 1978 work that takes center stage in Wender&amp;rsquo;s documentary, is a case in point. Some critics have asserted that &lt;em&gt;Caf&amp;eacute; Muller&lt;/em&gt; is a meditation on Bausch&amp;rsquo;s childhood: her parents ran a restaurant attached to a small hotel, and as a girl, Pina used to sit under the tables spying on the customers and, occasionally, entertaining them. If you think you&amp;rsquo;ve seen &lt;em&gt;Caf&amp;eacute; Muller&lt;/em&gt; before, you&amp;rsquo;re probably right. Excerpts were used in Pedro Almoldovar&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xk57w_pina-bausch-parle-avec-elle_news"&gt;Talk to Her&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (2002), and the choreography has spawned many imitations, especially among performance artists with a taste for European pessimism.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wenders has taken the opportunity to blend archival footage of Bausch&amp;rsquo;s own performance in &lt;em&gt;Caf&amp;eacute; Muller&lt;/em&gt; with vibrant performances by members of her troupe. She dances with her eyes closed as a man rushes to knock chairs and tables out of her path. In the film&amp;rsquo;s context, Bausch&amp;rsquo;s sleepwalking, set to Henry Purcell&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Dido&amp;rsquo;s Lament&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;&amp;ldquo;when I am laid to rest in earth/may my soul create/no trouble in thy breast&amp;rdquo;&amp;ndash;-truly seems to rise from beyond the grave.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting by the ticket purchasing location 30 minutes before the movie begins.  Movie starts at 5:25</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327294776000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325624372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wim Wenders 3D movie:  Pina</name><id>46496512</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327184100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/46496512/</event_url></item>