<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 Oxford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.378357</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Museum of Natural History</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692976</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116480</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Gallery Talk:&lt;/b&gt;The Best Fossils Darwin Never Saw &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speaker:&lt;/b&gt; Ben Kotrc &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;7:00 pm, Free with admission to museum&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Harvard Museum of Natural History:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/lectures_and_special_events/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The fossil record brought up many questions for Charles Darwin: Why did animal fossils appear so suddenly in the Cambrian Explosion? Where were all the transitional animals? In this gallery talk with Harvard earth and planetary sciences graduate student Ben Kotrc, explore the museum’s diverse range of fossil specimens, from the giant Ice Age mammals, which Darwin saw, to ancient microfossils discovered in recent decades&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting inside the museum. Just go through the front entrance, up the stairs, and off to the right, T.J. Maher will be assembling people. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair spiked in the front, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. He'll be there by 6:20 pm. We can head in at 6:30 pm to wander around before the gallery talk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Care to grab a bite to eat beforehand?&lt;/u&gt; T.J. will be in &lt;b&gt;The Garage&lt;/b&gt; lower level food court at 36 JFK St in Harvard Square from 5:30 pm to 6:15 pm. They have a Subway sub shop, Flat Patties where you can get a greasy burger, and a Taqueria where you can get tacos. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Care to grab a beer after&lt;/u&gt;? Personally, I love &lt;b&gt;John Harvard's Brew House&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.johnharvards.com/index.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.johnharva...&lt;/a&gt; at 33 Dunster Street, Cambridge, MA. We can grab a few pitchers and sample what they have in stock that day. We can wander around the museum until 8:00 pm or so, then head out to John Harvard's after. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Summer Nights at the Harvard Museum of Natural History:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join us for extended hours on three Thursday nights this summer to explore the galleries and participate in special programs. The museum will offer half-price admission (and a 15% discount in the Museum Shop) from 5:00 to 8:00 pm on the third Thursday in June, July, and August. Each night will feature a special talk in the museum’s galleries, highlighting EVOLUTION, a new permanent exhibition&amp;quot;. &lt;i&gt;Thursdays, June 18, July 16, August 20, 5:00 - 8:00 PM&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the EVOLUTION exhibit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/exhibits/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;EVOLUTION invites visitors to examine the fossil, anatomical and genetic evidence that all life is connected through a shared evolutionary history. View animals and plants that sparked Darwin’s theory, dramatic displays of diversity within species, and computer simulations that demonstrate how natural selection acts. EVOLUTION offers behind-the-scenes looks at ongoing evolution research at Harvard from exciting new discoveries about human origins to surprising insights from new genetic and developmental studies on Darwin's Finches&amp;quot;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Glass Flowers exhibit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/exhibits/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of the Museum’s most famous treasures is the internationally acclaimed Ware Collection of Blaschka Glass Models of Plants, the 'Glass Flowers.' This unique collection of over 4,000 models—some 3,000 on display—was  created by the glass artisans, Leopold Blaschka and his son, Rudolph. The commission began in 1886, continued for five decades, and represents more than 830 plant species&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Ben Kotrc:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fas.harvard.edu/~knollgrp/people.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fas.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Ben hails from Vienna, Austria. He has an undergraduate degree in geology from Imperial College, London, and a master's degree in paleobiology from the University of Bristol. He has worked on the Paleocene/Eocene Thermal Maximum in the North Sea, during a brief stint working for Shell, and on the Cenozoic evolution of size and silica use in Radiolaria while in Bristol. He carried out field work for his undergraduate thesis in the Precambrian Mozambique Orogenic Belt in the Samburu District, Kenya. His research interests are broad-ranging and include, but are not limited to, the interaction and coevolution of the biological and geological earth systems over time, evolution and biogeochemical cycles, macroecology, complexity, computer modeling and the evolutionary history of marine plankton&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>24</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257958091000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245083992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August's Summer Nights - Half Price Tickets @ Harvard Museum of Natural History </name><id>10655390</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250807400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/10655390/</event_url></item>