<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>160 Lincoln Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.413826</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lincoln Commuter Rail Station</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>669235</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.326610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This walk is for those who enjoy a fast paced walk.  If you were on the July 29th Broadmoor Walk you will do fine!  Sunset for this walk is exactly at 8:00.  Twilight will last until about 8:30 and the walk should be completed around 8:10.  In other words, the end of the hike will be at twilight and perhaps in the dark.  If you bring a flashlight you will be fine.  I actually find this time of day to be the most beautiful and peaceful.  For those up for the adventure it should be a great experience.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 5:30 and begin walking at 5:40.  There will still be plenty of daylight to enjoy.  We will be getting plenty of sun as the first part of the walk is mostly through fields and farmland heading west right into the sun!  From the train station we will walk through fields, then the Codman Estate, then an active farm that the public is welcome to walk through, then the Walden Woods, then the southern portion of Walden Pond, then a steep climb up Pine Hill.  Through this portion of the walk daylight won’t be an issue.  The remainder of the walk goes through a beautiful deciduous forest (sometime during this portion it will change from daylight to twilight) and the last 5 minutes goes through another field.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet at the Lincoln Commuter Rail station at 5:30PM. I can give people a ride back to Alewife or Riverside after the walk. Parking is available. The walk will be inspiring, beautiful and fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281026713000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Walkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Evening-Walkers</urlname><id>865474</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Evening Walkers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280463190000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploring Lincoln and Walden Pond - Fast Paced Workout and Beautiful Walk </name><id>14260611</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280957400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Evening-Walkers/events/14260611/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/a/global_8188554.jpeg</photo_url></item>