<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>After doing an amazing job explaining to us about the Enneagram of Personality, Myers-Briggs, and Astrology, Herb Pearce will teach us about Eckhart Tolle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description of the workshop from Herb:  “Learn about Eckhart Tolle's perspective and keys on enlightenment. Learn about the tradition of advaita vedanta (Eckhart Tolle's background), which comes from a Hindu mystic tradition. Part of the evening will be a traditional spiritual satsang which includes meditation, the teacher speaking from a more conscious state, followed by questions. Herb will highlight and summarize all of Eckhart's Tolle spiritual freedom ideas.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it. Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit of 30 has been set. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce ****** &lt;br /&gt;Besides being a teacher of the Enneagram and Myers-Briggs, Herb has been an active student of advaita vedanta (Eckard Tolle's background) for over 10 years, has attended many spiritual satsangs with numerous teachers and has been a student of a spiritually conscious teacher for well over a year and a half on a weekly basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241221739000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236880345000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eckhart Tolle </name><id>9940456</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240614000000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/9940456/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/e/a/global_7649354.jpeg</photo_url></item>