<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>4th Floor</address_2><address_1>595 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.349350</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BU SMG Colloquium Room</name><city>Boston</city><id>441156</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Luce Program in Scripture and Literary Arts at Boston University is pleased to present an evening with Rosanna Warren, University Professor, Emma Ann MacLachlan Metcalf Professor of the Humanities,  and Professor of English and Romance Studies at Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Professor Warren will read her own poetry, as well as the work of other writers that has inspired her as a writer and a teacher. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;She is the author of four collections of poetry: Snow Day (1981), Each Leaf Shines Separate (1985), Stained Glass: Poems (1994), and Departure: Poems (2003).  She is also the editor of The Art of Translation: Voices From the Field (1989), to which she was a contributor; a translation of Euripides' Suppliant Women (with Stephen Scully, 1995); two volumes of William Arrowsmith's translation of the poems of Eugenio Montale (Cuttlefish Bones, 1992 and Satura 1998); three anthologies of verse by prison inmates (In Time with Teresa Iverson, 1995; From This Distance with Meg Tyler, 1996; and Springshine with Meg Tyler, 1998). Professor Warren was elected to the American Academy of Arts and Sciences in 1997, and the American Academy of Arts and Letters in 2004; from 1999 to 2005 she was a Chancellor of the American Academy of Poets.  In 2004 Professor Warren received the Boston University Metcalf Award for Excellence in Teaching.  She has been teaching at Boston University since 1982.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This reading is free and open to the public, and will be followed by a light reception.  For more information visit www.bu.edu/luce or contact Cristine Hutchison-Jones at crissy@bu.edu or 617-358-1754. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196550189000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196274221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening with Rosanna</name><id>6819396</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196377200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/6819396/</event_url></item>