<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>177 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.405438</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-686-6080</phone><name>DrumConnection</name><city>Arlington</city><id>1904081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.141810</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/9/2/event_9674738.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/AfricaTravel/about"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/AfricaTravel/about&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip to Guinea, Africa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For all those interested in learning about our Trip to Guinea in November 2013 with Mamady Kourouma, Sire Diallo Konate and more, come Saturday, March 2, 2013. With slides and uplifting discussion, we will give you a lot of insight into what will happen on a trip like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will hear and see all of the experiences of trips past and how we do what we do! You will be impressed and we hope you will eventually join us on this trip. Perfect for educators, students, musicians and non-musicians. Refreshments will be served.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at DrumConnection, 177 Mass Ave., Arlington, MA location. We start at 6PM. Plan on a 1.5 to 2 hour event! FREE Hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In rhythm spirit, Alan Tauber, Director&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.triptoafrica.org"&gt;http://www.triptoafrica.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DrumConnection 781.316.8068&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By car:&lt;/strong&gt; You can easily find us about 0.5 mile from the Rt 16 intersection at Mass Ave where Cambridge becomes Arlington. Across from Lake Street (off Rt 2) and the Capital Theater. Directly across from the great restaurant, Flora.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Parking&lt;/strong&gt;: 2 hour free parking right outside our door on either side of Mass Ave. No spaces? Try a right-hand turn onto Winter St. and park on the Right. Or take Winter to the end, a Right on Broadway and your 1st Right onto Cleveland St. Go near the Mass Ave end and park on the Right or Left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Secret spots!&lt;/strong&gt; Across the street from DrumConnection is Cambridge Savings Bank and a parking lot. You can park there till 9:30PM. Easy. There are other side streets and more parking on the Quebrada Bakery, Capital Theater side of Mass Ave. More secret parking as we find it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;By MBTA:&lt;/strong&gt; Take the Red Line to Alewife (the West end of the line). Walk the bike path to Thorndike Street and walk up Thorndike to Mass Ave. Take a Left onto Mass Ave and we are up on the Right about 4 blocks. Takes 13 minutes to walk and feels good! &lt;br /&gt;

 Or grab a bus from Alewife or Harvard Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;MBTA buses:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#77 (Mass Ave/Winter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#79 (Mass Ave/Winter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#350 (Mass Ave/Winter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#87 (Broadway/Winter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We hope to see you here at the DrumRoom at DrumConnection!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alan</member_name><member_id>1328052</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363499479000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Africa Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>AfricaTravel</urlname><id>1300355</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Africa Travel Group! Learn Drumming &amp; Dance in Guinea!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359275642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trip to Guinea! Drum, Dance and Sing this November 18, 2013!</name><id>101584882</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362261600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/AfricaTravel/events/101584882/</event_url></item>