<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51-14 Shunpike Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.616239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.635.1860 </phone><name>Rookies AKA Chicago Sams</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>881749</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.675053</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;This will be a very HIGH ENERGY Rock n Roll Fun night&lt;/span&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no &amp;quot;typical&amp;quot; Amish Outlaws show, but the average crowd can expect to see men in full Amish garb releasing all of their pent up energy with an infectious joy. With a set that is always evolving as the Brothers discover more and more music and culture, The Amish Outlaws constantly surprise the audience and keep them guessing as to what they could possibly play next, from Judas Priest to Jay Z, Neil Diamond to Snopp Dogg and Dr. Dre, Queen and Twisted Sister, to theme songs from the TV shows they have come to know. Throughout, The Outlaws spin yarns about the Brothers' upbringing and adventures since Rumpsringa. Amish Outlaw gigs are less performances than they are initiations into the life of an Amish Outlaw and parties celebrating the Brothers’ newfound freedom. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amishoutlaws.com/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to check out the Amish Outlaws.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rookies is a sports bar casual attire!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking for great food, great live entertainment, pool, games, special acts, special promos, giveaways…. and a great time? Come to Rookies! We have a 120 foot bar with over 30 seasonally-changing different beers and hard ciders on tap, a great menu with over 90 delicious items, 70 TVs (15 Big Screens), 7 nights a week of entertainment and 10,000SF of pure enjoyment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’re not just your ordinary hangout. We strive, daily, to make your visit to Rookies a great time… plain and simple. Stop by and see for yourself! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rookiesct.com/site/" target="_blank"&gt;Click Here to check out Rookies.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find us right near the band dance floor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292300605000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286213527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Amish Outlaws @ Rookies Sports Bar</name><id>14996174</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292121000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/14996174/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/0/global_11521968.jpeg</photo_url></item>