<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Southbridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.253700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miss Worcester Diner</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1199511</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.806300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Worcester Photo Studios will be taking over the famous Miss Worcester Diner for an exclusive pin-up style photo shoot. &lt;br /&gt;

 We've been dying to shoot here and now we finally have the opportunity to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your own setup or use some of ours. We plan to bring minimal equipment to this event because of space limitations. &lt;br /&gt;

 Models, please meet at 90 May Street, Worcester MA before the shoot so we can do a quick overview and also you will be able to get your hair and makeup ready as well as change into any outfits. At 1:45 or so we will head down to Miss Worcester to start setting up and shooting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reserve your spot for this shoot today, space is limited so make sure to pre pay. Pre-registration is required for Photographers. Cost: $40 for photographers, $20 for Studio Members. Payments through PayPal: payment@worcesterphotostudios.com. Reference Miss Worcester Diner Shoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are able to take up to a dozen models for this shoot, models for this event come for free. Bring your own props and maybe some to share. Make sure to wear something snazzy, navy uniforms, polka dotted dresses, blue collar outfits and aprons or anything else creative you can bring to the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So hope to see all of you very soon for a very memorable shoot at a New England landmark.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351980479000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348088227000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Miss Worcester Diner Shoot</name><id>83166612</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351965600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/83166612/</event_url></item>