<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>02114</address_2><address_1>215 Charles Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.361607</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>http://www.alibiboston.com/</phone><name>Alibi at the Liberty Hotel</name><city>Boston</city><id>513121</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Freed after work? Hang out at the Liberty Hotel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gather where Boston once locked up its most notorious prisoners at an event sponsored by the BSA Young Professionals Network (YPNet). Network with other young professionals and enjoy drinks in the iron-clad Alibi bar followed by a virtual and self-guided tour of the new &lt;a href="http://www.libertyhotel.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Liberty Hotel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jail was built in 1851 in the Boston Granite style by architect Gridley James Fox Bryant in collaboration with penologist and prison-reform advocate Rev. Louis Dwight. Shaped like a cross, the granite structure housed 220 inmate cells. After a 5-year, $150 million renovation, the decrepit jail has been transformed from a facility once unfit for prisoners to one providing four-star luxury accommodations as the Liberty Hotel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.c7a.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Cambridge Seven Associates&lt;/a&gt; worked with &lt;a href="http://www.annbeha.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ann Beha Architects&lt;/a&gt; and a number of historians and conservationists during the restoration to ensure that historically significant portions of the building remained intact. This National Historic Landmark retains the 90-foot central atrium, granite exterior, and even Bryant?s original vision of a dramatic cupola.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will congregate in the &lt;a href="http://www.alibiboston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Alibi bar&lt;/a&gt; (the former drunk tank) for networking and drinks--with light fare provided and a cash bar. Following a virtual tour led by Gary Johnson AIA of Cambridge Seven Associates, you can take a self-guided tour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP at &lt;a href="http://www.architects.org/meetup" target="_blank"&gt;www.architects.org/meetup&lt;/a&gt; or to &lt;a href="http://bsa@architects.org" target="_blank"&gt;bsa@architects.org&lt;/a&gt; or 617-951-1433 x221 by March 7 at 5:00 pm. Seats are going fast for this free meetup!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Moser-Booth</member_name><member_id>6447986</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205512156000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>29</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>145</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202399785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BSA YPNet Social and Virtual Tour of the Liberty Hotel</name><id>7283689</id><headcount>145</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205271000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/7283689/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/f/global_3163247.jpeg</photo_url></item>