<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the third anniversary of this group, so I&amp;rsquo;ve scheduled a variation of our first meeting,&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Is Philosophy 'A Kind of Involuntary and Unconscious Memoir?' &amp;ndash; Nietzsche.&amp;rdquo;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I thought that it was a great topic then, and I still do!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this meeting, we will broaden the topic which was described last time around as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Is philosophy an articulation of subconscious motives? If this is the case, is all of philosophy beside the point: a case of the tail wagging the dog? While I think that there is some truth to this conjecture, basically my view is that despite the difficulty of its project the whole point of doing philosophy is to prevent the tail wagging and to get the dog back in the driver's seat."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this discussion, we will feel free to stray from formal philosophy to the whole range of beliefs from academia to business to everyday life that may be &amp;ldquo;an articulation of subconscious motives." This is a hugely important topic, I think, that is a big part of human destiny (hmm, perhaps that will be our next topic) because our conscious and unconscious beliefs concerning self-image and actuality may or may not be in alignment. If we want to know who we are and who we are becoming we will need to comprehend the distinctions between our conscious and subconscious perceptions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, from philosophy, to science, to art, to society and culture we will discuss the role of conscious and subconscious perceptions.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; This topic&lt;/span&gt; is a rich source of a interdisciplinary perspectives, and should be highly stimulating, eye opening and, of course, lots of fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people). &amp;nbsp; After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.&amp;nbsp; It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp; And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!&amp;nbsp; While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).&amp;nbsp; Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.&amp;nbsp; However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night. &lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337218828000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333130497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Conscious and Subconscious in Philosophy, Culture and Everyday Life</name><id>58551652</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336777200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/58551652/</event_url></item>