<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/b/0/event_133418832.jpeg" width="240" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;From boardgamegeek.com:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The classic real estate game. Buy properties, build houses and hotels, collect rent from fellow players. Repeat as necessary until everyone else is bankrupt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the USA in 1933, Charles Darrow devised Monopoly. The patent was filed 31st August 1935 while the game was on sale in America. Based on an earlier game, The Landlord's Game, it was at first rejected by Parker Bros., as being too complicated to be a success. How wrong could they be! It came to the UK in 1936, made under licence by Waddingtons. Darrow died in 1967 having realised he had developed one of the most successful board games of all times. It was awarded as &lt;em&gt;Game of the Century&lt;/em&gt; by the TRA (Toy Retailers Association).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monopoly&lt;/strong&gt; was patented in 1935 by &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgamedesigner/1268/charles-darrow"&gt;Charles Darrow&lt;/a&gt; and released by &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgamepublisher/28/parker-brothers"&gt;Parker Brothers&lt;/a&gt;. The game was actually one of a number of variants in existence at the time, all of which date back to an earlier, 1904 game by &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgamedesigner/3109/elizabeth-j-magie-phillips"&gt;Elizabeth J. Magie&lt;/a&gt;, called &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/29316/the-landlords-game"&gt;The Landlord's Game&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgamedesigner/3109/elizabeth-j-magie-phillips"&gt;Magie&lt;/a&gt; was a proponent of the Single Tax put forth by famous author Henry George. The game was designed to show how the Single Tax would work - players could choose to play under regular rules or alternate "Single Tax" rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game didn't really go anywhere and &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgamedesigner/3109/elizabeth-j-magie-phillips"&gt;Magie&lt;/a&gt; lost interest in it. Variations of the game evolved, however, and homemade versions traveled up and down the Atlantic coast and even as far west as Michigan and Texas, being developed all along the way. Eventually the game was noticed by &lt;a href="http://www.boardgamegeek.com/boardgamedesigner/1268/charles-darrow"&gt;Charles Darrow&lt;/a&gt; who introduced it to the world in its current form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send out my house number the day before the event to those who have RSVPed 'Yes'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342492354000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340755328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night: Monopoly</name><id>70883912</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342481400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/70883912/</event_url></item>