<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-3721</phone><name>Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>875759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105592</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us on Saturday, February 9, as we plunge ahead with the Xen'drik Expedition adventures at Pandemonium Books &amp;amp; Games!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, from 12;30 PM to 5 PM - Expedition 5 - Shargon's Rage&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sailors say that a bright new day rolls in on every tide. But when darkness and dire fog cloak the coming of a deadly fleet, will the city of Stormreach survive to see another dawn? The heroes and villains of Xen'drik are in for the longest night of their lives... ((DMed by Andy French)) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, from 6 PM to 10:30 PM - Expedition 6 - Taming the Hydra&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In the City of Storms' greatest time of trial, an ancient tower rises to the need. By riding the hydra and finding the Stair Invisible, the old will save the new and be reborn itself.&amp;quot; Following the Shargon strike attack by the pirate fleet, things look grim. With the weather still out of control and ships unable to get to Xen'drik easily, supplies have become increasingly rare and the hopes of the city's survivors grow bleaker by the day. The factions ally to bring relief to Stormreach. ((DMed by Andy French)) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7th level Characters can be created using the Xen'drik Expedition Campaign Standards available at &lt;a href="http://www.rpga.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rpga.com...&lt;/a&gt;, or you can choose from a premade fastplay character. If you are creating a character, please have the character completed and with you. Characters from any faction can be played in these special expedition modules.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are only 6 slots for each adventure, so please sign up in advance by emailing aethan [AT] bloopwatch [DOT] org   Please indicate which slot (or both) that you want to sign up for.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy DMing the Xen'drik Expeditions events.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204909325000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200601861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Xen'drik Expeditions @ Pandemonium Books</name><id>7137854</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202578200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/7137854/</event_url></item>