<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>754 Hopmeadow St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06070</zip><lat>41.874399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-658-0666 </phone><name>ENO HALL</name><city>Simsbury </city><id>750653</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.801946</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Theatre Guild of Simsbury&lt;br /&gt;CABARET&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 6: 8 PM - Eno Hall - Eno Memorial Hall - &lt;br /&gt;754 Hopmeadow Street, Simsbury, CT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simsbury - Tickets: $15&lt;br /&gt;It's back! Theatre Guild of Simsbury's Cabaret returns! &lt;br /&gt;Please join us for &amp;quot;A Century of Song&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;A musical review celebrating 100 years of broadway's best!&lt;br /&gt;Seating is limited-reservations are STRONGLY encouraged. &lt;br /&gt;Please call 860-658-0666 to reserve your tickets. &lt;br /&gt;You may bring snacks and drinks (beer and wine ONLY are permitted). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eno Hall is in the center of Simsbury on Hopmeadow Street (also known as Route 10), a main thoroughfare that runs north/south through Simsbury from Granby to Avon.&lt;br /&gt;From Farmington:&lt;br /&gt;At its intersection with Route 4 take Route 10 North towards Avon and Simsbury. After roughly five miles, at the large intersection of Route 10 and Route 44, turn left onto Route 44/Route 10 (Route 10 takes a dog leg at this point). Continue approximately 2 miles on Route 44 to a four way intersection (White Church on far right corner). Turn right at this intersection (still Route 10). At this point you are approximately 5 miles from the center of Simsbury. Follow Route 10, also known as Hopmeadow Street, into the center of Simsbury. Eno Hall will be on the right.&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 44 (Albany Avenue) into Avon. Turn right onto Route 10/Hopmeadow Street, and follow directions as indicated above).&lt;br /&gt;From Torrington:&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 44 to Avon. Turn left at major intersection (white church on left corner) where Route 10 bears north towards Simsbury. Follow five miles to center of Simsbury. Eno Hall is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;From Granby:&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 10 South into center of Simsbury.&lt;br /&gt;From Bloomfield:&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 185 to intersection with Route 10/Hopmeadow Street. Turn right and follow to center of Simsbury.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please burchase tickets a head of time   Bring a bottle of wine and some munchie</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220918745000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220197588000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CABERAT In Simsbury.      One of our own is Preforming!!!!!!!!!!!!!</name><id>8657317</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220745600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8657317/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>