<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302 at Willey House Station Road</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.170815</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Webster Cliff Trail parking lot</name><city>Hart's Landing</city><id>5370322</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.388030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Time to do a nice easy multi-pitch snow and ice climb...Shoestring. &amp;nbsp;This is probably my favorite climb: great views, relaxing, easy snow and ice (WI2), four or so pitches. &amp;nbsp;Shoestring is located on Webster Cliff, the last gully on the south end before the Webster Cliff Trail. &amp;nbsp;The plan is to start at 9 AM on Saturday Feb 18, climb up the gully, then finish with the left-side ice climb. If you want to do the 5.5 rock route (chimney) instead, be my guest. &amp;nbsp;After the climb, we'll hike out via the Webster Cliff Trail. &amp;nbsp;This climb will probably end around 3 PM, maybe earlier. &amp;nbsp;Although it is easy,&amp;nbsp;this is a popular climb, and we will need to be on our guard. If conditions in the gully are poor, or weather forecast is bad, we'll try another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;We will need two or more lead climbers capable of WI2, preferably with experience with climbing Shoestring Gully. &amp;nbsp;Ideally, no more than two seconds per leader. &amp;nbsp;Seconds will need to have experience in top rope climbing at a minimum. I will be climbing the gully in early Feb to get the beta, and will be a leader for this climb. &amp;nbsp;Please answer the questions I ask in the RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;All will need their own mountaineering boots, crampons, harness, locking biner+belay device, helmet, balaclava, two or more pairs of gloves (they get wet), water proof (eg, Gore-Tex) tops and bottoms, warm fleece layers, and thermal wicking layer. &amp;nbsp;In addition, each must have&amp;nbsp;their own ice tools (axes). &amp;nbsp;But, because this is an alpine climb, try to keep light. &amp;nbsp;Leaders will need rope, biners, webbing, ice screws, rock pro, etc. &amp;nbsp;We'll have to coordinate to make sure we bring the right gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Let's meet up at 9 at the Webster Cliff Trail parking lot (the southern end of the Webster Cliff Trail that is in the Notch). &amp;nbsp;Be ready to go at 9, so come 15 minutes earlier to get your boots on and packs set. From there, we will walk up the road to the start of the climb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, check out &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/messages/boards/thread/10228789"&gt;the FAQ's on ice climbing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on Shoestring,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.summitpost.org/shoestring-gully/168328"&gt;http://www.summitpost.org/shoestring-gully/168328&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A nice video of the last pitch of the climb: &lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/9492026"&gt;http://vimeo.com/9492026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/9492026"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;For weather, &lt;a href="http://www.accuweather.com/en/us/bartlett-nh/03812/weather-forecast/2174533"&gt;Accuweather&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/"&gt;Mount Washington Observatory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current ice climbing conditions: &lt;a href="http://neice.com/"&gt;neice.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://neclimbs.com/"&gt;neclimbs.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If staying overnight, consider lodging at the White Mountains Hostel:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.whitemountainshostel.com/"&gt;http://www.whitemountainshostel.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ken Domino</member_name><member_id>4332297</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329746880000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327609786000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>On a Shoestring</name><id>49763352</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329573600000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/49763352/</event_url></item>