<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>501 Fellsway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.404572</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 393-9681 </phone><name>Not Your Average Joe's Restaurant Station Landing Medford, MA</name><city>Medford</city><id>699902</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081657</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meetup member Debbie is also a member of the Cards and Conversation Meetup, and has graciously invited us to share in a joint Meetup next Tuesday. They meet at the Not Your Average Joe's near the Wellington T stop. If using transit, it's an easy trek from Wellington Station across the bridge that leads to the secondary parking garage. It's also easily accessible by car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details from the C&amp;amp;C site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Words, words, words, and more words!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight will be a fun night dedicated to those favorite word games which so many of us enjoy. So, all of you fellow wordsters out there feel free to break out the Boggle, Taboo, Balderdash, Catch Phrase, Scattergories, Bananagrams, Scrabble, or your favorite game!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a open game format so any and all games (even non word related ones) are welcome! I will personally be bringing Scrabble, Scrabble Slam, Bananagrams, and Apples to Apples.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO GET THERE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location is easily accessible from Rt. 16, Rt. 28 and Rt. 93, and is walking distance from the Wellington Orange Line subway stop, near the new Station Landing apartment complex. Although there is free parking around the building, we recommend that C&amp;amp;C members park in the garage underneath the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are driving, be aware that Station Landing is at the intersection of Rt. 16 and Rt. 28, and you can enter the Station Landing complex from the north-bound side of Rt. 28, or the east-bound side of Rt. 16. There are a number of stores in the Station Landing complex -- look for Starbucks or Qdoba. Not Your Average Joe's is right next to these shops, and has a blue and white sign.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debbie</member_name><member_id>10965927</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269557930000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Word Freaks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston</urlname><id>1385528</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Scrabble Enthusiasts of (Greater) Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268687716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wondrous Word Games with Boston Cards and Conversation</name><id>12884281</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269384300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scrabble-Enthusiasts-of-Boston/events/12884281/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/e/global_7376798.jpeg</photo_url></item>