<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1253 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373447</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 576-1253</phone><name>Improv Boston Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>276259</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098660</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Meet for dinner and conversation at 7 PM, at a restaurant in Inman Square, there are several options available.. At 9:30 head over to the ImprovBoston Theater to catch the 10 PM show. OR if preferred, we could do the earlier show and have dinner/drinks, maybe even dancing after. Also has been discussion of meeting up at Alewife and going in together to avoid the parking hassle in Cambridge...We'll see what most people want to do. Please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;Reservations will be required beforehand and I will contact everyone to plan the arrangements a few days before the event. &lt;br /&gt;Show tickets are $12.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ImprovBoston presents an evening of comedy, drama and song with an improvised storyline created on the spot each week by a cast made up of some of Boston's best improvisational comedians. The 8 PM show is:&lt;br /&gt;Rodgers and Hammerstein. Kander and Ebb. Harnick and Bock. Ladley and Craig.&lt;br /&gt;Join ?world-renowned? composer/lyricist team Robert Ladley and Dennis Craig for an evening of retrospection and song as they discuss and reminisce about the peaks and valleys of their career as one of America?s premier (and oft-forgotten) Broadway duos. Beginning in the late 1960's through their sudden split in the late 1980's, the composing team of Ladley and Craig, together with a core group of actors and collaborators, created some of the most memorable shows that ever graced the stages of Broadway. From their first show, Romp In The Sheets, to their later collaborations Hindenberg! and Hellfire, you'll have a front row seat to witness the lives and loves of this remarkable group as they discuss and relive their triumphs, tribulations, and moments in the spotlight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR at 10 PM:   Theater Sports...No holds. Bard.&lt;br /&gt;This official Boston franchise of the world-renowned format pits two teams of improvisers in a match to the comedic death! A stern referee keeps the players in line, and the audience scores each scene to determine the winning team. The action is fast-paced and fanatically funny.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.improvboston.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.improvbost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181045271000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178315970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DATE CHANGED:  Improv Comedy and Fun</name><id>5742850</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180738800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/5742850/</event_url></item>