<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Boston Dreamers is now one year old! To celebrate this, we're having a dream party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What's a dream party?&amp;quot; you may very well ask. A dream party is a party with dreams as the theme. We will have some fun and meet the other members of this Meetup group. We will play dream games and share dreams. We will use oracle cards, such as dream cards, animal cards, shaman cards, and tarot cards. Bring your favorite dream games and oracle cards to show off and play with. In keeping with the party theme of dreams, feel free to bring your pajamas to wear and your teddy bear if you want. The theme of the party is dreams, so bring anything which reminds you of dreams and dreaming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have a vegetarian potluck, so bring some vegetarian food to share. There will be plenty of opportunity to share dreams and talk about dreams. This will also be an opportunity to follow up on &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=200100329434&amp;amp;ref=mf" target="_blank"&gt;Dreaming In the New Year 2&lt;/a&gt;, the worldwide dream event. If you want you may share your New Year dream experiences or any other dreams. Please bring your dream journal if you have one and you want to share your dreams with other dreamers at the party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting in Cambridge, Massachusetts, 6 PM - 12 Midnight. This is a party, so you can drop in whenever you feel like it. If you wish to attend the First Anniversary Dream Party you must RSVP to be sent the address of the party. Sorry, I can't put the address on the net.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264435017000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262141911000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Anniversary Dream Party</name><id>12173163</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263682800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/12173163/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/e/global_12421790.jpeg</photo_url></item>