<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I looked on line last night and tickets are still available for this event.  When I bought my ticket on Sunday, I was told that there were about 100 seats left.  If you want to attend, you should get your ticket (on-line or in person) asap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a special screening at which the filmmaker and her husband, Andre Gregory (from My Dinner with Andre), will be present.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is about the dysfunctional marriage of the parents of the filmmaker and offers a penetrating look at marriage when middle-class women (and men) didn't have many options.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The screening and discussion should be over by 6 - and we will head over to Zaftigs for conversation and dinner after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will keep you updated about tickets.  But if you want to go, be sure to get yours ahead of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what the Coolidge Corner web site has to say about the event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special screening Sunday, July 25 @ 3pm with director Cindy Kleine and producer André Gregory (My Dinner With André) in person in the upstairs 217-seat MovieHouse 2!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE member tickets has reached capacity. To guarantee a seat you may still purchase general member-priced tickets for $6.75. We will have some FREE rush tickets available day-of-show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets to the regular showtimes during the week of July 23rd will be available for purchase by Thursday, July 22nd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Phyllis and Harold is an astoundingly frank journey through a disastrous 59-year marriage. Drawing on a lifetime of her family's home movies and interviews made over 12 years, filmmaker Cindy Kleine mixes reportage, cinema verité and animation to uncover family secrets and tell a story that could not be shown publicly as long as her father was still alive. Phyllis and Harold delves into the mystery of time passing, the nature of living a life, and the challenges of losing those we love. But it is also a loving, funny exposé on the sins of suburbia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cindy Kleine is a film and video artist whose prolific career began when she was an undergraduate at Tufts University, School of the Museum of Fine Arts and at the legendary (now defunct) MIT Film/Video Section, studying with Richard Leacock and Ed Pincus, and among a legion of future filmmakers in the program, including Ross McElwee, Robb Moss and John Gianvito. In line with her Boston peers, Kleine has developed a central body of documentary work focused on family dramas: camera visits with her grandmother and her sister, and intense exploration of her parents’ 59 years of a dubious, fractured marriage. Additionally, she has gone outside of family for films about odd artists and off-the-wall musicians, and she’s gone inside herself for some deeply personal, poetically framed psychodramas about love lost, spirit gained.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Cindy Kleine, 1h25m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279473850000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Phyliss and Harold at the Coolidge</name><id>14137498</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280084400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14137498/</event_url></item>