<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Just north of Dunkin Donuts on same side (south of ski area) Rt 138/ Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02021</zip><lat>42.141953</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rt 138 Park and Ride (3173 Washington St, Canton MA)</name><city>Canton</city><id>7535312</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.149345</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Pam Wilmot (six one seven) nine six two- 0034 (cell) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/strong&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We are doing a double traverse of the Great Blue Hills Reservation from 138 Park and Ride to the Shea rink and back.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Despite this being in the Blue Hills this is &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not a beginner hike&lt;/span&gt; - we are going from one end to the other and then back again. We will be hiking about 15 miles and climb about 4,000 feet - this is the equivalent of a long hike in the White Mountains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Great Blue Hill is the highest point in the 7,000 acre Blue Hills Reservation and the highest coastal elevation along the Atlantic seaboard south of Maine. This large dome of granite measures 635 feet at the summit. Hikers will be rewarded with a spectacular view of the surrounding countryside. To the east, you see the Harbor Islands dotting the coastline. To the north, skyscrapers tower among the Boston skyline. To the west, Mount Wachusett can be seen 44 miles away.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will leave from the Park and Ride as it steeply ascends the Great Blue Hill following the Skyline Trail as it passes over numerous hills on the way to Shea Rink in Quincy and then return following the Skyline back to the parking lot. Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue%20hills%20brochure.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for a link to a map of the area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt; permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate but stiff pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; round trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 15 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 4,000 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. These are estimates since no matter where you look you get different information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using a trail map and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for a link to a map of the area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.211003028609895&amp;amp;lon=-71.44580841064453&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=42.21231085282779&amp;amp;lon=-71.1159610748291&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;(noaa.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Three_Season_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a day hike&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Appalachian Mountain Club&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be meeting in the park and ride lot on Rt 138 (3173 Washington St, Canton MA) just north of Dunkin Donuts on the same side of the street and just South of the Ski area and Trailside Museum (opposite side).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;q=3173+Washington+Street+Canton,+MA&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=0x89e37e1fef28510f:0xf3b4ba1b2a53f8f0,3173+Washington+St,+Canton,+MA+02021&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;ei=_KzMT9T8IMf46QHmuIDNCA&amp;amp;oi=geocode_result&amp;amp;ved=0CAoQ8gEwAA"&gt;Click here for location in Google Maps:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam</member_name><member_id>6419698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339374593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338814039000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills Double Traverse (Intermediate)</name><id>67646302</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339241400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/67646302/</event_url></item>