<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be outdoors, enjoying the summer with food, refreshments and friends. Please join us as we will have a special guest speaker, Matthew LaClair. Matt Cherry, having recently left the IHS, will be unable to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matthew LaClair, of Kearny, NJ, stood up for religious freedom and the separation of church and state in the face of ridicule and opposition. During his junior year in high school, Matthew had a history teacher who promoted creationism and other personal religious beliefs in the classroom. When Matthew confronted the teacher and asked the school officials to address this, he became the target of harassment and even a death threat from fellow students. Despite this opposition, Matthew worked with the ACLU of New Jersey to make sure that the First Amendment is respected and upheld at his high school. Matthew won the battle at his school and thanks in large part to his advocacy, the Student Education Assembly on Religious Freedom was created at his high school so that all members of the school community will understand their rights and responsibilities.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216055446000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215714793000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Worcester Humanists July Meetup</name><id>8315350</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215882000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/8315350/</event_url></item>