<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01062</zip><lat>42.335938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Florence Civic Center </name><city>Florence </city><id>8746012</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.673225</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Film by Jeffrey M. Smith; narrated by Lisa Oz - A production of the Institute for Responsible Technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never-Before-Seen-Evidence points to genetically engineered foods as a major contributor to rising disease rates in the US population, especially among children. Gastrointestinal disorders, allergies, inflammatory diseases, and infertility are just some of the problems implicated in humans, pets, livestock, and lab animals that eat genetically modified soybeans and corn. Trailer: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://youtu.be/Vv96D_ZURzs"&gt;http://youtu.be/Vv96D_ZURzs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be meeting at 6:30 pm which is when the doors open.  The Florence Civic Center has parking in the back and a ramped entrance from the lot. I will try to get there early enough to be one of the first in the door.  If I am allowed, I will find 15 seats and block them off for us.  It's not a super huge space, so it might be pretty crowded if the word has gotten out successfully enough about the movie. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 While waiting to get inside, I will have a sign - Western Mass Movie Meetup - probably taped to both my back and front! - so that you can locate me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There should be a pretty interesting and rich discussion at the end of the movie so I hope that you'll be able to stay after the show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Jensey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jensey</member_name><member_id>33110712</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362345751000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>filmgroup</urlname><id>1279822</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Western MA Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358381381000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Genetic Roulette</name><id>99965372</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361403000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/filmgroup/events/99965372/</event_url></item>