<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate (est. 4-6 miles, steep hill) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt; East Main Street, New Salem, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is an "exploratory hike." We have done parts of it seperately, but not the whole thing. From Gate 27, it's about 1 mile to where we cross the water; to the summit, 2-3 miles. So the hike is probably 4-6 miles. This is an estimate. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; These are old dirt roads with hills. After hiking a mile, we will cross the upper reaches of Quabbin Reservoir (once each way). Then we will follow an old road around the hill, and a power blaze and a trail to the top. Rattlesnake Hill is a steep, rocky hill with amazing views! Others been up before, not me, so I can't give the exact distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring:&lt;/strong&gt; Bring food, water, and non-leaky shoes. (Some areas may be wet.) Camera recommended! The "New Salem General Store" on Route 202 has an outhouse, food, books, maps, etc. I don't know if there are any outhouses on this hike (I doubt it), so plan accordingly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There's a possibility of showers, though they are most likely in early morning and late afternoon to evening. Please wear a raincoat and appropriate clothing. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reservation Rules:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a public water supply...no pets are allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trash is "carry in, carry out"...there are no receptacles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading, or removing things from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from points north:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get to Route 202 via Routes 122 or 2. &lt;em&gt;I previously specified Exit 19 off Route 2; however, this is only for 202 north! The correct exit for 202 south is Exit 16.&lt;/em&gt; Take Route 202 south several minutes past the end of Route 122...maybe about 4 miles. Look for the "New Salem General Store" on your right. (See above.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from points south:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 to Belchertown. Turn north onto Route 202. It will be about 15-20 minutes until you see the "New Salem General Store" on your left. (See above.) Those coming from Amherst may find it faster to take the road, whose name I forget, that ends on Route 202 at the Pelham Historical Society near Gate 11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you see the "New Salem General Store" on Route 202:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please look for the "New Salem General Store" on the southbound side of the road.&lt;/em&gt; There are 3 streets on both sides of the highway. You want East Main Street on the northbound side, across from the store. It's hard to turn in the correct street, depending on traffic, due to the high speed limit. That's okay! Whichever one you take, they quickly intersect! Then stay left, but not a sharp left back to 202. &lt;strong&gt;Please look for the "E Main St" street sign.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(If you pass an old cemetary and historic-looking buildings, you are on S. Main St. Please turn around and backtrack, then take a right on E Main St.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll pass some houses, and it will become a bumpy dirt road. It's rather long. Near the end, &lt;strong&gt;on the left, is Gate 27&lt;/strong&gt;. (Please park to either side, but don't block the gate.) At the end of the road is Gate 26; we're using 27!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I don't always stay caught up on my email, I've been so busy lately. Please use the "comment" feature on this page to ask questions about this meetup.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>East Main Street, New Salem, off Route 202 (Daniel Shays Highway). We'll park on the road and gather on foot at the gate.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph P</member_name><member_id>4253893</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332334458000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331866488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploratory Hike: Gate 27 to Rattlesnake Hill</name><id>56562042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332255600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/56562042/</event_url></item>