<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>81 Ocean Blvd, Floor 2</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03842</zip><lat>42.903999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ocean Gaming Casino</name><city>Hampton</city><id>10098242</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.811882</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/6/8/event_183517992.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Holiday season internationally known mentalist Jon Stetson will tell the Seacoast residents what they are thinking. Stetson will deliver a unique brand of psychic entertainment with his distinctive style of humor, intensity, and compassion. The Stetson Experience will debut at the newly renovated Ocean Gaming Casino Sunday December 9, 2012 for 2 shows. The matinee show will start at 1:30 pm and the evening show will start at 4:30 pm. Jon Stetson’s charismatic and lively demonstrations provide his audiences a rare opportunity to experience the fascinating phenomenon of an intuitive experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jon Stetson began the study of the mystic arts at a very early age and has been blessed to receive formal training from some very gifted and proficient mystics, psychics, clairvoyants, and teachers over the years. Stetson has performed around the world, for audiences numbering in the hundreds as well as for "custom" gatherings as small as two. He's performed at the White House and on the A&amp;amp;E network, and is also a consultant for the CBS series The Mentalist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire audience is empowered to understand and further develop their psychic skills during a diverting and thought-provoking evening. Everyone in the audience participates and will indeed, amaze themselves and discover their unlimited potential-no one in the room remains a spectator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you plan to go:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday December 9th at Ocean Gaming Casino at 81 Ocean Boulevards in Hampton Beach, NH. Shows run at 1:30 pm and 4:30 pm. Dinner Show tickets are $25 and include show and chef prepared Italian buffet, show only tickets are $20. For Tickets and more information visit www.drinkwaterproductions.com!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup badges will be supplied to all meetup members</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355149319000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Men and Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-527</urlname><id>501015</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Cocktail Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354120409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Stetson Experience- America's #1 mentalist Jon Stetson</name><id>93179442</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355088600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-527/events/93179442/</event_url></item>