<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Members need not have any previous experience in Energy Healing.  You can join simply to LEARN all the latest modalities, if you so choose!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can compare different energy healing modalities in regards to what frequency level healing currents are accessed and applied.  For example, chi is name of dimension 1 current, ki is name of dimension 2 current, rei is name of dimension 3 current, etc.  (Chinese modalities focus on balancing out the chi flows, ReiKi uses D2 &amp;amp; D3 current, etc.)   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other modalities use higher dimensional currents.  If there is sufficient interest, a modality which uses frequencies from the 12th dimension will be discussed.  This level contains the original blueprint for perpetual health and wellness, with NO distortions.  Accessing and directing these currents progressively clears out all distortions at the lower levels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your own refreshments until we have organized a refreshment committee for future meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully, we will discuss possible future topics, and agree on the topic for the following month's meeting, before we adjourn.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the lady with long black hair and a BIG smile (see photo here).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269201554000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238932486000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Energy Healing Association May Meetup</name><id>10118663</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241305200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/10118663/</event_url></item>