<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When:&lt;br /&gt;    Sunday, December 16, 2007, 2:15 PM 20071216T191500Z &lt;br /&gt;Where:&lt;br /&gt;    Faneuil Hall&lt;br /&gt;    1 Faneuil Hall Square&lt;br /&gt;    Boston , MA 02109&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        * Info/Map&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    December 16th, 2007 is the 234th anniversary of the Boston Tea Party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Chip-In: &lt;a href="http://bostonteaparty.." target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonteaparty...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;    Web site: &lt;a href="http://www.freedomral.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.freedomral...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    To commemorate this important day and show support for Ron Paul, we have booked Faneuil Hall. We will have many speakers to liven the day, including Rand Paul addressing issues important to us as he promotes Ron Paul for President.&lt;br /&gt;    .&lt;br /&gt;    WE WILL GATHER AT THE BOSTON COMMONS AT 1:00 PM AND THEN MARCH TO FANEUIL HALL AT 1:30 PM. THE DOORS TO FANEUIL HALL WILL OPEN AT 2:15.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    As Ron Paul supporters man a literature table outside the hall and distribute Ron Paul invitation cards to join us inside at the rally, there will also be Ron Paul banners floating from helium balloons in the sky above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Next to Faneuil Hall the Granny Warriors from North Carolina will set up their mobile Ron Paul campaign headquaters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    We have invited C-Span to also join us with either their C-Span Campaign '08' bus or with on site coverage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Confirmed speakers include Jacob Hornberger, Carla Howell, Norman Tregenza, James Forsythe, Hal Shurlteff and John McManus with others not yet confirmed. Projectors outside the hall will play relevant Ron Paul videos and show in real-time the donations coming in onthei major fundraising day. Also, if the blimp from RonPaulBlimp.com becomes a reality, it will be flying over the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    After the Faneuil Hall rally ends, we will march from there to the Old South Meeting House and do a sign wave at 4:30 while people visit the Tea Party reenactment taking place inside there (unrelated to Ron Paul).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    We hope as many people as possible, thousands, will attend and make this event a success with national press coverage. Let's all come together to promote Ron Paul peacefully :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    We Need Your Financial Support! &lt;a href="http://ronpaul.meetup.com/68/calendar/6622547/"&gt;RSVP for Boston Meetup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198005469000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196577772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Tea Party - IN Boston</name><id>6840230</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197832500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/6840230/</event_url></item>