<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>580 mt auburn street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.370590</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>mt auburn cemetery</name><city>Newton</city><id>610388</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.158960</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>mount auburn cemetery is one of the most beautiful and historic landscapes in america. its impressive collection of over 5,000 trees represents 630 taxa. thousands of shrubs and herbaceous plants weave through 175 acres of hills, dells, ponds, woodlands, clearings, and sweeping vistas through majestic trees to small enclosed spaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;may is mount auburn?s glory month, when its flowery bowers seem stuffed to the bursting point with hummingbirds and flycatchers and thrushes and vireos and tanagers and orioles and, above all, warblers - at least 25 species in dazzling breeding plumage, filling the spring air with their songs (though seldom warbling!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;bring your binocs, magnifiers, field guides and other provisions.  there's tons of natural beauty in this bone lot, and you'll want to be ready to soak it all in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Birds Recorded at &lt;br /&gt;Mount Auburn Cemetery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Compiled by Janet Heywood and Robert Stymeist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Common Loon ^ &lt;br /&gt;Pied-billed Grebe &lt;br /&gt;Great Cormorant &lt;br /&gt;Double-crested Cormorant &lt;br /&gt;American Bittern &lt;br /&gt;Least Bittern &lt;br /&gt;Great Blue Heron &lt;br /&gt;Great Egret ^ &lt;br /&gt;Snowy Egret ^ &lt;br /&gt;Little Blue Heron &lt;br /&gt;Green Heron &lt;br /&gt;Black-crowned Night-Heron &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-crowned Night-Heron &lt;br /&gt;Glossy Ibis ^ &lt;br /&gt;Turkey Vulture ^ &lt;br /&gt;Canada Goose * &lt;br /&gt;Wood Duck &lt;br /&gt;American Wigeon &lt;br /&gt;American Black Duck &lt;br /&gt;Mallard * &lt;br /&gt;Green-winged Teal &lt;br /&gt;Ring-necked Duck &lt;br /&gt;Oldsquaw &lt;br /&gt;Bufflehead &lt;br /&gt;Hooded Merganser &lt;br /&gt;Red-breasted Merganser &lt;br /&gt;Common Merganser &lt;br /&gt;Osprey &lt;br /&gt;Northern Harrier ^ &lt;br /&gt;Sharp-shinned Hawk &lt;br /&gt;Cooper's Hawk &lt;br /&gt;Northern Goshawk &lt;br /&gt;Red-shouldered Hawk &lt;br /&gt;Broad-winged Hawk &lt;br /&gt;Red-tailed Hawk * &lt;br /&gt;Rough-legged Hawk &lt;br /&gt;American Kestrel &lt;br /&gt;Merlin &lt;br /&gt;Peregrine Falcon &lt;br /&gt;Ring-necked Pheasant * &lt;br /&gt;Ruffed Grouse &lt;br /&gt;Wild Turkey &lt;br /&gt;Northern Bobwhite &lt;br /&gt;Black-bellied Plover ^ &lt;br /&gt;American Golden-Plover ^ &lt;br /&gt;Killdeer &lt;br /&gt;Greater Yellowlegs ^ &lt;br /&gt;Solitary Sandpiper &lt;br /&gt;Spotted Sandpiper &lt;br /&gt;Semipalmated Sandpiper &lt;br /&gt;Western Sandpiper &lt;br /&gt;Common Snipe &lt;br /&gt;American Woodcock &lt;br /&gt;Laughing Gull &lt;br /&gt;Ring-billed Gull &lt;br /&gt;Herring Gull &lt;br /&gt;Great Black-backed Gull &lt;br /&gt;Rock Dove * &lt;br /&gt;Mourning Dove * &lt;br /&gt;Black-billed Cuckoo &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-billed Cuckoo &lt;br /&gt;Barn Owl &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Screech-Owl * &lt;br /&gt;Great Horned Owl * &lt;br /&gt;Snowy Owl &lt;br /&gt;Barred Owl &lt;br /&gt;Long-eared Owl &lt;br /&gt;Northern Saw-whet Owl &lt;br /&gt;Common Nighthawk &lt;br /&gt;Chuck-will's-widow &lt;br /&gt;Whip-poor-will &lt;br /&gt;Chimney Swift * &lt;br /&gt;Ruby-throated Hummingbird &lt;br /&gt;Belted Kingfisher * &lt;br /&gt;Red-headed Woodpecker &lt;br /&gt;Red-bellied Woodpecker &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-bellied Sapsucker &lt;br /&gt;Downy Woodpecker * &lt;br /&gt;Hairy Woodpecker &lt;br /&gt;Northern Flicker * &lt;br /&gt;Pileated Woodpecker &lt;br /&gt;Olive-sided Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Wood-Pewee &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-bellied Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Acadian Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Alder Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Willow Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Least Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Phoebe * &lt;br /&gt;Ash-throated Flycatcher &lt;br /&gt;Great Crested Flycatcher * &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Kingbird * &lt;br /&gt;Northern Shrike &lt;br /&gt;White-eyed Vireo &lt;br /&gt;Blue-headed Vireo &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-throated Vireo &lt;br /&gt;Warbling Vireo * &lt;br /&gt;Philadelphia Vireo &lt;br /&gt;Red-eyed Vireo * &lt;br /&gt;Blue Jay * &lt;br /&gt;American Crow * &lt;br /&gt;Fish Crow * &lt;br /&gt;Purple Martin &lt;br /&gt;Tree Swallow * &lt;br /&gt;N. Rough-winged Swallow * &lt;br /&gt;Bank Swallow &lt;br /&gt;Barn Swallow &lt;br /&gt;Cliff Swallow &lt;br /&gt;Black-capped Chickadee * &lt;br /&gt;Tufted Titmouse * &lt;br /&gt;Red-breasted Nuthatch * &lt;br /&gt;White-breasted Nuthatch * &lt;br /&gt;Brown Creeper &lt;br /&gt;Carolina Wren &lt;br /&gt;House Wren * &lt;br /&gt;Winter Wren &lt;br /&gt;Marsh Wren &lt;br /&gt;Blue-gray Gnatcatcher &lt;br /&gt;Golden-crowned Kinglet &lt;br /&gt;Ruby-crowned Kinglet &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Bluebird &lt;br /&gt;Veery &lt;br /&gt;Gray-cheeked Thrush &lt;br /&gt;Bicknell's Thrush &lt;br /&gt;Swainson's Thrush &lt;br /&gt;Hermit Thrush &lt;br /&gt;Wood Thrush &lt;br /&gt;American Robin * &lt;br /&gt;Gray Catbird * &lt;br /&gt;Northern Mockingbird * &lt;br /&gt;Brown Thrasher &lt;br /&gt;European Starling * &lt;br /&gt;American Pipit &lt;br /&gt;Cedar Waxwing * &lt;br /&gt;Blue-winged Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Golden-winged Warbler &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Brewster's&amp;quot; Warbler &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lawrence's&amp;quot; Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Tennessee Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Orange-crowned Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Nashville Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Northern Parula &lt;br /&gt;Yellow Warbler * &lt;br /&gt;Chestnut-sided Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Magnolia Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Cape May Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-rumped Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Black-throated Blue Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Townsend's Warbler # &lt;br /&gt;Hermit Warbler # &lt;br /&gt;Black-throated Green Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Blackburnian Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-throated Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Pine Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Prairie Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Palm Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Bay-breasted Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Blackpoll Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Cerulean Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Black-and-white Warbler &lt;br /&gt;American Redstart &lt;br /&gt;Prothonotary Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Worm-eating Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Ovenbird &lt;br /&gt;Northern Waterthrush &lt;br /&gt;Louisiana Waterthrush &lt;br /&gt;Kentucky Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Connecticut Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Mourning Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Common Yellowthroat * &lt;br /&gt;Hooded Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Wilson's Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Canada Warbler &lt;br /&gt;Yellow-breasted Chat &lt;br /&gt;Summer Tanager &lt;br /&gt;Scarlet Tanager &lt;br /&gt;Western Tanager &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Towhee &lt;br /&gt;American Tree Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Chipping Sparrow * &lt;br /&gt;Clay-colored Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Brewer's Sparrow # &lt;br /&gt;Field Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Vesper Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Savannah Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Sharp-tailed Sparrow (species) &lt;br /&gt;Fox Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Song Sparrow * &lt;br /&gt;Lincoln's Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Swamp Sparrow * &lt;br /&gt;White-throated Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;White-crowned Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Golden-crowned Sparrow &lt;br /&gt;Dark-eyed Junco &lt;br /&gt;Northern Cardinal * &lt;br /&gt;Rose-breasted Grosbeak * &lt;br /&gt;Blue Grosbeak &lt;br /&gt;Indigo Bunting * &lt;br /&gt;Bobolink &lt;br /&gt;Red-winged Blackbird * &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* breeds or has bred at Mount Auburn &lt;br /&gt;^ usually seen flying overhead &lt;br /&gt;# first state record&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>main gate on mt auburn street where mt auburn and brattle streets meet.  my vehicle:  red jeep with big wheels.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6025746</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211900798000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>it's a haven for birds, and a horticultural gem!</why><group><who>Subnats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>science-88</urlname><id>1005141</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Suburban Naturalists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210806644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>mt auburn cemetery</name><id>7940016</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211727600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/science-88/events/7940016/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/4/global_4126660.jpeg</photo_url></item>