<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets earn some good elevation gain and get a good workout for our legs on Sunday morning. For all those of us who have obligations later in the day and can't head to the mountains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we will do: &lt;br /&gt;

 Use the steps and seats of the 37 sections of the stadium to run/walk up and down, and up and down, and up and down,... One tour (heading up and down all 37 sections once) adds to approx. 1.2mi, approx. 40% uphill, 40% downhill, 20% flat as you walk from section to section, as measured by another runner. Good times &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everybody can go at his/her own pace to get a great workout, and we can cheer each other on across the sections. Every time I have been there many locals were working out; it is a great atmosphere as strangers root for one another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On-street parking as well as free parking right at the stadium (as you drive in through the gates around the stadium). Only one entrance into the stadium is open --&amp;gt; you have to walk up some stairs and you arrive in section 1. We will meet right there in Section 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be starting my workout at 7:30am sharp. I will be there approx. 10minutes early to 'meet and greet' all of you. Should you be arriving past 7:30am, yell my name, and I will 'wave' from another section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal is to complete 2 full sections, mixing using the seats and steps 50/50. I hope to complete this in less than 1.5hours without break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some background on what this meetup will be like: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2012/04/building-endurance-step-by-step/" class="linkified"&gt;http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2012/04/building-endurance-step-by-step/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://november-project.com/stadium/" class="linkified"&gt;http://november-project.com/stadium/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 (you can watch the video to get a sense of the steepness of the steps)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to the Stadium as provided by official website: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.gocrimson.com/directions/index" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.gocrimson.com/directions/index&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you need to bring: &lt;br /&gt;

 -something to drink &lt;br /&gt;

 -possibly dress in layers (weather dependent) &lt;br /&gt;

 -possibly a sweat towel &lt;br /&gt;

 I am not sure whether an evening event will occur on Saturday evening. If so, then the Stadium will be cleaned that morning and you canNOT leave your water bottle and/or jacket in one section; then you will need to carry your belongings with you. (Last weekend the cleaning crew was busy cleaning after a football game; they are awesome guys, stepping out of your way as you are running up and down, respecting our workouts in their workspace; but they will clean EVERYTHING; it was the only time a cleaning crew was in the Stadium thus far when I was there, so I say the odds are low; when they are not, you can leave your belongings in one place.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; You agree not to hold the Organizer, Event Organizers, Assistant Organizers, or any other members responsible for any injuries, mishaps, or any other situation that may happen at a planned event. You are responsible to research the event, know the area, and bring the proper gear and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Standing in section 1 of the Stadium</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica</member_name><member_id>10925522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369000441000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368649943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Run the Harvard Stadium Steps... The Steps We Love to Hate</name><id>119570062</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368963000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/119570062/</event_url></item>