<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>465 Foxon Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06471</zip><lat>41.330479</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-484-0588</phone><name>Doody's Restaurant</name><city>North Branford</city><id>822079</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.806252</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing a new Meetup for 40's...Let's Get Together and have Fun! (30-50ish)! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: Doody's Christmas Dinner and Karaoke. Dinner starts at 7 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: December 16, 2008 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Click the link below to find out! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Description: Hi All, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHRISTMAS PARTY at Doody's Restaurant/Bar in North Branford on Tuesday December 16th. This Place holds alot more people than Side Street. I am setting this limit to 75 people since the room usually is at least half full, and only holds 100 people. There is a bar area on the back side, for more seats.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Meetup price is only a $2 donation to cover miscellaneous fees. At 9 pm, a karaoke show starts. I hope some of you bring your voices. If you sing in the shower, car, or on stage, they are all good here. Dave, the Karaoke Jock has a lot of songs to pick from. For those of you who have ideas, remember to bring them to post so we can fill the calendar. IE: Place, dates available, time, Menu's, Entertainment, Etc. Lets all work together to fill the calendar. If you have that longing to sing, IT'S TIME TO SING, AND BE HEARD!!  If you just want to be a part of the party, and enjoy the fun, come along also.  We all want to meet you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a beef buffet for $10.95. On the regular menu they have sandwiches/Burgers for around $8. Full Dinners are up to $20. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Restaurant wants an approximate count on the Buffet, so they can provide enough food for us. I am going to ask questions when you sign up to get an approximate count to tell the restaurant. If you don't really know which way you would go, just guess. it's not really that important.  Please answer just your choice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dress code is Casual, Jeans and Sneakers are acceptable.  But for those of you who want to dress for Christmas, you'll look &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;HoT!!&lt;/span&gt;.  We will do a secret Santa, so if you want, you can bring a gift from between 5 and 15 dollars.  GAG gifts are acceptable.  For those who participate, you will get a gift in return.  There will also be a 50/50 raffle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Woooo Hoooooo. Welcome all new members to the group. It's CHRISTMAS TIME.  Party On ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve C.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Party will be in the front Hall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve C</member_name><member_id>6197158</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1231696570000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227664315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Doody's Dinner and Karaoke Christmas Party.  7 PM.</name><id>9231956</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229472000000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/9231956/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/5/global_6461797.jpeg</photo_url></item>