<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Members-Free, Non-members</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;The NEREIA Welcomes:&lt;/b&gt; LARRY GOINS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come see &lt;b&gt;Larry Goins&lt;/b&gt; and let him teach you his secrets that allow him to buy &lt;b&gt;10-15 properties a month&lt;/b&gt; without leaving his house!  His proven system will make real estate profits easier than ever!  You don't want to miss this event...it could change your life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Larry H. Goins&lt;/b&gt; is not only licensed as a mortgage lender and mortgage broker in North Carolina and South Carolina, he is also licensed in both North Carolina and South Carolina as a Real Estate Broker and General Contractor. He is a member of the North Carolina Association of Mortgage Professionals and a member of the National Association of Mortgage Professionals.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the past few years, Larry has served as President (2003 &amp;amp; 2004) of the Metrolina Real Estate Investors Association in Charlotte NC, a not-for-profit organization that has over 350 members and is the local chapter of the National Real Estate Investors Association. In addition to conducting his own sold out 3 day &lt;b&gt;Dream Big &amp;amp; Wakeup Wealthy Boot Camps&lt;/b&gt; several times a year, he is also an active real estate investor and speaks at various Real Estate Investment Associations about investing and finance. His new home study course, &lt;b&gt;The Ultimate Buying &amp;amp; Selling Machine&lt;/b&gt; has been a HUGE SUCCESS selling out 4 times within a 7-day period and the orders and testimonies keep rolling in!!. His latest software, Ultimate Property Analyzer, has already been released and has rapidly gained popularity as a valuable tool for new and experienced investors alike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;NEREIA and Associated REIA Members are admitted for FREE, Guests pay $20 Admission Fee&lt;br /&gt;For more information about our Memberships and how you can attend 10 local REIA meetings each month for FREE, Contact Us at NEREIA.  www.nereia.org or nereia@gsinet.net&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk into the front of the building, and straight ahead you will see our Welcome table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie Trajlinek</member_name><member_id>4673573</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294884626000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nereia</urlname><id>593272</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254960403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association November Meetup</name><id>qffsfympbgb</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257379200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nereia/events/11576038/</event_url></item>