<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>419 Andover Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.674090</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-685-3546</phone><name>Ethan Allen Interiors</name><city>North Andover</city><id>884400</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.125792</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SWISHISTA&lt;br /&gt;                      swapping.....the new shopping!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for Eco Fabulous Party! Experience ethical shopping,bargain hunting and social networking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                           Friday March 27th&lt;br /&gt;                           Ethan Allen Interiors Design&lt;br /&gt;                           419 Andover Street&lt;br /&gt;                           North Andover,M&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Merrimack Valley is about to embark on the hottest fashion trend: Swishista, The trend of swapping instead of shopping. The popularity of clothes swapping parties across the nation has been on the rise since the economic downturn last year. The idea of ethical shopping, bargain hunting and social networking is about to leap on the radar of women in the Merrimack Valley with his month's Swishista event at Ethan Allen Interiors in North Andover. Swishista, is derived from the term swish which is defined by the dictionary to mean to &amp;quot;rustle, as in silk material.&amp;quot; We have coined the term to mean to &amp;quot;rustle fabulous frocks from friends.&amp;quot; says event creator, Shari Wilkinson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Swishista is an eco-fabulous party, where you come and recycle your clothes and accessories by swapping with other fun and fabulous gals in the community. Landfills in the U.S. contain almost one million tons of shoes and clothes that are thrown away each year. This practice has a negative impact on the environment. Swishista is a great opportunity for guilt free disposable shopping. &amp;quot;Many of us are passionate about saving the planet, but we want to look good while doing it&amp;quot;, laughs event producer Lisa Knight.&amp;quot; It is the most glamorous way to recycle clothing.&amp;quot; The nonprofit organization, Dress For Success will receive any left over clothing from the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The beautifully decorated interior rooms at Ethan Allen create a boutique environment for the event. Learn style tips from Motives Cosmetics and relax with a complimentary mini massage by Bliss Spa. Enjoy a Women and Wine discussion by Samanta Turner of Wine-Sense accompanied by local wine distributors also food sampling by an Affair To Remember. &lt;br /&gt;             tickets are $10 and are on sale &lt;a href="http://www.drinkwaterproductions.com" target="_blank"&gt;click here to purchase tickets!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 visit www.drinkwaterproductions.com for event details and swishing rules!&lt;br /&gt;          lef over clothing will be donated to nonprofit organization      Dress For Success&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340338371000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>women-303</urlname><id>472102</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Girls Night Out Shopping Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235277802000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Swishista-Swapping is the new shoppping!</name><id>9794006</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238187600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/women-303/events/9794006/</event_url></item>