<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Science Shaping Our World (SHOW) – Ongoing Seminar/Networking Series: &lt;br /&gt;“The Development of Humanized Mouse Models for Biomedical Research”&lt;br /&gt;When:             Thursday, January 27 from 6:00 p.m. – 9:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:            Work Bar Boston &lt;br /&gt;                       711 Atlantic Ave, Lower Level &lt;br /&gt;                       Boston, MA 02111&lt;br /&gt;Register:          &lt;a href="http://showjanuary2011.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://showjanuary201...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Science Shaping Our World (SHOW) is an ongoing seminar and networking series that highlights areas of life science research possessing significant application potential. The seminar will bring together researchers, entrepreneurs, investors, technology and business professionals, among others in a setting where they can gain exposure and insight into the life science advancements changing our world. Further, we seek to promote active inter and cross-disciplinary networking toward fostering the creation of opportunities for the development of these emerging technologies and their applications. January’s SHOW will focus on the development and application of humanized mouse models toward the better understanding of human disease and therapeutics development. The presentation will focus on a general overview of humanized mouse models, a brief description of how these invaluable research models are created, and how they are used to study human immunology.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296229446000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294804931000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>“The Development of Humanized Mouse Models for Biomedical Research”</name><id>16017942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296169200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/16017942/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>