<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This group started off with a bang, and we have had a wonderful time every night we have gotten together.   This warrants some year-end celebrating.  So, prepare to dust off your holiday duds and your good cheer!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing makes the holidays more festive than spending an evening with good friends and good food--something this season has been full of.  So, let's have a night of it on Saturday, December 15.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The party will start at 7:00 and last until...  Please, feel free to bring a dish or appetizer for a buffet and the refreshment of your choice.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, for those who are feeling extra festive, please bring a (gender-neutral) gift under $10 for an exchange game.  There will also be multiple door prizes and surprises throughout the evening, celebrating what a wonderful season we have had as a Meetup group--you may even be honored.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll pass for the evening on the board games (because we'll have a large number of people), but get excited for some party games and milling with some people you might not have met at the previous Meetups.   Also, if this will be your first Meetup with us, prepare to have a great time and meet some fabulous people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(As always, some notes: For those who are allergic, this is a household with cats.  The house is pumpkin-colored.  Parking can be found on Lemon St., Northey St., and Cross St.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201033266000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192845049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yuletide Soiree</name><id>6582934</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197763200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/6582934/</event_url></item>