<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 49</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03215</zip><lat>43.955712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sandwich Mtn Trail Head</name><city>Waterville Valley</city><id>819567</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.507879</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A last minute Member lead hike to Jennings Peak.
.
More details:
This trailhead is not that far off of I-93 (10 miles east?) and in a beautiful area of NH.
 
From White Mountain Guide:
"This trail runs to the summit of Sandwich Mountain (Dome) (DonnaM-which we may or may not choose to do) from parking lot just of NH 49, 0.4 miles southwest of its junction of Tripoli Road. There are fine views from the trail at several different elevation levels..."
 
Brook crossing and a steep climb to Noon Peak at 1.7 mi....beautiful mosses, passes several outlooks. Ledgy summit of Jennings Peak "which commands impressive views".
 
Sandwich Trail to Drakes Brook Trail : 2.7 miles, 1850 ft, 2 hrs. 15 min.
(Option) Sandwich Trail to Sandwich Dome:  3.9 miles, 2600 ft, 3 hrs. 15 min.
 
Then ascend the Drakes Brook Trail:
 
Some switchbacks but described elsewhere on the internet as "the grades on Drakes Brook Trail are much gentler ..."
 
Drakes Brook Trail from intersection of Sandwich Trail back to trailhead: 3.2 miles, 1850ft, 2 hrs 35 min.
 
Options: 1) Sandwich Dome which is on a couple of peakbagger's lists; 2) Fletcher's Falls which doubles back from Drakes Brook Trail for about a mile.
 
I've done way much harder hikes than this one (from the description of the White Mountain Guide), so it should be a fun, casual day out, some great views, water, and hopefully great company! - DonnaM
&gt; ----------------------------------------------------------------


email Donna asap  if you will be coming.
&gt; ----------------------------------------------------------------</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249911592000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249607490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jennings Peak</name><id>11055063</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249738200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11055063/</event_url></item>