<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Lang Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.899410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>664559</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I need to walk the puppy so thought I would invite anyone who would like to join us along.  We'll meet in the parking lot at Northwest Park in Windsor and head out for about one-and-one-half hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More on Northwest Park including directions on their website, &lt;a href="http://www.northwestpark.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.northwestpark.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please know that I will have my very large and very active puppy, who will no doubt go swimming in the reservoir and come out and shake on anyone near!  So if you are not a dog fan, this may not be the hike for you.  If you have a dog you want to bring along, feel free -- leashes required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking lot.  I drive a tan/gold Ford Edge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252618359000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252369259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Short walk at Northwest Park</name><id>11313458</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252445400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11313458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>