<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>948 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.369298</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Weeks footbridge Charles River</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1285312</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117472</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2010 REUNION VILLAGE Sat, Oct 23rd&lt;br /&gt;Located on the  Boston side of the Charles River which is &amp;quot;best view at the half way spot for the races&amp;quot; between Week's and Anderson Bridges&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN OR SHINE Event: Be prepared to bring &lt;i&gt;rain gear &lt;/i&gt;and dress for cold weather as needed. Do bring binoculars and mud shoes. You may bring a lawn chair or blanket as there is NO SEATING at this event anywhere along the river.  There is a &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;shuttle bus&lt;/span&gt; available however some of us will be  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;biking&lt;/span&gt; the distances along the river between reunion village at the footbridge and the Fitness Expo at Soldier's Field Park. There is no parking...cars are not permitted.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's Meet at the Week's Foot Bridge (&lt;b&gt;Cambridge side&lt;/b&gt;) In front of the Chicago UNOs Pizza and Chipotle Food Booths at 1PM. At 1:30 we walk over to the Boston side and walk along the river to &amp;quot;REUNION VILLAGE&amp;quot;(Center Tent). The center tent sells beer and wine (cash only, plus $3 admission for all day access; 2 persons for $5...so let's go inside in pairs...&lt;i&gt;I have preregistered with &amp;quot;Lesley University&amp;quot; for  free admission.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Check with your college or university to see if you can preregister to also have free admission&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes: You may bring your own food into the village...However, no alcohol into the village from outside. Wine and Beer are available for purchase in the village. No alcohol beyond the village is allowed.....I have preregistered with &amp;quot;Lesley University&amp;quot; for  free admission. &lt;i&gt;Check with your college or university to see if you can preregister to also have free admission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Fitness Expo: Try out the rowing machines and see what the fitness pros have to say about rowing as a sport. This is the second of two places to get food at booths&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING : Parking will be impossible in the Charles river area. Parking is available at the Alewife T stop. Take the Red line T to Harvard Square. Walk 6 blocks on JFK street toward the Charles River. Memorial Drive..and both JFK and Anderson Bridges will be CLOSED&lt;/b&gt;...so Take the Red Line to Turn left onto Memorial Drive. The Weeks footbridge bridge will be a few blocks away along the river.Food booths will be at the foot of the Week's Footbridge Bridge on the Cambridge side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING ONLY FOR THOSE COMING FROM NEW HAMPSHIRE:  Parking is unrestricted in Cambridge on Sunday but very difficult to find the day of the big event. The key is to get to Cambridge EARLY before noon. When you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;..alert me by making a comment about needing help to find parking so that I my assist you. Please remember that your GPS will not tell you about the bridge and road closures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1965, the Charles River has welcomed a breadth of athletes from near and far to participate in the world's largest two day regatta. But the fun isn't limited to competitors - there are many opportunities for spectators to share in the weekend's racing and festivities.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2010 Reunion Village Hours: 12 -5PM&lt;br /&gt;The Village offers a fun and relaxed atmosphere located at the halfway point in the race on the Boston side of the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome at the Village. Clubs, schools, alumni groups, parents, boosters and travel groups are all urged to visit! Admission is $3/person (or 2 for $5) for unlimited day access. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hocr.org/home/default.asp" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;www.hocr.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will disclose my cell number  after you rsvp "yes"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288739956000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281533962000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHARLES RIVER REGATTA: REUNION VILLAGE/FITNESS EXPO</name><id>14389085</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287849600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/14389085/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/e/global_17946478.jpeg</photo_url></item>