<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.566138</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artichokes</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>1269592</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184882</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Artichokes and the Inviting Meetup has asked for an RSVP update since there is a minimum for the free room. There are&amp;nbsp;over 40&amp;nbsp;people from 3 groups attending. Please update your RSVP if you will be attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melody Gaeta and the Wakefield Weeknights Group has invited the Red Sox Natives and Boston Happy Hour to their monthly Happy Hour at Artichokes in Wakefield on Wednesday, November 16&amp;nbsp;at 6:30pm. Patti and&amp;nbsp;Melody from Wakefield Weeknights will be hosting and are very friendly.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the LAST Happy Hour at Artichokes until the Spring of 2012. Melody has reserved the entire lower level of Artichokes for this evening. We will have our own bar, lounge and special guest bartender, Charlie Sheen. Artichokes is located in the former Wakefield YMCA building. If you have never been to Artichokes here is your chance.&amp;nbsp;Sample the martini and wine lists, have a drink at the bar, order dinner from&amp;nbsp;the full menu,&amp;nbsp;relax and socialize in this intimate setting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay as you order&amp;nbsp;drinks and food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friends, guests, and co-workers are welcome. Arrive early or later. Stay as long as you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public transit access is via the 136 and 137 MBTA bus stopping at Wakefield Square or the Reading/Haverhill Commuter Rail station&amp;nbsp;on North Street, a 5 minute walk from the venue.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter and proceed down the stairs. We have reserved the entire lower level room, bar and bartender.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melody Joy Gaeta, Realtor</member_name><member_id>3036353</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321575793000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319563670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour at Artichokes Lower Level in Wakefield by Invite (with other groups)</name><id>38662862</id><headcount>43</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321486200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/38662862/</event_url></item>