<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/b/event_5825323.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm not one to go out on New Year's Eve, and was just waiting for the forecast to see if the weather was going to hold out for this...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potluck and Bonfire (should be possible since it is going to rain Friday into Saturday, then clear up)&amp;nbsp; I won't know until 5pm on the bonfire, but we can still do the potluck and party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring an appetizer, or healthy munchy to share.&amp;nbsp; Maybe some can bring sweets, but I'd rather the good stuff.&amp;nbsp; I'm trying to watch my sugar and cholesterol...lol.&amp;nbsp; lately I've been watching it go up...water and soda will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please park on my side of the street only.&amp;nbsp; Bring an outdoor chair, and some slippers for inside, so my floors aren't a total disaster, when everyone leaves ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BYOB and if you drink too much, I will be calling AAA, they are offering a free "tipsy tow" and ride to anyone who needs it, or I'll get you where you're going myself.&amp;nbsp; If you don't come, but want to save the number here it is 1-800-222-4357.&amp;nbsp; I don't have any plans on drinking, other than a champagne toast (I have one bottle, if anyone would like to bring another)&amp;nbsp; Bring a sleeping bag, if you think it will be necessary ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have the whole family coming over for New Year's day, so I'm going to have to ask everyone to be out by 1-1:30am the latest.&amp;nbsp; I'll need my rest...lol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love to bring in the New Year with my very good friends, don't know if I'll make the dance on Friday, as it is supposed to snow, and I'm a real chicken in the snow.&amp;nbsp; Plus I've got a full weekend.&amp;nbsp; Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugs and a Happy, Healthy, Safe and Prosperous New Year to you all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;susan&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll email my address/phone number to those of you who respond with a "yes" or "maybe"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325468603000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325167419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck and Bonfire on New Years Eve ;)</name><id>45827372</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325376000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/45827372/</event_url></item>