<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; This hike was originally scheduled for May 31st, but has been rescheduled two weeks later due to there still being large amounts of snow present.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance&lt;/b&gt;: 11.41 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;: 4321 ft &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time&lt;/b&gt;: 7 hours and 55 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the trail, roughness, steepness, and exposure this hike will only be done in reasonably good weather. If there is even a small chance of rain, high winds, if the trail is wet from previous rain, water levels are high, or snow and ice is still present this trip will be rescheduled. It may get rescheduled several times, but it will happen. If you RSVP Yes and I don't know you I may contact you to assess that you are prepared for this hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start up the Great Gulf Trail to the Madison Gulf Trail. Then we will climb up Madison Gulf (steeply) to Star Lake, the Parapet, and Madison Hut. From there we will either go over Mt. Madison or bypass around it depending on how everyone is doing. We will go down the Osgood Trail to rejoin the Great Gulf Trail, closing the loop and back to the start. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to expect&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Great Gulf Trail - This is the first 2.78 miles and is a moderate climb with just over 1000 ft of elevation gain. We will climb a high gravelly bank called The Bluff which will give good views into the Gulf and surrounding mountains. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Madison Gulf Trail - This is the fun part (or not) depending on your tastes. It climbs 2600 feet in 2.6 miles. That is 1000 feet per mile. The AMC guide describes as: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;The section of this trail on the headwall of Madison Gulf is one of the most difficult in the White Mountains, going over several ledge outcrops, bouldery areas, and a chimney with loose rock. The steep slabs may be slippery when wet, and several ledges require scrambling and the use of handholds? Hikers with short arms may have a particular problem reaching the handholds. Stream crossings may be very difficult in wet weather. The trail is not recommended for the descent, for hikers with heavy packs, or in wet weather. Allow extra time, and do not start up the headwall late in the day. The ascent of the headwall may require several hours more than the estimated time; parties frequently fail to reach the hut before dark because of slowness on the headwall.&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parapet Trail - From here we can access The Parapet (a ledge with excellent views over the Gulfs), Star Lake, Madison Hut (opened June 4th, water available), and Mt. Madison. This trail can also be used to skirt around Mt. Madison if we are not up for more climbing. From the Hut to Mt. Madison is about half a mile and 600 vertical feet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Osgood Trail - This is used for descent back to the Great Gulf Trail. It follows the crest of a crescent shaped ridge over 10 or 12 small rocky peaks with rough footing. It then descends the crest entering the trees. This section of descent is steep. What goes up must come down. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;Disclaimer and things you must know&lt;/a&gt;. Cancellation will be posted by 12 PM the day before. Please update any Maybe RSVPs by 9 PM Wednesday the 11th of June. After that time they will be considered as No RSVPs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213621972000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>This is part one of a series of hikes I have planned in the Great Gulf area. This is the easiest of the three but is by no means easy.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209243077000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Madison Gulf: Part 1 of a 3 hike series in the Great Gulf</name><id>7818187</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213448400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7818187/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/d/global_3924973.jpeg</photo_url></item>