<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ballsbridge </address_2><address_1>27 Pembroke Road </address_1><lat>53.332642</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lansdowne Hotel</name><city>Dublin 4</city><id>956497</id><country>ie</country><lon>-6.240982</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hey there, all my Ireland Peeps. What a treat...Jeff and his Dublin Group are hosting a great evening for us while we are in Ireland!!!&lt;br /&gt;This was on his meetup site.The site is NEW AND NOT SO NEW IN DUBLIN.  Read on...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the 13th November 34 Members of the &amp;quot;Have Fun, Will  Travel&amp;quot; meet up from the United States ( Connecticut , New York, New Jersey &amp;amp; Mass.) will visit Dublin and Ireland for a week. As part of the trip The New and Not so New have suggested that we have an event at the Irish House Party. Come and Join us for Food Music and Fun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Irish House Party is completely unique in Dublin. Unlike any other traditional Irish music night in the city, it is organised and hosted by All-Ireland Champion traditional Irish musicians and dancers in an intimate and homely setting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are no stages, microphones or fake antiques hanging from the walls commonplace at the many 'Irish music nights' around Dublin. This has made the evening hugely popular with both Irish guests and guests from abroad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On arrival you are welcomed by your host for an evening of traditional Irish music and Irish dancing that will both entertain and educate. You can take part as much as you like or simply sit back in comfortable surroundings and enjoy the best traditional Irish music and Irish dancing party in Dublin.  All of this at an elegant and historical Dublin 4 city location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is €43.00...approximately $65.00 US dollars&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Booked as New and Not So New in Dublin-</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258575630000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256196790000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Food Music And Fun -Dinner &amp; Live traditional Irish music -Craic &amp; Ceol </name><id>11684760</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258156800000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/11684760/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/6/global_11354262.jpeg</photo_url></item>