<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Middletown</address_2><address_1>85 Miner Hill Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miner Hill Golf Course</name><city>Middletown</city><id>567976</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><fee><label>4 Lessons $100 Online</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>$130 at the Golf Course</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Golf 101 Is A Complete Hands-On Course Ideal For New Golfers And Anyone Who Wants To Improve Their Game&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Golf 101 Starts At The Driving Range, And Then Brings You On The Course For Real Playing Experience&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf 101 starts out at the driving range, developing your swing, video swing analysis, golf rules, terms and strategy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next, we work on putting and chipping. The next lessons are on the golf course to play a scramble, learning about technique, course management, rules, and scoring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All clubs, equipment, driving range fees, golf course fees, and golf balls are included, &lt;br /&gt;-or bring your own clubs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 4 Golf 101 Lessons total 6 hours of hands-on instruction is only $100 ($17 per hour) and are taught by Certified Golf Professionals&lt;br /&gt;Class size is kept small to ensure personal attention - the best value available in Golf Lessons anywhere!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The best way to improve your Golf score is out on the course with playing Golf lessons  -Having a Golf Pro teach and coach you while you are playing Golf is so much better than just practicing on the range.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting with the basics of Golf, you will learn how the game is played, terminology, technique, strategy, and skills to make you a competitive Golfer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each lesson starts with 30 minutes of warm-up including stretching, putting and chipping -or hitting a bucket at the driving range. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next, on to the Golf Course and Driving Range with our Golf Pro, as he helps you improve your swing, technique, and course management while you play - so there is no down-time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Video Swing Analysis is included to help you improve your swing and technique&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RESERVE YOUR SPOT TODAY! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Your 4 Golf 101 Lessons are:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday June 14 -3 to 4:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Saturday June 21 -3 to 4:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Saturday June 28 -3 to 4:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Saturday July 5 No Lesson Holiday Weekend&lt;br /&gt;Saturday July 12 -3 to 4:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday July 1 -6:30pm to 8:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday July 8 -6:30pm to 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday July 15-6:30pm to 8:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday July 22 -6:30pm to 8:00pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve Your Spot Today! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign up below by clicking on PayPal, Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTGolfTips.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.CTGolfTips.com&lt;/a&gt;, or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;CTGolfTips.com is able to offer Golf 101 Lessons at an unbeatable price &lt;br /&gt;- just $100 for 6 Hours of Golf Instruction ($17 per Hour)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213645005000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212264173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Golf 101 Lessons for New Golfers - Learn From The Pros! Start -June 14 </name><id>8050071</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213471800000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/8050071/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/f/global_3735727.jpeg</photo_url></item>