<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>160 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351261</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.266.1122</phone><name>Bar Lola</name><city>Boston</city><id>702736</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.078624</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;*FOR NEW MEMBERS ONLY*&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a lot of you who are new to the group (or have joined but never made an event), and this is a great way for you to find out about nightlife events and to meet other new members. It can be difficult to go to an event where you may not know anyone - and this is especially true for the new member meetups. People are almost always very friendly and open to conversation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bar Lola has great atmosphere and they serve a wonderful selection of tapas, along with wine and sangria. This will be a very laid back, no agenda meetup - just food, drinks and good company!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: I have a reservation under my name (Kanwar) for 5pm at Bar Lola, and the event will last until 8pm.  If you come after 7pm, be sure to give me a call.  My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site and if you have any problems finding the group, call/text at 410-404-4236. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Bar Lola is a Spanish Tapas Restaurant/Lounge located at 160 Commonwealth Ave, on the corner of Dartmouth St.  It is located 5 minutes from the Copley Square T station on the Green Line.  You will need to walk downstairs to enter the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;*FOR NEW MEMBERS ONLY*&lt;br /&gt;**If the RSVP is full, please put yourself on the wait list, as I will be opening up more spots as the event date approaches. I reserve the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout **&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site, call my cell if you need help finding the group.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1289249178000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288061331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New members meetup - Sunday Wine and Tapas</name><id>15229569</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288558800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/15229569/</event_url></item>