<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Love was definitely in the air during our Fantastic February Valentine's Pug Meetup. A great turnout as usual, will new faces as well as some seasoned ones! We had punch and exchanged Valentines, and Kelly made some wonderful treats as usual, cupcakes for the peeps and peanut butter bananas heart pug biscuits! Hopefully everyone had as good a time as we did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a lot of you know with Kely and my busy schedules, we are going to still attend, but step aside and let some other pug loving friends of ours be your gracious hostesses of the Grafton Pug Meetup. Luara Mazzola and Julie Bunce will be taking over the official duties of setting up these fun-themed monthly events starting in April along with a few understudies of their choice. If you are interested in lending a helping hand, please let them know&amp;nbsp;at the&amp;nbsp;March Meetup. We will make and official announcement at the March Meetup and passing the "Puggy Torch", which by the way will be a Luck of the Puggish, St Patty's Day theme. Please note the monthly meetup time has already officially changed from 1 to NOON. &lt;strong&gt;All future Meetups will be at NOON unless further notified, so just watch the website.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALSO, we will be having a special guest join us at the March Meetup, Sandy Quadros Bowles, the&amp;nbsp;Editor&amp;nbsp;from the&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://Grafton.Patch.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #004182"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafton.Patch.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, a online local news site who learned of our Pug Meetup and would like to come and take pictures and interview us!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are lots of surprises and wonderful things to come at the Grafton Pug Meetup, so if you have been thinking of joining us, nows the time to come, and if you've been away for a while, nows the time to get your precious puggie socialized and come on back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another quick note: We have so much fun at these meetups, but all comes with a small price to us as organizers. We do ask that each family pay a small $5 fee at the door when you arrive to each meetup so please be sure to bring that with you as your "ticket" in. It costs us money each month to be a member of this website, we always provide sweets and drinks and prizes and decorations all cost money. Any leftover, are donated to Pug Rescue organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Kelly and I truly enjoy being the Organizers of the Grafton pug Meetup. We hope that we have met each of you individually, and if we have not, please come up and introduce yourself at the next one. We are constantly trying to come up with new treats for our precious pugs, and ideas to keep it informative and interesting. We welcome all suggestions. It seems to be very personal and we all have tons of fun. We always welcome new members to come join in the fun and excitement at watching our little puggie friends romp and play in the spacious room at the Gibson Kennel in Grafton. Note: &lt;strong&gt;this is a PUG Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;...as not all breeds play well together. There are other small breed Meetups, but this is for PUGS ONLY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;******A receipt of current vaccinations must be brought with you in order to enter the play area (kennel rules)********* (this has not been strictly enforced at the Meetups but, it's better safe then sorry since the owner of the kennel did request we have this on-hand)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will ask for a $5 fee per family for each Meetup&lt;/strong&gt; to cover Meetup costs and any leftover money will be donated to the Curly Tail Pug Rescue as well as other animal related charity that we all agree on as a group. These donations go toward paying the monthly dues, snacks and to keep this website going so we can all see when the next Meetup is taking place. We will also do special events from time to time to keep it fun and interesting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you all and I look forward to playing again with all you pug lovers out there and your pups! =)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will introduce ourselves...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erin maguire</member_name><member_id>3828727</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth Mott</member_name><member_id>6811754</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>10300396</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301423902000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Puggy Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pug-569</urlname><id>252667</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6900024414</group_lon><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>fdfdnypfbjc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301155200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pug-569/events/16734031/</event_url></item>