<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>46 Bridge Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.763428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Behind chiropractic office</name><city>Nashua</city><id>7528542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449173</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly Nashua video screening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This month's video: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/16219493"&gt;What in the World are They Spraying?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/8/e/event_155729582.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Chemtrail/Geo-Engineering Coverup Revealed. By now everyone has seen crisscrossing streaks of white clouds trailing behind jet aircraft, stretching from horizon to horizon, eventually turning the sky into a murky haze. Our innate intelligence tells us these are not mere vapor trails from jet engines, but no one yet has probed the questions: who is doing this and why. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 With the release of this video, all of that has changed. Here is the story of a rapidly developing industry called geo-engineering, driven by scientists, corporations, and governments intent on changing global climate, controlling the weather, and altering the chemical composition of soil and water - all supposedly for the betterment of mankind.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Although officials insist that these programs are only in the discussion phase, evidence is abundant that they have been underway since about 1990 - and the effect has been devastating to crops, wildlife, and human health. We are being sprayed with toxic substances without our consent and, to add insult to injury, they are lying to us about it. Do not watch this documentary if you have high blood pressure. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Produced by G. Edward Griffin and Michael Murphy &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Be sure to join this Meetup group at &lt;a href="http://mv911t.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mv911t.org/&lt;/a&gt; to get automated email reminders. You can also join our Facebook group for discussion there: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/159949076301/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/159949076301/&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a new venue in Nashua at 46 Bridge Street in the rear of a chiropractic office. If you've been in Nashua for a while, you'll know the building as the old Maine Manufacturing Company office. Here's what it looks like: &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/2dAI" class="linkified"&gt;http://goo.gl/maps/2dAI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the parking in the rear and if that is full, there is some available on the right side of the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any folding chairs, please bring one for yourself. We're not sure we'll have enough. Also, plan to bring snacks. We can get this location set up better and better to suit our needs, so come on over so you can check it out and make suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll get together at the new place at 7, so please even come early or be there at 7 so we can get off to a prompt start.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the basement room that you access from the rear of the building</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346810741000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345678271000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - What In The World Are They Spraying?</name><id>qqflqcyqmbgb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346799600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/78932342/</event_url></item>