<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>545 Boylston</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.350512</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Vlora</name><city>Boston</city><id>712994</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075795</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Mobfather Mystery Dinner Cruise&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are invited to attend a surprise 40th birthday party cruise on Boston Harbor for the Mobfather, leader of Boston Mafia. But, after the boat has left the dock, it is the guests who are surprised when gunshots are fired and there's no way out until the family honor has been restored and the killer captured. Enjoy an interactive murder Mystery up close and personal with your favorite Hollywood mobsters including Marlin Brand &amp;quot;O&amp;quot;. Figure out who did it while enjoying a delicious Italian family style meal and great live music. Our talented CharActors add comedy and intrigue and personalized anecdotes to make this a night to remember. Question the suspects during the 2 and a half-hour cruise and maybe you could earn the title of super sleuth and win the prize.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Delectable Antipasto Salad&lt;br /&gt;A wonderful refreshing feast of crisp greens mingled with mortadella, capiocola, salami, and provolone cheese; vegetables, tasty Mediterranean olives and pepperocinis drizzled with our minced fresh herbs, balsamic Dijon vinaigrette&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ricotta Stuffed Shells&lt;br /&gt;Topped with our own savory fresh Basil Roma Plum Tomato Sauce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chicken Marsala&lt;br /&gt;Light and delicious with sautéed mushrooms&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mouthwatering Meatballs&lt;br /&gt;From Mama Lena’s Kitchen, served with freshly grated cheese&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gala Apple Crisp&lt;br /&gt;Scented with cinnamon, nutmeg and cloves&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara</member_name><member_id>6525575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219100881000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>40-plus</urlname><id>1222683</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2699966431</group_lon><name>40/50 Something Year Olds - Men &amp; Women Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216229269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cruise You Can't Refuse</name><id>8352299</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218927600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/40-plus/events/8352299/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/c/4/global_4814244.jpeg</photo_url></item>