<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sunday's performance is called Noche Flamenca with Lead Dancer Soledad Barrio.  &amp;quot;Madrid's Noche Flamenca celebrates the essence, purity and integrity of flamenco. The company has been hailed internationally for its transcendent and deeply emotional performances and is recognized as the most authentic flamenco touring ensemble in the field today. Featuring award-winning lead dancer Soledad Barrio.&amp;quot; The show starts at 7:00 and there is a pre-show talk from dance critic Debra Cash 45 minutes before the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket will cost $40.  Tickets normally go for $65, but I am going to get them from www.goldstar.com.  (This web site has discounted tickets to most Boston shows.)  So that we can have seats together, I set up a payment option on the event website and then I will purchase the tickets at one time.  You can purchase ticket on your own, but if you do, you probably won't have a seat with the group.  If you purchase your own ticket, please make a comment with your RSVP that you have a ticket.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any question, let me know.  This is going to be a good show and I'm looking forward to it.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting a inside the theater entrance with a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235443435000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233188159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flamenco Festival 2009</name><id>9623099</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234738800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/9623099/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/d/a/global_7131034.jpeg</photo_url></item>