<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Castle Rd, </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03087</zip><lat>42.814056</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Salem Town Forest</name><city>Salem </city><id>1184275</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.240704</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will avoid a section of the trail where a pond is partly thawed so dogs don't go swimming - please see my comment below&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Salem Town Forest is another great hiking spot. The conditions are probably the same as the Musquash hike but I'll be checking it out this week and will update the meet information after. There are some steepish hills at the beginning of the hike but they mellow out as you progress through... :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should be ok with our dogs roaming free as long as we can control them with our voices/whistles etc., I haven't hiked here as often as Musquash but always take Beau off-leash and have seen others with dogs free.  This is a great place to go as there are lots of woods and no roads to worry about once we get onto the trail. This trail system DOES allow ATV's and snowmobiles.  I actually found the hike more interesting than Musquash but that's probably because I just discovered it this past Spring.  In the summer there are some spots for the dogs to swim in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.salemnhconservation.org/pictures.php" target="_blank"&gt;Salem Town Forest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;help with directions:&lt;br /&gt;It may sound confusing but once you go you'll see how easy it really is to find.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take 93 to exit three. Take a right off the ramp. Follow Rte.111 East to Rte. 28. Take a right onto 28 south. Take a hard left at the large intersection w/ a Hess gas station (take the first left, the second has the Honda Dealership). Salem Town Forest is down 1/2 mile on the right. Parking is in a circle at the trail head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;more help:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/salem-town-forest-salem" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the sign at the trail head in the parking area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracey</member_name><member_id>8472167</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267494039000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265556459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salem Town Forest</name><id>12542633</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267284600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/12542633/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/c/global_12979836.jpeg</photo_url></item>