<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Annual Fall Middlesex Canal Walk&lt;br /&gt;Hosted by the Appalachian Mountain Club &amp;amp; Middlesex Canal Association&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Sunday, Oct 14, 2007&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Place: North Billerica&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our fall walk will originate at the Middlesex Canal Museum and Visitor Center in the Faulkner Mill, on Faulkner St. in North Billerica. The walk will cover the route of the canal south of the mills. Sites will include a lock, the anchors for the floating towpath bridge which once crossed the Concord River Mill Pond, and many stretches of canal, some still watered. The walk will cover about 3-4 miles over generally level wooded terrain and streets in about 2-3 hours, rain or shine. The Museum and Visitor Center will be open from 12 noon to 4pm. Our bookstore will be open as well.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: From Route 3 toward NH, take exit 28, Treble Cove Rd. At end of ramp turn left toward North Billerica. At about 3/4 mile, bear left at fork and cross Route 3A (traffic light). Follow the &amp;quot;S&amp;quot; turn in the road and continue straight (across Pollard St.) onto Talbot Street (passing to the right of St. Andrews Church). As you approach Talbot Mill, bear right onto Old Elm St. and cross the bridge by the dam (becomes Faulkner St.). Park in the lot on the right just after the bridge. The Middlesex Canal Museum and Visitor center is directly across the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.middlesexcanal.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.middlesexc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192555161000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190173701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middlesex Canal walk</name><id>6386735</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192382100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6386735/</event_url></item>