<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;Growing High BRIX Nutrient Dense Foods&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2010 Workshop Series &lt;br /&gt;with Organic Farmer Dan Kittredge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open to both backyard growers and professional farmers, these workshops include information, techniques, tools, and support necessary to become a producer of cutting edge maximum quality nutrient dense crops in the Northeast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2010 High BrixWorkshops are led by Real Food Campaign Director, Dan Kittredge, an organic farmer since 1984 who has directed a non-profit called, Remineralizethe Earth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;March 21&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how to facilitate biological life in soil: Tillage, Soil Aeration and Soil Dynamics. Specific recommendations based on soil tests. Hands on demonstration in the greenhouse for inoculating transplants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Workshops will be held at The Growing Green Wellness Center in Hartford or at UdderlyWooly Farm in Glastonbury on six Sundays. Cost is $50 per workshop and includes an delicious organic lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Email Imani@thegreenvibration.com to register.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://latebloomersfarm.com/images/ctnofa.png" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by Northeast Organic Farming Association’s (NOFA) CT Chapter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nutrient Dense Foods Workshop Program 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;January 24&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduction to the Real Food Campaign and Nutrient Dense quality standards. Learn basic&lt;br /&gt;soil agronomics and biological inoculation of seeds.&lt;br /&gt;Prepare potting soils and address mineral deficiencies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;March 21&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how to facilitate biological life in soil: Tillage, Soil Aeration and&lt;br /&gt;Soil Dynamics. Specific recommendations based on soil tests. Hands on&lt;br /&gt;demonstration in the greenhouse for inoculating transplants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;May 16&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perform plant sap analysis (brix) to discern effectiveness of foliar sprays&lt;br /&gt;and nutrient drenches. Learn techniques and timing for weed control,&lt;br /&gt;use the biodynamic planting calendar and interpret pH readings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 18&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consider long-term mineral management and whole farm system building.&lt;br /&gt;Analyze plants to determine what deficiencies exist. Identify weeds and&lt;br /&gt;their indication of soil condition. Participate in weedwalkthrough fields.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;September 19&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perform fall soil test to inform completion of mineral balancing. Learn how to keep tomatoes going one&lt;br /&gt;more flower &amp;amp; fruit cycle, and double your pepper crop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;November 21&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coordinate biology with cover crops and soil minerals.&lt;br /&gt;Plan for next year’s farm: Rotations, Fall Mineral Applications and Crop Planning. Make appropriate decisions about local soil conditions &amp;amp; remediation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269353017000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266358447000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nutrient Dense Food Growing Workshop</name><id>12621838</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269180000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12621838/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/3/global_13155667.jpeg</photo_url></item>