<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt. 114</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02809</zip><lat>41.677090</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-253-7482</phone><name>Colt State Park</name><city>Bristol</city><id>903157</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.278679</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please read the entire Write Up and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver before signing up for this event. &lt;br /&gt;

Event Rating: Moderate (Because of the length) &lt;br /&gt;

Distance: 6.0 Miles &lt;br /&gt;

Time Duration: 2 Hours &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Blaze Orange: Not Required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will walk three separate loops that if you do all three will end up being a total of six miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Colt State Park (CSP) in Bristol is often referred to as the 'gem' of the RI State Parks System. The entire western border of the park is an open panorama onto Narragansett Bay. Open year round, the park offers four miles of bicycle trails passing along the Bay and through 464 acres of groomed fruit trees, carefully nurtured flowering bushes, and manicured lawns. Rich in history, it proudly displays ten large playing fields, a historical museum, six picnic groves containing 400+ picnic tables and its' popular open air Chapel-By-The-Sea. &lt;br /&gt;

We will be meeting at five o'clock  at the statue of Senator Chafee across from the fishing pier parking lot in CSP. There is plenty of additional parking throughout the park. &lt;br /&gt;

Colt State Park is located off Hope Street (Route 114) in Bristol, RI. Headed south on RI 114, turn right at the traffic light onto Asylum road and follow Asylum Rood as it bears left toward a rotary. Turn right at the rotary past a kiosk to enter the park and follow the park road (Colt Drive) to the parking lot just past the bridge. The statue of Senator Chaffee will be on the left and the parking lot is on the right. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

Safety First!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liz</member_name><member_id>31266642</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368497121000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367891801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Colt State Park and if you behave....dinner</name><id>118099662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368392400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/118099662/</event_url></item>