<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Did you have a traditional Asian childhood? Then you probably had huge family gatherings that seemed to last all day...there was a ton of food, the kids ran around, and everyone asked how school was going!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Too many of us don't have extended family nearby, so let's get together and make sure our kids don't miss out on the same wonderful experience. Catch up on what's been going on the past month, make friends and plans for the coming month!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We'll do something different every month to keep things interesting. If you have suggestions, please contact Yooree.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This month our meal will be at the Williams residence in E. Arlington. &amp;nbsp;We will provide a main dish (think it's going to be gumbo), beverages, and probably dessert as well. &amp;nbsp;Please state in your RSVP what you'd like to bring (entree, appetizer, side dish, dessert, or beverage). Also, let us know if you have any dietary preferences/restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other things you should know:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can definitely have the Celtics-Knicks game on if people are interested in watching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My son is only 8 months and not quite mobile, so we're not really babyproofed yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to BYOT (toys) in case 8 month old toys will bore your kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a cat that will insist on socializing with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>East Arlington close to Mass Ave. and Capitol Theater.  Plenty of parking and 12 min walk from Alewife T.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330976804000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Parents &amp; Kiddies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>1371768</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Asian-American Families of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325900881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our Monthly Family Meal</name><id>ppfsxyqfbgb</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330891200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston/events/47023242/</event_url></item>