<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>America's Cup Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02840</zip><lat>41.489529</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newport Yachting Center</name><city>Newport</city><id>980750</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.316861</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE 6/2/12: Chowder Festival is Rain or Shine - no refunds. Hopefully the worst will have passed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am thinking of having us go to Parrot Club after we are done with festival if a stroll around wet Newport is not working out.  They have inexpensive salads to offset the chowder if you want and/or just for a drink(s).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I will be on the steps of Post Office at 2:45 to go into Festival for 3:00PM. Bring an umbrella and/or raincoat if it is still raining. Some of the Chowder Festival is under tents.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Keep RSVP up to date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s Cookin’ at the Great Chowder Cook Off?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, June 2, 2012, the legendary Great Chowder Cook-Off officially kicks off summer in Newport! Be a part of the original, largest, and longest running (over 30 years!), chowder bonanza in New England located right in the buzz of historic downtown Newport.  With a wide spread from national to regional competitors, festival-goers will taste-test a myriad of traditional and exotic chowders from all kitchens, then vote for the best in three categories: Clam, Seafood and Creative. The winners’ pots are bigger than ever this year making this culinary competition piping hot! In addition, we have added some  new and exciting culinary competitions, contests, live music and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, June 2, 12pm – 6pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Admission:&lt;/strong&gt; $25 / $20 Advance*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://newportwaterfrontevents.com/"&gt;http://newportwaterfrontevents.com/&lt;/a&gt; - buy tickets today -come and go from 12-6 all you want, but meet Meetup on the steps across the street of the Post Office at 2:45.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Parking in Newport: Mary's lot has the least expensive public parking. It is off of Thames Street. When you turn onto the one-way Thames Street after you pass Brick Alley Pub (yellow awning) on left look for the first left hand turn you can make - Mary's Street. Mary's lot is seconds away on right. Walk back tothames street and walk to the left towards the Post Office across on the corner of Memorial Blvd across the street from the Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For free Parking - it is a 10 min. walk after parking, but Kay street runs after Bellevue street and has free parking. Park - walk towards the Viking hotel make a right onto Bellevue street and follow to Memoria Blvd. Make a right on Memorial and at bottom on right is Post office on the corner of Memorial and Thames Street.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lonnie is meeting guests at 2:45 on the steps of the Post Office on the corner of Thames and Memorial across from the chowder fest (to avoid crowds and you can sit on the steps) we are entering Fest promptly at 3PM.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>michael </member_name><member_id>6215889</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lonnie</member_name><member_id>6911660</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338765469000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newportfriends</urlname><id>429443</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>Newport Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337455155000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Newport Chowder Festival / stroll around Newport after for some food/drinks..</name><id>65488432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338660900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newportfriends/events/65488432/</event_url></item>