<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>FREE every WEDNESDAY w/</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>promo T-Shirt</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>NEW Event: ?Wacky Wednesday? 08/08&lt;br /&gt;What: Comedian Jim David   (see below).&lt;br /&gt;When: Wednesday, August 8 ? gather @ 6:15 PM&lt;br /&gt;Where: ?FUNNY BONE? Comedy Club (within Manchester?s Buckland Hills Mall)&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $13.50, or FREE with promo Tee-shirt - Must be over 21 ? all are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read all details below and DO NOT hit reply or write directly.  Please RSVP ?yes? (by 4:00 on the day of the event) via my FREE ?FREE Live Outdoor Music? MeetUp online calendar reservation system.  Only by doing so, can we hold a seat for you if running late.  (If applicable, please change your ?yes? to ?no? by 4:00 on the day of the event to free up that seat for someone else!)  To cut down on emails, I will ONLY post updates, etc. on my MeetUp site and strongly recommend you check it for any changes after 3:00 on the day of the event.  You?ll also see many other events that are going on and see who else has RSVP?d for this event, too!  Please go to:  &lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/"&gt;http://livemusic.meet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We gather 6-24 (some regulars, always some newbies, too!) from our combined ?MeetUp? and ?Single Event? ?Wacky Wednesday? Group at Manchester?s new ?Funny Bone? stand-up comedy club.  A fun and funny time is had by all!  Rather than pay the $10-20 admission fee, almost everybody purchases a promo Tee-shirt (only $15) to gain admission to this and (almost) all WEDNESDAY performances for FREE by wearing your promo Tee-shirt to the Box Office ? forever (whether attending as part of our irregularly scheduled group, or not).  Such a deal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After RSVP?ing ?yes?, simply show up and gather in the ?Funny Bone? BAR @ 6:15 (after picking up your FREE ticket from the Box Office by buying and/or wearing your promo Tee-shirt).  This will give us a chance to gather, have a drink, chat, and enter as a ?group?, thus allowing us to sit together as their policy is ?first come, first seated?.  Look for Rob P. (55, 5?11, 210#, brown hair, glasses).  When the Club doors open at 6:30, those present will enter together so we can be assigned good tables together and optionally have appetizers, dinner, drinks (no minimum; separate checks have been pre-approved) and get to know each other while waiting for the show to begin at 7:30 (lasting to @ 9:00).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I?ll ?try? to hold seats ONLY for those who?ve RSVP?d ?yes? via my free MeetUp reservation calendar (see above), as no doubt some may need to run late.  If entering after 6:30, please ask the ticket taker to assign you a seat with, or nearest to, ?Rob?s Wacky Wednesday? group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All (over 21) are welcome to join us!  Invite your friends and encourage them to join the ?Single Event? www.TheSingleEvent.com and ?MeetUp? www.MeetUp.com to be invited to these, and MANY MORE fun activities of all sorts!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please MapQuest directions to: 194 Buckland Hills Drive, Manchester, CT 06042.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ?Funny Bone? is located within the Buckland Hills Mall, on the first floor, between JC Penney and Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, via the external ?Blue Turtle? entryway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Funny Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: I organize this, and many other events, as a volunteer but get inundated with numerous emails and phone calls asking about information clearly posted within my detailed announcements.  As such, I can no longer address you individually, but will post periodic updated information on my free MeetUp calendar.  Please RSVP ASAP, and check the online posting after 3:00 PM on the day of the event for any last-minute changes.  Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please visit or call the Box Office (860) 432-8600 for info regarding the FREE ?Wacky Wednesday? Tee-Shirt promo and/or check their web site: www.HartfordFunnyBone.com for upcoming shows, general information, bios, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** This Week?s ?Headliner?: ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jim David&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JIM DAVID's comedy has been seen on his own 1/2 hour special &amp;quot;Comedy Central Presents Jim David,&amp;quot; as an uninformed comic pundit on Comedy Central's &amp;quot;Tough Crowd With Colin Quinn,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Out on the Edge&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;USO Tour.&amp;quot; He was a guest &amp;quot;comedy consultant&amp;quot; on Bravo's smash &amp;quot;Queer Eye For the Straight Guy,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Greatest Things About Being....&amp;quot; He has written for The Advocate and Us Weekly. He has also appeared on ABC's &amp;quot;The View,&amp;quot; Comedy Central's &amp;quot;Comic Cabana,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;New Joke City&amp;quot; with Robert Klein, NBC's &amp;quot;Comedy Showcase&amp;quot; with Louie Anderson, A&amp;amp;E's &amp;quot;Caroline's&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Evening at the Improv,&amp;quot; MTV's &amp;quot;Half Hour Comedy Hour,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Dateline NBC,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Star Search,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Last Call&amp;quot; and others. He performed on Comedy Central's &amp;quot;Friar's Club Roast of Rob Reiner&amp;quot; and hosted the webcast of Comedy Central's &amp;quot;Friar's Club Roast of Hugh Hefner&amp;quot; A headliner across the world, he can be heard on his CDs, Eat Here and Get Gas (2000) and Live From Jimville (2003). He is two time winner of the MAC (Manhattan Assn. of Clubs &amp;amp; Cabarets) Award for Outstanding Comedian and the Backstage Magazine Bistro Award for Outstanding NY Comedian. He has appeared on Broadway, Off-Broadway, in films, and in his one-man comedy &amp;quot;South Pathetic&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186784624000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186526068000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Wacky Wednesday": Comedian Jim David</name><id>6141721</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186611300000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6141721/</event_url></item>