<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>Meetup.com Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to all of you who attended the June NLP meetup. It was another great meeting, this time focusing on an NLP technique for changing beliefs. In keeping with the spirit of NLP, rather than simply talking about it, we all practiced helping each other change less-than-useful beliefs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For July:   This month?s meeting is going to be even more open than usual.  I?ve got a bunch of NLP techniques that I?d be excited to teach (Six-step reframing, Walt Disney strategy, Einstein sub-strategies, Quick allergy cure, visual swish, more language patterns).  I may take a vote at the meeting to see which one(s) we?ll do.  Alternately, if people come to the meeting with problems they?d like to get solved, you may end up learning some new NLP through demonstration.  Let?s see what happens!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;July's NLP meetup does not depend on having attended any of the previous NLP meetups. It also does not presuppose that you know anything about NLP. Everyone is welcome, from beginners to experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you. &lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185059121000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183075731000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Neuro Linguistic Programming July Meetup</name><id>5950344</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184886000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/5950344/</event_url></item>