<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>811 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.350563</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-345-5432</phone><name>Rudi's Cafe&amp;Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>1220315</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110346</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Successful Anonymous and Networlding Boston are collaborating on our event on June 8th at 6:00pm at Rudi's Cafe/Verve Lounge 811 Mass Ave in Boston, with a featured guest speaker, Neil Licht, Managing Director “HERE WE ARE” &lt;u&gt;How to Reach Prospects and Capture Business in our Ever Changing Market Place&lt;/u&gt;  Neil will focus on giving us a roadmap for thriving and growing our business in this dynamic, ever changing world.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Here We Are&amp;quot; will help you to learn how to use 2 proven key sales success axioms to thrive in your changing audience and targeted marketplace &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.    “Target audiences” do things for their reason’s not yours - Find out what matters to them, use it to retool messaging so it connects with those unique issues and helps address them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.    Imagine a sign on a person’s forehead saying “so what” – Understand their priorities, values, what they spend for, why- Retool specific approaches to address those values. You will connect!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Licht has 25 years of experience in helping businesses successfully proactively manage changes in a marketplace, retool and be proactive to thrive in a changing business environment.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, there will be time for 'elevator speech'/introductions and open networking, so be sure to bring your business cards as you are guaranteed to be meeting fellow professionals. The methodology behind growth and expansion is incredibly important in the business world. Pooling resources, gaining knowledge and fresh perspectives, and surrounding yourself with fellow 'drivers' will undoubtedly help in your own professional and personal development. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dimitry</member_name><member_id>10566344</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276098679000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Success Addicts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>successfulanonymous</urlname><id>1551084</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Successful Anonymous</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274713944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>S.A. &amp; Networlding Boston present: How to Reach Prospects and Capture Business</name><id>13577712</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276034400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/events/13577712/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/3/global_13312019.jpeg</photo_url></item>