<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Haverhill rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03079</zip><lat>42.841980</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>America's Stonehenge</name><city>Salem</city><id>3434042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.203697</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/6/4/event_95239812.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is America's Stonehenge?&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Built by a Native American Culture or a migrant European population? No one knows for sure. A maze of man-made chambers, walls and ceremonial meeting places, America's Stonehenge is most likely the oldest man-made construction in the United States (over 4000 years old).&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Like Stonehenge in England, America's Stonehenge was built by ancient people well versed in astronomy and stone construction. It has been determined that the site is an accurate astronomical calendar. It was, and still can be, used to determine specific solar and lunar&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; events of the year.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Various inscriptions have been found throughout the site including Ogham, Phoenician and Iberian Punic Script. Dr. Barry Fell of Harvard University did extensive work on the inscriptions found at the site. They are detailed in his book America B.C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;America's Stonehenge is home to eight &lt;strong&gt;alpacas&lt;/strong&gt;. They are here year round for your enjoyment. We also sell 100% alpaca yarn made from our animals in the gift shop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/9/0/event_95242672.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After visiting America's Stonehenge, which should be about one hour, we will head over the the &lt;strong&gt;Windham Country Store&lt;/strong&gt; for lunch. The store&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;offers a wide variety of unique new gifts and antiques. Ramble through the store and&amp;nbsp;discover old coffee mills, dishes, crocks, and furniture. Here you can find primitive folk art, custom wood crafts,&amp;nbsp;painted glass, and beautiful pottery. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Local artists help supply the store with a fresh look at the many talents&amp;nbsp;found in the State of New Hampshire. We have cards, jewelry, stained glass, knit gloves and mittens. Candles,&amp;nbsp;hand-made soaps, and fresh seasonal potpourri fill four rooms with their scents. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The Kitchen&lt;/span&gt; Homemade Foods, Breakfast, &amp;nbsp;Lunch, &amp;nbsp;Coffees and Teas along with Dessert. We have everything you need. &lt;br /&gt;

 One stop shopping and YES we have seating available as well as take out! We have a cozy dining room with some old&amp;nbsp;nostalgic tables and nice music.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.windhamjunction.com/index.html"&gt;http://www.windhamjunction.com/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those of us who would like to get a little more exercise can take a walk on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Windham Rail Trail, conveniently located 150 feet behind the country store. &amp;nbsp;It is a beautiful, newly paved 4 miles scenic&amp;nbsp;trail south that is perfect to walk or bike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event fee covers your admission to America's Stonehenge, PayPal fees, organizer dues paid to Meetup, and an organizer fee.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1330972387000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329757642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>America's Stonehenge &amp; Windham Junction Country Store</name><id>53050562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330876800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/53050562/</event_url></item>