<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25A Portland Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.196813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-516-3276</phone><name>The Farm Bar &amp; Grille</name><city>Dover</city><id>4790072</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870963</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brave Boat Book Group&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, a non-fiction book discussion group!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We read and discuss most any genre of non-fiction including, biography, memoir, history, science, politics, nature, the arts, cooking, travel, current affairs, interpersonal relations... you name it. Our goal is to learn about all sorts of new ideas, things, trends, and cultures - and to make new friends in the process. The only ground rules are that everyone is at all times respectful of the ideas and opinions of others, and that everyone be conscious of allowing others time to speak.  &lt;em&gt;Be nice. Be brief.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;This Month's Selection:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : xx-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pine Barrens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;by John McPhee&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;156pp. Originally published in the New Yorker, 1967. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Most people think of New Jersey only as a suburban-industrial corridor that runs between New York and Philadelphia. Yet in the low center of the state is a near wilderness, larger than most national parks, which has been known since the seventeenth century as the Pine Barrens. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Although New Jersey has the heaviest population density of any state, huge segments of the Pine Barrens remain uninhabited. The few people who dwell in the region, the “Pineys,” are little known and often misunderstood. Here McPhee uses his uncanny skills as a journalist to explore the history of the region and describe the people—and their distinctive folklore—who call it home. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;John McPhee has&lt;/strong&gt; at least 32 books and numerous awards to his credit. He has written about folklore, natural resource issues, geology, tennis, ecology, and many other topics. At age 81, he still teaches nonfiction writing to undergrads at Princeton University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: Last Wednesday of the month - 6:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: The Farm Bar &amp;amp; Grille in Dover, NH. &lt;br /&gt;

 ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Membership&lt;/strong&gt;: Your first meeting is free. After that, membership dues are $2/meeting, or $12 per year. Dues may be paid in person, or online here: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Brave-Boat-Books/events/45224832/"&gt;Brave Boat Membership Dues&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release -&lt;/strong&gt; AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Brave Boat Book Group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. This includes any risks associated with driving to and from meetings, and consumption of alcohol before, during or after meetings. Participation in this activity is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meetings are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337867457000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326993756000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brave Boat Book Group: The Pine Barrens</name><id>48766462</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337812200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/48766462/</event_url></item>