<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's join in on this event!&lt;br /&gt;Greetings! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once in a while you'll get a tip from an unexpected source.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This one came by way of Slow Food Boston. You know, they're the folks who encourage you to eat foods grown nearby while they're in season. Think asparagus from Concord in April, rather than asparagus from Peru in November.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a short, delicious step from slow asparagus to slow wine. When you're used to considering locality in your food, it's natural to also consider it in your wine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Which means that when a Slow Food devotee recommends a wine - or, in this case, a wine buyer - we sit up and take notice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Thursday, January 22, Slow Food Boston will host a tasting of wines orchestrated by wine buyer Felisha Foster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ms. Foster finds wines that, according to Slow Food Boston, &amp;quot;express something about their origin, some kind of intent on the part of the winemaker to identify him or herself not as part of some global industrial marketplace but rather as a representative of a given place in a given season.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What wines are they, exactly?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We don't know yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But we do know that they'll be French. There will be six of them. They'll be paired with (slow) appetizers. The tasting will be held at Dave's Fresh Pasta in Davis Square. And the whole night will cost you $35.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Haven't you been wanting to s...l...o...w... down, anyway?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT: Tasting of Slow French Wines&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Dave's Fresh Pasta, Davis Square&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Thursday, January 22 at 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;COST: $35&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP: &lt;a href="http://www.slowfoodboston.com/events.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.slowfoodbo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3552363</member_name><member_id>3552363</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240078236000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231334059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tasting of Slow French Wines</name><id>9466790</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232668800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/9466790/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/4/f/global_5427151.jpeg</photo_url></item>