<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Chestnut Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.818417</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The ROI Food &amp; Music</name><city>Providence</city><id>7381892</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.410042</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check o&lt;span&gt;ut the different restaurant and event scenes in Providence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: The ROI!!! in the "Knowledge District: otherwise known as the Jewelry District (for those here before the fancy name-change ;-)  )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here's some exciting news - The ROI is now open in MONDAYS! So you all know what that means........we have to go there, of course!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GREAT NEWS! THE ROI is generously offering 1/2 OFF PIZZAS for our group! Make sure you tell them you're with the Providence Collective!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some may have been before, and some may not. You're probably saying, "Where's that in the Jewelry District?". It's best explained that it's near where The Spot Underground "used to be", and just across the street from Art Bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located on the corner of the building, The ROI is a real gem. A trendy getaway from the typical downtown scene, intimate, yet spacious, it's a great place to know about! Perfect for drinks and appetizers before a show or dinner afterwards, it's the perfect place to enjoy a relaxed atmosphere and is also walking dist&lt;span&gt;ance from PPAC. The bar is large and there is ample seating for tables for 4&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;or more including a section for large parties. There is also live music on weekend evenings if you're looking for a little more liveliness. You'll be pleasantly surprised and definitely back again!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://theroiprov.com/"&gt;http://theroiprov.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy and NYE 2012!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're hard to miss!!! Just in case, I'll be wearing the brown and pink scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368503920000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368134117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - The ROI!!! 1/2 Price Pizzas too!!!!</name><id>118618422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368482400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/118618422/</event_url></item>