<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey, everyone!  NEW LOCATION AND TIME:  SOMERVILLE PUBLIC LIBRARY, 79 Highland Ave, Somerville&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next meetup will be Sunday May 3, but we're starting at &lt;b&gt;1:30pm&lt;/b&gt; and will go until 4:30pm, including a brief discussion at the end about what we all learned.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Why the different meeting place?&amp;quot;, you may ask.  We are always on the lookout for great places where we can hold our meetups.  It just so happens that this weekend in particular was tough for a few Cashflow players to get all the way to NEU, so we chose a location more feasible to those regular players.  &lt;i&gt;See the special treatment you get when you show up on a regular basis??  AND you get to learn how to become rich too??  HAHA!  What a DEAL!!&lt;/i&gt;  Please remember to be on time for this, and bring your pencils, ERASERS, and calculators!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on attendance and skill level, we will have one 202 board and at least two 101 boards. As we've mentioned before, 202 is much more complicated than 101 and involves a STRONG knowledge of the principles that lead to success in 101. This includes being able to accurately and quickly make changes to your Financial Statement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the 202 board will be restricted to only those who have gotten out of the Rat Race at least FIVE times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call my cell (617-519-3163) if you have problems finding us. There is plenty of parking in the library lot as well as on Highland Ave.  Also you can take the 88 bus from Lechmere or the 90 bus from Sullivan.  Visit www.mbta.com for more info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Russ&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Who Moved My Cheese (in the public meeting room)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Russ</member_name><member_id>3610750</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241899833000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Will-Be Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCashflowMeetup</urlname><id>302998</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Cashflow Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240509017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May 3 Cashflow Meetup</name><id>10252442</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241371800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCashflowMeetup/events/10252442/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/8/global_1225096.jpeg</photo_url></item>