<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for a Last Minute Friday Night Dinner!  Members of the SSDOMG (and their Guests) will be enjoying a casual last-minute Friday night dinner @ Jamie's in Braintree, which is located on the Weymouth line.  Please meet us outside the front door as we may have to wait as reservations are accepted for parties of 10 or more.  If we do have 10 people I will call in a reservation.  Otherwise, we may have to wait up to 15 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, October 3rd @ 6pm&lt;br /&gt;Jamie's Grill and Pub&lt;br /&gt;63 Columbian Street&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;781-356-5544&lt;br /&gt;www.jamiesgrillandpub.com/braintree&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: There is a minimum of at least 5 people by Noon on Friday, October 3rd, however, there is no max. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Up to 2 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees: Annual Members - FREE, Group Members - $2, Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 4pm on Friday, October 3rd (I will call-in a reservation around this time, if applicable.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: Outside the front door.  If you arrive after we are seated ask for me at the Host Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note in your RSVP Comments your top 2-3 restaurants and locations.  The actual restaurant and location will be determined by your RSVP Comments no later than 2pm on Friday, October 3rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may click on the restaurant name for door-to-door directions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are listed on the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 16/Route 18(S).  At first set of lights take a right onto West Street.  Follow through one blinking yellow light.  Immediately after the railroad tracks Jamie's is on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 18(NB): Take a left onto Clumbian Street at SSH.  Bear left at the stop sign.  Follow into Braintree.  Jamie's is on the right in between the next two sets of lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Braintree: Follow Grove Street towards Weymouth (pass the Stop and Shop (on your left) and Sunoco gas station (on your right).  Jamie's is in between the double sets of lights on your left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the front door near the benches.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224171046000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222956940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Friday Night Dinner</name><id>8880531</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223071200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8880531/</event_url></item>