<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 Shrewsbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.265980</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New England Business Media</name><city>Worcester</city><id>7087752</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.786697</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Photo Friends-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was asked to pass this message along to all the members of the Worcester Alliance of Photographers. It's an opportunity to have your work published in the new Worcester Book... Please read the details below. I hope you'll submit some of your beautiful images of Worcester. Anyone who submitted to the the City Hall gallery show consider submitting here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna and Scotty Pants&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;March 1, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

Dear WAP Photographers, &lt;br /&gt;

In the fall of 2012, New England Business Media, LLC will publish a limited-edition hardcover volume called Heart of the Commonwealth: A Photographic Portrait of Worcester &amp;amp; Central Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This collector’s piece, featuring four-color glossy pages, will explore the areas unique heritage and showcase over one hundred stunning images that truly reflect the character of our region. Via images and words, we’ll capture the essential spirit of the area—one of the most vibrant in New England and in the nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Heart of the Commonwealth will feature the works of our area’s best and brightest photographers. As Photo Editor of this project, I would like to personally invite you to submit your collection of greater Worcester/Central Massachusetts photography for review and possible publication in this volume. Please see the attached list for content ideas. Photos should be sent either electronically (preferred) or via mail. Submitted images will not be returned unless you make special arrangements to do so, therefore do not send originals. Electronic images submitted for review should be scaled down to “email-friendly” &lt;br /&gt;

sizes. Please email submissions to: eddcotephoto@gmail.com. Please also include a brief caption of what the picture is. Should any of your images be chosen for reproduction in the book, I will contact you regarding securing a high-resolution copy for publication. All photos used in the book will be credited to the photographer and all copyrights will be retained by the photographer. Both color and B&amp;amp;W photos are acceptable. Prints and/or duplicate slides should be mailed to my attention at the following address:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edd Cote &lt;br /&gt;

New England Business Media &lt;br /&gt;

172 Shrewsbury St &lt;br /&gt;

Worcester, MA 01604&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

If you choose, you can submit a maximum of 30 images, but please do a tight edit before considering your selection. Deadline for submissions is June 15, 2012. &lt;br /&gt;

Thank-you in advance for your interest and submissions. Should you have any questions, please contact me at eddcotephoto@gmail.com or call me at 508-865-6483. &lt;br /&gt;

Together, we can produce a fabulous piece worthy of our region’s great heritage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt;

Edd Cote &lt;br /&gt;

Photo Editor &lt;br /&gt;

Heart of the Commonwealth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heart of the Commonwealth &lt;br /&gt;

We are looking for photo entries on the following topics. This list is by no means exhaustive, but rather a &lt;br /&gt;

starting point. Should you have images that you feel capture a unique aspect of the area’s spirit, please send &lt;br /&gt;

them along for review. &lt;br /&gt;

• Historic Sites &lt;br /&gt;

• Landscapes &lt;br /&gt;

• Architecture, iconic buildings, bridges, etc. Including architectural details. &lt;br /&gt;

• Skylines, daytime, nighttime. &lt;br /&gt;

• New England mills, working, restored, or “retired” &lt;br /&gt;

• Rivers and lakes &lt;br /&gt;

• Four season images, city and country, including the same view photographed throughout a year. &lt;br /&gt;

• Local celebrations and events - town fairs, parades, block parties, 4th of July, car shows, flea markets, etc. &lt;br /&gt;

• Ethnic and cultural diversity - holiday celebrations &lt;br /&gt;

• Statuary, memorials, etc. &lt;br /&gt;

• “Slice of Life” – the events that define daily life. Work, commute, play, family, reunions, etc. &lt;br /&gt;

• Churches, mosques, synagogues, etc. &lt;br /&gt;

• Parks, town commons &lt;br /&gt;

• Academia: schools, colleges, campus images &lt;br /&gt;

• Local artisans and artists &lt;br /&gt;

• Food &lt;br /&gt;

• Night life &lt;br /&gt;

• Neighborhoods &lt;br /&gt;

• Museums &lt;br /&gt;

• Industry &lt;br /&gt;

• Airports &lt;br /&gt;

• Hospitals &lt;br /&gt;

• Sports (all kinds, including indoor and outdoor, on the court, in the water or on the slope. Team and &lt;br /&gt;

individual. Professional and amateur. Youth. “Wide and high” shots of stadiums and arenas. &lt;br /&gt;

• Diners, restaurants, road houses, local faves, both upscale and budget dining. &lt;br /&gt;

• Life events, births, graduations, weddings, “coming of age” celebrations. &lt;br /&gt;

• Interesting people, from well-known to the general public. &lt;br /&gt;

Please note – Photographers will be responsible for obtaining any necessary model and/or property &lt;br /&gt;

releases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heart of the Commonwealth: Re-use rates &lt;br /&gt;

The pay scale is as follows, and applies to both color and B/W photos in any format &lt;br /&gt;

 2-page spread: $325 &lt;br /&gt;

 Full page: $200 &lt;br /&gt;

 1/2 page: $115 &lt;br /&gt;

 1/3 page: $80 &lt;br /&gt;

 1/4 page: $65&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is done online by contacting Edd Cote Directly- please read and follow instructions below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339726412000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336437597000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Heart of the Commonwealth call for Photos of Worcester!</name><id>63857142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339714800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/63857142/</event_url></item>