<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How are you doing?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last month we had a wonderful discussion. Thanks for sharing your experience and input and let us learn a lot from each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last month we discuss about inter-being, which we are deeply all connect to each other.&lt;br /&gt;I shared the same story before. If I am in the other planet, when I meet someone also from earth, I will be friend with them right away. I will not has any conflict even we has different believe on politic or from the country which is enemy to each other. If our mind can elevate to different level, than everything around us could be very different. I will not mad with my neighbor or someone from the same company….etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, we are going to share and discuss about what we can do more for this world. How can we make this world more peaceful and how can I do in my daily life to change. Butterfly effect, every small step counts. Weather is getting better, if Saturday weather is great, we may take a little walk after discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to meet more friends with the same interest about seeking a spiritual life, please come and share your thoughts and experiences about how to practice spirituality in daily life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the day and let’s create positive energy to the whole world. Hope see you all in our meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://spirituality.meetup.com/149/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The building will be second on the right when you coming to Condos, you may park any place which is avaliable.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan</member_name><member_id>4981726</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272305898000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spirituality-149</urlname><id>670379</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5999984741</group_lon><name>The Westborough Spirituality Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271340853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Westborough Spiritual April  Meetup</name><id>13190469</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272132000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/events/13190469/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/6/global_2055446.jpeg</photo_url></item>