<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>P.O. Box 270896</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06127</zip><lat>41.762336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1447422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CT REIA Virtual Trade Show: Step by Step System to Building Wealth through Self Storage Investing with Scott Meyers December 26, 2011 through January 3, 2012. 9:00pm to 10:00pm each day Free Online Event Register and Learn More at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=399" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt; The Inside Scoop Behind &amp;quot;Storage Wars&amp;quot; As Seen on TV! Self Storage investing can be very lucrative - especially in today's market. During this program first presented to CT REIA at the very snowy 8th Annual New England Real Estate Conference and Trade Show, Scott will teach you: * How to maximize the 20+ Profit Centers available in Self Storage to maximize cash flow and create value that isn't available in any other form of real estate. * How his goals of wanting to obtain true financial independence. * How to enjoy all the benefits of owning property without all the risks and hassles. * Discover how to acquire properties in any area with no money down, the safe way, and how to manage from afar by implementing the multitude of new technologies available in this exploding industry. * How he takes Cinderella facilities and turns them into the &amp;quot;Belles of the Ball&amp;quot; and how he has created $ millions doing so. * Increased Competition. * Increase in Value. * Increasing Demands.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325128194000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325014763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA Virtual Trade Show - Complete Guide To Self Storage Investing</name><id>45614692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325124000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/45614692/</event_url></item>