<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>west hartford</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.764294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>caryl's house</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>462542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.727501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/a/b/e/event_69811422.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treemagedon has cancelled our Friday dinner for this month. We will reschedule shortly!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occupied&amp;nbsp;Territory, that is the theme for November. Stake your claim, invade your neighbor or simply set up camp, but plan on cooking something that represents your take on occupied territory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I expect since I have done a unilateral decision for this month's theme there will be protests. Be sure and get your permits before you protest (I issue the permits and they are costly, indeed) watch out for zip ties, rebels in caves, kettling and those twirling batons!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to speak your mind, but I may not listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you have occupied a territory you must plan to stay for quite a while, perhaps a settlement is in order? It worked on the Native Americans pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320452418000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317735258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Occupied Territory - Cancelled for 11/4/11</name><id>cwqfzyppbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320447600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/36081132/</event_url></item>