<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>44.2178°N, 71.4111°W</address_2><address_1>Route 302 Crawford Notch</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03598</zip><lat>44.206845</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-278-HIKE</phone><name>AMC Highland Center</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>839145</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.403199</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for the first official hike of winter.  We will hike in below treeline to the base of the southern presidentials on the first day (December 21) and then summit Monroe, Ike, Pierce, and Jackson on our way out on the 22nd.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since winter starts at 12:47 ET (17:47 UT) we will start our hike at 1pm in order to make it an official winter hike.  I will withhold the exact itinerary of the hike until the saturday night before the trip as I want to have a chance to screen everyone on that saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will &lt;b&gt;require&lt;/b&gt; the following gear:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warm winter jacket, hat, and mittens/gloves&lt;br /&gt;Thermal underwear&lt;br /&gt;Waterproof jacket and pants (snowpants are fine)&lt;br /&gt;3+ pairs of warm wool socks&lt;br /&gt;warm, ankle-protecting boots&lt;br /&gt;15 degree or colder Sleeping bag&lt;br /&gt;Plenty of food and water&lt;br /&gt;Headlamp with extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;Spare warm clothes for emergencies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on conditions you may need:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;microspikes/stabilizers&lt;br /&gt;snowshoes&lt;br /&gt;poles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be bringing my stove and I have a tent which others can use if needed (I will be in my bivy sack which I highly recommend buying if possible).  I also have emergency supplies and will cook friday dinner for everyone (probably pasta).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of other gear which is useful to bring, but it is up to you if you want the extra weight.  Having a pocket rocket would be very useful as you can melt snow to replenish your water.  If you think I forgot anything in the above list please let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is an approximate address. I will include the exact address in my itinerary.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261591735000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259247018000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike!  Southern Presidentials Overnight</name><id>11959391</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261418400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11959391/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/3/global_11989971.jpeg</photo_url></item>