<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Webb place</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.220908</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Starbucks</name><city>Dover</city><id>848927</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>New Hampshire Wool Arts Tour &lt;br /&gt;Columbus Day Weekend, Oct. 9th, 10th &amp;amp; 11th&lt;br /&gt;Open: 10am - 4pm daily&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1983 a small group of women came together with a shared appreciation of sheep and their wonderful fiber. Through their dedication and hard work, the Wool Arts Tour was born. This year, our 27th, we would like to thank Diane Chauncey of Chauncey Farm who has decided to retire from the Tour this year, and Anne Hennessey of The Wool Room who retired from the Tour last year, for all of their hard work and dedication over the years for this great event and the legacy they helped to create. We also thank Ellen Dumas of Ten Talents Farm who in past years has organized our hosts, vendors, and exhibitors. Ellen and her husband lost their beloved home and barn to fire earlier this year. Despite this tragedy, they will be at Spring Pond Farm again this year. Also we welcome Ann Desmet and David Hull of Windfall Farm in Antrim as a new site on the Tour this year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the years, the faces and places have changed, and different species of fiber animals have been added, but the original intent - to share the love and knowledge of fiber and the animals that produce it - has stayed the same. The farms and studios on the tour have something for everyone, adults and children alike. Whether you knit, spin, weave or just appreciate quality handiwork, whether you like watching the artistry of ages-old home industries in a modern setting, or whether you just want to watch a demonstration or see the animals that produce the fiber, you will enjoy this weekend jaunt over the colorful autumn roads of New Hampshire. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come tour our lovely area of the state and become a part of this ever more popular Columbus Day weekend tradition. Admission to all sites is FREE! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact us at &lt;a href="http://woolartstournh@spinnerfarmsheep.com" target="_blank"&gt;woolartstournh@spinnerfarmsheep.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or 603-464-0232. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet at the Starbucks and head out from there!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Regan</member_name><member_id>5074107</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286810475000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Seacoast Knitters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>seacoastknitters</urlname><id>642244</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Knitters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282599176000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Hampshire Wool Arts Tour -Monday Oct 11th, day 3</name><id>14516505</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286805600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/seacoastknitters/events/14516505/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/global_17214160.jpeg</photo_url></item>