<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.254236</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt Washington Ammnoosuc Trail Head</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>1252706</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ammonoosuc Trail &lt;br /&gt;Distance: 9 miles round trip to the summit &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain: 3,800 &lt;br /&gt;Difficulty: strenous&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to find the trail head: Take 93 north to route 3 take until 302 you will be looking for Base Road. &lt;br /&gt;When you see popular resturant Fabyans turn left this will be base road follow the trailhead will be on your right. If you should get to the Cog Railway parking lot you have gone to far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will be weather and trail sensitive given the time of year and recent snow fall. Please note that this is an ADVANCE Hike ( strenuous ) Must have winter hiking experience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Full winter gear a must to attend this hike which will include Hat, Two pair of Mitts, Mitt covers, Mitt warmers, Face protection, goggles, Two base layers ( wicking material ) No Cotton! Middle layer ( fleece or down),Outer shell ( water and wind proof ) Wool socks plus extra pair. Sturdy hiking boots, gators, crampons,micro spikes and snowshoes. Everyone should have a head lamp in their backpacks. Food,snacks, water lots of water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have two choices: &lt;br /&gt;Ammonoosuc Ravine Trail or Lions Head &lt;br /&gt;I will call mid week to check on trail conditions and get back to everyone. If it turns out that we will not be able to do either trail we can have a back up hike weather permitting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272283926000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271935830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Washington</name><id>13257115</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272110400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13257115/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/2/global_14305586.jpeg</photo_url></item>