<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Granite St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.355700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rock</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1222089</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So you just ran the Boston Marathon? Or maybe you decided to stick with your favorite 3, 5, or 6 miler. Either way, TMIRCE is proud of you. To celebrate achievements both large and small, we have invited New Balance to be our special guest on April 24th for our weekly Breakfast Run (yep, potluck brunch after the run!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;As always, all levels of speed and ability will be running with us and newcomers are particularly welcome - we'll do a 3, 5 or 6 mile loop and let's make this the biggest and best ever!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A greeting from our Special Guest:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who said running apparel can’t be fashionable AND functional?! New Balance will be hanging out with The Most Informal Running Club Ever for our Saturday morning run to showcase a brand new line of running apparel on April 24th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be showcasing a new clothing collection including women’s and men’s shorts and tops, geared towards the fashion conscious fitness runner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to take the shorts for a spin?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come early&lt;/b&gt; and the New Balance professionals will outfit you in some great looking running shorts to literally take for a spin…and if that’s not enough, you get to take the shorts with you after the run.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The New Balance team will be hanging out after the run as well to answer any questions and get your first-hand feedback on the shorts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you on the 24th!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please be sure to &lt;b&gt;RSVP&lt;/b&gt; on here so we have an idea of attendance and make sure there's enough stuff for everyone... please invite your friends too!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get a sneak peak at some of the fashionable, functional gear - &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/yecavqt" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/ye...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: coral"&gt;This is also on Facebook if you'd prefer to register on there - &lt;a href="http://tiny.cc/TMIRCE_NBFB" target="_blank"&gt;http://tiny.cc/TMIRCE...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* There will be limited stocks of shorts in various m/f sizes which will be distributed on a first come, first serve basis. If you don't get a pair of shorts then, don't worry, there'll be plenty of other goodies!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TMIRCE MAILING LIST&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Want to be in on all of the extra-curricular activities of TMIRCE? Join the mailing list:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/the-most-informal-running-club-ever" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eat, Run and Be Merry &lt;br /&gt;The Most Informal Running Club Ever aims to promote healthy living and community by uniting people through the simple act of running together. &lt;br /&gt;informalrunning.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the New Balance logos!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy - ti.mer.see - Marx </member_name><member_id>6766032</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272660412000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>103</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269001005000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Balance new product showcase @ TMIRCE (and some other fun stuff!)</name><id>12931425</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272117600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/12931425/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/6/global_14003974.jpeg</photo_url></item>