<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>131 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.355974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common - Parkman Band Stand</name><city>Boston</city><id>696736</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062287</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing the fourth annual Bookcrossing Shakespeare Meetup!  See the free performance of Othello by the Commonwealth Shakespeare Company in Boston Common with your fellow Boston Bookcrossers!  Meet at the Parkman Bandstand 6:30 p.m. (Take the green line or the red line to Park Steet Station.)  I'll be wearing a t-shirt that says &amp;quot;Unconvention 2010 - Liberate Your Literature&amp;quot; and I'll have a small sign (8 1/2 x 11) that says &amp;quot;BookCrossing&amp;quot; with the Ballycumber logo on it (that's the little yellow running book). I'll hang around the bandstand for 20 minutes, and anyone who comes later than that can find us on the lawn -- I'll prop up the sign.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(This is the Parkman Bandstand: &lt;a href="http://z.about.com/d/boston/1/0/p/0/-/-/IMG_4150.JPG" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://z.about.com/d/boston/1/0/p/0/-/-/IMG_4150.JPG" target="_blank"&gt;http://z.about.com/d/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things you might want to bring:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Something to sit on -- blanket, towel, lawn chair, or something  &lt;br /&gt;Food - picnic!  &lt;br /&gt;Beverage - refreshing, non-alcoholic  &lt;br /&gt;Bug spray - just in case  &lt;br /&gt;Registered books for release - Boston Common will be full of people who like literature and free things!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And note -- the out-of-town bookcrossers will be with us! Yes, this event is part of the unconvention, going on from August 13 to August 16.  If you have not yet registered for the unconvention and you would like to join bookcrossers from all over the country (and beyond!) for many other fantastic bookcrossing-related events, just contact me through meetup or the unconvention website and I'll get you signed up.  Here's a link to the unconvention website so you can find out all about the great activities that we've planned:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://uncon2010boston.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://uncon2010boston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://uncon2010bosto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the bandstand holding a Ballycumber sign (yellow running book)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liz</member_name><member_id>220016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281883897000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>BookCrossers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookcrossing-195</urlname><id>23495</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Bookcrossing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281015966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Shakespeare in Boston Common: Othello</name><id>14327935</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281825000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookcrossing-195/events/14327935/</event_url></item>