<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 West St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 587-1011</phone><name>NORTHAMPTON MA_ FORBES LIBRARY </name><city>Northampton </city><id>832342</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Hope you can join us on Monday, April 6, from 7 to around 9 to talk about &lt;i&gt;Giovanni's Room&lt;/i&gt;, by James Baldwin. &lt;/b&gt; We decided to stick with the same book because only a few of us had had a chance to read it at the first get together.  Giovanni's Room is a quick (but intense) read, hopefully short enough to give folks time to get to it before the 6th, but feel free to stop by even if you haven't read it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who couldn't make it make it on the 16th, we had a great first meeting - there were about 8 of us -  a really nice group of folks, and there was general excitement and commitment about continuing to meet.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring a snack or beverage to share with the group, if you feel inspired!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My apologies for posting this a bit late, I wanted to be sure the community room was available (we've now reserved it.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, I want to remind folks that this meetup.com group is temporary (because it's unfortunately kind of expensive) so we've started a google group home for us (which will be free) - please send an email to westernmassbookgroup@googlegroups.com to join the email list.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you soon : )&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>this time we're meeting in the community room, downstairs by the kids section</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie</member_name><member_id>1543974</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>lauren</member_name><member_id>4142079</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265247928000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paradisecityreaders</urlname><id>1404829</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Paradise City Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238351138000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd meetup!  the book is still "Giovanni's Room" (only 150 pages)</name><id>10063081</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239058800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paradisecityreaders/events/10063081/</event_url></item>