<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>My goal is to complete my attempt to hike the entire Wapack Trail (in sections) by ascending and descending Mt. Watatic via the Wapack trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at parking area at Mt. Watatic/Wapack/Mid-State Trail in Ashburnham, Mass at 8:30am.  The parking area is off of Route 119.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a loop hike, so no carpooling to another trailhead is necessary.  We'll ascend to the summit of Watatic via the Wapack Trail (about 1.2 miles), descend the backside of the mountain via the Wapack Trail  (about 1.2 miles) and then take the Midstate trail (about .8 to 1 miles) out to the parking lot.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for winter cold and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This can be dangerous in cold weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.   Microspikes are advised at this time.  I am unsure about snow cover next week.  As of Dec 4th, there was no snow on the ground on the Wapack Trail further north.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a short hike - a little over 3 miles, so I expect it to take about 2 hours.  I intend to be back on the road and on my way home by noon.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did the northern section of the 18 mile Wapack Trail several weeks ago and the southern section (excluding Watatic) on the weekend of Dec. 3rd.   I would like to finish out the entire Wapack Trail by completing Mt. Watatic on the weekend of the 18th.  This is a lovely trail with several summits and some areas of former farmland that have now grown in around old stone walls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some form of traction will be required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunrise is at 7:15am.  Sunset will be at 4:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I am not familiar with this mountain, but I have been told that the summit is open and exposed, rocky and has great views. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Elevation of Mt. Watatic is 1,891 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is a shorter and somewhat easier hike.  If you have proper cold weather gear, can keep a moderate pace and have appropriate traction for potentially icy spots, this should be a very manageable hike for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I am not a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around.  The mountain will be there another day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog in cold weather.  I will have one of my two dogs with me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike.  I rely on NOAA.gov for my forecasts because it allows me to pinpoint forecasts for mountaintop areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors, SO if the weather looks like it will be miserable or the sky will be too cloudy to see anything, I will reschedule. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), I will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;  I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN  (OR EXPERIENCED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic with two dogs &amp; usually a Meetup Sign in the window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292702756000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292107775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Watatic - Ashburnham, Mass.</name><id>15707858</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292679000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15707858/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/5/global_3608437.jpeg</photo_url></item>