<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This presentation will examine the roots of Islam and it's foundations in the desert sands of the Middle East. We'll look at the the 'whys' of the current state of Middle Eastern politics and how Islam understands the role of Muslims in the world today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Much of Europe is grappling with Muslim demands—Germany, Italy, Denmark and Great Britain have recently made concessions to Islamic demands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll look at such practices as wife-beating, decapitation, stoning, and honor killing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, we'll discuss Islamic culture and society and what we can anticipate should the West ever fall under the law of Islam—Sharia Law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to stay awhile for questions and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HER'S WHAT SOME PEOPLE WHO HAVE SEEN IT ARE SAYING:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ This type of class is an absolute necessity in order for our society to understand what we are up against. If you don't know your enemy, how can you fight it? And when I say enemy, it is not initiated on our end, but on theirs. Their entire culture/religion is predicated on the destruction of the Infidels...which is us! ” Shannon McCarthy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ Julianne put on a great, informative class once again. She recommended some books to follow up with regarding Sharia Law. I also love staying after class and talking with other members about their thoughts and ideas. ” Lisa Gravel&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ This was a great vehicle for expanding my understanding of Islam and Sharia Law and how it disproves the notion that we should all be able to get along. Sure wish our folks in Congress understand what we can expect when the Hamas &amp;quot;victims&amp;quot; arrive in the U.S. Julianne has a wealth of knowledge which she presents in a very straight-forward yet entertaining manner ” Lisa Sisoian&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>highland st. towards east rochester . salmon falls rd lights take left 2 tenths</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259625506000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rochester-912-project</urlname><id>1452537</id><group_lat>43.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>Rochester 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247528124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>rochester 912 project August Meetup</name><id>10869027</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249943400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rochester-912-project/events/10869027/</event_url></item>