<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>294 Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.551907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-922-0004</phone><name>Organic Garden Cafe</name><city>Beverly</city><id>598589</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.879082</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Brian and Jody Calvi will tell about their personal journeys of using raw foods and natural lifestyle to manage their chronic health challenges of symptoms like fibromyalgia and arthritis respectively and sharing their incredible knowledge at their wellness center, Farm of Life, in Costa Rica. They deliver their FREE motivational presentation with humor and authenticity about who they are and what they experienced. Their FREE talk takes 40 minutes and is accompanied with a beautiful slide show.  Their respective wellness journeys are chronicled online at &lt;a href="http://www.fincadevida.com/about_us-health_recovery.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;www.fincadevida.com/about_us-health_recovery.aspx&lt;/a&gt; . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Farm of Life is a travel lodge and wellness center based on the Living Foods Lifestyle. Their purpose is to share knowledge, inspiration, and appreciation of the miraculous capacity of the body with others. Guests thrive on delicious raw and vegetarian cuisine made with fresh organic ingredients and revive body and spirit with detoxification, wellness coaching, yoga, massage, physical exertion, waterfalls, wildlife, beaches, jungle and mountain hikes, and exciting eco-adventures. Farm of Life is a place of immense beauty, amazing energy, stunning vistas, and affordable, modern accommodations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Information about the Calvi's travel lodge in Costa Rica&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.farmoflifecr.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.farmoflifecr.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rawbert</member_name><member_id>11144266</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286217333000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282853325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brian &amp; Jodi Calvi (FREE Talk!) @ Rawbert's</name><id>14553413</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286112600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/14553413/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/7/global_17482103.jpeg</photo_url></item>