<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Marcy St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075943</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Players Ring</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>671462</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.751850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Players&amp;rsquo; Ring&amp;nbsp;continues its 20th season...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;DARWiN'S WAiTiNG ROOM presents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;COMEDY, ENLiGHTENED&lt;/span&gt; - a collection of plays written by Eric Doucet, featuring&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&amp;nbsp;"&lt;span&gt;;The Inner Light Movement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;, Cool Hand Kenny," "All Goats Lead to Home" and more. Audiences will be taken into the world of a typical DARWiN'S play - this means a lot of laughs and unexpected situations!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/4/6/event_83737702.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;DARWiN'S WAiTiNG ROOM is a collection of entertainers from the Seacoast of New Hampshire, who work together to produce original, family-friendly comedy for the stage and screen. The group has been performing out of Portsmouth since 2008. It has a membership of over 50 performers, artists and technical crew. Created by Eric Doucet and held together by the organization and talent of Kaitlyn Huwe, DWR seeks to bring laughter and entertainment to the masses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We're meeting&amp;nbsp;at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.agavedos.com/"&gt;Agave Mexican&amp;nbsp;Bistro, 111 State St.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;@&amp;nbsp;6pm&lt;/strong&gt; for drinks/dinner.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;...let me know if you're coming so I can reserve a table.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets&lt;/strong&gt;: Only $12 each with the Seacoast Outdoors discount!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive 7:30, show begins @ 8pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Reserve by phone at&amp;nbsp;603/ 436*8123 and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;say you're with Seacoast Outdoors Meetup to receive a discount&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Then pay at the door. Or, buy tickets online.&amp;nbsp; These shows do sell out so make sure you reserve!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/b/0/event_22902928.jpeg" width="326" height="220" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.playersring.org/"&gt;The Players' Ring Theater&lt;/a&gt; - &amp;nbsp;Since 1992, the mission of The Players' Ring has been to promote the efforts of local artists through the production of original works, while providing an affordable theatre space to local production companies. &amp;ldquo;The Ring&amp;rdquo; as we know and love it, nurtures all artists and provides an environment where artists can thrive, grow, take risks and make daring choices. The Players' Ring is located in a nineteenth century brick building on Marcy Street on the grounds of Prescott Park in Portsmouth, New Hampshire. The historic building is owned by the City of Portsmouth and is fitted out as a &amp;ldquo;black box&amp;rdquo; theatre. With a seating capacity of 75, The Players' Ring annual attendance is approximately 6,500. Since its creation, more than 30 local production companies have presented plays at The Players' Ring. While some form to produce a single special event, some production companies produce shows on an annual basis. Over 200 actors, directors, playwrights and technicians work together to produce plays at The Players' Ring each year. Over the past five years, over $180,000 has been distributed to those involved in Players' Ring productions. Original works account for half of each season&amp;rsquo;s offerings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release -&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Participation in this activity is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors. &amp;nbsp;Always check email &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327433579000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325738361000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>COMEDY ENLIGHTENED @ The Players' Ring</name><id>46742832</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326495600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/46742832/</event_url></item>