<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Address to be emailed 1 week in advance</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.659065</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Joanne's House</name><city>Portland</city><id>1438552</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.258240</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Time for our monthly "&lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Girl's Night&lt;/span&gt;"!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what are we going to do this this &lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Girl's Night&lt;/span&gt;?! Whatever we decide! I'm hoping we'll have a theme for every month, and rotate to each others houses or to different locales. It'll be a great way to get out, make new friends, and have something to look forward to each month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the meeting, we will choose the date for the next Girl's Night, the location, the host, and the theme!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This Month's Girl's Night:  &lt;br /&gt;1. &lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Date:&lt;/span&gt; Saturday, April 9th, 2011 at 5pm  &lt;br /&gt;2. &lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Location:&lt;/span&gt; JoAnne's House in Portland  &lt;br /&gt;3. &lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Host:&lt;/span&gt; JoAnne &lt;br /&gt;4. &lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Theme:&lt;/span&gt; Roaring 1920's Speakeasy  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/4/3/event_21440803.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's 1920 and Prohibition has just taken effect. Prohibition, during which the sale of alcohol was illegal, ran from 1920  to 1933, yet in San Francisco, where the thirsty, working-class  populace refused to hop on the temperance wagon, spirits flowed in  hotels, dance halls, coffee shops, clandestine rooms and underground  tunnels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're invited to a secret speakeasy in a shady part of downtown San Francisco called the &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Cotton Club&lt;/span&gt; (otherwise known as JoAnne's House). However, you can't just show up, as you may be an officer of the law. When you arrive, knock on the door 3 times. Once the door is open, you'll be asked for the password. &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tonight's password is:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Josephine"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Make sure you dress up as a flapper&lt;/span&gt;, or you may be denied entry. Remember, if you don't look the part and don't know the password, the Cotton Club may be closed for the evening. If you don't know where to buy your Cotton Club outfit, check out this website where they have plenty of flapper dresses that are $35 and under:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flappercostumes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flappercostumes.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please sign up to bring one of the following by adding a comment when you RSVP:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. 2 bottles of Champagne (You can get great champagne for $4.99 at Trader Joe's. Make sure you have it hidden in a paper bag when you arrive, because it's 1920 and the time of Prohibition when alcohol is illegal).  &lt;br /&gt;2. Chocolate Cigars and Candy Cigarettes (These can be found many places, including Haven't candies) &lt;br /&gt;3. Speakeasy Spinach and Artichoke Dip  &lt;br /&gt;4. Al Capone's Cheese Platter &lt;br /&gt;5. Great Gatsby Gaucamole and Chips &lt;br /&gt;6. Cotton Club Crab Cakes &lt;br /&gt;7. 1920's Music on CD and a couple decks of cards &lt;br /&gt;8. Moonshine (This can be any alcohol, but bring a clear bottle labeled "Moonshine" that we can put it in once we get to the party for the 1920's effect) &lt;br /&gt;9.&amp;nbsp; Soda and Juice  &lt;br /&gt;10. Waldorf Salad &lt;br /&gt;11. Pina Colada Cake (A recipe can be found here: &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;http://allrecipes.com//Recipe/pina-colada-cake-iii/Detail.aspx) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;12. Shrimp and cocktail sauce &lt;br /&gt;13. Fresh Fruit &lt;br /&gt;14. Baked Brie with Bread &lt;br /&gt;15.&amp;nbsp; Fake Pearl Necklaces to be provided to people as they enter as a sign they knew the password. &lt;br /&gt;16. Dessert Items&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;17. A 1920's themed item of your choice (This may be food, games, etc. Please specify what you will be bringing when RSVP'ing)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18. A 1920's themed item of your choice (This may be food, games, etc. Please specify what you will be bringing when RSVP'ing)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19. A 1920's themed item of your choice (This may be food, games, etc. Please specify what you will be bringing when RSVP'ing)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20. A 1920's themed item of your choice (This may be food, games, etc. Please specify what you will be bringing when RSVP'ing)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should plan to spend $20 or under for the items you've signed up to bring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/2/c/event_21440780.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>JoAnne will be answering the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303061396000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283971388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Girls Night! Theme: Roaring 1920's Speakeasy!</name><id>chcvpypgbmb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302382800000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/15265056/</event_url></item>