<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Ann Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.768055</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>860-278-8852</phone><name>Sally's Fish Camp</name><city>Hartford</city><id>435089</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.677864</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I decided to put this event off until after the holidays but have been looking forward to this since the middle of November!  One of our members, Dawn, recommended this restaurant.  Here is what their website &lt;a href="http://www.sallysfishcamp.com/info.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sallysfishcamp.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sallysfish...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has to say:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Critics say Hartford's newest restaurant is &amp;quot;off the hook&amp;quot;. It is a blend of cool urban chic and New England Fish Camp. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I spoke with Debbie, the manager, and because we have a large group, we have to stick to a predetermined menu so the chef can prepare accordingly.  Each person will pay $39, which includes tax and gratuity.  The choices for food are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$39 per guest (inclusive of tax and gratuity)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Course:&lt;br /&gt;Mixed Greens tossed with julienne carrots, tomatoes, chopped cucumbers and balsamic vinaigrette&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Caesar salad with fresh shaved parmesan, garlic croutons and camp?s Caesar dressing&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;New England Clam Chowder&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrees:&lt;br /&gt;Pan Seared Hanger Steak with garlic herb butter, fries, and baby carrots&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Pine Nut &amp;amp; Parmesan crusted breast of chicken over mashed potatoes and haricot verts, with a garlic herb veloute&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Dijon &amp;amp; Brown Sugar Glazed Salmon with haricot verts over wild rice&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Linguini alla vongole:  little neck clams steamed in parsley, olive oil, garlic, and white wine over linguini&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;New England Lobster Roll on a grilled top loader with drawn butter accompanied by Camp fries and slaw&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Campfire Grilled Trout over wild rice and julienne vegetables in a tomato saffron mussel broth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dessert&lt;br /&gt;Chocolate S?mores Tart&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Vanilla Bean Crème Brulée&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Warm Apple Cranberry Tart topped with walnuts with house-made cinnamon ice cream&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coffee or soda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep an eye on your RSVP.  If you cannot attend or are not sure, please don't RSVP.  I have a feeling that a lot of people will want to attend this event.  Let's make sure that everyone who RSVPs actually comes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have a reservation under Kelly.  I believe we will have our own room.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200444731000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195569659000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Finally...Sally's Fish Camp</name><id>6776087</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200096000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/6776087/</event_url></item>