<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/c/8/event_131334472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copied &amp;amp; pasted directly from &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/265872856849148/271957386240695/?notif_t=plan_mall_activity" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/events/265872856849148/271957386240695/?notif_t=plan_mall_activity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For location and other details, check out the above link or visit the New England American Pit Bull Terrier Club on facebook at &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/newengland.apbtclub" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/newengland.apbtclub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NEW ENGLAND APBT CLUB IS PROUD TO ANNOUNCE OUR FIRST 2 FUNSHOWS AND ALL BREED WEIGHT PULL IN ORDER TO BECOME SANCTIONED WITH THE ADBA!! THE LAST ADBA MASSACHUSETTS SHOW WAS HELD OVER 6 YEARS AGO- IT IS DEFINITELY TIME FOR US TO GET BACK ON THE MAP!! WE NEED MORE EAST COAST SHOWS AND CAN'T DO IT WITHOUT YOUR SUPPORT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*THIS SHOW IS BEING HELD ON PRIVATE PROPERTY. THE PROPERTY IS A WORKING AND OPERATIONAL FARM. PLEASE DO NEED TRY TO PET, TOUCH OR FEED THE ANIMALS!!! PLEASE DO NOT SPEED- 5MPH!!! WE WILL HAVE &lt;br /&gt;

 ZERO TOLERANCE FOR ANYTHING OF THE SORT!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*REGISTRATION WILL START AT 8AM! FIRST SHOW WILL BEGIN AT 10AM SHARP. WE WILL BEGIN WITH AN INFORMATIVE HANDLER'S MEETING BEFORE THE ACTUAL SHOW TO GO OVER A COUPLE THINGS AND ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS! SECOND SHOW WILL FOLLOW AFTER A SHORT BREAK. WEIGHTPULL REGISTRATION AND WEIGHINS WILL ALSO BE DURING THAT TIME.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*YOUR "PITBULL/BULLY BRED" TYPE DOGS DO NOT HAVE TO HAVE ANY CLUB REGISTRATION PAPERWORK OR KNOWN PEDIGREES. RESCUED, SPAYED, NEUTERED, ONE EYED, THREE LEGGED DOGS ARE ALL WELCOME!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*WE WILL BE ABIDING BY ADBA RULES AND JUDGING ON THE ADBA CONFORMATION STANDARD. CONFORMATION CLASSES ARE AS FOLLOWS: &lt;br /&gt;

 4-6 MONTHS &lt;br /&gt;

 6-9 MONTHS &lt;br /&gt;

 9-12 MONTHS &lt;br /&gt;

 12-18 MONTHS &lt;br /&gt;

 18-24 MONTHS &lt;br /&gt;

 2-3 YEARS &lt;br /&gt;

 3-5 YEARS &lt;br /&gt;

 5 YEARS +&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*WE WILL ALSO HAVE FUN CLASSES: &lt;br /&gt;

 JUDGE'S CHOICE &lt;br /&gt;

 BEST CONDITIONED &lt;br /&gt;

 JUNIOR HANDLER &lt;br /&gt;

 BEST BLACK &lt;br /&gt;

 BEST BRINDLE &lt;br /&gt;

 BEST REDNOSE &lt;br /&gt;

 BEST BLUE &lt;br /&gt;

 BEST BULLY &lt;br /&gt;

 UGLIEST DOG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*IF YOU SIGN UP TO BECOME A MEMBER OF THE NEAPBT CLUB PRIOR OR THE DAY OF THE SHOW YOU WILL RECEIVE HALF PRICE CLASS REGISTRATION FEES!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*THERE WILL BE RAFFLES!! OBRIENS CANINE SUPPLY DONATED A GOOD AMOUNT OF BULLDOG SUPPLIES!! (THANK YOU GUYS!!) SOME PEOPLE ARE GOING TO WALK AWAY WITH SOME REALLY COOL STUFF!! IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO DONATE ANY ITEMS TO THE CLUB FOR THE RAFFLE, PLEASE LET US KNOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*WE WILL BE SELLING FOOD, SNACKS, WATERS AND SODAS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*BRING THE WHOLE FAMILY, TO HELP SUPPORT US, AND ENJOY THE DAY WITH SOME AWESOME DOGS!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*DON'T WORRY IF YOU HAVE NEVER SHOWN BEFORE- THERE WILL BE VERY DEDICATED, KIND AND FRIENDLY PEOPLE WHO HAVE MANY YEARS OF EXPERIENCE TO ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS YOU MAY HAVE!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*ALL ADBSI RULES APPLY: ALL DOGS MUST BE CRATED. ONE DOG PER CRATE. NO DOGS LEFT IN VEHICLES. FLAT BUCKLE COLLARS WITH 4FT LEADS. NO SLIP, PRONG, OR QUICK RELEASE COLLARS. NO PUPPIES UNDER 4 MONTHS OF AGE. NO FEMALES IN HEAT. NO PUPPY SALES. NO DRUGS. NO ALCOHOL. NO HUMAN AGGRESSIVE DOGS!! NO DOG AGGRESSIVE HUMANS!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For address and other details, must visit &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/265872856849148/271957386240695/?notif_t=plan_mall_activity" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/events/265872856849148/271957386240695/?notif_t=plan_mall_activity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350857766000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350246335000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NE American Pit Bull Terrier Club's Conformation FUNShow &amp; All Breed Weight Pull</name><id>86957632</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>36000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350820800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/86957632/</event_url></item>