<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Pub</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>733190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This one is for the suburban&amp;nbsp;drinking buddies.&amp;nbsp;Sorry I forgot to post it with all of the Patriots game distractions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives&amp;nbsp;have been organizing Patriots Game Watching Events over the past&amp;nbsp;4 months with up to 60 people attending at Boston, Wakefield,&amp;nbsp;and Woburn&amp;nbsp;venues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now it is time for the Red Sox Natives first Happy Hour of 2012 followed by a Bruins Game Viewing Option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great and the full menu is available for purchase.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early by 6:00pm and get yourself a prime seat to enjoy some pre-game socializing. Stop by for drinks, stay for dinner and stick around to watch the Bruins game. Or arrive later and stay until whenever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game time is 7:05 PM for the Bruins vs the New Jersey Devils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's in front of Bank of America and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center and Commuter Rail accessible from North Station&amp;nbsp;by the&amp;nbsp;Reading and Haverhill Trains stopping at Wakefield Station,&amp;nbsp;less than a 10 minute walk up Albion Street 1 block, right on to to Main Street and 1 block to Water Street. If you are joining us from the City the Commuter rail is the way to go.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food/drink.&amp;nbsp;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER AND TIP YOUR SERVERS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP&amp;nbsp; if you think you will attend. Invite guests, friends, and co-workers.&amp;nbsp;We have&amp;nbsp;over 20 RSVPs from&amp;nbsp;the Red Sox Natives and Wakefield Weeknights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope&amp;nbsp;to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fenway Frank&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be att he bar on the first floor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327031593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326841185000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour followed by Bruins Game Watching Option at Harrington's Pub</name><id>48523142</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327014000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/48523142/</event_url></item>