<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361406</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857.453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft N.E.R.D. Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1210878</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a night with ZEND. We will have Kevin Schroeder of Zend give two topics that are most interesting to PHP Developers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Guidelines for Deploying PHP Applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For many PHP shops, moving code from development to production sounds like it should be easy, and it can be. The problem is that sometimes deployment strategies can result in longer downtime than is desired, rollbacks can be difficult or there can even be uncertainty on what is actually in the production environment. In this talk we will look at a few basic methods that you can use to manage a predictable deployment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do You Queue? &amp;ndash; Characteristics of Scalability (ZendCon 2010)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;There has been a lot of talk over the past several years about the difference between performance and scalability. When talking about building a scalable application queuing is a concept that many PHP developers are not overly familiar with. In this talk we will demonstrate some of these principles using the Zend Server Job Queue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Presenter: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Kevin Schroeder, Technology Evangelist for Zend Technologies, is well versed in a wide variety of technologies pertinent to both small and large scale application deployments. He has developed production software using a wide variety of languages including PHP, Java (standalone and web-based applications), Javascript, HTML, SQL, Perl, Visual Basic, ASP and occasionally C. His software development experience is accompanied with extensive experience as  system administrator on platforms including Linux, Solaris and Windows on scales of a single server up to several hundred servers on installations that range from a few to millions of users.  He has spoken at several conferences and is also the co-author of &amp;ldquo;The IBM i Programmer&amp;rsquo;s Guide to PHP&amp;rdquo; and author of &amp;ldquo;You want to do WHAT with PHP?&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his spare time he races Ferraris, with a dismal win record in his Honda.  He can be found online at &lt;a href="http://www.eschrade.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eschrade.c...&lt;/a&gt; speaking in the first person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;6:00 - 7:00 : Doors open, socializing, Free Pizza &lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 7:15 : Announcements&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;7:15 - 8:45 : Presentation&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;8:45 - 9:00 : Questions&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;9:00 - ???? : Beers somewhere?&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Schroeder</member_name><member_id>14244357</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303944825000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>123</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296014442000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great tips on how to deploy your new PHP applications, as well as Zend Queueing.</name><id>16189377</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303164000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/16189377/</event_url></item>