<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-380-9254</phone><name>Watertown Center</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1195181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183898</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity to meet like-minded folks interested in connecting to themselves and each other on a deeper level.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These monthly&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Tantra Together gatherings&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;are an opportunity to meet &lt;strong&gt;men and women&lt;/strong&gt; that live locally. Come and learn Tantra practices that will support   you in being Present, Loving and Open-Hearted. &amp;nbsp;Together we will   consciously create more love in the world, heal what is needed and have   fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;** This Tantra  gathering has a special element included!!&amp;nbsp; Adam Bauer, dear friend and  Tantrika, will bring us his wisdom to help us answer the age-old  question:&amp;nbsp; What is Tantra?&amp;nbsp; Adam is a old soul who deeply connects to  his audience with humor and grace.&amp;nbsp; I expect everyone to enjoy being  together and in his company.&amp;nbsp; We both welcome you whole-heartedly to  come to this event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us in breathing, meditation, yoga and more in the presence of other divine beings in a safe and sacred space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beginners are welcome. Meet new friends and leave feeling peaceful, open, and joyful!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover how to truly experience new levels of pleasure in your life.   This ANCIENT and REVOLUTIONARY work will teach you powerful tools that   will allow you access to your own BLISS and JOY!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DETAILS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We are meeting at The Watertown Center, 22 Mt. Auburn Street,   Watertown, MA (there's plenty of parking on the street and in the back   lot!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please arrive at 5:45 pm as we will start right at 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Sacred ritual will end at 8 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please bring $20 in cash to pay for the workshop&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please wear comfortable clothing and something colorful and celebratory&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please let your friends know and bring them along!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a&gt;change&lt;/a&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303679293000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tantra-international</urlname><id>383662</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Tantra International</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300108524000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra Together Gathering -- What is Tantra anyway?</name><id>16913793</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303596000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tantra-international/events/16913793/</event_url></item>