<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 635-4505</phone><name>Boston Common Frog Pond</name><city>Boston</city><id>795283</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(This event is postponed from Thursday.  The rink prepartion is taking longer with the warm weather and rain.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi,&lt;br /&gt;This is the third time I'm running this event with the group.  The first year it was 29 degrees out and last year it was 47 degrees out.  Let's hope for something more like last year.  If the weather is really bad, I will cancel by 4:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's opening day at the Frog Pond and some dignitaries will be there to speak, there will be some professional skaters and demonstrations, etc., plus admission is free this night.  It all starts at 5:30 p.m. which is kind of early for some so I thought we could meet at 6:30 p.m., watch a little, skate a little and then get something to eat at Chau Chow City in Chinatown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI the Frog Pond (www.bostonfrogpond.com) isn't actually a pond for those of you who don't know.  It's just an outdoor rink that's frozen from underneath.  I know some people don't skate on ponds for fear of ruining their blades.  Also, if you don't have skates you can rent them for $8.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location is T accessible by Park Street on the red and green lines.  If you are driving you can pay to park at the Boston Common Garage or drive around the Public Gardens no more than three times and you should get a metered spot.  (I always get one there.)  Just be aware if the meters go until 8:00 p.m. instead of 6:00 p.m. or that the metered spots don't turn residential after 6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, we'll go eat at Chau Chow City on Essex Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm giving the option to RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot;.  Please update your RSVP if your plans change.  I'll also be combining this event with the Social Fun group too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dee&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will meet at the Frog Statues in the photo.  Look for Claudia from Social Fun.  I will show up later wearing a white ski jacket.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290448589000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289369019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Boston Skating at the Frog Pond Opening Ceremony</name><id>15401153</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290378600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/15401153/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/6/global_11414390.jpeg</photo_url></item>