<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/c/2/event_127346562.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The most notable thing hiking Mt. Jefferson 5715 feet via Caps Ridge, is simply how quick you get from trail head to treeline. Great views of the Presidentials and all great views seem to have a price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/a/e/event_1551886.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The first mile is fairly easy, then gets steep, rough, involves scrambles over ledges, and is totally exposed and in the alpine zone.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Hiking this as a group has always been one of my favorite experiences.  It's hard not to bond as you are scrambling up the ledges.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/e/f/event_1809455.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;You get a leg up on elevation on the Caps Ridge Trail, which starts at Jefferson Notch, the highest trailhead on a public road in the White Mountains at an elevation of 3,008 feet.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;This is the "easiest" route up Mt. Jefferson and was one of my first challenge hikes.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;[rt: 5.0 miles, 2,700 ft elevation gain , 3:50h AMC book time&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Our pace will add about 1 hour for more stops, trail challenges and a slower pace].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/a/d/event_1551885.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;This is definitely a fair weather hike, besides for fog, wind and rain- we must conceder the summer danger of thunderstorms, which could develop in late afternoon. We will keep our 1pm turn around time. A weather advisory will cancel this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;This pace of this hike is suitable for slower but experienced mountain hikers. We will return the same trail, so the summit is optional if you should decide on a shorter hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Our goal is to enjoy the hike and have fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;All hikers are welcome to hike. We will meet together and identify pace groups so everyone hikes at a comfortable pace.  The summit is an option. Your group can enjoy a great hike with a shorter turn around option.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;A minimum of 4 hikers will be required. While we will hike at a comfortable pace, no one should hike alone.  Due to the rugged nature of the summit, our lead group, if any, will hold at the junctions and challenges to insure that the end group has descended safely back to the kettle holes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Proper "Hikesafe" clothing and gear required. Know your equipment and how to pack your gear, review the weather conditions before you arrive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Hike Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Difficulty/hike rating:  moderate/experienced  {easy paced but have mountain trail experience  1 mph pace if elevation is steep}&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Mileage: about 5 miles  (that means short but a steeper ascend)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Elevation gain: about 2700&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;What to pack: gear up for sudden changes of temperature, wind exposure, sun block, rain/wind jacket, fleece pullover, gloves for rock scrambles. First aid items for scrapes, cuts and bruises, sprains. toilet kit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;NO WATER SOURCE noted on this trail.  pack 3 ltrs total of water &amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"gatorade" drinks or gels to replace your electrolytes along with easy to eat foods. This is advised for any high endurance exercise that lasts for over one hour.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/f/2/event_1809458.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1"&gt;http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/d/4/event_128896852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 hike 1.10 mi/58 min/+792 ft on the Caps Ridge TrailThe trail leaves the parking area and crosses a wet section on log bridges, then ascends steadily up the lower part of the ridge. There is an outcrop of granite on the right that provides a fine view, particularly of the summit of Jefferson and the Caps Ridge ahead. There are several potholes in this outcrop; such potholes are normally formed only by torrential streams, and such streams occur on high ridges like the Ridge of the Caps only during the melting of a glacier, so these potholes indicate to geologists that the continental ice sheet once covered this area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to the junction of The Linkentering alpine zone hike 1.00 mi/1 hr 7 min/+1245 ft on the Caps Ridge TrailAbout 100 yd. beyond this outcrop, the Link enters from the left, providing a nearly level but rough path that runs to the Castle Trail just below the Castles, making possible a very scenic though strenuous loop over the Caps and Castles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Caps Ridge Trail follows the narrow crest of the ridge, becoming steeper and rougher as it climbs up into scrub, and views become increasingly frequent. The trail reaches the lowest Cap after a steep scramble up ledges, and it runs entirely in the open from here on. The trail ascends very steeply up the ridge to the highest Cap, then continues to climb steeply as the ridge blends into the summit mass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to the junction of The Cornice hike 0.40 mi/32 min/+663 ft on the Caps Ridge TrailThe Cornice enters left, providing a very rough route to the Castle Trail and Edmands Col, and then diverges right in 20 yd., providing an easy shortcut to Monticello Lawn and points to the south. to Mt JeffersonBack to here hike 0.40 mi/12 min/-663 ft on the Caps Ridge Trail to the junction of The Cornice hike 1.00 mi/30 min/-1245 ft on the Caps Ridge Trail to the junction of The Linkleaving alpine zone hike 1.10 mi/34 min/-792 ft on the Caps Ridge TrailThere is an outcrop of granite on the left that provides a fine view, particularly of the summit of Jefferson and the Caps Ridge ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several potholes in this outcrop; such potholes are normally formed only by torrential streams, and such streams occur on high ridges like the Ridge of the Caps only during the melting of a glacier, so these potholes indicate to geologists that the continental ice sheet once covered this area. The trail descends the lower part of the ridge steadily, crossing a wet section on log bridges very near the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail terminates at the parking lot. to Caps Ridge TrailheadTotalsDistance 5.00 miTime 3 hr 53 minElev Gain +2760 ftElev Loss -2760 ftElev Change 0 ftDriving DirectionsShow in Google EarthDownload to GPS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>8:30 am trailhead. (restrooms at the rt 302 Irving Station before Baseline Rd great wraps &amp; sandwiches).  phone/text so we have real plans to meet you for the meetup, and no question of if your in the right location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340887903000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330515241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Whites! Mt Jefferson Via Caps Ridge  4000ft  360 views! CasualMX pace</name><id>dgmrlcyqjbgc</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340541000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/54319292/</event_url></item>