<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/9/c/c/event_98999852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Enneagram at the Movies has been very successful, informative and fun with Herb Pearce's Personality Types group.&amp;nbsp; Herb has invited Unique People over to experience a new way of getting experience with the Enneagram and more importantly having a meal and watching a movie with interesting people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie will be The Wizard of Oz.&amp;nbsp; Most of us have seen this classic but how many years ago was the last time you saw it?&amp;nbsp; There are many interesting characters to type in this film.&amp;nbsp; Herb will also be serving a vegetarian dinner and snacks. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of dinner, snacks, movie and lessons about the Enneagram (and life) is $20.&amp;nbsp; This is less than what most would spend going out to dinner and a movie theater.&amp;nbsp; If you can't afford the $20 please contact me or Herb and we can try to make it affordable to you.&amp;nbsp; Likewise, if you can afford more than $20 and want to donate by paying a bit more it will help those who pay less.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner starts at 7:00pm and the movie starts at 8:00pm.&amp;nbsp; It is recommended that you attend both but if you only are able to attend the dinner or movie that is fine too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a description of the event from Herb:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We'll see a great movie The Classic "Wizard of Oz" - great way to learn the Enneagram - and clarify all the characters regarding type and type relationship dynamics - a perfect way to deepen your knowledge of the Enneagram. We'll stop and start the movie to clearly see types and relationship dynamics in the movie, including subtypes. Lots of fun. Dinner and snacks provided! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Vegetarian Dinner 7:00 Movie 8:00 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Herb Pearce is an Enneagram expert, workshop leader, therapist, phone coach and author of the Idiot's Guide to the Enneagram and Herb's Tips for Living."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332635041000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330932883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enneagram at the Movies - The Wizard of Oz</name><id>55017162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332630000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/55017162/</event_url></item>