<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01864</zip><lat>42.577489</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kittys Restaurant</name><city>North Reading </city><id>795105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;The R rated hypnotist, Frank Santos Jr.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;3.26.10 UPDATE: We WILL be getting the discount price of $18.00 per ticket.  When you call leave a message on the machine and Craig will call you back with in 24 hours to hold your reservation.  Please remember to update the site saying something to the effect &amp;quot;called my reservation in&amp;quot;.  Between the 3 Meetup groups looks like we will have 14-18 people.  It only takes a minute to call.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;b&gt;The phone # to call to reserve your ticket is: 978-430-2990&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TICKET INFORMATION:&lt;/b&gt; To reserve your ticket you will need to call in your own reservation at the phone number below, when you call leave a message and they will call you back to get your information, when you call tell them &amp;quot;you want to reserve your ticket with the Meetup.com group&amp;quot;! They will be putting us all at 1 or 2 tables (depending on the amount of people we have attending the event, we have this posted on all 3 of our groups.) When you call they will need a credit card # to reserve your spot. They will NOT charge your card all that does is hold your spot. When you get to the restaurant then you can pay for your ticket with cash. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If you don't call and want to pay at the door the night of the event you can do that but be prepared that if the event is sold out, then you will not be able to get it and that you may not be sitting with the rest of us from the group(s). It only takes a minute to call in your reservation.  &lt;b&gt;PLEASE remember to put on you RSVP that you have called in your reservation seeing that we need to get a count to the restaurant! See you all there!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little bit about Frank Santos: Be amazed when you, your friends or strangers across the room become stars of the show, as I make them believe that they are singers, dancers and much, much more. This is a performance where the audience becomes the show. My performance has limitless variations and can please every appetite. This is a hilarious, energetic and unique show that you will never forget!  Frank takes all his participants by volunteering he will not pick you out of the crowd and make you go up infrom of everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little bit about the restaurant: Kitty's restaurant has been a fixture in North Reading for over 60 years. Join us for family-style Italian cooking with one of the largest menus in the North Reading area. Our menu has something for everyone, from grilled cheese and delicious pizza to home-style lobster pie. Whether you are a regular at Kitty's or just find yourself visiting North Reading, MA we look forward to seeing you. Enjoy our spacious dining rooms, or sit in our barroom where you can enjoy, good friends, our full bar, Keno &amp;amp; MA State Lottery, and root on the local sports teams playing on one of our HD TVs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out Frank Santos Jr's Website at &lt;a href="http://www.franksanto.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.franksanto...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info and reservations for any show, please call 978-430-2990. Full Kitty's menu available before and during the show, leave your name and phone # on the answering machine, you will get a return phone call with in 1 day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20 per person, I will be sending an update as the date gets closer to see if we can get the discount again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 6:30pm and the show starts at 8:15pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meetup early get settled, grab a bite to eat and sit back and enjoy the show! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the date gets closer I will call and see if I can reserve a few tables for us and I will update the site accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are responsible for getting your own ticket, paying your portion of the bill, tax and tip!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When the bill comes and you figure out your portion of the bill, we ask that you DON'T leave until all the money is collected and the bill is finalized!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt; Park in the back of the building and come in the door w/the awning over the stairs, walk in the 2 doors, stop and pay for your ticket and look for the Meetup table(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come out and get a really good laugh!&lt;br /&gt;We Look forward to seeing you!! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside look for the Meetup sign(s).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270508087000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264913561000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The R-Rated Hypnotist Frank Santos Jr.</name><id>12471754</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270334700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12471754/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/4/global_9199748.jpeg</photo_url></item>