<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.240210</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.572320</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or   instructors.&amp;nbsp; The organizers only set the time and place, each person   participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.&amp;nbsp;   Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions   for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are   appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll take a leisurely "sunset" paddle for about 2 hours looking for signs of wildlife along the shore and in the boggy areas.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We should be able to get into some areas that are usually too shallow or too weedy in the summer months.&amp;nbsp; Please arrive in time to be in your kayak and ready to paddle by 6:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are new to kayaking and you are not sure if you can paddle well enough to stay with the group, I can arrive earlier and we can paddle together for a while so you can assess your skills.&amp;nbsp; Please let me know if this is of interest to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make sure you wear a PFD that&amp;nbsp; fits you properly, and have a whistle and a headlamp or flashlight since we will be out near or past sunset.&amp;nbsp; You should not need the headlamp, but it is a state requirement after "dark"/sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at boat ramp</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307803862000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305672209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After work paddle at Whitehall</name><id>18755771</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306360800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/18755771/</event_url></item>