<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AMC Auditorium, 4 Joy Street, Boston MA &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM potluck, 7:00 PM slideshow &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Erica Bloom for a potluck dinner and slide show by from her numerous trips to Tanzania, including AMC treks up Kilimanjaro and AMC safaris with the Hadzabe and Maasai tribes. A land of beauty and contrasts, Tanzania sits near the equator in East Africa and is home to Mount Kilimanjaro, Ngorongoro Crater, the vast Serengeti Plains, the Zanzibar islands, and people from over 100 different local tribes. This colorful mix of people, places, and animals enchants visitors and has kept Erika returning over and over again.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan to attend, please RSVP at AMCBostonSlideshows@gmail.com. For those who wish to participate in the potluck at 6:30, feel free to use the following guidelines for what to bring: Last names beginning with A-J bring a main dish, K-P bring drinks/dessert, Q-Z bring appetizer or side dish. Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome. Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (stovetop, oven, microwave, sink, fridge, etc).  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287198286000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283305642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tanzania &amp; Kilimanjaro: People, Mountains, and Wildlife (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>14612894</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287009000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/14612894/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/a/7/global_17632263.jpeg</photo_url></item>