<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather looks ok so far&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; TODAY&lt;br /&gt; NW WIND AROUND 10 KT, BECOMING W 5 TO 10 KT THIS AFTERNOON.&lt;br /&gt; SEAS AROUND 1 FT.  so that means the river should be less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I TRY TO CHOOSE THE BEST DAY SO THE EVENT IS MEANINGFUL AND PLEASANT ALONG WITH BEING WORTH IT FOR THE TRAVEL, ETC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with all my paddles, i dont set a finish time, when we are done exploring/ socializing .etc, then we are done or you can always head back earlier.SO MOST OF YOU KNOW THIS, NOT A NEW THING and then there is the after event time,etc.&lt;br /&gt;I dont have no cheap meetup, might go on for 8 hours LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok i chose this particular location because there is an interesting current down here, Hambuger cove is also nice..but mostly because this will be our take out point when we do the longer CT river trip from the OPRAH House down through Chapman Pond, Waleboane Cove, Seldon iLand / creek and if time some of this hambugger again its also close to LORD cove for another fall paddle.&lt;br /&gt;ok you get the idea, this is an important boat launch for us in the fall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so bring a portable lunch, grinders or whatever.&lt;br /&gt;Barbie-q-is later&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Essex starting with August 9, 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa   9      Low  12:11 AM     0.8   5:53 AM    Rise  2:49 PM      50&lt;br /&gt;     9     High   5:46 AM     2.4   7:56 PM     Set 11:50 PM&lt;br /&gt;     9      Low  12:04 PM     1.0&lt;br /&gt;     9     High   6:19 PM     3.4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The river will be at its fastest current but on the return trip it should be moderating.&lt;br /&gt;be ready to PADDLE FAST AND HARD to cross the river (we will PADDLE upstream a bit so to correct for the high drift), BIG boats may swamp you.&lt;br /&gt;SO you should be ready now that you have been out on the ocean and felt the waves and currents there.&lt;br /&gt;this is just a bit more serious here (boats, logs, stringer trees and whatever) please dont fall in and if you do hold onto your boat and blow the whistle, you should have a paddle leash a string or anything is ok paddles are expensive, but really it acts as a SLOWING anchor and something to grab on to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I DONT WANT TO GO IN THE WATER TO SAVE YOU..THERE ARE BUGS AND OTHER THINGS I DONT WANT IN MY MOUTH THERE..SOMETIMES DEAD BODY'S FLOAT ALL THE WAY DOWN FROM hfd...LOL..AND FORGET THE SHORE, (LOW TIDE) ITS GOT 5 FEET OR MORE DEEP OF MUD IF YOU THINK YOU CAN TRY TO RE-ENTER THERE..YOU WONT BE ABLE TO AND YOU WILL DIE THERE LIKE ONE OF THOSE STICKY MOUSE TRAPS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most likely you wont be able to do a paddle float entry..but an assisted entry is quit probable here with good success.....if you know some of the stuff and if you seen and did that stuff at the lake this summer with us..you will be back in in a flash..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AFTER PARTY:&lt;br /&gt;SINCE WE ARE ON RTE 9, THE AFTER PARTY / BARBIE-Q WILL AGAIN BE AT 7 FALLS PARK...THIS WAS A POPULAR SPOT LAST TIME.&lt;br /&gt;ON OUR RETURN TRIP , take rte 9 north Off of exit # 10 take a right (south direction) RTE 154, go about half mile, go down hill, look left for the park.&lt;br /&gt;I have to go past the park to find a big driveway to turn around, then pull up on the side of the park near the end of the road entrance part.&lt;br /&gt;GPS users 9a / rte 154 = # 1 Saybrook Rd, Higganum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE PUT IN SITE FOR THE EVENT FROM HARTFORD:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;TAKE RTE I 91 south to rte 9 (its a left exit)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take rte 9 south to exit #3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(You can take a left at rte 154 it simply connects to 153 a short distance up)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But you can also Take a left onto rte 153 = Plains Road that turns into West Ave under the bridge..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;just look at your maps you will see what i mean..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK things are a bit weird in town so follow the directions and look at your map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay on West Ave for apx .8 miles till you get to the center rotary like thing..&lt;br /&gt;Just stay on West Ave&lt;br /&gt;you will pass Main street, then Pratt St, then take ~~&amp;gt;North Main street for one block, the first right should be Bushnell St, take that..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow it down toward the Dauntless Boat Yard..right before the boat yard take the left dirt road = Teal Lane to the boat launch area...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS use either  BUSHNELL Street, or TEAL LANE  some GPS dont recognize TEAL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But i know ALL of you have GPS's now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:  ALL KAYAKS ARE NOW RESERVED&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their handling characteristics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks must be reserved before i load some of them; about 3 hours before the event, after then forget it.&lt;br /&gt;None can be left on the trailer at the boat ramp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Homless Persons Bathtub= Pungo 12' with F/R floataion bags 1nstalled= ANNIE&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper &amp;amp; Dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= AL-r&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = ALEX&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'=  JIM&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= JIM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 10 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all soon. &lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Toyota Avalon/kayak trailer/Orange striped cones on car roof</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218470972000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217808184000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recreational &amp; Sea Kayak Event... ESSEX COVE TO HAMBUGER COVE  TRIP</name><id>8469886</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218297600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8469886/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/0/f/global_5044879.jpeg</photo_url></item>