<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 90</address_2><address_1>45 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 523 5260</phone><name>SunDo Mountain Taoist Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>489318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Taoist Practice, Tao Te Ching Discussion &amp;amp; Tea&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a one hour Taoist Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation practice.  Following the practice, we will have a discussion focusing on a verse 25 from the Tao Te Ching while enjoying some roasted corn or barley tea. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taoist meditation is a method for cultivating, refining, and circulating internal energy within the chakras and meridian channels in the body. Taoists believe that breathing and energy meditation fills the reservoirs of the chakras and meridian with energy, which is then distributed to all the major organ systems. Please wear comfy clothing. No previous experience necessary. This event is FREE and all physical fitness levels are welcome. Practice can be adapted to suit individual needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more about the Tao Te Ching, here are a few paragraphs from the forward of Stephen Mitchell's translation of this famous book.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: beige"&gt;&amp;quot;Tao Te Ching (pronounced, more or less, Dow Deh Jing) can be translated as The Book of the Immanence of the Way or The Book of the Way and of How It Manifests Itself in the World or, simply, The Book of the Way. Since it is already well known by its Chinese title, I have let that stand. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Lao Tzu, its author, there is practically nothing to be said. He may have been an older contemporary of Confucius (551—479 B.C.E.) and may have held the position of archive-keeper in one of the petty kingdoms of the time. But all the information that has come down to us is highly suspect. Even the meaning of his name is uncertain (the most likely interpretations: &amp;quot;the Old Master&amp;quot; or, more picturesquely, &amp;quot;the Old Boy&amp;quot;). Like an Iroquois woodsman, he left no traces. All he left us is his book: the classic manual on the art of living, written in a style of gem like lucidity, radiant with humor and grace and large heartedness and deep wisdom: one of the wonders of the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Verse 25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There was something formless and perfect&lt;br /&gt;before the universe was born.&lt;br /&gt;It is serene. Empty.&lt;br /&gt;Solitary. Unchanging.&lt;br /&gt;Infinite. Eternally present.&lt;br /&gt;It is the mother of the universe.&lt;br /&gt;For lack of a better name,&lt;br /&gt;I call it the Tao.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It flows through all things,&lt;br /&gt;inside and outside, and returns&lt;br /&gt;to the origin of all things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tao is great.&lt;br /&gt;The universe is great.&lt;br /&gt;Earth is great.&lt;br /&gt;Man is great.&lt;br /&gt;These are the four great powers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Man follows the earth.&lt;br /&gt;Earth follows the universe.&lt;br /&gt;The universe follows the Tao.&lt;br /&gt;The Tao follows only itself.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/b1/Sunbeams.jpg/800px-Sunbeams.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287603232000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281234666000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taoist Practice &amp; the Tao Te Ching</name><id>xxrrnynnbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287527400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/14353461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/d/global_17722653.jpeg</photo_url></item>