<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Are you ready for your total empowerment?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    My name is Matthew, the organizer of Total Empowerment; are you a seeker of knowledge, unlimited confidence, power, energy, health and financial freedom? - you can have it all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    My personal story first...&lt;br /&gt;    I am a successful entrepreneur who has founded, built, and sold several companies starting at the age of 19. Now I own several million dollars of ocean &amp;amp; lake front, commercial, and residential property.&lt;br /&gt;    I was financially free at the age of 29 and a self made millionaire by age 30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I would like to share with you my experiences &amp;amp; extensive studies of wealth psychology, real estate, business start-ups, personal development, NLP, belief &amp;amp; value systems, mind power, mastering influence, spiral dynamics, fitness &amp;amp; nutrition to name but a few.&lt;br /&gt;    The culmination of several hundred books, thousands of audios and certified graduate of more than 30 self development courses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This group will tap into the cutting edge of the newest and most powerful techniques, processes and concepts leading to Total Empowerment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm tall, brown hair,  and will be wearing a button downshirt, sweater, and dress pants.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Croteau</member_name><member_id>5083434</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218236663000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>You will walk away with a new mindset that will empowr you with a choice for freedom, seriously, you will not be disapointed!!</why><group><who>Millionaires</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>millionaire-76</urlname><id>692993</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Millionaire Total Empowerment Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214525177000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Millionaire Total Empowerment August Meetup</name><id>8223946</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218063600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/millionaire-76/events/8223946/</event_url></item>