<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Head Beach Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04562</zip><lat>43.719730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hermit Island Campground</name><city>Sagadahoc</city><id>9545002</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.848686</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If the weather is good that weekend Ingrid is going to go Camping for the Columbus Day Long Weekend.  This campground is on the Casco Bay in Maine and does allow dogs on this weekend according to Ingrid. She would be interested in having others and their dogs joining her.  There are hiking trails on the campground and several beaches on the campground or near by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to the campground website:  &lt;a href="http://www.hermitisland.com/index.html"&gt;http://www.hermitisland.com/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the off season sites are on a first come first served basis and cost $35 a night.  Check in is any time but check out is by noon time the next day.  Based on your schedule you could also choose to arrive on a later date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ingrid would like to make it clear that she in one sense isn't "officially hosting" this event as she hasn't actually been there yet and she has never been a host for an event.  She feels it will be an adventure for all of us if we go.  She says, "&lt;span&gt;I can help coordinate with someone but feel a bit uncomfortable being the official "host" since I've never been one!  She thinks it would take a minimum of 4 people to make it workable and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;pls note that in all likelihood I will head out on Fri Oct 5......people can come that day or any other day of the weekend.Since two tents are allowed per site , one could share with the person already there as long as there is some coordination since only one car can be parked at the campsite .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is one of this rare spots where one can camp on a beautiful beach I am told.It is the only weekend open to dogs !&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This trip will happen ONLY if the weather is good.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349753520000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347937829000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping Hermit Island Campground - Columbus Weekend Oct 4-9</name><id>82894642</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349451000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/82894642/</event_url></item>