<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.329926</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-964-6684</phone><name>Union Street Bar and Grill</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>851424</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Kathe D. has organized this event. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and join your Sitz friends and guests at one of our favorite spots to meet for an after work gathering. &lt;br /&gt;

Union St. is located in the heart of Newton Centre near the intersection of Beacon St. and Centre St. It is a neighborhood restaurant and bar focusing on great food, beverages, sports, entertainment and a warm and friendly atmosphere. &lt;br /&gt;

We have had many after works in the “Attic” and everyone seemed to enjoy themselves along with receiving wonderful service. Light appetizers will be served compliments of Sitzundjibers Social Club. Cash bar. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Union St. restaurant is located in Newton Centre down the driveway behind the “Big Sky Bread Company”. &lt;br /&gt;

FROM MASS PIKE EASTBOUND: Take exit 17, go straight and take the first right at the lights. This is Centre St. You will continue and go past Newton Country Day school and B.C. Law on your right. Cross Commonwealth Ave. and you will soon be in Newton Centre. Once there, take a left on to Beacon St. and a quick right on to Union St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM MASS PIKE WESTBOUND: Take exit 17 Newton/Watertown and stay in the left lane passing Citizen’s Bank and the Crowne Plaza Hotel. Take a left over the bridge after the parking lot seeing the Crowne Plaza on your left again. Take the first right at the lights which is Centre St. Follow the directions above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FROM THE GREEN LINE “D” TRAIN: get off at the Newton Centre stop and go directly across the street to the driveway next to the Big Sky Bread Co.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING: There is on street parking with no fees after 6p.m. There is also a municipal parking lot right in the middle of Newton Centre across from the Bank of America which is right near Union St. restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>14</waitlist_count><updated>1368732078000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365330428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An afterwork in Newton</name><id>113100802</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367964000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/113100802/</event_url></item>