<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 585-9777</phone><name>Woodstar Cafe</name><city>Northampton</city><id>669288</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will meet at the Woodstar Cafe at 3:00 and 4:00 pm to help place flyers around Northampton for upcoming Aprill 11 event with Mike Berger and film, &lt;a href="http://www.improbablecollapse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Improbable Collapse: the Demolition of our Republic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will post flyers at Smith College around 4:30 PM and then meet at 5:00 PM at the Smith College campus center cafeteria for an organizational meeting. The meeting should conclude around 6:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for part or all these events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And remember!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, April 11, 2007&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;First Churches&lt;br /&gt;Main Street and Center Street&lt;br /&gt;Northampton, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth presents: &amp;quot;Improbable Collapse: The Demolition of Our Republic,&amp;quot; the first film to look at the events of September 11, 2001 from a scientific perspective. Discussions will follow the film screening with film-maker Michael Berger; DVDs and other resources will be available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On September 11, 2001, the World Trade Center Twin Towers disintegrated in a manner that some scientists say resembled deliberately calculated demolitions. The facts open for discussion include: at 5:20 p.m. that same day another building, the 47-story WTC 7, completely collapsed within 70 feet of its footprint in 6.6 seconds. These three buildings became the first such structures to ever suffer complete collapse due to fire and structural damage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The new documentary, &amp;quot;Improbable Collapse: The Demolition of our Republic,&amp;quot; closely examines one of the world?s worst catastrophes from a civil engineering perspective. Using photo and video footage as well as expert scientific testimony, the film thoroughly analyzes the official reports, offering varied criticisms of the official findings, while presenting a more plausible hypothesis. Both government investigations and the mainstream media have quietly ignored the findings from these scientific experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the media coordinator for 911truth.org, Berger has appeared on ABC World News Tonight, CNN Showbiz Tonight, and Scarborough Country as well as dozens of radio appearances including a recent debate with Matthew Rothschild, editor of The Progressive Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please help promote this event. Download one of these flyers, make copies, distribute everywhere! [Bring as many color flyers with you to share as possible for those who cannot print color copies.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org/images/resources/Poster%20color-Northampton%20MA.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org/images/resources/Poster%20color-Northampton%20MA.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.911truth.o...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org/images/resources/Poster%20bw-Northampton%20MA.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org/images/resources/Poster%20bw-Northampton%20MA.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.911truth.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And to link for more information on tour for all venues from April 10-23, see: &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.FlybyNews.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541227000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175552580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meeting for northeast Improbable Collapse</name><id>5630496</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175799600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/5630496/</event_url></item>