<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1660 Soldiers Field Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.358898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>California Closets </name><city>Brighton</city><id>1677021</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.153595</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Put on your most glamorous shoes, join us for a fabulous ladies night and come mingle with other shoe loving  fashionistas while enjoying complimentary wine, cheese, and delicious  appetizers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amidst the footwear, fashion, and fun, you can check out California  Closets' gorgeous showroom, enjoy the latest in spring and summer  fashions, compete for fabulous prizes in the pink carpet walk-off, and  enter to win a $2,500 California Closets gift certificate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California Closets is the leader in creating beautiful, functional home  closets, and the Brighton  facility showcases many different design  options for you to peruse and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raffle proceeds will benefit &lt;a href="http://www.projectsmile.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Project Smile&lt;/a&gt;, a nonprofit organization dedicated to  helping children involved in traumatic events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California Closets is located at 1660 Soldiers Field Road, Brighton.   There's plenty of free parking.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo)  inside California Closets . If you have trouble finding us, please call 774 232 0000.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305848769000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Join the Hello Stiletto Shoe Club and other fabulous ladies for a spring cocktail party- enjoy complimentary wine, cheese, and delicious appetizers.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305072026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ladies Night at California Closets, Brighton. Wine Tasting, Free Apps and More!</name><id>17918881</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305844200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/17918881/</event_url></item>