<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;UPDATE 4/24: Again, the response for this event has been HUGE!  If you haven't heard? the weather forecast for tomorrow is very warm. We will be meeting up at the picnic tables/ in order to secure them at 1pm (please see &amp;quot;where to meetup...&amp;quot; Our hike(s) will be BEFORE the pot luck picnic, With so many attending, due to hiking abilities, we are planning on the picnic at 3pm (which is tentative). &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE 4/16:The response among the groups invited has been great! So, we have decided to add a &amp;quot;POT LUCK PICNIC&amp;quot; to this event! This way everyone will have a chance to socialize. It will be FUN!  SO, if you would like to participate? Please bring a dish/snack or dessert to share, and your own water/beverage and outdoor chair/blanket to sit on. There are tables, but not sure how many will be available when we want them. That's part of the reason why we are meeting up where the tables are.. as to secure them.  I will provide the paper/plastic, trash bags, etc. and my food items.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you feel you need to get out?  Come join us!  This will be a moderate hike / walk.  &lt;br /&gt;Let's hope for good weather!  Don't forget your camera! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;***NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; This is a cross posted event - 5 meetup groups.  &lt;br /&gt;                         Foul weather cancels the hike. If I know in advance, I will send  &lt;br /&gt;                         out a message to all RSVP. But, please make sure to check for an update before &lt;br /&gt;                          heading out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT PURGATORY CHASM: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A unique natural landmark, Purgatory Chasm runs for a quarter of a mile between granite walls rising as high as 70 feet. Popular with picnickers and rock-climbers alike, the Chasm is believed to have its origin in the sudden release of dammed-up glacial meltwater near the end of the last Ice Age, approximately 14,000 years ago. &lt;br /&gt;Trails lead to a wide variety of rock formations, with such romantic names as The Corn Crib, The Coffin, The Pulpit, Lovers' Leap and Fat Man's Misery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Go to: hppt://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/purg.htm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE 4/ 16: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will all meetup at the picnic tables behind the visitor center</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241374987000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239385078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>  PURGATORY  CHASM - Hike/Walk  &amp; Quick- Pic</name><id>10159436</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240678800000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/10159436/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/c/global_8084060.jpeg</photo_url></item>