<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>165 Martins Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.257970</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>World's End Reservation</name><city>Hingham</city><id>1257585</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.873442</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's get out to Hingham, MA and hike World's End. After we Finish the hike we will head into Hull to the Sea Dog Brew Pub for a late lunch and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's Meet at the Gate House NOT AT MY CAR. The Gate House is Easier to find on the property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About World's End&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Rolling hills and rocky shorelines offer sweeping views of the Boston skyline, while tree-lined carriage paths designed by famed landscape architect Frederick Law Olmsted make delightful walking trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes World’s End a special place? &lt;br /&gt;

 We think it’s the tree-lined carriage paths and sweeping views of the Boston skyline, only 15 miles away. The 251-acre coastscape includes rocky shores, broad hillsides, and open fields bracketed by pockets of woodlands. The property is ideal for walking, picnicking, jogging, horseback riding, cross-country skiing, or simply enjoying nature and the outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/worlds-end.html"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/worlds-end.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please wear shoes made for walking/hiking. Bring water and a light jacket. I sugest that people try and carpool as there is limited parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trails&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 4.5 miles of carriage paths and footpaths. Moderate hiking. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Facilities&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Public restrooms. Benches. Drinking water fountain. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;When to Visit&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Year-round, daily, &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;8 a.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to sunset. Allow a minimum of 2 hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regulations &amp;amp; Advisories&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Dogs must be kept on a leash at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Martin’s Lane &lt;br /&gt;

 Hingham, MA 02043 &lt;br /&gt;

 Telephone: &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;781.740.7233&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Gatehouse: &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;781.740.6665&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Latitude: 42.2584 &lt;br /&gt;

 Longitude: -70.8734 &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=42.25840929910,-70.87341600180" target="_blank"&gt;Get directions on Google Maps.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From Rt. 3, take Exit 14, Rt. 228 North for 6.5 mi. Turn left onto Rt. 3A and follow for 0.7 mi. Turn right onto Summer St. and, at major intersection with Rockland St., continue straight across onto Martin’s Lane. Follow for 0.7 mi. to entrance and parking (70 cars) at end. Roadside parking is not permitted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Admission Fees &amp;amp; Permits&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Trustees members and children free. Nonmember adults: $6.  Parking is free with admission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sea Dog Brew Pub Hull | Sunset Bay Marina, 2 A Street| (781) 773-1840&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Maine's famous micro-brewery has now come ashore on the waterfront of beautiful Sunset Bay in Hull, Massachusetts. With an array of award winning beers, the best local seafood and classic pub fare, Sea Dog Hull has become the hottest casual dining destination on the South Shore. Enjoy our great beer and food while taking in one of the most spectacular seaside views you'll find anywhere. Our location at the Sunset Bay Marina overlooks the Boston Harbor Islands and the city skyline. Sea Dog Hull's sunsets are a must see! Hang out on the deck or tie your boat up to one of our Sea Dog slips, either way you are guaranteed to have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Gate house</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria</member_name><member_id>2096131</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369099594000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368026124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Hike - World's End, Hingham MA</name><id>118364422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368892800000</time><rsvp_limit>33</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/118364422/</event_url></item>