<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 William St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.399172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.623.1212</phone><name>Unity Church of God</name><city>Somerville</city><id>790021</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119963</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>National Award-Winning Performer of Scottish, Irish, Jazz, &amp;amp; American Music &lt;b&gt;Jeremy Kittel&lt;/b&gt; ~ fiddle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tristan Clarridge&lt;/b&gt; ~ cello&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Simon Chrisman&lt;/b&gt; ~ hammered dulcimer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bodek Janke&lt;/b&gt; ~ drums/percussion&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jeremykittel.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jeremykittel.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jeremykitt...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonicbids.com/epk/epk.aspx?epk_id=8535" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonicbids.com/epk/epk.aspx?epk_id=8535" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sonicbids....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy Kittel is rapidly earning a reputation as one of the nation’s most creative young musicians. Classically trained, he grew up in the Irish, folk and jazz music scenes of Ann Arbor and Detroit. As a youth he often traveled to Ireland and Scotland to further his studies of traditional music. In addition to performing with his own band and as a soloist with orchestras, Jeremy tours worldwide as the newest member of the Grammy-winning Turtle Island Quartet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 24-year-old fiddler/violinist/composer has earned an impressive list of accolades including multiple U.S. National Scottish Fiddle Championships, Alternative Styles Awards from the American String Teachers Association, and six Detroit Music Awards for Outstanding Folk Artist, Jazz Recording, and Jazz Composer. Jeremy graduated at twenty from the University Of Michigan School Of Music and was awarded the Stanley Medal, their highest musical honor. He was the first recipient of the Daniel Pearl Memorial Violin, and he recorded as a soloist on the multiple Grammy Award-winning CD “Songs of Innocence and Experience” by William Bolcom. At twenty-three he earned a masters degree in Jazz Violin from the prestigious Manhattan School of Music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy has performed at over a thousand concerts and festivals including the Kennedy Center, “A Prairie Home Companion,” the Ryder Cup Opening Ceremony, and Carnegie Hall. He has been guest artist with the Vancouver Symphony, Detroit Symphony, and Rochester Philharmonic Orchestras; Mark O’Connor, and Darol Anger’s Republic of Strings. Jeremy has taught at many camps and schools including the International Music Academy in the Czech Republic, Swannanoa Gathering and Mark O’Connor Fiddle Camps. He also works with school orchestras nationwide in workshops and performances, focusing on developing students’ fiddling, jazz, and improvisation skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy’s first CD, “Celtic Fiddle,” was named “one of the top 20 Celtic albums of 2000” by the radio show Celtic Connections. His second, “Roaming,” took second place for Best Celtic Instrumental Album in an international competition. His most recent recording, “Jazz Violin,” won the 2006 Detroit Music Award for Outstanding Jazz Recording. His fourth CD, soon to be released, features special guests including Edgar Meyer and Chris Thile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As one reviewer said, “It’s a much over-used cliché, but I really believe this is what genius sounds like. Highly recommended!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minimum suggested donation $15 at the door, $12 in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations are recommended - notlobreservations @ comcast.net&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the producer, ask for me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260148370000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259213113000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jeremy Kittel Band</name><id>11958571</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259974800000</time><rsvp_limit>175</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/11958571/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/2/global_11987618.jpeg</photo_url></item>