<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's hard to believe, but Ghostbusters is 25 years old this year.  They've made an all new remastered print and the best way to see a 100-foot marshmallow man is on a big screen!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie:&lt;/b&gt; Ghostbusters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie time: &lt;/b&gt; 9:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $9.50 [ &lt;b&gt;Tickets online:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/090822.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;  ] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be waiting outside the main entrance to the movie unless it's raining, in which case I'll wait in the lobby.  Look for me - I have short blonde hair with purple in my bangs and I'll be wearing a Meetup logo button.  I may or may not be wearing a Ghostbusters costume and holding a jar of Fluff.  At about 15 mins before, we'll go in and get seats.  I'll also post a 7pm dinner for this one as a separate Meetup event, so look for that. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About &amp;quot;Ghostbusters&amp;quot;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/ghostbusters/" target="_blank"&gt;93% on Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;When Dr. Peter Venkman (Bill Murrary) and his Columbia University colleagues (Dan Aykroyd, Harold Ramis, Ernie Hudson) are kicked out of their prestigious academic posts, they start a private practice as professional ghost-catchers. Although the three parascientists are idle for awhile, their television advertisements finally pay off when beautiful Dana Barrett (Sigourney Weaver) contracts them. It seems her apartment has become the entryway for ghastly ghosts and goofy ghouls hellbent on terrorizing New York City. Soon they're going to her rescue, trying to rid the city of the slimy creatures. GHOSTBUSTERS hit US screens in June of 1984 and went on to become one of the most successful comedy films of all time, spawning a sequel and a popular animated series.&amp;quot; (Rated PG)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The theatre entrance is on the left side of the building - look for our sidewalk poster case&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Brattle Theater:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle shows the best in classic, cutting-edge, foreign, and art-house films. We also show first-run films and new releases of classic films, but our specialty is a repertory programming format consisting of films from a particular director, genre, or subject shown over the course of a week, or on the same weekday throughout the month. Visit our Series Archive to learn more about past repertory programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Movies have been shown at the Brattle Theatre since 1953, when Bryant Haliday and Cyrus Harvey Jr. started things off with a screening of the German film, Der Hauptmann von Köpenick (The Captain from Köpenick). Haliday and Harvey later founded Janus Films for the purpose of distributing foreign films nationwide&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296062783000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250695593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nerdy Movie: Ghostbusters (remastered on the big screen!)</name><id>11147852</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250989200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11147852/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/global_5310283.jpeg</photo_url></item>