<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for the Starry, Starry Night event on August 12 from 6 to 9 p.m. at Ferns and Flowers. The cost is $10. You must register in advance with &lt;a href="http://www.fernsandflowers.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ferns and Flowers&lt;/a&gt; (FF) at 401-821-1105 or &lt;a href="http://www.peoplesliquorwarehouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;People's Liquor Warehouse &lt;/a&gt;(PLW) at 401-737-0900. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group attended a wine tasting here a few months ago and it was great!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carlos Figueroa will be featuring his South American wines, Sally Donahue of Best Beverage will feature International Wines from her portfolio, and Marc 'the Wine Guy&amp;quot; of PLW will be doing a wine &amp;amp; sparkling wine cocktails demo. Also featured will be appetizers from Ferns &amp;amp; Flowers new menu, including Duck wings! The back garden will be open for the Perseid Meteor Shower viewing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will send my cell phone number to those who RSVP yes on August 11. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perseid Meteor Shower (I found this on the Web) &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;August 12, 13 - Perseids Meteor Shower. The Perseids is one of the best meteor showers to observe, producing up to 60 meteors per hour at their peak. This year's peak occurs on the morning of August 12, but you may be able to see some meteors any time from July 23 - August 22. The waning gibbous moon will provide some interference in the early morning, so the best viewing will be in the evening before it rises. The radiant point for this shower will be in the constellation Perseus. Look to the northeast after midnight.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250387051000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249003156000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine Tasting, Appetizers and Meteors!</name><id>10998256</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250114400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/10998256/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>