<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday March 8th at City Bar inside the Lenox Hotel located at Copley Square!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Back Bay neighborhood  6:15-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday March 8th. This time we are taking the party to City Bar, a stylish lounge located inside Copley Square's Lenox Hotel.  City Bar is known for having the  best martinis Boston has to offer!    This venue  is a  favorite afterwork destination   for many Bostonians and Back Bay resdients alike.  With spring time almost here ,  I encourage many  of the new members who have not been able to make an event  to please join the group this Thursday for a few cocktails  as we gear for another festive weekend in the city! ( A warm one I hope)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet at the front bar , please look for me upon entering, my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, with winter time in Boston this place will fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line to Copley station &lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to Back Bay station&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173568606000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173075046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Its March Madness!!  Afterwork Mixer at City Bar Back Bay!!</name><id>5537735</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1173395700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/5537735/</event_url></item>