<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>114 Essex  Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.656400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 356-0216</phone><name>Wolf Hollow</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>1239638</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.814900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Let’s go check out the wolves at Wolf Hollow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wolf Hollow is a non-profit organization established in 1990 to teach people about the importance of the wolf in the wild. Wolf Hollow offers a unique opportunity to view gray wolves in as natural a setting as possible. Come see how they interact with their pack members and live in a social unit very similar to human families.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket sales:&lt;/strong&gt; Start at 1:00, formal presentation will start at 1:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Admission:&lt;/strong&gt; $7.50 Adults, $5.00 Seniors, $5.00 Children (Ages 5-17).  &lt;span&gt;Children are more than welcome at this event, but note that it is an hour long presentation and the recommended age is five years and up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Wolf Hollow is located approximately 3 miles outside downtown Ipswich on route 133 heading east. From the Boston area take route 128 north to exit 20A (route 1A) heading north.  Turn right onto route 133 east about 8 miles from 128.  We are about a mile and a half down 133 on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;If it is raining then they are closed.  Please remember to check back to this site to see if there are any updates.  If it does rain then we will reschedule.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little information about Wolf Hollow:&lt;/strong&gt; It was founded in 1988 by the late Paul C. Soffron, with the mission of preservation of the wolf in the wild through education and exposure.  Visitors are welcome at Wolf Hollow, where they meet the resident wolves and learn the importance of the wolf in the wild as top predator. By observing how a wolf pack functions, visitors learn how wolves are a benefit to the environment around them and ultimately to us as humans because of the many parallels to our own families.  Wolves are still very much a threatened species and visitors will learn what can be done to help alleviate the threat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wolf Hollow is fully licensed by the State of Massachusetts and the federal government as a 501(c) 3 non-profit organization.  We support our work solely through our admission, gift shop sales, adopt-a-wolf program and donations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their pack of British Colombian timber wolves started with five pups donated by other facilities in the United States.  The original five were from three different litters so that a family could be started at the facility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visitors have the opportunity to view the wolf hollow pack while a one hour educational lecture is presented.  The recommended age for this program is five years and up. While learning about how the wolf lives in a family group, its role in nature, its history with man, and the fight to preserve their species in the wild, visitors observe the wolves interacting with their pack-mates at close range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are running late or get lost call the Meetup phone at 978-304-2811, please note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues?  Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can pay your dues at any event.  Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to seeing you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350417218000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347074342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go check out Wolf Hollow</name><id>81417322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350145800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/81417322/</event_url></item>