<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hello All, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I am pleased to announce that our group will be experiencing a new and exciting transition in the upcoming months. Over the last five years, I have had the privilege creating one of the largest meetup groups in New England. Collectively, we as a group have not only provided a safe environment for our pets to socialize but also raised funds for the MSPCA and Animal Rescue League.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For the last five years, I have maintained and funded the group myself. The time has now arrived for new organizers to take over and continue to provide fresh activities and the best possible atmosphere that is in line with the group's mission. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please welcome Kim and Aimee as our new co-organizers. Many of you may already be familiar with them and their pets. Both Kim and Aimee are long standing members as well as the resident photographers of our group for several years now.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I am thankful to leave the group to two wonderful individuals who I have no doubt will provide our members and their pets with a great experience at each and every meetup. Over the next few months I will stay on in an auxiliary role, as both Kim and Aimee will take over the group entirely.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

All the best to you. Valerius and I are grateful to have met so many kind and generous people.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Valerius now serves as a "therapy pet for empty-nesters" to my parents and extended family along with his adopted brother Slate. I am in process of planning my 2012 nuptials. Both Slate and Valerius are looking forward to it. I hope to see you all in the near future.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Best, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Susana&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Contact Kim and Aimee</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329094945000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326825854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup</name><id>pmhznyqdbqb</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329069600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/48473122/</event_url></item>