<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Argilla Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.670464</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Castle Hill/Crane Beach</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>417392</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.794418</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee </label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Meeting Place:&lt;/b&gt;  Castle Hill, in the upper parking lot by the main house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date/Time:&lt;/b&gt;  Sunday, November 16th at 2:00PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking Fee:&lt;/b&gt; $5/per car at Castle Hill&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the CAPE Group's November excursion we'll spend part of an afternoon photographing the beautiful grounds surrounding the Great House at Castle Hill.  Afterwards we'll have the option to do a little sunset shooting at the Great Marsh right down the road.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Castle Hill is home to a wide diversity of wildlife typical of northeast Massachusetts forests. Deer, fox, turkey, and a multitude of songbirds can be observed from the many trails and roads on Castle Hill. In addition, it is home to several pairs of nesting great horned owls and red-tailed hawks. Due to its location on the Atlantic Ocean and adjacent Crane Beach, unusual species such as turkey vultures, migratory hawks, and even an occasional bald eagle can be seen soaring above the landscape.  Castle Hill is also a link in the &lt;a href="http://www.baycircuit.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Bay Circuit Trail&lt;/a&gt;, offering four miles of moderate hiking trails and roads. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The grounds immediately surrounding the Great House may be closed during an event. If that should happen, our focus will change to the trails around Crane Beach and Wildlife Refuge.  Notice of event changes are posted here, and an e-mail will be sent to the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS (from the Crane Estate website):&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128 north (towards Gloucester), take exit 20A (Route 1A north) and follow for 8 miles to Ipswich. Turn right onto Route 133 east and follow for 1.5 miles. Turn left onto Northgate Road and follow for .5 mi. Turn right onto Argilla Road and follow for 2.3 miles to entrance on left. Gatehouse attendant will direct you to parking area (20 cars) behind Farm Building Complex.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229269877000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220286411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CAPE Group November Meetup: Great House at Castle Hill and Sunset</name><id>8663104</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226862000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/8663104/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/e/global_5361166.jpeg</photo_url></item>