<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Small Wonders: The Keys to Start-Up Success&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfapril12.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Tues. April 17, the EntreTech Forum, co-sponsored by the Medical Development Group, presents a panel of company founders and a venture capital representative from Polaris Ventures who will share their recent experiences in transforming an idea into an operating venture. Our panel will focus on the keys to overcoming common start-up challenges, from forming a great team to attracting (and landing!) the right financial and strategic partners. First time and experienced entrepreneurs are encouraged to bring their questions to what will be an interactive and instructive discussion. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr2012Mtg/cifric.jpg" width="90" height="99" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirza Cifric, founder and CEO of AbVitro Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; a Harvard/Church laboratory startup company, focuses on startups in life sciences, biotechnology, pharma and medical devices. Mirza has co-founded several companies including ImThera Medical of San Diego, a medical device company. He has previously held the following positions: Head of Corporate Development at FORMA Therapeutics, and Chief Executive and General Manager of Solmap Pharmaceutical, and is an Advisory board member at Endicott College and Huamei Diagnostics. Mirza holds a degree in Electrical and Computer Engineering from Northeastern University and Harvard Business School Executive education program. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr2012Mtg/farra.jpg" width="90" height="103" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robert Farra, President &amp;amp; Chief Operating Officer of MicroCHIPS,&lt;/strong&gt; has 20 years of leadership experience developing complex electro-mechanical and fluidic based medical devices and combination products. His experience bridges early stage development through scale-up. Previously he held the following positions: Vice-President of R&amp;amp;D of MicroCHIPS from 2007 &amp;ndash; 2011, Vice-President of Engineering and Manufacturing for Abiomed, Senior Leadership positions at Accellent Endoscopy and Arthur D. Little, Inc. He has 12 domestic and international patents, and an SMME from MIT. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr2012Mtg/hill.jpg" width="90" height="90" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paulina Hill, Senior Associate at Polaris Venture Partners&lt;/strong&gt;, focuses on investments in the life sciences sector. She completed her postdoctoral fellowship in the Chemical Engineering Department at MIT, where she was the Founding President of the MIT Postdoctoral Association. She is a Member of Intellectual Property Presidential Committee at MIT and on the fundraising committee of the nonprofit Women Entrepreneurs in Science &amp;amp; Technology. She received her PhD in Molecular Medicine with a Tissue Engineering focus at Wake Forest University and has over 50 abstracts, manuscript publications, awards and patent contributions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr2012Mtg/russell.jpg" width="90" height="96" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hathaway Russell, Partner &amp;amp; Registered Patent Attorney at Foley Hoag LLP&lt;/strong&gt;, practices intellectual property law with a focus on the life sciences industry. She has extensive experience assisting research institutions, start-up biotechnology companies, and established U.S. and international corporations with many aspects of intellectual property law, including patent portfolio management, freedom-to-operate analysis, due diligence, complex patent litigation and interference proceedings. Hathaway has a particular interest in the areas of pharmacogenomics, proteomics and disease biomarkers, and their application to personalized medicine. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;MDG Members&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a member of the Medical Development Group (MDG) you will receive a discounted admission to the EntreTech Forum for the April meeting. Discount ticket is $15.00 online/ $20.00 at the door. Please choose the MDG Member ticket option when registering online. All registrants under this option will need to verify their MDG membership identification at the meeting attendance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfapril12.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/7_contact.htm"&gt;Map and Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334706131000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314976379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Small Wonders: The Keys to Start-Up Success</name><id>qnlkbcyqgbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334701800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32004622/</event_url></item>