<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-119</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01430</zip><lat>42.697506</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt. Watatic </name><city>Ashburnham</city><id>776106</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.906753</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;TSummit Elevation: 1832 feet &lt;br /&gt;

Elevation gain: About 650 feet &lt;br /&gt;

Total hiking distance: About 3.5 - 4 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 Time: 3+ hours &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Mount Watatic has long been a popular destination for hikers and other outdoor enthusiasts who wish to experience the scenic views that are afforded in all directions from its summit. The Mid-State Trail and Wapack Trail are both long-distance hiking trails that traverse the Reservation property. The diversity of ecological features, including the bald summit, rocky outcrops, forested slopes, seeps and wet lowlands, abut additional lands managed by the DCR (a 211-acre block of Ashburnham State Forest) and the Department of Fish and Game (the 150-acre Watatic Mountain Wildlife Sanctuary and the 263-acre Ashby Wildlife Management Area). The abundant wildlife attracts national hiking, birding and conservation groups to the area. The summit is one of the best places in the northeast to view the annual hawk migration.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topo map of hike &lt;a href="http://www.newenglandtrailreview.com/singlemappage.asp?TID=156"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail map (of sorts) &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/stewardship/rmp/downloads/watatic/Infrastructure.pdf"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Info about dogs on the trail &lt;a href="http://www.wapack.org/faq.html#3"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Massachusetts Route 119:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. West on Rte. 119 from Ashby Center&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. After the intersection with MA Rte. 101 in Ashburnham, continue west on Rte. 119 1.4 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. The parking lot is on the right. There is a chain-link fence with an opening in it. Just before the entrance, there is a sign that says "Mid State Trail" (The Wapack and the Mid State run together for a ways in that area.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From NH Route 119:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. East on Rte. 119 from Rindge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. After crossing the MA/NH border, continue east on Rte. 119 1.7 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. The parking lot is on the left. There is a chain-link fence with an opening in it. Just before the entrance, there is a sign that says "Mid State Trail" (The Wapack and the Mid State run together for a ways in that area.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;he Class 1 Wapack Trail is the preferred way up to the summit of Mt. Watatic. The trail is moderate with some steeper sections but nothing on the trail comes close to approaching Class 2. Via the most direct route this summit is only 1.1 miles one way and 1000 feet of elevation gain. A 4 mile loop hike can be made of this mountain as well adding more scenery and views. Toward the top the trail eases and the panorama awaits. To the north, the rest of the Wapack Range rises with the trail highpoint of North Pack Monadnock and Pack Monadnock rises in the background. To the easy most of Massachusetts hilly countryside rises. On clear day the skyscrapers of Boston can be seen. To the south lies Mt. Watchusett and it's ski run. Due to the close proximity to Boston this mountain always has a crowd. Best time for solitude is on a winter weekday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most popular hikes in Massachusetts, Mt. Watatic stands as the southernmost summit on the 22 mile Wapack Trail and lies just east of the end of the Midstate Trail. Formerly home to a ski area this mountain is very rewarding in terms of views. The ski resort has been open from time to time in the past until 1988 when all chances for opening the ski resort finally ended.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340042312000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339714492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT WATATIC..........</name><id>69221162</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339876800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/69221162/</event_url></item>