<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Boylston Street at 180 Lamartine Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.317017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Southwest Corridor Park</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>317277</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104340</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>**New Date**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www2.milwaukee.k12.wi.us/roosevelt/Kidwebs/Nic/Images/basketball.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So it's set. Sunday's Basketball for Justice event is going down at the Stonybrook court right off Lamartine Street in JP. (Exit Stoneybrook station on the Orange line, walk directly across the street to the park, the courts are right in front of you.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, we'll be prepared for spontaneous 4-square, badminton, and frisbee games (or whatever other outdoors game you bring) so no worries if you're not down with the dribble.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather is looking good so stop by for some sensational outdoor time this Sunday afternoon! Then join us afterwards for a drink at Doyle's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while perfecting your hook shot, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. If you're interested in building cross-issue coalitions courtside...even better!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?  Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and learn about our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/pages/Annual_Membership_Fee_details/"&gt;Suggested Annual Membership Fee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184447190000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179173440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Basketball for Justice near Stonybrook T stop</name><id>5777223</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183917600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5777223/</event_url></item>