<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>343 Washington Terrace</address_2><address_1>Mansfield Freeman Center</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 805-2078</phone><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship</name><city>Middletown</city><id>437051</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buddhism 101 Course: Spring – Autumn 2013&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 "This is not just a course but a transformational experience." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - enrollment on an ongoing and limited basis - &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Registration ends April 10, 2013&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Are you looking to learn more about the Buddha’s teachings? Let 2013 be your opportunity. This is the tenth year of our most popular and comprehensive course on the Buddha’s teachings. It surveys the Buddhist life, his disciples and teachings, and how they may be applied to daily living in 21st century America. This non-sectarian course covers the vastness of the Buddhist religion through Theravada and Mahayana traditions. Begins April 23, 2013. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 It will meet for 6 sessions in 6 months. Open to Buddhists and Non-buddhists. No pre-requisites. This course is oriented to beginner’s who are looking for a concrete, practical and sequential study of Buddhism. For details and online registration visit our web site below. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Furthermore, Buddhism 101 is a getaway course to further your spiritual journey via our intermediate and advanced courses like Buddhism 201, 301 and 401 courses. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 To keep the courses engaging, there is limited enrollment in all of our courses. We highly suggest that if you are interested in registering that you do so, sooner than later. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Visit our New England Institute of Buddhist Studies web site below for more details and online registration. Donations can be made via web site or made on an installment basis (check with us at amida@bffct.net ) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://dharmaquest.bffct.net/"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;http://dharmaquest.bffct.net/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366572815000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361587107000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhism 101 Spring Course (basic) - Discover the Buddha's teachings</name><id>105961762</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366561800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/105961762/</event_url></item>