<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A full moon makes a perfect night for meditation &amp;amp; yoga. Lots of energy and opportunities for abundance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This November evening, the moon will be full within just three days (Dec 2 at 7:30 am). Named the Full Cold Moon, December is usually the month when winter's icy chill begins to fasten its grip. All liquids freeze as the natural world goes into a state of suspended animation. Therefore, the night's meditation will be a guided visualization focusing on breath awareness and intentions for accessing inner reserviors of energy and exploring the depths of the subconscious mind. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*** This evening we will be joined by special guest, Erik Harris, of Chi for Healing. Erik will lead us in some healing Qi Qong, which is a type of meditative stretching &amp;amp; movement performed in conjunction with deep breathing. Also, Erik will be brewing an exquiste batch of Pu'er Tea to sample. Pu'er can be from the green or black tea family and  has a long list of beneficial health properties that are truly amazing.&lt;/b&gt; (see below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the night's yoga practices, the Moon Salutation, will enact the journey of descent--sinking into the depths to discover one's creativity, the process of literal or metaphoric birth. Just as the moon goes through its dark phases and then returns to its full brilliance, so the Moon Salutation drops into the depths of lunging and squatting, returning to triangle, star, and half moon poses with radiant joy and openness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Combined with deep yoga stretches to circulate warmth and energy, an infrared sauna will be available for use to aid in clearing blockages and toxins from the body and internal organ systems. Purifying teas, juices and water will be provided for cleansing and hydration. Massage therapy will also be available for private sessions. &lt;b&gt;Please arrive promptly at 6 pm to sign up for massage or the sauna! First come, first served. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later in the evening, we will have a bonfire with drumming and organic snacks under the Full Cold Moon. Bring your positive energy to share with the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2 donation requested. Use of the sauna is optional for a $10 donation. All donations are to support the operations of the Growing Green Co-op's community center and healing arts space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From NaturalNews.com:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pu-erh Tea has been used in traditional Chinese medicine for generations to inhibit &amp;quot;internal dampness&amp;quot; (a term used in Chinese medicine to describe a build up of internal energy due to the spleen`s inability to transform energy that it receives from the stomach) and to invigorate the activity of the spleen and stomach. Other traditional uses include the removal of toxins from the body, curing dysentery, weight loss, improving eyesight, promoting blood circulation and reviving those who have over indulged in alcohol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More recently, researchers have taken interest in Pu-erh tea for its ability to reduce cholesterol, lower blood pressure, protect connective tissue, and its ability to attack free radicals within the body. In multiple studies done in several countries, pu-erh tea has shown significant success in reducing blood cholesterol. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259709278000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257010109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Cold Moon Meditation, Yoga &amp; Wellness Night</name><id>11756247</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259535600000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/11756247/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/b/b/global_11535515.jpeg</photo_url></item>