<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rt 125</address_2><address_1>1250 Osgood St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.718580</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-531-0500</phone><name>Beijing Restaurant</name><city>North Andover</city><id>288058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112320</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE 1/21/2011:  Here in North Andover/Haverhill the snow has stopped, the sun is shining and the roads are fine.  With that said, this event is still on.  If you feel that you will make the decision not to attend please change your rsvp as soon as possible.  If you were not planning on coming but would like to come, you are more than welcome please rsvp. Hope to see everyone at the Beijing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: black"&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE 1/20/2011:  Snow is a coming and MeetupStormCast245 is on the lookout!!!!   No seriously, as of right now we are keeping this event on the calendar.  Around 2pm tomorrow we will be going out to see the conditions on the local streets and will make a decision whether to cancel or not.  We will email an update no later than 4 pm tomorrow on whether this event will take place or not.  So please, before leaving for the event, please check your email for the event update.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok all you shower singers, come on out to the New Beijing and show us what you got.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The new Beijing has kicked it up a notch and now has weekly Karaoke contests and believe it or not Beijing Idol.....who will be the next idol????????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't sing?  Like to Laugh? Well come on down to join the rest of the crowd that can't sing.  We will watch the Karaoke contests, socialize, have some laughs and a really good time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be going to the New Beijing Restaurant for dinner at 7pm, so check out the calendar and RSVP for that event also.  After dinner we will move into the lounge for some fun at Karaoke.  We are hoping to get a seating area, but the place fills up fast so it maybe standing room only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been to this event in the past, prior to the new ownership and the lounge gets VERY crowded.  Please be prepared if you are the type that does not like crowds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember if your plans change, please update your RSVP and if you are running late, get lost or can't make it, please call the meetup cell phone and let us know.  The meetup cell # is 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are at that time of year again, bad weather will cancel this event.  The organizers will make every attempt to cancel so that you can plan accordingly.  Please check the site before heading out to the venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have not paid your dues in the past year, please be prepared to pay your yearly dues at this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you at the Beijing&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Organizers</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295706629000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292980909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Karaoke @ the New Beijing</name><id>15794796</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295661600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15794796/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/d/global_20408637.jpeg</photo_url></item>