<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1200 Quaker Ln</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02818</zip><lat>41.664478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 885-1621</phone><name>Showcase Cinemas </name><city>Warwick</city><id>714672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.498646</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Center Stage at Showcase Cinemas Warwick&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 14, 2009&lt;br /&gt;8 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's something cool -- they've turned one of the movie theatres at Showcase Warwick into a comedy club. It has cabaret-style seating with dining tables and &lt;i&gt;comfortable&lt;/i&gt; chairs, as well as stadium seating. (Sounds like the seating for &amp;quot;Cabaret&amp;quot; at Brown, although this theatre holds over 200 people and the chairs sound like they're a little more comfortable)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They serve food, too -- Providence Monthly recommends the fried pickles and the Strawberry Pop'n Martini (rimmed with pop rocks). They also have a full menu of sandwiches, pizzas, etc. plus drinks. And apparently, if you want movie popcorn with butter, you can get that too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are two shows on Saturdays -- this Meetup is for the 8 p.m. show. The comedians listed are&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/tonydaro" target="_blank"&gt;Tony Daro&lt;/a&gt; and Mike Stork. Tony Daro has written for SNL, Leno, Letterman, etc. Here are some &lt;a href="http://www.jokes.com/stand-up-search/videos/tag/Tony+Daro" target="_blank"&gt;videos &lt;/a&gt;of him -- they're kind of old, but the Bike Cops one is pretty funny!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About MIKE STORK -- Take the unconventional, the unexpected, and occasionally, the unthinkable. Now make it all accessible, refreshingly original, and downright hilarious, and you begin to have a small glimpse into the stand-up comedy of Mike Stork.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please buy your own ticket in advance -- at the &lt;a href="http://www.nationalamusements.com/theatres/current_theatre.asp?theatre=3455" target="_blank"&gt;theatre&lt;/a&gt;, by telephone at 1-800-315-4000 (be prepared for an exercise in frustration), or online at www.nationalamusements.com. Admission is $10 and seating is on a first come, first-seated basis. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;In order to get good seats, let's meet by 7:15 p.m. inside the lobby, near the Box Office closest to the back parking lot. Look for a small Meetup sign. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; If you're late, you may have to look for us inside the theatre. The show runs for 90 minutes, and it's over 18 only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please note: This is not the theatre at Warwick Mall, it's the one near E. Greenwich, across from Panera Bread.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the show, for whoever is up for it, we can head down the road to E. Greenwich and grab a drink at the &lt;a href="http://www.pinellimarrarestaurants.com/grille_on_main.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Grille on Main&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet near the Box Office closest to the back parking lot -- look for Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238286178000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235930353000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Comedy -- Showcase Cinemas Warwick</name><id>9851901</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237072500000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/9851901/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/3/global_6290483.jpeg</photo_url></item>