<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>159 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318267</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-586-5427</phone><name>Lhasa Cafe</name><city>Northampton</city><id>1303814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631510</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet new friends and eat great Tibetan traditional foods at the Lhasa Cafe, Downtown Northampton, right across from Thornes Market.  There are a few tables right out front on the sidewalk if the weather is good, or they have nice indoor dining with some fantastic large-format photos from Tibet on the walls.  Their food is great - delicious - and feature both vegan/vegetarian choices as well as meat dishes.  For the adventurous, there's even yak meat!  For traditionalists, there's beef, chicken and lamb.  Their dumplings are awesome.  Something for everyone.  Parking at the parking Garage behind Thornes is easy and cheap (first hour is free, $0.50 per hour thereafter, and you never have to drive around &amp;amp; around looking for a space.  There is a walking corridor that goes from parking level 3 directly into Thornes Market, so all you have to do is walk through the market, out the front doors, cross the street and you're at Lhasa Cafe.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone so inclined can join those of us who are going over to Herrells for ice cream after dinner, or to Starbucks for an expresso/latte/chai or whatever tickles your fancy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Separate checks for everyone...  unless anyone wants to pick up someone else's tab! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch for me (Dave) with my signature straw Panama hat :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Xanatos</member_name><member_id>3183746</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285541637000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Western Mass Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>western-mass-singles</urlname><id>414498</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>The Western Mass Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277143480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lhasa Cafe Good Food Meetup</name><id>13865461</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280008800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/western-mass-singles/events/13865461/</event_url></item>