<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>352 Hooksett Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>43.011730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Livingston Park</name><city>Manchester</city><id>671425</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.453660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 On May 19th, Manchester will once again go to the dogs! Snag your tennis shoes and your four-legged friend for the 3rd annual Mutt Strut! Make plans to enjoy the day with your pup and other animal lovers walking around Livingston Park to benefit the Friends of the Manchester Animal Shelter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab all your friends (two legged and four) to strut your stuff with a fun-filled morning including: &lt;br /&gt;

 - Scenic walk around Livingston Park &lt;br /&gt;

 - Pet Fair featuring Vendors, Live Entertainment &amp;amp; Goodies Galore &lt;br /&gt;

 - Canine Demonstrations &lt;br /&gt;

 - Raffles &amp;amp; More! &lt;br /&gt;

 When: Sunday, May 19, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 Check-In/Registration opens at 10 AM, Start Strutting at 11 AM!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: Livingston Park, Manchester, NH &lt;br /&gt;

 (Daniel Webster Highway North, across from Puritan Backroom – Plenty of free parking!) &lt;br /&gt;

 REGISTRATION INFORMATION: &lt;br /&gt;

 (Online Registration opens April 15th!) &lt;br /&gt;

 All registered strutters receive FMAS goodies and dog bandana on the day of the event, plus earn prizes as you raise money for FMAS’ lifesaving efforts: &lt;br /&gt;

 - Raise $50 for an Official Mutt Strut ’13 T-Shirt &lt;br /&gt;

 - Raise $100 (and for every $100 after), receive one entry into our exclusive Mutt Strut Fundraiser Prizes* &lt;br /&gt;

 - Top Fundraising “Pup Pal” (Individual Strutter): First choice of exclusive Mutt Strut Fundraiser Prize! &lt;br /&gt;

 - Top Fundraising “Dog Pack” (Team): Exclusive Group Prize to be announced! &lt;br /&gt;

 *Mutt Strut Fundraiser Prizes soon to be announced! &lt;br /&gt;

 For more information, to register, or for sponsorship opportunities, visit www.ManchesterAnimalShelter.org, e-mail us at muttstrut@manchesteranimalshelter.org, or call us at (603) 623-3544. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to register/learn more: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.manchesteranimalshelter.org/blog/mutt-strut/"&gt;http://www.manchesteranimalshelter.org/blog/mutt-strut/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course if you want to you can always wait to register the day of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As this is a Manchester Animal Shelter fundraising event it would be an on leash activity for the dogs by their rules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369045264000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367341509000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MUTT STRUT for the manchester animal shelter!</name><id>116975292</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368972000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/116975292/</event_url></item>