<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Allison St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.191335</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>223-0335</phone><name>Liberty Books</name><city>Concord</city><id>682917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.538397</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FREE video night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to forward this announcement around to friends who are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join our &lt;b&gt;Facebook group: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/home.php?#/group.php?gid=159949076301" target="_blank"&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;follow us on &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mv911truth" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter: mv911truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This month in Concord:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://video.google.com/videoplay?docid=5832390545689805144#" target="_blank"&gt;The Revolution Will Not Be Televised&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sometimes, a good documentary is all about being in the right place at the right time. It does not get much better for Kim Bartley and Donnacha O'Briain, who, in late 2001 began filming a documentary about Hugo Chavez, the controversial President of Venezuela. As they worked on their documentary, events in Venezuela reached a fever pitch and the duo was able to capture on film a coup from the perspective of the Chavez government. The footage is remarkable, especially given that actual events were so clouded by propaganda on both sides. What is clear is that this was a coup orchestrated with the crucial help of the media. Without their support, it would not have been successful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HUGO CHAVEZ elected President of Venezuela in 1998 is a colorful, unpredictable folk hero, beloved by his nation's working class and a tough-as-nails, quixotic opponent to the power structure that would see him deposed. Two independent filmmakers were inside the presidential palace on April 11, 2002, when he was forcibly removed from office. They were also present 48 hours later when, remarkably, he returned to power amid cheering aides. Their film records what was probably history's shortest-lived coup d'état. It's a unique document about political muscle and an extraordinary portrait of the man The Wall Street Journal credits with making Venezuela &amp;quot;Washington‚s biggest Latin American headache after the old standby, Cuba.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This documentary shows the role of the police as guardians of the people and the importance of us educating our protectors. There has been concern stated that &amp;quot;they'll just do what their paymasters tell them to&amp;quot;, so we offer this video for your consideration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awards 'The Revolution Will Not Be Televised'&lt;br /&gt;has won to date include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jury Award, Best Documentary,&lt;br /&gt;Malaga Int'l Film Festival (Spain)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Needle Award,&lt;br /&gt;Seattle Film Festival (USA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Le Prix George du Beau Regard International, Best Documentary,&lt;br /&gt;FID Marseilles Film Festival (France)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best Feature Documentary,&lt;br /&gt;Galway Film Fleadh, (Ireland)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The David Wolper Documentary Film Grand Prize, for Best Documentary, 2003 Wine &amp;amp; Country Film Festival (USA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1st Prize, Best Documentary,&lt;br /&gt;3 Continents Film Festival, (South Africa)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Silver Hugo Award&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your blank DVDs&lt;/b&gt; to the meeting and be sure to get a copy of each video we screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We may have time for other short videos, so bring your favorites to view and suggest to others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have screenings every Tuesday&lt;/b&gt; somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: 1st Tuesday-Nashua; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; &lt;b&gt;3rd Tuesday-Concord&lt;/b&gt;; the 4th Tuesday is open for a more northern meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at 6:30&lt;/b&gt; if you can, in order to help set up the healthy snacks and beverages (that you bring to share with others - a box of tea for Jim's inventory would be appreciated) and enjoy the pre-meeting networking. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and then on to the video showing right after that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bring your friends!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - Forward this invitation to everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Write us&lt;/b&gt; at MerrimackValley911Truth@gmail.com with suggestions for next month.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be preparing snacks and tea in the kitchenette</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282088417000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281932553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concord - The Revolution Will Not Be Televised</name><id>rfzqnynlbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282084200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/14434669/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/d/global_17229101.jpeg</photo_url></item>