<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The weather looks great this weekend and I have only one peak left to complete the 48.  As Mount Hale is not a very long hike in it self, I am planning to make the hike more interesting, scenic and fun by taking trails less traveled.  I am looking for other fast paced hikers interested in joining me to celebrate this exciting milestone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HIGHLIGHTS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Mount Hale, Ethan Pond, Shoal Pond, Thoreau Falls &amp;amp; Zealand Falls&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOTAL MILEAGE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12.3 excluding detours to ponds and falls, about 9 hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PACE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;moderate plus&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRAILS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ethan Pond Trail, Twinway, Lend A Hand Trail &amp;amp; Hale Brook Trail&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To reach &lt;b&gt;Mount Hale&lt;/b&gt; we will take the Ethan Pond Trail.  The trail crosses the tracks and ascends on an old logging road climbing steadily then becoming more gradual.  At 1.6 miles the Ethan Pond Trail turns lefts and climbs steadily to the height of land at 2.1 miles, passing from Crawford Notch State Park into the WMNF.  It enters and follows an old logging road down to the point close to the southeast corner of Ethan Pond, which however is not visible from the trail.  Here at 2.6 miles from the Wiley House Station, we will take a short side trail on the right which leads past the inlet of &lt;b&gt;Ethan Pond&lt;/b&gt;, where there is a view of the Twin Range over the pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ethan Pond Trail now descends gradually, skirting to the right (north) of a boggy area.  At 4.4 miles it bears right, merging into a spur of the old Zealand Railroad and following it to the main line at 4.6 miles where the Shoal Pond Trail enters from the left.  Here we will make  a short detour to check out scenic &lt;b&gt;Shoal Pond&lt;/b&gt; (I estimate about 15 minutes each way to reach the pond).  Returning to the Ethan Pond Trail and traveling a short distance, at 4.9 miles we will cross the North Fork on a wooden bridge.  At 5.1 miles the Thoreau Falls Trail diverges left to continue down to the North Fork.  Here we will stop to admire &lt;b&gt;Thoreau Falls&lt;/b&gt;.  Returning to the Ethan Pond Trail we will follow an old railroad grade on a gradual curve into the Zealand Notch, with its steep, fire-scarred walls.  As the trail crosses the talus slopes of White Wall Mountain it comes into the open with fine views.  The trail soon reenters the woods and continues on the remains of the old railroad grade to the junction of with the Zealand Trail and The Twinway.  We will turn sharp left onto the Twinway for 0.2 miles to the Zealand Falls Hut and &lt;b&gt;Zealand Falls&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leaving the hut we will take the Lend a Hand Trail to the summit of Mount Hale.  The trail climbs steadily crossing a brook three times.  At about 0.5 miles the grades becomes easy in a long section with numerous log bridges where small brooks flow in and out of the trail.  At 1.5 miles the trail enters a scrubby, ledgy area and ascends moderately.  In a rocky area at 1.9 miles at a ledge 15 yards off the trail offers a good outlook toward Carrigain Notch.  At 2.4 miles the trails climb another rocky pitch and continues in dense conifers to the summit clearing and the location of my big celebration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The summit of &lt;b&gt;Mount Hale&lt;/b&gt; is bare with limited views over trees which have been slowly reclaiming the summit in the more than 30 years since the fire tower was removed. &lt;u&gt; CAUTION:  Hiking with a pace maker?&lt;/u&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Many of the rocks around the former tower site are reputed to be strongly magnetic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the celebration complete will we take Hale Brook Trail to Zealand Road to cars we have spotted earlier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ETHAN POND TRAIL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DISTANCES from the Willy House Station, Elevation 1,440 feet)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to Zealand Falls Huts (2,630 feet) via Twinway - 7.4 miles, 1700 feet, 4 hr. 35 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LEND A HAND TRAIL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DISTANCES from the Twinway, Elevation 2,730 feet)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to Mount Hale Summit (4,052 feet) - 2.7 miles, 1,300 feet, 2 hrs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HALE BROOK TRAIL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DISTANCES from Mount Hale, Elevation 4,052 feet)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to Zealand Road (1,770 feet) - 2.2 miles, 2 hrs. &amp;amp; 15 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOTAL MILEAGE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12.3 excluding detours to ponds and falls, about 9 hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the NEHAAG disclaimer.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>directions will be sent by email</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252329656000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251840106000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scott's Last 48 Peak - Hiking Celebration</name><id>11261490</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252151100000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11261490/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/global_10506009.jpeg</photo_url></item>