<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Bosworth Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357152</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 422-0004</phone><name>Marliave</name><city>Boston</city><id>868071</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060208</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;U35 is a bi-monthly reading series for poets under the age of thirty five, conceived as a space for greater community as well as diversity of voice and vision. On Tuesday, January 29, we are pleased to welcome Randolph Pfaff, Sam Cha, and April Ranger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Randolph Pfaff lives in Boston, where he plays with words and pictures. He edits for a magazine called apt and a small press called Aforementioned. His work has appeared or is forthcoming in PANK, Word Riot, The Destroyer, Open Letters Monthly, and Heavy Feather Review, among others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April Ranger is a poet and playwright. Her poems have been published or are forthcoming in Muzzle Magazine, Off the Coast, and Apt. She is a three-time member of Boston Cantab's National Poetry Slam Team. April recently completed a full-length play titled The Mouth of Jordan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam Cha is an MFA candidate at UMass Boston. His poems, translations, and essays can be found in apt, ASIA, Amethyst Arsenic, Anderbo, Banipal, decomP, Opium Online, Printer's Devil Review, and Radius, among other places. He was a finalist for the 2007 Anderbo poetry prize and the 2012 Memorious Art Song Contest, and he was awarded the Academy of American Poets Prize at UMass Boston in 2011 and 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(from &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/385508871541436/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/events/385508871541436/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359515458000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357686776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>U35 Reading with Randolph Pfaff, April Ranger, and Sam Cha</name><id>98627692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359504000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/98627692/</event_url></item>