<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Update, changed to 8AM at first pickup location..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey folks! I know it's last minute, but I feel like some Rt 90 slab tomorrow, part of it has to do with a worn front tire and shocks that are less forgiving than they used to be. Meet at the following Mass Pike locations starting at 8am and on 30 min intervals as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:00 AM   Framingham Plaza (Westbound) between exits 13 and 12.&lt;br /&gt;8:30 AM   Westborough Plaza (Westbound) between exits 11A and 11.&lt;br /&gt;9:00 AM   Charlton Plaza (Eastbound and Westbound) between exits 9 and 10 East and Exits 10 and 9 West.&lt;br /&gt;9:30 AM   Ludlow Plaza (Eastbound and Westbound) between exits 7 and 8 East and 8 and 7 West.&lt;br /&gt;10:00 AM   Blandford Plaza (Eastbound and Westbound) between exits 2 and 3 East and 3 and 2 West.&lt;br /&gt;10:30 AM   Lee Plaza (Eastbound and Westbound) between exits 1 and 2 East and 2 and 1 West.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP make a note of the time and plaza so we know to expect or not. The pickup schedule is so if you want to leave earlier or ride a lot faster you can and know where and when to pick up the pack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there's time, we can get some coffee and talk shop otherwise we'll move on to the next plaza, or skip it all together if there's no reason to stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Destination? What! Well, I thought about going to Albany and see if there is any crazy shit from the rain and flooding there. Kinda like a ride we did when that ice storm did so much in middle mass, found some new roads on that adventure too! Though the Berkshires are lovely this time of year.. we could go up Rt 8 0r 22 and take a spin up the backside of Greaylock and then come home on Rt 2?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google Maps says 152 Miles from Framingham to Albany, about 3 hours - I'd like to get there by noon and then take the next 6 hours to get back home with a mixture of slab and new road discovery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your camera as will I - After slabbing it to the state line, I will def be ready for a little photo time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you in the AM, dress in layers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286192414000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286059258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Westward pickup ride</name><id>14977793</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286107200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/14977793/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/c/global_15367708.jpeg</photo_url></item>