<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Beginner/moderate, 4+ miles. Goodnough Dike loop road, then main park road, perhaps to Hank's Meadow. (Depends on level/pace of the group; will be a group decision.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Goodnough Dike, Quabbin Reservoir&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/5/4/event_73249492.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park is at the southern end of the Reservoir, with paved roads, long dams, and beautiful viewing spots. Park in the dirt lot on the right, before the Goodnough Dike loop (barely a mile into the park via the East Entrance).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll walk the loop over the dam. Then we'll go west on the main park road, distance dependent on the group (group decision). This probably means we'll go to Hank's Meadow or Enfield Overlook. There are outhouses with sanitizer where we park and at both viewing spots. Bring a drink and a snack/lunch. Cameras highly recommended! The views in Quabbin Park are &lt;strong&gt;stunning&lt;/strong&gt;, and sometimes you see bald eagles, moose, or deer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry-in, carry-out. (Take your trash with you when you go.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove items from the Reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No special clothes or equipment needed...paved roads. Just dress for the weather.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please be aware I leave my house by 10am. If you have questions, it's best to comment right here, in case I don't check my email.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware there are two long, steep hills. Look for a dirt pull-off with a barrier after the second hill. The East Entrance is around a curve, a short distance after the pulloff. (If you pass a marsh on both sides of Route 9, you've gone too far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Using the East Entrance, continue straight almost a mile. On the right is a small brown "Goodnough Dike" sign. The dirt parking lot is immediately before this, on the right.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI, if you missed the East Entrance just use the middle one. Eventually, you'll come to a rotary; go straight, not uphill to the right. Goodnough Dike will be on the left, more than a mile after the rotary, maybe closer to two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 31 or I-290 south to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above. Or, if it's closer, take 122 north (it goes diagonally west), then Route 37A south to Route 9. See the directions from Worcester...pick it up from downtown Ware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Or if Route 2 is convenient:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 2 to exit 19, onto Route 202 South. After 20 minutes on 202, turn left to go east on Route 9. The East Entrance is the 3rd entrance on your left; it takes 5 minutes to pass all 3 entrances. Before you see the East Entrance, you will pass a marsh on both sides of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus. Go in the East Entrance, and almost a mile, there is a small dirt parking lot on the right, immediately before Goodnough Dike loop road (sm brown sign).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331371221000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330924658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goodnough Dike @ Quabbin Reservoir</name><id>55009682</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331308800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/55009682/</event_url></item>