<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Yard</address_2><address_1>Harvard College</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374528</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John Harvard Statue</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>710042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117194</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Straight from the polls, going with our current &amp;quot;mystery based on times past&amp;quot; theme, our next read is: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Historian by Elisabeth Kostova&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Excerpts copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.bookbrowse.com/reviews/index.cfm?book_number=1589" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bookbrowse...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Late one night, exploring her father's library, a young woman finds an ancient book and a cache of yellowing letters. The letters are all addressed to &amp;quot;My dear and unfortunate successor,&amp;quot; and they plunge her into a world she never dreamed of—a labyrinth where the secrets of her father's past and her mother's mysterious fate connect to an inconceivable evil hidden in the depths of history&lt;br /&gt;Parsing obscure signs and hidden texts, reading codes worked into the fabric of medieval monastic traditions—and evading the unknown adversaries who will go to any lengths to conceal and protect Vlad [the Impaler]'s ancient powers—one woman comes ever closer to the secret of her own past and a confrontation with the very definition of evil. Elizabeth Kostova's debut novel is an adventure of monumental proportions, a relentless tale that blends fact and fantasy, history and the present, with an assurance that is almost unbearably suspenseful—and utterly unforgettable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're gonna bank on good weather and meet in front of the John Harvard statue like a mob of tourists (or, on the stairs to the right if the tourists are crazy).  I'll be carrying my comforter for sitting.  If it's clearly pouring all day, plan on heading back to our staple, CCC in Central Square.  If it looks ominous, head to the yard, worst case scenario, we'll hike over to Au Bon Pain in Harvard Sqare and brave the noise of the fans:-)  I'll try and remember to toss my cell number out to provide clarity to the chaos day of:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep hitting those polls!!  The next few choices are getting a little ambiguous! :-)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be lugging around a peach/white comforter for sitting.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245713660000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241104491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers:The Historian by Elisabeth Kostova</name><id>10303053</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243897200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/10303053/</event_url></item>