<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This event is open to all members of the group.  I am hosting an Arbonne party at my house.  Arbonne is a great way to get some gifts bought for those people on your list that you never know what to get.  Arbonne is a swiss skin care line (www.arbonne.com)  that rocks.  I will be selling gift bags stating at $15 and all products will be available for individual purchase.  There are products for men, women, babies, and teens.  Scents include Mandarin Cashmere, luxurious Almond, Ginger Citrus and many more.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who have attend previous open houses you know it is just a casual way to get together at someone's home and sample some fun stuff.  There is no pressure to buy but instead a fun way to do some shopping and have some food and drink while meeting new people.  Trust me it is very low-key and we always have a blast.  I would love to have all of you attend so we can have a great open house event.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who can't make Friday night please see the website as I have scheduled another open house on 10/29/06.  I would love to finally meet you all.  Also anyone who brings a friend will be entered into a drawing for a free prize.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You MUST RSVP on this site and you must send me a personal email at kristie.goodgion@genzyme.com if you will be attending.  Once again this is only to ensure attendance so that I can plan food and drinks.  I really hope to see you all there and get in the Holiday spirit early this year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI.....these events usually last about 2 hours but I am very happy to have people stay and hang out after....as some of you already know!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kristie &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540596000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialnetworking</urlname><id>251346</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1159982990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Holiday Open House</name><id>5174166</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1161990000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialnetworking/events/5174166/</event_url></item>