<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>357 Great Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.484830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bedford American Legion Hall</name><city>Bedford</city><id>284903</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.260270</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thank you to those who have registered for our first Seven Minute Dating event.  Enjoy your dates!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Countless couples have met at instant dating events.  Plan to join us for this instant dating event.   You'll meet lots of singles.  And then you get to choose whom you would like to see again. Each date is one-on-one.  You'll talk for seven minutes, finding out about each other and getting a sense of how you feel.  After seven minutes it is time for another date -- every seven minutes, another date. During the event, you will date approximately ten to twelve people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRIVACY.  Our unique system allows you complete privacy.   You are known only by your first name.  Only the people you select will be given your contact information.   You control the contact information you give out.  You may give out your e-mail address and/or your phone number. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     RESULTS.  Back at the office, we tabulate the results.  Where there is consensus that two people would both like to pursue their acquaintance, the club will facilitate the exchange of phone numbers and/or e-mails.  Typically, we have a 60% to 70% matching rate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To make 7-Minute Dating work, people must register in advance. We ensure a gender balance for each age range, (see registration form for the age ranges). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:00 to 6:30 PM, sign-in, get your nametag, etc.&lt;br /&gt;          6:30 PM to 8:00 PM, Instant Dating&lt;br /&gt;          8:00 PM to 12:00 AM, Singles Dance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost:  $35 includes Dating and Dance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deadline to Register:  December 15, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow the link for more information and registration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.funfunfun.org/events/200912197minutedating.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seven Minute Dating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>8198815</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261436679000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Single Parents</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pwp817</urlname><id>1298426</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Parents Without Partners- Single Parents</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260037917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Registration is closed-SEVEN MINUTE DATING prior to the SINGLES DANCE PARTY!!!!</name><id>12024245</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261263600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pwp817/events/12024245/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/global_5808065.jpeg</photo_url></item>