<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1741 S Willow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.953915</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-668-5557</phone><name>Barnes and Noble</name><city>Manchester</city><id>759357</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The topic for discussion for June, July and August will be the Dhammapada, a classic of Buddhist and Indian literature. The Dhammapada is one of the central teachings of Theravada Buddhism, contained in the Pali Canon, within the section called the Sutta Pitaka. The Dhammapada is a collection of 423 short verses attributed to the Buddha, divided into 26 chapters. For June we will discuss chapters 1-13, and in July we will discuss 14-26. As the Dhammapada is such a rich subject, the August discussion will touch upon any topics that were of particular interest in the previous two discussions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several translations of the Dhammapada available. This one is recommended: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Dhammapada: A Translation” (includes an explanatory introduction), by Thanissaro Bhikku, Dhamma Dana Publications, Barre Center for Buddhist Studies, available for free distribution in book form and can be downloaded (free) in pdf form at &lt;a href="http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/dhp/dhp.intro.than.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/dhp/dhp.intro.than.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.accesstoin...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are three other translations in print, with explanatory material included:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “The Dhammapada” translated by Balagonda Ananda Maitreya, foreword by Thich Nhat Hahn, 1995 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “The Dhammapada – A Classic of Indian Spirituality” introduced and translated by Eknath Easwaran, 1985 &amp;amp; 2007, Nilgiri Press&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The Dhammapada – A New Translation of the Buddhist Classic with Annotations” by Gil Fronsdal, foreword by Jack Kornfield, 2005, Shambhala Publications&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278406401000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263227018000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dhammapada - Chapters 1-13</name><id>12286826</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276556400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/12286826/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/5/global_1946069.jpeg</photo_url></item>