<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Starr King Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03584</zip><lat>44.418267</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Starr King Trailhead</name><city>Jefferson</city><id>1247432</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.468010</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This trip will hit one of the official 4,000 foot peaks in NH - Cabot (#46 @ 4,006&amp;rsquo;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;lt;a href=" &lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php%22%3E"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click this link for the current weather forecast&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;John (LAG) Lagasse: Cell (978) 973-5022&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;I have upgraded this to an INTERMEDIATE hike as snow has fallen in the mountains.&amp;nbsp; During the hike the temperatures at the base are supposed to be 30 to 50 degrees which means much colder at the top.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;MICRO-SPIKES are now MANDATORY on this hike as the potential for icy conditions has increased dramatically.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Please dress in layers and NO COTTON. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winter should be closing in so prepare for the cold!!&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;If you are not used to hiking uphill then this will test you as all 4K's do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;No Headlamp and Microspikes, No Go!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; I will check. We should not need the Headlamps&amp;nbsp; on this trip but we have less daylight.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will leave the trailhead at &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NO LATER than 9:00AM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; According to Google Maps this location is about&amp;nbsp;165 miles from Boston - it should take about&amp;nbsp;2 hours&amp;nbsp;54 minutes to drive there-Taking Rte 95.&amp;nbsp;(Starr King Rd, Jefferson, NH 03584)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please call, text (978) 973-5022, or email me (mrplumislander@comcast.net) the morning of the hike to inform me if you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;NOT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;are coming. Do it early so I receive it before I lose cell signal. In this way if everyone shows up and is ready before 9:00am we can start earlier. Thanks.&amp;nbsp; Should be a fun hike!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;lt;a href="&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/"&gt;http://maps.google.com/&lt;/a&gt;"&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click this link for driving directions that are close to the Trailhead location&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will follow &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Starr King Trail&lt;/span&gt; and return the same route. This moderate pace hike will cover about&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;7.2 miles and climb about 2,650 feet&lt;/span&gt; &amp;ndash; it is considered &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;INTERMEDIATE&lt;/span&gt; because of the WEATHER CONDITIONS, pace, distance, and elevation gain. It should take an average hiker about&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;4 hours&amp;nbsp;55 minutes&lt;/span&gt; to complete this trip we'll be taking our time so count on &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;6 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I keep my limit to 10 hikers so we do not get strung out.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;If you have done this before hike please give the hikers who need it for their 48 a chance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Assistant Organizers do not count on total.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you want to bring a friend have them sign up for the group and join the hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you. The goal of this hike is to summit safely, and to do that, everyone in the group needs to be at a similar fitness and experience level. If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire event please contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Winter hiking is more strenuous than hiking in the summer. We will assess travel and weather conditions and make changes to our planned trip as necessary - &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;"Reaching the summit is optional, getting down in mandatory" (Ed Viesturs).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum clothing and equipment required to participate in this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;HEADLAMP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;MICROSPIKES &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sturdy hiking boots.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Synthetic shirt and pants, including at least one insulating layer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Gloves and Mittens&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;High-energy snacks, food for lunch and water.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Trekking poles. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There will be a group first aid kit that contains basic items but you will need to bring any personal medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Cell is 978-973-5022: I'll be driving a Silver Toyota Matrix with "MEETUP RANDOM HIKERS" license plate cover. Be sure to call ASAP if you are going to be late or not coming as cell coverage is spotty up north.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John (LAG) Lagasse</member_name><member_id>2667639</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1320602469000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316997725000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH 48- Mt Waumbek - Slower Paced Hike</name><id>34936092</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320498000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/34936092/</event_url></item>