<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>April 21, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The sun is out and I am sure this makes for a &amp;quot;brighter&amp;quot; day... Hope all is well with you and yours. Here I am truly enjoying the colors, sounds and smells of Spring. The shrine is beautiful and when you have the time... come for a visit...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, our next INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB gathering... mark your calendars is going to be:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: May 23rd at 4:00PM &lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are continuing reading and sharing on THOMAS MERTON'S book: &amp;quot;THE INNER EXPERIENCE - Notes on contemplation&amp;quot;. For our May 23rd gathering we are going to share on Merton's book, chapters 6 and 7 (pages 71-88). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following are some of the phrases we touched upon in our reading of chapters 4 and 5: reflections: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;... this divine life remains hidden and formant within us unless it is more fully developed by a life of ascetism and charity and on a higher level, of contemplation. Contemplation will be denied to a man/woman in proportion as he/she belongs to &amp;quot;the world&amp;quot;. The expression &amp;quot;the world&amp;quot; signified those who love the transient and unimportant things of this world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is therefore a matter of great courage and spiritual energy to turn away from diversion and prepare to meet, face to face, that &lt;u&gt;&lt;i&gt;immediate&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/u&gt; experience of life which is intolerable to the exterior person. This is only possible, when, by a gift of God we are able to see our inner selves not as a vacuum but as an &lt;i&gt;infinite depth&lt;/i&gt;, not as emptiness but as fullness. This change of perspective is impossible as long as we are afraid of our own nothingness, as long we we are afraid of fear, afraid of poverty, afraid of boredom - as long as we run away from ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The life of contemplation in action and purity of heart is, then, a life of great simplicity  and inner liberty. One is not seeking anything special or demanding any particular satisfaction. one is content with what is. One does what is to be done, and the more concrete it is, the better. One is not worried about the results of what is one. One is content to have good motives and not too anxious about making mistakes. In this way one can swim with the living stream of life and remain at every moment in contact with God, in the hiddenness and ordinariness of the present moment with its obvious task.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At such times, walking down a street, sweeping a floor, washing dishes, hoeing beans, reading a book, talking a stroll in the woods - all can be enriched with the contemplation and with the obscure sense of the presence of God. This contemplation is all the more pure in that one does not &amp;quot;look&amp;quot; to see if it is there. Such &amp;quot;walking with God&amp;quot; is one of the simplest and more secure ways of living a life of prayer, and one of the safest. It never attracts anybody's attention, least of all the attention of him/her who lives it. And he/she soon learns not to want to see anything special in him/herself. This is the price of his/her liberty.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We always have some great sharing and exchanges.... So I hope that all of you will be able to make our next meeting. See you, then, on May 23rd, 4:00pm at the Peace Abbey in Sherborn - MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings on you and yours. Enjoy the sun and walk with the Divine.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PEACE &lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx &lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries &lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144 &lt;br /&gt;pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274648764000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271874975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UP COMING INTER FAITH BOOK CLUB MEETING!</name><id>13249917</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274644800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/13249917/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/a/global_4353546.jpeg</photo_url></item>