<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>156 King St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02025</zip><lat>42.241051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Constantine's Tavern</name><city>Cohasset</city><id>2935091</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.828773</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered just how quickly a dining event can be put together?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No? Well, don't worry, you're not alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You also won't be alone if you head on over to Constantine's Tavern in Cohasset this Friday evening - Because SSDOMG will be there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, a conversation that started out focusing on the end of the month somehow veered toward the end of the week instead and wound up, as whodunit lovers like to say, establishing both motive and opportunity. At least half of the Org Team members are available this Friday...and Constantine's is on our "hit list".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason for that is that Constantine's is one of the few local restaurants featuring some Greek dishes (along with American and Italian offerings). We can't exactly say that the Greek dishes dominate the menu, but a quick scan online reveals entrees like chicken souvlaki and Greek style braised lamb shank which, combined with the Italian dishes, do bring a touch of the Mediterranean to the South Shore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope that those of you with some flexibility in your schedules will join us this Friday evening in Cohasset. We're providing you with the opportunity, and we hope our motive is one you all share... Because we'd rather meet and mingle than sit solo with our souvlaki.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Constantine's Tavern&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;156 King St. (Route 3A) Cohasset, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(781) 383-2228&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: 
&lt;a href="http://www.constantinesrestaurant.com/"&gt;Constantine's Tavern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizer: Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests: Yes. Two per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact Mike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Price Range: It's worth having a look at the 
&lt;a href="http://www.constantinesrestaurant.com/dinner-menu-2/dinner-menu"&gt;online menu&lt;/a&gt; to get an idea of what Constantine's offers, but prices at Constantine's are pretty affordable - Only one or two entrees top $17.99, and most are less. There are also pizettas and hot sandwiches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event Fee: Current Annual Members - None, Group Members - $2.00, Guests - $2.00; Now $6.00 to become a 2011 Annual Member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP Deadline: Thursday, August 11th @ 7:00 pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to "No" after the deadline will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: Constantine's Tavern is located directly on Route 3A in Cohasset. It's on your left if you're coming from Hingham, heading south.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313288129000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312830344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sudden Supper at Constantine's</name><id>28711641</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313188200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/28711641/</event_url></item>