<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2500 North River Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>43.037674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Southern New Hampshire University </name><city>Manchester</city><id>1502108</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.454033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thomas E. Woods joins us in New Hampshire to talk about his book, Nullification: How to Resist Tyranny in the 21st Century.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woods is the New York Times bestselling author of nine books, including Meltdown and The Politically Incorrect Guide to American History.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A senior fellow at the Ludwig von Mises Institute, he holds a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in history from Harvard and his master&amp;rsquo;s, M.Phil., and Ph.D. from Columbia University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through historical writings, case studies, and speeches by the Founding Fathers, Woods will give you a logical, moral, and constitutionally sound case for nullification, revealing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How we can roll back Obamacare, cap and trade, and other unconstitutional expansions of federal power through nullification&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why the Founding Fathers believed that nullification was the &amp;ldquo;moderate middle ground,&amp;rdquo; not the road to secession&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why the Tenth Amendment to the Constitution gives the states the power to nullify unconstitutional laws&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why states &amp;ndash; not the Supreme Court &amp;ndash; should arbitrate disputes between the states and the federal government over the constitutionality of the federal government&amp;rsquo;s actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also Speaking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan Itse is a conservative Republican member of the New Hampshire House of Representatives. A native of San Francisco, California, Itse is a professional engineer who resides in Fremont, New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He advocates the revival of state sovereignty in an era of otherwise expanded government through the revival of the 1798 Kentucky and Virginia Resolutions, authored by Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, respectively, to permit the empowerment of individual states within the federal Union.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His slogan? Keep New Hampshire Free!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Boldin is the founder and director of the Tenth Amendment Center, based in Los Angeles, CA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boldin and the Tenth Amendment Center have been leading the charge to re-educate the American public on the meaning and importance of decentralization as a path to liberty &amp;ndash; which is just what the Tenth Amendment affirmed in the U.S. Constitution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His bottom line is the Constitution &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;every issue, every time, no exceptions, no excuses.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More speakers will be added soon!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Southern New Hampshire University, Dining center upper level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brent</member_name><member_id>5128580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300971152000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Learn about the 10th Amendment and nullification from best selling author Tom Woods!</why><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296874576000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nullify Now Tour</name><id>16448940</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300543200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/16448940/</event_url></item>