<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Conference Room,Main Floor</address_2><address_1>305 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.730762</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-686-4080</phone><name>Nevins Memorial Library</name><city>Methuen</city><id>403806</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190002</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Specific Topic:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;It’s Time to STOP What Stops You!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #548dd4"&gt;How to Use or &lt;em&gt;Change&lt;/em&gt; the Often Misunderstood and Overlooked NLP Pattern of Counter Examples&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #548dd4"&gt;Guest Speaker: Marilou Seavey, Master NLP Trainer &amp;amp; Executive Coach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;Both NLP and hypnosis have a strong focus on language patterns and language patterns absolutely reveal and shape our experience. One of the most overlooked and misunderstood language patterns is the Counter Example.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;In others this pattern is frequently considered an objection or negativity. In our own thinking structure it will quite effectively cause doubt, procrastination, and in the extreme can put a full stop to our ‘well formed’ outcomes and goals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;If NLP and Hypnosis are so effective how is it that you don’t have what you want?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;Do you find it easy to get you or stay focused?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;Do you sometimes have doubt about your success?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;Do other people who give you reasons why something can’t happen irk you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;Do you find ‘negative’ people difficult?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;All of the above questions address a little understood pattern called Counter Examples.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000090"&gt;Wanting to do something and the natural motivation to actually do it are two different things. So, what's the difference between those who never reach their goals, year after year, and those who achieve one goal after another? It’s time to check in with how your brain is using Counter Examples. Join us and learn how to use counter examples conversationally and experience a powerful NLP process to reset your brain and widen your bandwidth for success. It’s one of the most interesting discoveries you will have in learning NLP. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;About Marilou:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Marilou Seavey, NLP Master Trainer and Executive Coach has worked in the field of human potential and NLP for over 25 years.  She is exceptionally skilled at helping people gain extraordinary results in all areas of life. Her clients include Fortune 500 executives, business owners, senior political advisers, educators and people from virtually every walk of life. Marilou’s focus is on pragmatic and useful applications for people to enrich the quality of their everyday lives. Her presentations are informative, interactive and highly entertaining.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come Learn and Play!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Monthly Hypnosis/NLP Meetup in Methuen. Learn/Experience/Share techniques and strategies to help yourself or others overcome fears, phobias, negative emotions, illnesses, and many others, as well as to become the person you always wanted to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kevin Martin &lt;a&gt;978-273-5905&lt;/a&gt; kenda_assoc@msn.com www.poseffects.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Garden Room - Bottom Floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marilou Seavey</member_name><member_id>11416757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340917997000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338579136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grtr Boston NLP Meetup - Methuen -It’s Time to STOP What Stops You!</name><id>dmrxkcyqjbcc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340319600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/67312292/</event_url></item>