<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I've been waiting patiently for this film to screen again at a local theater for a few years now and hope you can make it to this presentation of Stanley Kubrick's masterpiece. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;2001: A Space Odyssey&lt;/b&gt; 1968 USA 141 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A mind-bending sci-fi symphony, Stanley Kubrick's landmark 1968 epic pushed the limits of narrative and special effects toward a meditation on technology and humanity.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yet while reviews will try and lend answers and interpretation to &amp;quot;2001&amp;quot;, it is ultimately a very personal film to many. Its triumph lies in its scope of cinematic splendour and the attempt to marry some of man's most beautiful music to the infinite mystery of space. If there's ever a re-release in a cinema near you, take advantage of the big screen to get the most out of this visual masterpiece. BBC Films&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2001 will doubtless retain its mythic resonance -- an optimistic prediction of first contact with other, presumably wiser, life forms -- long after we've stopped scribbling that cluster of numbers in our checkbooks. San Francisco Examiner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A bit difficult to provide a plot synopsis for this one- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stanley Kubrick's dazzling, Academy Award-winning achievement (Special Visual Effects) is an allegorical puzzle on the evolution of man and a compelling drama of man vs. machine. Featuring a stunning meld of music and motion, the film was also Oscar nominated for Best Director and Best Screenplay. Kubrick (who co-wrote the screenplay with Arthur C. Clarke) first visits the prehistoric age-ancestry past, then leaps millennia (via one of the most mind-blowing jump cuts ever) into colonized space, and ultimately whisks astronaut Bowman (Keir Dullea) into uncharted space, perhaps even into immortality. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should make for an  interesting conversation afterward-&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign, alas no monolith, after the film near the front row .</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213396713000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210382154000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2001: A Space Odyssey</name><id>7909404</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213223400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7909404/</event_url></item>