<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; This is our first BIG seminar for our group.  It's going to be different than anything we've done before, so be sure to read the whole description.  I think you're going to love what we've created here :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would you like to be surrounded by warm, caring people who support you in getting what you want in life?  If so, then you're going to love this special seminar we're having in January.  You're going to learn how to build a rich and rewarding social life in 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm strongly believe that life is a whole lot more enjoyable when you've got wonderful people in your social circle.  At this seminar, you're going to learn some of my best tips, techniques, and strategies for attracting high quality friends and romantic partners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a small sample of what you'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to attract the people into your life that are a perfect match for your personality type.  You'll learn who they are, and where you can find them.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My proven method for creating almost-instant plans anytime you find yourself home alone.  You can use this anytime you want to go out and have fun, but don't have any set plans made at the moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have you ever had a friendship that started out really strong, and then suddenly faded away?  You'll learn why this happens, and how you can attract friendships and relationships that last from now on.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &amp;quot;secret question&amp;quot; that everyone's subconscious mind is asking when you first meet them.  Once you know this, you'll be able to put people at ease and make them feel comfortable around you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simple steps you can take right away to transform yourself into the kind of person whose social life continues to expand automatically.  People will start coming to you looking for fun things to do, and you'll always get invited to the best parties when you use these steps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You'll also walk away with a step-by-step action plan you can start using immediately to improve the quality of your social life (and attract someone special to you very quickly).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;And that's only the first half of the meeting.  During the second half, you'll have an opportunity to do an amazing set of exercises that will stimulate your creativity and inspire you with new possibilities for your social life that you never knew existed.  You'll walk away with a step-by-step action plan you can start using immediately to improve the quality of your social life (and attract someone special to you very quickly).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The meeting is limited to 40 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings almost always sell out within a day or two, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Tuesday, January 6th available.  The meeting runs from 7pm to 10pm and is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that evening free, go ahead and RSVP for this meeting right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  These meetings always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which helps pay the cost of running this group, classroom rental, and printed materials.  Please bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems.  My cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk in the bldg and the signs will guide you to the right room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234643619000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230853260000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Skills Meeting - How To Create A Rich and Rewarding Social Life In 2009</name><id>9421157</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231286400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/9421157/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/b/global_4864315.jpeg</photo_url></item>