<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.352823</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 478-3100 </phone><name>Institute of Contemporary Art</name><city>Boston</city><id>731894</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043059</lon></venue><fee><label>Group expenses</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to gallery walk with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns admist new contemporary art exhibitions?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in and folks who want to compare modern and post-modern art?  Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions AND seeing the new ICA?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at the new Institute of Contemporary Art for Contemporary Art for Justice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker.  Just show up and take in the art.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP yes, maybe or no.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*We will be taking advantage of FREE Target Thursdays (includes entry &amp;amp; tour) but plan to bring some cash for Wolfgang Puck's Water Cafe afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ICA is located at 100 Northern Avenue on Boston's waterfront, adjacent to Anthony's Pier 4 restaurant.  If utilizing public transportation, take the Red Line to South Station. At South Station take the Silver Line to Courthouse stop. Once above ground, walk down Seaport Boulevard toward the World Trade Center (away from the city), turning left onto Northern Avenue at the light. The ICA is on the right side of the street immediately around the corner. Visit www.icaboston.org for more info.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1169332413000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1166283017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Contemporary Art for Justice</name><id>5330593</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1169159400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5330593/</event_url></item>