<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Time: 10:15 AM&lt;/strong&gt; (I should be there by 10, maybe a little earlier) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 4.5 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; dirt roads with steep hills &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Duration:&lt;/strong&gt; 2 hours + lunch + photo-taking (2.5-3 hours?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HIKE DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are old dirt roads with steep hills. There are a few beaches, including two almost kitty-corner to each other (at ends of roads which cross before reaching the shore). Where the roads go into the water, there are &lt;strong&gt;beaches with AWESOME views nearly 10 miles&lt;/strong&gt;, to islands and Quabbin Hill, at the southern end of Quabbin Reservoir!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/8/b/c/event_59927292.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Islands 10 miles south from the beach (by Bob W.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also think the water is so low right now, we can literally walk from one beach to the other. You may want to bring a blanket or pillow to sit on; with the water so low, few or no tree trunks may be washed up for us. There were 2 there in Septermber 2011, but one was already washed away in spring. Hmm..may be able to sit on rocks now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We're now doing an out-and back hike&lt;/strong&gt; via Gate 27. It's downhill 1 mile, then parallel to Quabbin 1.5 miles to those 2 beaches. On the way, there's also another beach. There's one more beach further on, but it's too brushy (read, "too full of ticks"). We'll enjoy a pinic and have opportunity for nature photography here...or just bring your binoculars!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lunch/snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 liter of water/drink&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cameras highly recommended!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Something to sit on (or just sit in the sand).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Deep-woods"-type repellant. Ticks are sparse on the roads, but there's at least one little detour off the road some of us might take to a spit of land well north of the beaches after the long downhill. If you don't wan't to come, you can take a 5+ minute break, and we'll be right back!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The "New Salem General Store" on Route 202 has an outhouse, food, books, maps, and other conveniences. You may want to stop there before the hike. &lt;em&gt;The outhouse which was near the beaches last fall was &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; there this spring.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT REGULATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading; Quabbin Reservoir is a public water supply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No pets (same reason).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trash is "carry in, carry out"...there are no receptacles, so take it home with you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No removing things from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points north:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get to Route 202 via Routes 122 or 2. Take Route 202 south roughly 3+ miles. Look for the "New Salem General Store" on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points south:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 to Belchertown. Turn north onto Route 202. In about 20 minutes you will see the "New Salem General Store" on your left. (Those coming from Amherst may find it faster to take Pelham Road east to 202, then continue north 10 minutes.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you see the "New Salem General Store" on Route 202:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The General Store is on the southbound side. There are 3 streets on both sides of the 202. You want East Main Street on the northbound side, across from the store. It may be hard to choose the correct street, due to the high speed limit and traffic volume. That's okay! Whichever you take, they quickly intersect! Then stay left, but not a sharp left back to 202. &lt;strong&gt;Look for the "E Main St" street sign.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(If you pass an old cemetery and historic buildings, you are on S. Main St. Please turn around and take a right on E Main St.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll pass some houses, and it will become a bumpy dirt road. It's rather long. Near the end, &lt;strong&gt;on the left, is Gate 27&lt;/strong&gt;. The parking is for both Gates 26 &amp;amp; 27.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;It is best &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; to email questions to me, because (a) I'm never caught up, and (b) I may come directly from a sunrise hike. (Well, really, from breakfast!) Regardless, it takes me 1.5 hours to get there from my house.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you have questions, please use the "Comment" feature. I will check the meetup the night before, and another member may have the same question, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus 4-door.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347047063000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346291900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 27: the LONG view!</name><id>80014882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346508900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/80014882/</event_url></item>