<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am sending a message out hoping that everyone will read it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mary is a National Speaker and she has great information that energy workers, those looking for awakening, and those looking for deeper consciousness this is an important meeting to go to . Please take a closer look, really disect what you see and feel how this resonates with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are blessed that she is coming here before the end of the year. Call me if you have questions. I am comfortable that you will all learn many NEW things in this program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to do see you here. Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original notice...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ancient Codes &amp;amp; Emotional Well-Being&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever noticed that everyone has a life script, a set of patterns or themes that are repeated throughout a person’s life? Have you ever wondered if and how that script can be changed? Our patterns are literally electromagnetic pathways. Many of these pathways are formed out of an instinct to survive both early family experiences and certain educational practices. Once in place, these pathways are difficult to alter, even when one is fully aware of their presence. For over 30 years I Ching Systems has been researching and developing alternative pathways to mental health that address long-standing survival behaviors. Our research has led us to develop a simple balancing technology based on the principles of eastern medicine. Our technology is compatible with all forms of effective, natural health-oriented systems. Our research has led us to believe that you can know your own life script and you can do something to change your future. Join Mary Miller, MSW and Health Freedom Advocate, for the evening and discover the mathematical secrets to emotional balance. You may never see the world the same way again! Cost is $25 if paid in advance or $30 at the door. PLEASE CALL WITH QUESTIONS... or to make a payment...&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.thehsccenter.com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354755684000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351717966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reset Your Energy Compass- Changing Your Pathways</name><id>89377922</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354750200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/89377922/</event_url></item>