<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>450 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.342730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.267.8862</phone><name>South End Art Studios</name><city>Boston</city><id>769524</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065032</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/5/c/event_153383132.jpeg" width="230" height="213" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/e/8/event_153380712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SOWA Artists Guild First Friday South End Open Studios 5:30-8:00PM-...Its FREE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Above is a Map that shows Thayer street by the Star!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;You can ask to park for Free at the parking lot next to and behind this building or at the big parking lot next to Gaslight down the street. Just tell them you are here for the First Friday Art Studio event. Make sure you DO NOT pay to park it should be free!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The silver line is your closest T bus stop! &lt;br /&gt;

 Its a 10-15 minute walk from other train T stops!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exact meeting spot we will meet main the Main Lobby of South End Art Studios at 450 Harrison Ave Boston which is on the side of the Building. You will have to walk along a pedestrian way that is called Thayer Street and I was told its no longer a Street but it still has the Thayer Street sign for it to get to the Lobby it has a big elevator there! &lt;br /&gt;

 That is where we will meet at 5:30 PM or so wait here for 5 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Late comers can find us on 1 of the 3 main floors in this same building. I say this because people either find me or other members; its funny how that all works out in the end. :-p&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After most of us meet in the lobby, we will then start at the top 4th floor and work our way down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet back again at lobby at 7PM to re-gather to walk around outside and see more art! Later we MIGHT get Drinks/Dinner at J J Foley's Cafe &lt;span&gt;117 E Berkeley St South End Boston since it only 2 blocks away and INEXPENSIVE!...........&lt;/span&gt; but I have not decided yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The First Friday of each month, Guild member artists and others open their studios at 450 Harrison Ave. Boston, MA 02118. Meet the artists in their element and view their latest works. The SoWa Artists Guild strives to make art and artists accessible to everyone. Come and enjoy the fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is free and parking I was told is available. I was told there will be free wine and snacks offered too.---Web Site: &lt;a href="http://www.sowaartistsguild.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sowaartist" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sowaartist&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 First Fridays are an integral part of the SOWA Artists Guild mission. The aim is to give visitors access to the artists in their element – to offer a different and more personal way to experience art firsthand. By opening their working space to the public, the SOWA Artists Guild hopes to give people an avenue for viewing quality contemporary art that complements yet goes beyond the gallery experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First Fridays appeal to a wide range of art enthusiasts, from seasoned collectors to first time art buyers to those who have never considered art before. Through its participation in these popular events – and by establishing itself as a presence in the SOWA artistic community – the SOWA Artists Guild strives to make its art and its artists accessible to all, working together to inspire people to appreciate art on a whole new level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Artists: The SOWA artist district of Boston has developed into a major artist community with hundreds of artists' studios and dozens of galleries. At the center of SOWA, 450 Harrison Avenue is home to 15 galleries and over 50 artist studios. The members of the SOWA Artist Guild are an eclectic group - from different parts of the world, working in different mediums, each with a unique approach to creative expression. What they share is dedication to their work and a serious pursuit of artistic quality. &lt;br /&gt;

 _________________________________________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;

 OK have fun and Ciao &lt;br /&gt;

 Biagio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Main Lobby South End Art Studios 450 Harrison Ave look for Biagio by Elevator at 5:30PM, if you come late Biagio will be back at Elevator at 7PM to swing by + pick up latecomers. We always start at top floor + work our way down the main building</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365259222000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362436963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free First Friday Open Art Studios - South End Boston</name><id>107611582</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365197400000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/107611582/</event_url></item>