<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>244 Park Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.757393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 987 7888</phone><name>Playhouse on Park </name><city>West Hartford </city><id>1272274</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.725212</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>22.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SAT MAY 29 -This Is Our Youth at the Playhouse on Park West Hartford with The CT Theatre Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An unblinking portrait of young urban life in the 1980s, Kenneth Lonergan's lacerating look at affluent young Manhattanites depicts two days in the lives of three very lost souls in the big city at the dawn of the Regan Era.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kenneth Lonergan brilliantly captures the essential period of time when we think we've got the world figured out, only to realize that we know nothing.  Graduating from our teenage years to adulthood and the pressure of identity is an intense struggle. In Dennis, Warren, and Jessica the struggle is intensified by their dependency on parents. But that dependency is both a blessing and a burden, because it provides a safety net, but the net undercuts the very freedom they enjoy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With an ear attuned to the coarse, ironic language of city kids too cosmopolitan for their own good, Lonergan spins a wildly funny, bittersweet and ultimately quite moving story.  This is Our Youth has extremely strong language, adult situations, and drug use.  It is recommended for ages 17 and up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Matt Pfeiffer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting details will be emailed to all CT Theatre Group ticket holders&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show to extend the party  Details will be emailed to all CT Theatre Group Ticket Holders </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275193288000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274463350000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>This Is Our Youth at the Playhouse on Park West Hartford w/ The CT Theatre Group</name><id>13554049</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275177600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/13554049/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/global_15288327.jpeg</photo_url></item>