<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Asbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.654526</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bradley Palmer State Park</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>329919</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.909149</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's do some exploration at Bradley Palmer. We'll first take the river trail, and then up to the meadow on Blueberry Hill, before heading out on some more adventurous walking. I have been here several times, and am very comfortable with the first leg of our adventure, which will take about an hour. I'd then like to tack on a little more (maybe another hour?) by exploring another path. This is the "exploratory" part of it. Meaning, I don't know the trails very well...it's possible they'll be impassable (many of the trails here are not very well marked, and many are also heavily traveled by horses, bringing a whole new set of challenges to the trails). So we may get turned around, but I'll have maps, and it'd be pretty unlikely that we could stay lost for very long- it's a relatively small park with roads on all sides. Expect loose gravel, potentially some mud or horse "business", some roots to step over, and potentially (depending upon the weather) some slippery spots or snow. I'd recommend boots with good traction, layers for comfort (avoid cotton), water. I set a fairly quick walking pace, so we'll move right along. Friendly, well socialized leashed dogs are welcomed. This walk will be cancelled due to inclement weather or lack of interest. **Please bring $1 to help pay for the group Meetup dues** We'll meet inside the gate off Asbury Lane (on the Topsfield Rd side). Come through the gate and stay right twice until you come to the main lot where the bulletin board and trash cans are.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marilee </member_name><member_id>6596076</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1325629803000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325041639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bradley Palmer Walk- Day After New Year's</name><id>45667902</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325525400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/45667902/</event_url></item>