<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5701 Marinelli Road</address_1><state>MD</state><zip>20852</zip><lat>39.047119</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bethesda North Marriott and Convention Center</name><city>Bethesda</city><id>5608142</id><country>us</country><lon>-77.114494</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Annual Convention of American Atheists will be held March 25th and 26th, 2012 (following the Reason Rally; with pre-convention events on Friday and Saturday) at the Bethesda North Marriott and Convention Center in Bethesda, MD. Last year, nearly 800 people joined in our largest convention ever, and this year, we intend to break that record. JOIN US, following the Reason Rally, as we gather to hear some of the movement's best speakers, and to enjoy live entertainment and good old-fashioned atheist socializing. This year's theme: &amp;quot;Come out! Come out! Wherever you Are!&amp;quot; We will be concentrating this packed-to-the gills convention with help in all aspects of coming out of the atheist closet to your friends, family, and co-workers. The venue is the beautiful Marriott Bethesda North, which is right next to a METRO stop and boasts beautiful updated rooms and a truly FANTASTIC menu. We will have two meals, including our second-annual costume Buffet and our formal sit-down dinner, plus a fund-raiser &amp;quot;Dine with the Pros&amp;quot; event. Purchase Tickets now: &lt;a href="http://atheists.givezooks.com/events/2012-american-atheists-national-convention" target="_blank"&gt;http://atheists.givez...&lt;/a&gt; Reserve your room at the Marriott at 800-266-9432 (code &amp;quot;American Atheists Mar 2012&amp;quot;) for only $149 (you can stay at the Marriott through the Rally - Easy access to train.) Schedule on line: &lt;a href="http://atheists.org/upload/2012Convention/schedulev2.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://atheists.org/u...&lt;/a&gt;. (Please note there can be no refunds if your plans change or if speakers cancel.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332682156000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328799312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>American Atheists Convention 2012</name><id>51690862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332676800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/51690862/</event_url></item>