<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Avery st (Roofdeck)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.349089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-375-8550</phone><name>Blu Restaurant (Roofdeck)</name><city>Boston</city><id>1334215</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060177</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A speaker/panel discussion with senior level executives from cutting edge companies based in Boston and doing business worldwide. This will be followed by a photo shoot to demonstrate the importance of image development in the fashion industry. The focus will be the marketing/use of fashion and music in today's marketing environment-with a particular emphasis on new media and technology as a platform.&lt;br /&gt;Featured speakers will include:&lt;br /&gt;Ben Dolgoff, cofounder of Peekaboo Mobile will talk about how fashion businesses are using their mobile platform to increase sales. www.peekaboomobile.com&lt;br /&gt;Bettina Hein Founder and CEO, Pixability, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;www.pixability.com&lt;br /&gt;Pixability was founded out of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;From the Pixability website:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pixability began with a big idea: Make it simpler than ever for businesses and organizations of all sizes to tell their story via video. We offer the easiest, quickest, most economical way to create quality video to help you market your company or organization. Now anyone, from company president to cashier, can be part of the web video revolution.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Tamara Rodriguez, Singer-will be interviewed by Evan&lt;br /&gt;www.tamaraonline.net&lt;br /&gt;Panos Panay, Founder and CEO of Sonic Bids&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sonicbids is the website the helps bands get gigs and promoters book the right bands. Our community includes more than 245,000 bands and 21,000 promoters and licensors from all around the world. Sonicbids Brands, a division of Sonicbids, works with today’s leading consumer brands, like Diesel, Gap, Anheuser Busch, Converse and Universal Pictures, to tap into Sonicbids network to create authentic, powerful, viral marketing campaigns using independent music. To learn more about Sonicbids and Sonicbids Brands, go to www.sonicbids.com.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;John B. Davie, President and Founder of Fantourage&lt;br /&gt;www.fantourage.com&lt;br /&gt;From the Fantourage website:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fantourage is a free service that lets you earn rewards and recognition from Celebrities and Brands. Earn House points by simply posting and interacting with other fans.This is Where Celebrities and Brands recognize their loyal Fans!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ron Ranere of Positive Image Photography will do a fashion photo shoot after the panel discussion.  The shoot will show how image can be altered by changing makeup and accessories from the girl next door look to a hot edgy look.  What you need for your image depends on your music genre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The panel discussion will take place in the roofdeck at the Blu Restaurant at The Sportsclub LA.&lt;br /&gt;www.blurestaurant.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No admission fee.&lt;br /&gt;In lieu of an admission fee we encourage members to make a donation to Dress For Success&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dressforsuccess.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dressforsu...&lt;/a&gt; or Caitlin's Smiles &lt;a href="http://www.caitlins-smiles.org/donate.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.caitlins-s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go to the website's listed above to donate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>2523024</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>yasu</member_name><member_id>3356319</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280464839000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>fashionandmusic</urlname><id>1390310</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Fashion and Music Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277852439000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Event: Fashion and Music Marketing for 2010</name><id>13953465</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280440800000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fashionandmusic/events/13953465/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/6/global_12633862.jpeg</photo_url></item>