<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Happy New Year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To kick off 2008, we?re going to utilize a series of NLP techniques that have to do with time travel and goal-setting:&lt;br /&gt;? We?ll start with a guided Trans-Derivational search (review) of 2007, gathering up lessons learned in the past year.&lt;br /&gt;? We?ll use those learnings to generate Well-Formed Outcomes (can?t-miss goals) for 2008.&lt;br /&gt;? We?ll then ?Walk our Timelines? for 2008 to see more clearly how our well-formed outcomes come into reality in the coming year.&lt;br /&gt;? Finally (if we have time), we?ll use Circles of Excellence to give ourselves access to the internal resources that will be most useful to us in 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to learn (or review) a highly useful set of NLP techniques, while accomplishing some important planning for yourself for the coming year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A new feature for this meeting: we?ll be starting the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, and those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we?ll get rolling with the main events for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I?m looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200785880000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198198930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Neuro Linguistic Programming January Meetup</name><id>6947245</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200612600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/6947245/</event_url></item>