<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;How much? $35 discount rate for renters&lt;br /&gt;Members or Guests: $2 &lt;br /&gt;Annual Members: FREE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had such an overwhelming positive response from our last trip, we're scheduling another.  So let's get our paddles in the water gang and get together again for another great time!  The good news is that we were able to secure our discount rate from last time of $35 per rented kayak for a half day. We need a minimum of 6 for the group to rent in order to maintain our discount.  Reserving a kayak is not required, you can pay for the kayak when you arrive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;How many?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a minimum of 6 Participants (Non-organizers) by noon on Friday, July 10th. Up to 2 Guests per Member. Ages 18+ (Anyone under 21 must be accompanied by an adult family member.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Organizers:&lt;/span&gt; Susan (AO) and Chandra (AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Deadlines:&lt;/span&gt; The Final Deadline is noon on Friday July 10th. If people change their RSVPs to NO at the last minute the event may be in jeopardy of being canceled. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Details:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This meeting is open to both those who own a kayak and anyone who would like to rent one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People with their own Kayaks: If you have your own kayak, you need to bring your own PFD, paddle and a whistle for rescue. This is for your own safety. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rentals: Paddles, PFDs and whistles are included.  Kayaks are recreational and very user-friendly for beginners. We are near the shoreline, so there is little wind and very safe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring:&lt;br /&gt;    a snack/lunch and beverage&lt;br /&gt;    plenty of water&lt;br /&gt;    sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;    a hat&lt;br /&gt;    No alcohol&lt;br /&gt;    a smile for a good time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a brief kayak instruction before we head out.  The trip is planned for a leaisure 3 hour paddle which is quite beginner. SSFMG and its organizers are not responsible for any injuries to participants or damage to kayaks and/or kayak equipment. Personal flotation devices (PFDs) are required for all participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weather Alternative:&lt;/b&gt; None. This event will be canceled if it is raining or too foggy. We will do our best to cancel at least 6 hours in advance but we cannot control Mother Nature so we will do our best to notify everyone at least 3 hours prior to the event. Please do not change your RSVP based on weather forecasts. We check weather forecasts the night before and use those to determine if the event is canceled. Check Friday night or Saturday morning to determine event status.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool: There is no carpool for this event. Members should meet at Nantasket Kayaks at 9:45 am. If you would like to carpool you may note where from in your RSVP comment and someone else may choose to contact you if they are also interested in carpooling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.nantasketk.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nantasketk...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Nantasket Kayak Shack</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chandra</member_name><member_id>4844140</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>8338847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1247523611000</updated><rating><average>4.90999984741</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246301505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking at Nantasket</name><id>10761859</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247319000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/10761859/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/7/global_9417847.jpeg</photo_url></item>