<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Afterwork Mixer this Thursday April 19th  at Tavern on the Square located 730 Mass. Avenue.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Cambridge's Central Square neighborhood 6:15-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its a great time of the year:  Spring in Boston, the snow is gone, baseball is back,  a new season of Entourage, but more importantly The Boston Nightlife Group has some great events planned for the season. One of these  is an Afterwork Mixer  this Thursday  April 19th.    This time we are taking the party to  Tavern on Square, a premier destination among  the Cambridge afterwork  nightlife scene.  This venue has known to be a  favorite among local residents for quite some time, so please join the group as we celebrate the start of the weekend!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Also if you have not been to any or a few of our events whether an Afterwork Mixer,  MFA, or even a nite on the town in the city with the group,  I encourage all of you to come this Thursday and meet many of our wonderful members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet at the front bar , please look for me upon entering, my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, this venue is guaranteed to fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Line to Central Square &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178380230000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176428947000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Step into Spring!! Afterwork Mixer this Thursday Central Square Cambridge!!</name><id>5665216</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177021800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/5665216/</event_url></item>