<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Public Library</name><city>Boston</city><id>9629492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077309</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come! Get involved.... Its FREE.... Register..... Listen and Participate &lt;br /&gt;

Massachusetts Indian American Forum &amp;amp; NetSAP Panel Discussion. Indian American Forum- Mass Chapter &amp;amp; Network of South Asian Professionals - Boston Chapter (NetSAP)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When: &lt;br /&gt;

Sunday, April 7, 2013 from 3:00 PM to 4:30 PM (EST) Boston, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REGISTRATION: Click on link here: &lt;a href="http://forumandnetsapapril7panel.eventbrite.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://forumandnetsapapril7panel.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Seating is limited. First come, first served. Register early!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TOPIC: Violence in our Society. &lt;br /&gt;

Learning experiences to create better measures to protect our society against the impacts of community violence. Can and should Indian American values influence the National Dialogue?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indian Americans are representative of a diverse population in the United States and are part of the vast majority of people who have migrated over the years in the 20th century. Te Indian American Forum &amp;amp; NetSAP would like to host this discussion to gather views on the different aspects of social violence and the underlying laws that could be improved to create a culture of non-violence, peace and harmony inour society. As we read about acts of public violence like Sandy Hook Elementary School in CT or the Oak Creek Gurudwara in WI, we hope to collectively discuss the impact to our community and share values on how we could take preventive measures so that incidents of such nature are not repeated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To begin the dialogue, we will be hosting a moderated expert Panel Discussion on February 10th, 2013, on this subject to present different aspects and viewpoints This will be followed by an open discussion to relate the topic to our Indian values and heritage and by opening up the discussion to our audience to express their views and identify what action if any, the Indian American Forum can take to influence the national conversation as well as other State Forum chapters. Our selected panelists will include a Law Enforcement &amp;amp; Public Safety professional, a medical professional, a gun ownership advocate, a gun control advocate and a psychologist with expertise in Indian &amp;amp; American values &amp;amp; behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panel Moderator: Dean Bhaskar Chakravorti - Fletcher School, Tufts University&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Panelists include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Mr. Curtis Wood Undersecretary Forensic Science &amp;amp; Technology Executive Office of Public Safety, Comm. of Massachusetts &lt;br /&gt;

2. Mr. Jerry Belair Founder Stop Handgun Violence, Newton, MA &lt;br /&gt;

3. Dr. Steve P. Moysey, VP &amp;amp; Board Member, Gun Owners Action League &lt;br /&gt;

4. Dr. Peter Masiakos, Pediatric General &amp;amp; Trauma Surgeon Mass General Hospital &amp;amp; Asst. Prof. Harvard Medical School &lt;br /&gt;

5. Dr. Kumkum Malik Clinical Psychologist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SIGN UP TODAY and TELL YOUR FRIENDS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Indian American Forum for Political Education&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Indian American Forum for Political Education (IAFPE), known as the Forum, is the oldest and largest Indian American organization for political education in the country and is nationally recognized for its outstanding work in political empowerment process for the three-million strong community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Forum, established in 1982, has 22 State Chapters across the nation. It is a dynamic and growing organization that has helped educate the Indian American community to participate as full partners in the American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mass Chapter Forum Committee:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ramesh Advani – President, Dr. Anupam Wali – Vice President, Dr. Sapna Aggarwal – Treasurer, Anjali Wali – Secretary, Ajay Saini – Associate Secretary, Dr. Manju Sheth &amp;amp; Dr. Sanjay Kaul – Members at Large&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Network of South Asian Professionals – NetSAP &lt;br /&gt;

NetSAP’s mission is to serve as the unequivocal voice for the South Asian Diaspora by developing and engaging a cohesive network of professionals to benefit the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mission is to be more than just a networking forum. They also aspire to be the facilitating vehicle used by South Asian professionals to improve and enhance the communities in which we work and live. NetSAP lays the foundation for the best and brightest to forge cohesive relationships to work together for a lifetime. These are not just today's professionals who are the backbone of NetSAP, but are also simultaneously emerging to be tomorrow's leaders in business, politics and civic life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NetSAP believes that creating a strong personal bond between their members will strengthen our community across North America, as well as ties to each other. To that end, NetSAP's focus continues into the areas of economic growth and security, cultural awareness and preservation, family needs, and promoting education and learning. As an organization, they continuously persevere to help and give back to local communities by recruiting experts in areas such as health care, banking, education, finance and technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365425322000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363532286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Violence in our Society: Panel Discussion</name><id>109661962</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365361200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/109661962/</event_url></item>