<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The group had a blast there last weekend and &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/members/8643209/"&gt;Gabriella&lt;/a&gt;, one of our newest members, invited the group back at the &lt;a href="http://www.swgirlscouts.org/About/annejackson.html"&gt;Camp&lt;/a&gt; in Wilton, NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DO NOT ARRIVE too early, as the place will be occupied by another group until about 1 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 79 acres to explore, a large front yard for the dogs to play in, and lots of snow, some of it pretty deep. Bring your snowshoes... if you don't have any and would like to try snowshoeing there will be about 20 pairs available for our use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main lodge offers a place to hang out, rest &amp;amp; enjoy a snack. Bring food if you'd like. There is a complete kitchen available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I find it easier to take 101 to 101A, cross streets Wilson and Frye's Mill Road. Coming from Manchester or Nashua you pass the Monadnock Water and the storage units on the left on 101 A and then you will see a Mobile gas station on the left. Directly across the street from the Mobile take that right up the steep hill, that is Frye's Mill RD. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the top of the hill at the first place the road splits, go right onto Wilson and take a quick right into the parking lot. You will see a green dumpster in the lot so you know you have the right place. Walk down to the side door marked with a sign &amp;quot;Lodge&amp;quot; it will be open. If you see the &amp;quot;Playhouse&amp;quot; you have gone too far up the hill. My number is 603-475-3351 in case anyone gets lost. ~ Gabriella&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4894798</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235014425000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233749164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wilton Wilderness, Snowshoeing &amp;  Celebrating Liz's Birthday</name><id>9670476</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234722600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/9670476/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/a/global_7035066.jpeg</photo_url></item>