<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE 07/18:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The various segments for this year's race have been announced - the actual route will not be disclosed until two weeks before the race.  This year's race will cover about 55 miles and will consist of the following seven segments:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 1 - Run 4.3 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 2 - Road Bike  20.8 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 3 - Paddle (river) 4.8 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 4 - Mountain Bike 5.0 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 5 - Road Bike 17.0 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 6 - Run 5.8 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Segment 7 - Paddle (flat) 1.6 miles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The registration for this race is now open and will close on September 1 so if you are thinking of putting a team together to compete in this year's race now is the time. While my three-person team is pretty much all set - my brother will bike, I will kayak, and Monica will run - it would be great if we could form a few more teams to go out, compete, and have fun. Let me know if I can answer any questions or help out in any way if you want to put a team together (or if you are an iron person and are looking to go solo). If you would like to be part of a team indicate in your RSVP what part of the race you would like to do and maybe we can piece together a team or two. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Greenway Challenge is an annual adventure race held in the Blackstone River Valley National Heritage Corridor that spans Massachusetts and Rhode Island.  Monica and I have teamed up with my brother and others from the Random Group a few times to compete in this race and will be doing so again this year - we encourage others to join us.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The exact route, including overall distance, where it starts, and where it ends changes every year and doesn't get announced until later in the year, but it usually starts somewhere near Worcester, MA and ends somewhere near Lincoln, RI.  Teams of up to nine athletes run, paddle, and cycle over the approximately 50-mile course as a relay.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2009, the course consisted of two paddling legs, three running segments, one road cycling leg and one a combination of off-road and on-road bike leg. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part of the challenge is that you have to transport athletes and equipment from one transition area to another with only a map and your navigational skills.  Athletes complete the entire course on their own with the help of one support person who moves equipment between segments.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 5 different categories that teams can compete in.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the web site where you can get more information about the event or to register a team:      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenwaychallenge.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.greenwaych...&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see others there this year.  Contact me if you have any questions.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Blair    &lt;br /&gt;(978) 808-1932  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285540684000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268193014000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greenway Challenge - An Adventure Race Like No Other</name><id>12835678</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285419600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/12835678/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/7/global_13568231.jpeg</photo_url></item>