<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Kenoza Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.782185</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Universalist Unitarian Church</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>1565176</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075546</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This event is sponsored by another group, who's membership includes previouse members of the MoonPool coven. We plan on meeting at the UU Church of Haverhill no later than 5:30 and carpooling down. Let me suggest that traffic in that area, at that time of day, on a Friday will be horrendouse, so this should give us sufficient time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the official announcement from the other group:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrate Ostara this Weekend &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Posted by: "Rebecca )O(" nurserml@yahoo.com nurserml &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;Greetings All, &lt;br /&gt;Just&amp;nbsp; reminder about the Ostara celebration this weekend. &lt;br /&gt;Please join us !!! &lt;br /&gt;The Temple of Witchcraft, in the celebration of Ostara ! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 19 &amp;middot; 7:00pm - 9:00pm &lt;br /&gt;(PLEASE arrive by 6:45pm for check-in) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Salem Masonic Building &lt;br /&gt;107 Main Street &lt;br /&gt;Salem, NH &lt;br /&gt;($15-$25 Sliding Scale Donation) &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Ostara is a celebration of the Vernal Equinox, a time when light and dark are equal but the light's power is growing. Sacred to the Teutonic Goddess Ostre, many of our familiar celebrations of seeds, eggs, and rabbits originate with this pagan festival. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Come join the Temple of Witchcraft as we begin our second Wheel of the Year in Salem, NH, and bring the community together with the Sun, Moon, and Earth to turn the Wheel and keep the balance of the cycles of Nature and harmony with all worlds. All are welcome. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Please remember those less fortunate and bring a non-perishible food item (preferribly a protien source) for donation to a local Food Bank &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;A snack to share, at the after Ritual feast, is always appresheated.  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to contact me if you have any questions! We look forward to seeing you ! &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;www.templeofwitchcraft.org/ &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Blessings, Rebecca &lt;br /&gt;Lil 'Ole Gatekeeper, Me. &lt;br /&gt;Think Green !! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rick</member_name><member_id>44171</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300653677000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Due to the fact that Winter showed up late to the party and now refuses to leave (there's one in every family!), we are forced to cancel our traditional Sunrise Celebration. Instead we will be taking a field trip!</why><group><who>Acolytes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NorthShoreWitchesMeetup</urlname><id>1323749</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The North Shore Witches Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300296328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ostara Field Trip</name><id>16944371</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300570200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NorthShoreWitchesMeetup/events/16944371/</event_url></item>