<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Winter St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03431</zip><lat>42.934081</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Central Square &amp; Keene Public Library</name><city>Keene</city><id>690981</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.280904</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event is on the same night as our regular monthly screening in Concord, but our membership should know about this one, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to &amp;quot;follow&amp;quot; us on Twitter: mv911truth - see our group on Facebook, just search groups for Merrimack Valley 911 Truth and join the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An eye-opening new documentary film that covers several new independent investigations into the World Trade Center tragedy will be shown at the Keene Public Library auditorium on Tuesday, Nov. 17, at 6:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;b&gt;Loose Change 9/11: An American Coup&lt;/b&gt; is filmmaker Dylan Avery’s fourth DVD in a series that looks at both old and new evidence to reveal how the three tallest WTC buildings  were actually brought down, why it was done, and who may have been involved. The film includes historical footage of ‘false flag’ events in the U.S. and other nations where the governments used similar disasters to justify leading their countries into war.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;        A question-and-answer session will  follow, led by members of Monadnock 9/11Truth Alliance.  The showing is open to the public and free of charge.  All are welcome to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comment on An American Coup by Anthony J. Thorne: (on Amazon)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AN AMERICAN COUP&lt;/b&gt; takes a broad view of the events of 9/11, and places them within a continuum of incidents from recent history that display the clever duplicity of governments - or determined elements within them - to get what they want politically, absent any notion of democratic approval from an openly informed general public. We see well-presented overviews of the Reichstag fire, Pearl Harbor, and other vital historical incidents, some presented in more detail than others. This entire section, as well done as it is, is nonetheless completed within the first dozen minutes of the movie. (The film even makes mention here of the Kennedy assassination, conveying a good deal in just a handful of shots, and ending with a particularly telling montage). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The events of 9/11 make up the body of the movie, and &lt;b&gt;LOOSE CHANGE: AN AMERICAN COUP&lt;/b&gt; enters the front rank of all films that honestly address the events of that day. I have now personally watched a dozen or so films investigating 9/11, and digested a greater number of lectures and presentations covering the same topic, while simultaneously plowing through something like 20 or more related books. (This is a mundane fact, as I suspect a majority of people involved in 9/11 truth have done exactly the same thing). AN AMERICAN COUP conveys the sensation of building on that entire body of investigative research, paying careful attention to all the disparate facts and the overall narrative conveyed, then assembling them judiciously to offer the clearest possible overview and message to viewers. Many of the above books and films on 9/11 have conveyed the gravity of the event, and the importance of sharing this information with others, with a tremendous emotional impact. This new LOOSE CHANGE film offers the same potent message, but with an increased strength and clarity that stand out from those that came before. It's a blisteringly powerful movie. The previous LOOSE CHANGE FINAL CUT has remained a favorite of mine for its ability to convey useful information about 9/11 in an effective and energizing manner. LOOSE CHANGE 9/11: AN AMERICAN COUP is a more forceful experience that covers a similar breadth of material in a noticeably more polished way. It will evoke strong reactions from anyone who watches it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film provides an analysis of war-games taking place on the day, concurrent with the various attacks. This overview contains some extra details on the events that I hadn't fully understood before, and the additional information makes a big difference, clarifying the apparent methods used by covert figures within the government to distort the American military response to the hijackings. (These details had appeared earlier in Michael Ruppert's CROSSING THE RUBICON, but this is the first time I've seen them presented quite so clearly, with accompanying audio and video evidence). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The narrative of events shown post-9/11 includes the various contradictory appearances and messages made by Osama Bin Laden, who initially denied involvement in the 9/11 attacks, then (if the Bush administration and their fortuitously located, perfectly timed smoking-gun tapes could be believed), reversed his earlier comments and took credit for them after all. A thorough analysis of the overall unlikelihood of Bin Laden's `confessions of guilt' can be found in David Ray Griffin's recent `OSAMA BIN LADEN: DEAD OR ALIVE?'. AN AMERICAN COUP makes the same points through the juxtaposition of different images featuring Bin Laden - and not the two or three pictures you've probably seen used to present this argument elsewhere. This sequence is quite well done. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film covers the collapse of WTC7, and revisits important testimony made by witness Barry Jennings. Some of this has previously appeared in the excellent FABLED ENEMIES documentary, but we see here some extra moments, and then the upsetting epilogue to the story. The latter includes a full screen shot of an email sent to the filmmakers by a private detective, who suggests to them that some doors are best left unopened. Aspects of this story are left unspoken, others only hinted at, but viewers will have enough information at this point to reach some definite conclusions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AN AMERICAN COUP benefits from having the production resources to do what it wants. At one point, the narration discusses events in New York, and we see perfectly realized CG recreations of the Manhattan landscape from the day of 9/11, carefully detailed down to hundreds of individual buildings. The sound design of the film is also superlative, with some explosive moments hitting home very hard, and appropriately so. There are numerous moments like this, not dwelt on in a showy manner, but all simply used to make a particular point with clarity before moving ahead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is exceptionally well made, and strongly narrated by Daniel Sunjata. It's an important movie, and one that I highly recommend people watch. For anyone with an even halfway open mind, it should prove to be an emotionally overwhelming experience. In the light of the decade of horror resulting from the disaster of 9/11, its existence provides evidence to me of two notions. First, that truth maintains its own energy, continually grows in force and effect, and cannot be easily extinguished. Secondly, that deception rests on flimsy foundations, is supported only through increasing amounts of desperation and bluster, and will ultimately wither away in full view. Don't miss LOOSE CHANGE 9/11: AN AMERICAN COUP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258673614000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257740645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Loose Change 9/11: An American Coup</name><id>11829837</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258500600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/11829837/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/4/5/global_11723189.jpeg</photo_url></item>