<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Manchester Print Works Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02865</zip><lat>41.903866</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-723-7892</phone><name>Lincoln Woods State Park</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>902837</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422496</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join me at Lincoln Woods Park for a 5 mile walk around Olney Pond. It's getting cold out, so let's get this walk in before more snow comes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No one will be left behind. Once around Olney Pond is about 2.5 miles, and I am going for twice around. You are welcome to quit anytime, or if you're up for a challenge we can go for a third time around!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's getting cool out, so make sure to dress warm. I would recommend bringing water with you if you plan to walk the entire 5 miles (or more).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are familiar with Lincoln Woods, then I will meet you near the Rt. 146 booth entrance. When coming in via Rt. 146 entrance, turn RIGHT into the park headed towards the beach. Just past the entrance, AFTER turning right, there is a big rock on your left. This is where I will meet you. If you drive past the rock, there is a parking lot on the left just before the beach. You can park there or on the side in the dirt anywhere near the entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map with of the park: &lt;a href="http://www.riparks.com/pdfs/lincolnmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Lincoln Woods State Park Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Lincoln Woods State Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nestled between routes 146 and routes 123 , Lincoln Woods State Park is one of Blackstone Valley's great treasures. A short ride from Providence, Pawtucket, and Cumberland, it is a popular get away for northeastern Rhode Islanders. Visitors can enjoy swimming at the fresh water beach, trout fishing, playing ball, hiking, jogging, horseback riding, or just relaxing under a shade tree.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. If it rains or snows, I will send out a message if I decide to cancel this event. Hopefully I won't have to cancel this time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260889675000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260141359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter morning walk - Let's try this again.. 2.5 to 5 mile walk at Lincoln Woods</name><id>12031640</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260716400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/12031640/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/4/global_11459828.jpeg</photo_url></item>