<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Weir St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02780</zip><lat>41.900133</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-824-2200</phone><name>Baha Brothers Sandbar Grille</name><city>Taunton</city><id>707187</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.092322</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Super Tuesday Republican Primary Debate Watch and Straw Poll On Thursday, March 1, 2012, we will be sponsoring a Republican Presidential Primary Debate Watch and Straw Poll prior to the Super Tuesday Primary. The location for this fundraiser will be The Baha Brother's Sandbar Grill, in their Tiki Room. The Sandbar is located at 64 Weir Street, Taunton, MA. We will begin the evening at 7PM with a Cocktail/Social hour, with a cash bar and light refreshments. We will have some important guests in attendance, so you will want to take advantage of this opportunity to meet with some of the great names in the Republican Party here in Massachusetts. At 8PM, we will watch the Debate on CNN, and as soon as it has finished, we will hold our Straw Poll. The votes will be tabulated immediately and the results announced when the counting is done. The requested donation for this important event is $25 per person at the door, or $20 in advance. Please click the &amp;quot;Donate&amp;quot; button below for advance donations - your donation will also serve as an RSVP for the event. For those who cannot attend, but wish to vote in the poll, for a suggested donation of $10, we will send you a ballot.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330703346000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329350832000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Debate Watch and Straw Poll</name><id>52518452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330646400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/52518452/</event_url></item>