<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Audubon St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.311544</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 624-5189</phone><name>The Neighborhood Music School</name><city>New Haven</city><id>853944</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.921895</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come to Neighborhood Music School and see a FREE classical Music Concert Starring NHC's very own Alexis Zingale on piano with the extraordinary Mark Rike on violin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the program: &lt;br /&gt;THE ROMANTIC VIOLIN: Faculty Fridays at Neighborhood Music School&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Rike, violin &amp;amp; Alexis Zingale, piano&lt;br /&gt;Works of Kreisler, Sarasate, Szymanowski and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Program to include&lt;br /&gt;Sarasate - Zigeunerweisen&lt;br /&gt;Szymanowski - Chant de Roxana&lt;br /&gt;Achron - Hebrew Melody&lt;br /&gt;Moszkowski - Guitarre&lt;br /&gt;Kreisler - Marche miniature viennoise, Syncopation, Tambourin Chinois&lt;br /&gt;Kreisler/Poldini - Poupee Valsante&lt;br /&gt;Kreisler/Rimsky-Korsakov - Song of India&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concert is FREE at Neighborhood Music School, 100 Audubon St., New Haven (Audubon is off Whitney between Grove and Trumbull St.)  Parking can be found on Whitney, Orange and Audubon St. for free after 7 p.m., and it's well within walking distance of favorite downtown spots (around the corner from Anna Liffey's, and a block away from Caseus.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexis will host, but can only answer questions well ahead of time as in the hours just preceding the show she will need to be preparing. &lt;br /&gt;Outside of that AJ will be a second host and can be reached at 315-345-9348.  Note from AJ: I REALLY enjoyed a similar concert with these two a year ago, they are both High Class musicians and I hope some of you will come out and see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those of us from the collective can meet in the lobby about 7:15 and head in around 7:20, feel free to find us inside if later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards there will be a trip to a local bar for drinks and or food.  Actual place is TBD, but most likely just down the street at Anna Liffey's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alexis</member_name><member_id>2469731</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289671202000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288649719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Romantic Violin: Mark Rike, violin &amp; Alexis Zingale, piano - FREE concert!</name><id>15302161</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289608200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15302161/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>