<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Water Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06355</zip><lat>41.353419</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-536-5059 </phone><name>Mystic Arts Center</name><city>Mystic</city><id>1168937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.971788</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per meetup</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Frances Harkins, owner of Courtyard Gallery in Mystic is holding this venue exclusively for  our members. This will be a meet the artist type of venue, with one of the exhibiting Artists of the show &amp;quot;Divine Feminine&amp;quot;   An Artist Talk by Renee Rhodes, Sculptor and Clinical Psychologist, will explore the process of creating spiritual art that focuses on womens' issues.  Rhodes will discuss the role of visionary art and social consciousness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am hoping that a great number of us will take part in this day, it will be a nice chance for us all to mix and mingle as it is our very own private party and is a very generous offer from our host!  So come out, bring a guest, join us, right in the heart of Mystic a charming little arts district with much to take in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Divine Feminine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a collaborative exhibition of the sculpture and paintings of &lt;br /&gt;Renee Rhodes &amp;amp; Christopher Zhang&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Renee Rhodes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.reneerhodes.com&lt;br /&gt;The focus in this series is on sacred art and the divine feminine archetypes.  Renee draws her material from nature and a broad spiritual background of Christian, Hindu, Buddhist, and Ancient Greek and  Celtic traditions.  Rhodes believes that through sculpture,  the wisdom and the messages of the Devine Feminine can be transmitted into representational human form that is instantly recognizable and therefore easier to take in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Christopher Zhang&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chriszhangstudio.com/artist.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chriszhang...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zwangs paintings are &amp;quot;Soul portraits that emerge out of representational images with the eye of a portrait artist that sees into the essence of his subjects.  This series of Tibetan and other Chinese minority women captures the grace of the female form and power, beauty and pride of the Divine Feminine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A portion of sales from this exhibit will be donated to womans charities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can talk up some carpooling arrangements too.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267654033000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264114494000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your invited!!!  our own private gathering at: Courtyard Gallery, Mystic</name><id>12386632</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267387200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/12386632/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/f/global_12902559.jpeg</photo_url></item>