<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;***** Edited 4/5/13 ****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Considering our group's responses, and the fact the Sunday should be awesome, I'm going to adjust the plans so more of us can enjoy a hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start at the same spot. However, we'll do a 7-8 mile loop around the larger hills. Essentially following the larger 2 red loops, plus some side trails for fun. Start time will still be 7am, and plan for a pretty fast and steady pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that while this is a shorter hike, you should still plan for the conditions and possibilities. Proper footwear and hydration is a must.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*******************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm finalizing the details right now, but this will not be a walk in the park by any means. The goal is 18 miles. Realistically, we might only do half, but the goal is the full 18. We'll hike for 3-4 hours at a time (at a fast pace) with a minute or 2 break here and there, and a lunch break at the halfway mark. It's important that you know your (and your pet's) level of fitness and ability. I don't want to discourage anyone from joining, but it's not fair to the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start at the parking area by Houghton's Pond. It's the big one by the police station and reservation headquarters. We'll head east until we hit the end. Then we'll head back. From there people have the choice to bail. If we're still up for it, we'll finish the rest of the loop and head west towards the museum. This is 18 miles, and not easy by any means. The first section alone is probably going to be around 12 miles (I haven't checked the exact distance yet).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be prepared. While I organize hikes from time to time, it is your individual responsibility to be prepared. Please also note that while I have hiked this route many times, I am not a trained instructor and do not have any type of leadership certification. I am simply acting as a means of getting people together for a hike. You are responsible for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I plan to add more detail in the next day or two, but I wanted to get this posted sooner than later. Please feel free to message me any questions, but keep in mind that I might not be able to respond immediately.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tall guy with a buckskin (black mask) pit bull, and probably a teenager or two tagging along. Call me if you can't find me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luis </member_name><member_id>6933069</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate</member_name><member_id>10946499</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365730091000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314316707000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills - Skyline Trail - Down and Back.</name><id>30964701</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365332400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/30964701/</event_url></item>