<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Joe Ciarcia 415-480-4335&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BOOTS ON TRAIL AT 10:00 AM (&lt;/strong&gt;so aim to arrive in the parking lot around 9:40 to 9:45)&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you are interested in participating be sure to read the entire event listing before you RSVP - then answer the questions that are part of the RSVP process. While the objective of this event is to enjoy ourselves, your safety, and the safety of the others, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands, overestimate your skills and abilities, or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Please note that we will hike this mountain at a moderate pace - this is not a workout hike but also not a nature walk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Use the message board below to coordinate rides etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Tecumseh (4003’) is the shortest official 4,000 footer and home to Waterville Valley Ski Area. Views to the immediate north include Osceola (4340’), the highest peak in the region. East, across the valley there are views of North Tripyramid (4180’) and Middle Tripyramid (4140’).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Recent trip reports indicate that there may be some ice at he the upper portion of the hiking trails, &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;microspikes or Hillsounds are mandatory for this hike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While I have hiked these peaks before, I did all of my current research using the AMC's &lt;em&gt;White Mountain Guide&lt;/em&gt;, a trail map, and the Internet.  You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If dangerous weather conditions cancel this event I will notify confirmed participants of any planned changes a day or two ahead of time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this trip we will hike the Tecumseh trail that leaves the north west corner of the parking lot of the Waterville Valley Ski Area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace trip&lt;/strong&gt; we will &lt;strong&gt;hike 4.94 miles round trip&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you. Fatigue and other unexpected conditions can alter our plans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire trip please contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dogs:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Dogs are permitted on this hike provided they are experienced hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Guests are not permitted on this hike. All participants must be members of Random Group of Hikers. All participants must individually sign up and respond to ALL RSVP questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Spring has sprung but given New England's wild weather we need to be prepared. Be prepared with layers to layer up or down depending upon the temperature. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel this hike - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=43.9665415783306&amp;amp;lon=-71.5564904525892"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; (noaa.gov) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. Bring enough to keep you warm and protect you from the wind in case we have to stop/wait in one place for a prolonged period of time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microspikes or Hillsounds are mandatory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Be sure to have a way to attach these to your pack. There's still tons of snow at the higher elevations and warm days can turn a packed trail into a pile of mashed potatoes. Throw your &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;snowshoes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the car. I will make a determination at the trailhead as to whether or not we need to bring them. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater. Winter hat. Face shield/balaclava. Winter mittens/gloves. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwea&lt;/strong&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Windproof breathable shell, GoreTex or equivalent. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip. Hydration bladders may freeze during winter - bottles with insulating sleeves work best.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in cold temperatures). Chemical hand/foot warmers. Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack. Extra hat, mittens/gloves, and socks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional Items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof pants. Waterproof gaiters. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;prior&lt;/span&gt; to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will begin this hike by meeting at the north west corner of the Waterville Valley Ski Area parking lot at 9:30 AM. According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 133 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 43 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?daddr=43.966581,-71.526943(Mt+Tecumseh+%5BWaterville+Ski+Area%5D)&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;Click here for customizable driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/a&gt; (google.com) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Mazda 3 Wagon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ciarcia</member_name><member_id>40840452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367792645000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366812611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Tecumseh (INTERMEDIATE)</name><id>115939422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367761500000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/115939422/</event_url></item>