<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>321 Brookline Ave, Boston, MA 02115</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.341053</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Simmons College (Alumnae Hall)</name><city>Boston</city><id>12340332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105904</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us for our BIGGEST Japanese Taiko Drumming show of the year, and celebrate Women's History Month with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MAKING WOMEN'S HISTORY &lt;br /&gt;

March 24, 2013 2:30PM-4:30PM (DOORS OPEN AT 1:45PM)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simmons College, Alumnae Hall, 321 Brookline Ave, Boston, MA 02115 &lt;br /&gt;

$20 Suggested Donation (LIMITED SEATS AT THE DOOR) &lt;br /&gt;

(student/low income rates available – Email LeeAnn for details leeann dot photog at gmail dot com)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information: &lt;a href="http://genkimakingwomenshistory.eventbrite.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://genkimakingwomenshistory.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This performance also supports the non-profit Genki Spark performance troupe, which gives 100+ demonstrations, workshops, classes for community organizations, schools and universities, and the general public in New England throughout the year, with an all-inclusive, intergenerational message to inspire creativity, build community, and advocate respect for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DOORS OPEN at 1:45PM with a PRO-FEMALE SLIDE SHOW and PLAYLIST, so come early, have a bite to eat, and say 'Hello'. &lt;br /&gt;

 Our show KICKS OFF with an OPEN MIC tribute to women and features our NEWEST ARRANGEMENTS and taiko PLAYING STYLES as well as a SPOKEN WORD PIECE and a rendition of Alicia Keys song, 'GIRL ON FIRE.' Don't miss the FIRST TIME PERFORMANCE of our new TRIAL PERIOD MEMBERS with their version of the well known song 'renshu.' LET'S GO! &lt;br /&gt;

 REFRESHMENTS SERVED. Proceeds benefit programming for underserved communities. &lt;br /&gt;

 WHAT!?! CAN'T MAKE IT? Consider making a donation or buying a ticket for student/low income member. &lt;br /&gt;

 Information: &lt;a href="http://genkimakingwomenshistory.eventbrite.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://genkimakingwomenshistory.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Like us on Facebook: The Genki Spark: Taiko Projects with Attitude&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364158666000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363663496000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Japanese Taiko Drumming show Sunday, March 24, 2:30-4:30PM (DOORS OPEN 1:45PM)</name><id>109946592</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364147100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/109946592/</event_url></item>