<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Hi, Everybody! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm scheduling another hike and picnic lunch for this coming Sunday the 11th - it will be exactly the same as the meetup on Saturday the 17th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather for Sunday looks to be ideal for early April:  clear, crisp, and cool / chilly!  Some have expressed an interest in going to the ocean.  After the hike and picnic (for those that still have time and energy!),  we can head to the ocean for another walk to finish up the day!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pack a big picnic lunch with lots of food and join us on an early spring day for a great moderately paced hike with a super group of people! We'll meet at the base of Mount Agamenticus and do a loop of approximately 3 miles including a visit to the summit. From there we'll head across the street and enjoy our picnic before concluding the day. Afterward, for those that wish to join us, we can head over to a nearby coffee shop (Stonewall Kitchen) for hot coffee and dessert...and then a visit to the ocean. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The directions are easy: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 95 north over the big bridge to Exit 7 just before the toll booths. (NOTE: There are two Exit 7s -one in Portsmouth, NH and one in Maine; it's the second Exit 7, the one in Maine, that we're looking for). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit 7 - Go to the end of the ramp - stop sign - take left - and then the next immediate available right (the road ends at that point, so you have to turn right), and go approximately 6.3 miles (the name of this road is Chases Pond Road which becomes Mountain Road - same road; just keep going straight). You will come to a small parking lot at the base of Mount Agamenticus (the paved road ends at this point) - and you can park either in the lot, or if it is full like it often is, on either side of the road. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before RSVPing, please allocate sufficient time to enjoy the entire outing and picnic, which will last approximately 3 1/2 hours from 11:00 - 2:30. Total hiking distance, including Mount A, and back and forth from the picnic site is about 5 miles. While the terrain is generally gentle, there are occasional areas that are fairly steep. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Footwear with sturdy grips are recommended. You might also wish to pack a small blanket for the picnic along with - of course - food and beverages! No evidence of flies yet - but with all the warm weather that we've been having, it might not be a bad idea to have along a can of bug spray to be on the safe side. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you then! &lt;br /&gt;Randy &lt;br /&gt;RandyS@maine.rr.com &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting near a Silver Subaru Forester in the general vicinity of the above referenced meeting spot for the first few hikers.  After that we will be waiting at the inside edge of the parking lot near the bench and rocks.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272209058000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270635334000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Agamenticus Hike and Picnic Lunch</name><id>13111871</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270998000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13111871/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/3/global_7735123.jpeg</photo_url></item>