<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>F-29 colony Club, School House Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05751</zip><lat>43.649029</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Suzanne's Condo</name><city>Killington</city><id>5251502</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.793015</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Killington Winter Weekend &lt;br /&gt;

 Feb. 3rd.,6 pm.,or 4th.,5th., 9 am. &lt;br /&gt;

 Killington, Vermont &lt;br /&gt;

 Host: Suzanne A.&amp;nbsp; suzalien@verizon.net / 212.714-9310 &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost: $50. per night, Come up one or two nights. &lt;br /&gt;

 Suzanne said she may be able to SAVE us $30 on your ski lift per day!!!!!! &lt;br /&gt;

 Co-host: Steve Obermiller 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net &lt;br /&gt;

 Steve O. is carpooling from Nashua, Manchester &amp;amp; Concord NH. &lt;br /&gt;

 Steve O. wrote: &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Killington is one of the best mountains to ski or ride in New England, at any level. No matter what the weather is, or your skill level. It is still good skiing or riding. Suzanne A. our Host, and my friend Leo L. have been inviting me up for years now. I know this is a great opportunity for us to enjoy a new location and meet some new friends. So, join me and my new and old friends for a weekend of parties, Hot tub, Shopping, skiing, riding, snowshoeing, X/C skiing and more, in the mountains of Vermont. I will be carpooling. So &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/e/8/event_13040968.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;please, contact me for more info: about that. For more info about the condo? Please contact Suzanne A. or check out some of her web sites below. &lt;br /&gt;

 Suzanne A. wrote:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We will stay at my condo: &lt;br /&gt;

 - Beautifully furnished end unit 3 levels condo (5 bedrooms / 3 bathrooms) &lt;br /&gt;

 - Located on the access road in the Colony Club Condos (5 minutes from base lodge) &lt;br /&gt;

 - WiFi connection &lt;br /&gt;

 We are looking forward to another fun season of skiing, boarding, hiking, skating, dancing and partying. Hope you will join us. &lt;br /&gt;

 link with pictures for the house in Killington: &lt;a href="http://www.suzannecouturemodelmaking.com/Killington/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.suzannecouturemodelmaking.com/Killington/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Beds &amp;amp; bedrooms: rooms are 2 to 5 people per room. &lt;br /&gt;

 Upstairs left: Queen &amp;amp; single &lt;br /&gt;

 Upstairs right: Queen &amp;amp; single &lt;br /&gt;

 Main floor: Queen &amp;amp; single &lt;br /&gt;

 Downstair's&amp;nbsp; bedroom: 2 singles &lt;br /&gt;

 Downstair: Queen pull-out, double futon, double mattress (place in the corner near furnace door), single (Place at the foot of the queen pull-out). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Below is the full guest info. &lt;br /&gt;

 Call anytime. I have another request&amp;nbsp; for that weekend so book it asap (with a check). Right now I have +/-&amp;nbsp; spots available for that we. &lt;br /&gt;

 Guests info &lt;br /&gt;

 READ, PRINT &amp;amp; BRING WITH YOU please!!!!!!!! &lt;br /&gt;

 WELCOME to season-11/12 and Hello skiers! Your friendly manager Suzanne and Walt Welcomes you to a season of fun, lots of snow and friends. &lt;br /&gt;

 A weekend&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Walt Gorgas &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; waltgorgas@aol.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; C: 845-489-3999 &lt;br /&gt;

 B weekend&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Suzanne Couture&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; suzalien@aol.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; W: 212-714-9310 &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; C:917-836-9898 &lt;br /&gt;

 Guests &lt;br /&gt;

 The charge is $50/night including staples. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to mention the gender of your guest when making a reservation.&amp;nbsp; Collecting money is not fun. Help out by paying you dues UPON arrival. CASH only please. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cancellation policy &lt;br /&gt;

 There is no cancellation fee when a guest makes a reservation and do not come up. But there is a fee if the house is full (and other guests were turned down) unless another guest can be found to take the reserve spot. &lt;br /&gt;

 Very important &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring: bathing suit, slippers (no shoes policy in the house), sheets, towel, ear plugs. Optional:pillow &amp;amp; blanket(if you do not want to use house one's).Slip on shoes/boot are great to get in &amp;amp; out of house quickly! &lt;br /&gt;

 No smoking and no pets policy &lt;br /&gt;

 We invite you to light up just outside the front door. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cocktails &amp;amp; Food &lt;br /&gt;

 Bear &amp;amp; wine can be purchased at a high price at the Killington Market near by. I recommend bringing from the city or buying at a super markets in Rutland like Price Chopper or Hannaford. &lt;br /&gt;

 House is supplied by the following for make-your-own-breakfast:cereals, oatmeal, bacon, eggs, bread, english muffins, coffee, tea, milk, orange juice. &lt;br /&gt;

 Feel free to bring items to supply your personal diet or to pack a lunch. &lt;br /&gt;

 Parking &lt;br /&gt;

 There are usually 3 spots for parking in front of the house. IMPORTANT: leave the one in front of staircase available for the manager on Friday night. If all the spots are taken, use the additional parking lot situated directly above the condo around the hairpin turn. &lt;br /&gt;

 Key &lt;br /&gt;

 The key is hidden atop a loose plank underneath the corner of the house protubing opposite of the entrance door. That protubing corner of the house is 6 inches above the ground and has a log just below holding the loose plank. Slide out the log and pry open gently the loose plank (that plank is the floor of the house) . You will find a ziplock bag with a rock and a plastic bottle. The key is inside the bottle. YOU MUST PUT THE KEY BACK EXACTLY THE SAME WAY IMMEDIATELY AFTER USING IT, PLEASE! These instructions will be clearer once on location. &lt;br /&gt;

 Fireplace &lt;br /&gt;

 ALWAYS extinguish the fire before going to bed or leaving the house by dousing slowly with water until there is no more coals then close the glass door. Do not close the glass door when the fire is going on, it stains the glass and may crack it. &lt;br /&gt;

 Always close the doors BEFORE going to bed. &lt;br /&gt;

 ALWAYS close the flue when the fire is done. It looses a lot of heat when open. &lt;br /&gt;

 Windows &lt;br /&gt;

 Each windows have a locking mechanism at eye level on the side. If you do not release it before turn the crank to open the window, you will break the mechanism. It is expensive to get replaced so please be careful. &lt;br /&gt;

 Energy/Thermostats &lt;br /&gt;

 Please be kind to our planet and to me. Conserve energy every way you can. Keep thermostats at 65. Turn off the light in your room when you are NOT in the room please! &lt;br /&gt;

 Shoes &lt;br /&gt;

 Positively no shoes or boots in the house. I mean that! &lt;br /&gt;

 Ski boots &lt;br /&gt;

 There is a rack in the downstairs bedroom to place your ski boots. If you bring them in your room place some newspaper under them to keep the rug clean. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cleaning &lt;br /&gt;

 All members are expected to pitch in around the house. We have a cleaning lady but this is not an invitation to trash the place. This is your winter getaway. Treat it like your own house. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; -Clean up after yourself immediately. Don&amp;rsquo;t leave dirty dishes in the sink or anywhere else. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; - Keep the living &amp;amp; dinning room neat. Keep all your personal belonging in your room. &lt;br /&gt;

 Directions: F-29 colony Club,&amp;nbsp; School House Road, Killington, VT 05751 &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;4 west to Killington. Make a left on Killington Access Road. Make a right on School House Road shortly after the flashing light. Make the second left into Colony Club. Follow the sign to building &amp;ldquo;F&amp;rdquo;. We are at the end #29.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve O. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328369287000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326998120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Killington Winter Weekend</name><id>48777212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328364000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/48777212/</event_url></item>