<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>617-524-1667</phone><name>Harvest Co-Op Market/Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>428348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What is the What by Dave Eggers is winning next in the polls and barring any crazy vote swings, we'll plan to read this next in line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comments found at: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio?show=HARDCOVER:NEW:9781932416640:26.00#synopses_and_reviews" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publisher Comments:&lt;br /&gt;What Is the What is an epic novel about the lives of two boys during the Sudanese civil war. For those who think they know about the so-called Lost Boys of Sudan, this novel will be an eye-opener. And if you think you know the work of Dave Eggers, this is in many ways a complete departure: it's straightforward and unflinching, and yet full of unexpected humor and adventure amid the madness of war.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eggers has been working on the book for four years now, deeply entrenched in the community of Sudanese refugees in the U.S., and in 2003 went to southern Sudan with a refugee named Valentino Achak Deng. During that trip, Deng was reunited with the family he hadn't seen in 17 years. What Is the What is a book about the lives of these two boys ? one, at seven, too young to know what's happening to his country; the other, at ten, old enough to fight for the rebel army.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through it all, the two boys persevere through one of the most brutal civil wars the world has ever known, finding themselves in one unbelievable, utterly surreal situation after another. What Is the What is thought-provoking, exciting, and repeatedly heartbreaking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're back to the Clear Conscience Cafe!  See ya then&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Lisa with any questions!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205363085000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197286640000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Meetup- What is the What</name><id>6887340</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205190000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/6887340/</event_url></item>