<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets explore Tully Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Thank you very much for all your feedback thus far!  Based on the feedback, I have created  the following schedule:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : small"&gt;meet at 9am (please arrive before 9am so that you are ready to hike by 9am) and begin hiking the 7.5mi bike loop, starting on the west/left side of long pond (in other words, hiking the loop clockwise); we will join the official Tully Trail at the junction near Davis Hill; when we reach the junction where the Tully Trail goes up the hill (at the transmission lines) while the bike trail remains next to the lake we will split up the group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : small"&gt;Jeffrey will take all those interested seeing the look out points (Jacob's Hill and possibly The Ledges) and the Spirit Falls up the hill, while I will continue to lead the group who will remain on the bike trail (and for all I know, this may only be me)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : small"&gt;Jeffrey's group will rejoin the bike trail again, but will be behind the other group--Jeffrey, when we split, I will provide you with a walkie-talkie so that we can stay in touch to determine when we meet up at the parking lot again; the group that stays on the bike trail will most likely have time to check out Doane's Falls in the meantime&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : small"&gt;after we regroup, we will decide on what to do next--though the meetup as an entire group will end here: most likely, the following two groups will be created: 1) Jeffrey takes a group to Tully Mountain, while 2) Monica and Jesse take a group over to the parking lot near the shelter at Wyman Hill.  From there, we will be exploring the connection between M-M and Tully Trail.  Jesse will be leading this group, as I will most likely fall behind/stop somewhere where the elevation gets too much for my leg.  Whenever each group finishes, the respective group disperses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : small"&gt;Again, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the meetup itself ends when everybody has completed the loop hike; we will not regroup after the 2nd activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (though Jeffrey and I will check in with each other to ensure both groups have successfully completed their hikes)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : small"&gt;Looking forward to Sunday!  Weathers seems to be on our side.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Tully Trail is a 22-mile loop trail that encircles the largely undeveloped Tully Valley in the North Quabbin Region of Central Massachusetts. From the summit of Tully Mountain to the cascading waters of Doane’s Falls, the trail connects some of the region’s most scenic properties and views. (source: thetrustees.org)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We do not plan on exploring all of the 22miles.  Also, Tully provides other opportunities, incl. kayaking/canoeing on Long Pond, enjoying the scenery of Doane Falls, various look out points, biking on a 7.5mi loop trail, and, of course, Tully Mountain (for those who need a summit to feel accomplished :) ).  Check out the map link below to determine the possibilities.  The trail also runs through a disc golf course that borders the Tully Dam (see map for location).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;While this is a meetup, this is NOT necessarily one guided hike.  Rather, it is an opportunity for us to meet and form small groups who share an activity.  Therefore, everybody please print the map below so that you also can navigate the area.  &lt;strong&gt;In your RSVP add what you would like to do&lt;/strong&gt;, so that we start to get a sense of what people's interests are.  &lt;strong&gt;If you are bringing your own kayak/canoe, please add that as well&lt;/strong&gt;. (I have been to Tully a few times and overall trails are well marked.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;If you feel uncomfortable with not knowing for sure what you are doing, I plan on a fast-paced walk (3+mi/hour pace) of the 7.5mi bike loop. (I am recovering from injury and have to avoid elevation; no Tully Mountain for me, but I want a workout nonetheless.) Afterwards, I would like to enjoy Doane Falls.  (I have never played disc golf, but am open to trying it out, though do not have needed equipment; love canoeing/kayaking, but don't own one, so it is not an option for me.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;On a side note: our own Michael Blair and Monica Trust plan on participating in the Tully Trail triathlon in October:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/things-to-do/special-events/tully-lake-triathlon.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/things-to-do/special-events/tully-lake-triathlon.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Lets practice for them a little bit and check out the course :)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;For general information about Tully:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/places-to-stay/tully-lake-campground/tully-trail.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/places-to-stay/tully-lake-campground/tully-trail.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;For a map:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/assets/documents/places-to-visit/trailmaps/Tully-Trail-Map.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/assets/documents/places-to-visit/trailmaps/Tully-Trail-Map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;For more information about disc golf at Tully Lake:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pdga.com/course_directory/course/tully-lake-dgc" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.pdga.com/course_directory/course/tully-lake-dgc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nae.usace.army.mil/recreati/tul/tulrec12.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.nae.usace.army.mil/recreati/tul/tulrec12.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.discgolfscene.com/courses/Tully_Lake" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.discgolfscene.com/courses/Tully_Lake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>at the only parking lot for Tully Trail on that road</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica</member_name><member_id>10925522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1346676792000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346110046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Tully Trail</name><id>79644562</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346590800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/79644562/</event_url></item>