<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Bruegger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>972928</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121038</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>IMPORTANT:  MAKE NOTE OF NEW DATE OCTOBER 24, 2010.  We regularly meet on the last Sunday of the month but that would be Halloween and we have many parents (and partygoers themselves!) who can't be there on such a fun filled night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The book we have chosen for October is &amp;quot;Cutting for Stone&amp;quot; by Abraham Verghese.  Described often as an &amp;quot;epic&amp;quot; tale, it tells the story of two brothers from their birth to their eventual separation and reconciliation.  It has also been described as a fascinating medical tale as it is set in the world of medicine and written by a physician.  It's been a world wide best seller with rave reviews.  I think it's an exciting choice and I can't wait to get started.  Since it's a little longer than our normal selections, I suggest you pick it up right away so you'll be able to join us on the 24th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There were 14 of us at the September meeting.  &amp;quot;The Art of Racing in the Rain&amp;quot; provoked an even livlier discussion than I imagined.  The one point of agreement was that seeing the world from the view point of a dog added a unique quality to the book.  Aspects of the story tend to linger after you finish the book, always a good sign that a book got under your skin, for better or worse!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elaine    </member_name><member_id>7294680</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288023756000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285696112000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Brookline Book Club</name><id>14926474</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287950400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/14926474/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/9/global_12779209.jpeg</photo_url></item>