<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It is getting cold, have you noticed? Our December dinner is going to be at a new location, but we will be back at the penthouse in January.&lt;br /&gt;Meanwhile - ALL ABOARD THE POLAR EXPRESS!&lt;br /&gt;Our theme for December is the Polar Express, so choo choo yourself to the recipe files, reread the book or rent the Tom Hanks movie for inspiration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given our winter fantasy train theme it is appropriate that we are traveling to a new spot for our dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Polar Express is all about fantasy, hope, adventure and the ability to believe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most fun aspect of our group is the lack of organization so there is no need to coordinate dishes or let us know what you are bringing - unless you really really want to share. Just believe that it will all work out and it will.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us this month with your winter, travel, fantasy recipe.  Pack up the stuff you need and cook onsite.  The kitchen will be filled with people cooking and chatting, bring your imaginary ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the drill…&lt;br /&gt;Plan to assemble or cook on site unless your dish takes more than an hour to prepare. Bring any special equipment but I have standard kitchen tools and supplies.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231546639000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227316299000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes December Meetup</name><id>9209921</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229126400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/9209921/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/global_6396106.jpeg</photo_url></item>