<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>starting at Welch-Dickey Loop Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.90 mi/1 hr 45 min/+1525 ft on the Welch-Dickey Loop Trail &lt;br /&gt; In 15 yd. from the parking area, the trail forks. This description follows the counterclockwise direction, first taking the right-hand fork leading toward Welch Mountain—the ledges are steeper on this side and easier to ascend than descend for most hikers. This branch soon crosses a brook and follows its east side, then turns sharp right and angles up southeastward to reach the large, flat open ledges on the south ridge of Welch Mountain. There are fine views east across the valley to Mt. Tripyramid and Sandwich Mountain and its rocky Acteon Ridge. Then the trail climbs, steeply at times with several short scrambles, over open ledges interspersed with jack pines and dwarf birches to the ledgy summit of Welch Mountain. &lt;br /&gt; to Welch Mtn &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 1.90 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 1 hr 45 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +1595 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -70 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +1525 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.40 mi/20 min/+152 ft on the Welch-Dickey Loop Trail &lt;br /&gt; From here, the loop drops steeply to a wooded notch (use caution, staying left of the blazes along the top of the cliff), then rises, working to the left around a high rock slab. Just above the top of this slab an unmarked and obscure branch trail leads right 0.2 mi. over ledges to a fine north outlook from a large open ledge. &lt;br /&gt; to Dickey Mtn &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 2.30 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 2 hr 5 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +1861 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -184 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +1677 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list.  A yes list will be provided as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a slower pace than usual.  It will give us a chance to enjoy the foliage, take pictures, etc.  I estimate we will be done in four to five hours even at this relaxed and enjoyable pace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 2.10 mi/1 hr 4 min/-1672 ft on the Welch-Dickey Loop Trail &lt;br /&gt; The main loop continues over the partly open summit of Dickey Mountain and descends another prominent ledgy ridge to the southwest, soon angling down a large open slab that is often wet. It continues down alternately over open ledges and through patches of woods, with many outlooks, entering the woods to stay at the base of a particularly interesting ledge with an impressive dropoff . It drops over a ledge step and turns left along the base of ledgy wall, descends briefly through spruces, and continues down at a steady grade through oak woods. It turns left onto an old logging road (to the right is the Brown Ash Swamp Mountain Bike Trail, an easy route leading to beaver ponds in Dickey Notch in 0.8 mi. and the end of FR 23C in 1.7 mi.) and soon reaches the loop junction and the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 4.40 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 3 hr 9 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +1905 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -1900 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +4 ft &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1287453399000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286543399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WELCH DICKEY</name><id>15044554</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287322200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15044554/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>