<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;**NOTE: Our November Meetup is moved to the SECOND Tuesday in November.**&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************************************&lt;br /&gt;Many of us had the wonderful opportunity to join in the interactive high-content training TELE-Meetup with Michael Losier on Tues, 9/29.  Michael is an expert Law of Attraction trainer, best-seller author and radio host.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a recording of his TELE-training with us on 9/29.  We strongly recommend that you listen to this recording before you meetup with us on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.audioacrobat.com/play/WgFCRqbS" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.audioacrobat.com/play/WgFCRqbS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.audioacrob...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael informed us that the most immediate follow-up action to take after attending his training session is to take the time to sit down and work through his 3 Steps Process for Deliberate Attraction. How many of us intend to do this, yet we get caught up in the busy-ness of our lives, and we never get going on?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our October Meetup, we worked through Step 1 and part of Step 2 of &lt;b&gt;Michael Losier's three-step process for deliberate attraction&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our November meetup, we'll continue to &lt;br /&gt;- listen (via CDs* we have) of steps 2 and 3 of Michael's three-step process for deliberate attraction   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- work through worksheets and exercises, with support from each other&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Even if you've missed our October Meetup, you want to be at our November meetup.  We will be focusing on Step 3 which is all about ALLOWING - having belief that you will manifest more of what you want&lt;/b&gt;.  It's no surprise that this is the most challenging for most people.  You'll learn about&lt;br /&gt;- formulating powerful ALLOWING Statement(s) and&lt;br /&gt;- 12 Allowing Tools &lt;br /&gt;that will provide you with relief which helps remove doubt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Buck and Chew-Hoong Koh, the co-organizers of the BostonLOA Meetup, will be the facilitators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually provide handouts and have appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up.  Many of you have been wonderful with this and we very much appreciate your understanding and support!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;For &lt;b&gt;parking and directions (via T or driving)&lt;/b&gt; info to Dave's loft :&lt;br /&gt;(1) Go here:&lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/files/"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Sign in&lt;br /&gt;(3) Scroll down and open file &amp;quot;Directions &amp;amp; Parking_BostonLOA Meetup&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258143469000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>43</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254874064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Put Into Action Michael Losier's Step 2 &amp; 3: ALLOWING ( less doubt, More Belief)</name><id>hjcjdympbnb</id><headcount>44</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257897600000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/11567038/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/0/f/global_10979647.jpeg</photo_url></item>