<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>40 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.492.1557</phone><name>Algiers Coffee House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669147</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121338</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>After many discussions of novels by dead white men, we now turn to our first ever collection of short stories by woman (dead, white and Danish at that!). And what a fascinating dead white Danish woman she is, as are the stories.  To borrow one publisher's jacket copy and due hype: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In Isak Dinesen's universe, the magical enchantment of the fairy tale and the moral resonance of myth coexist with an unflinching grasp of the most obscure human strengths and weaknesses. A despairing author abandons his wife, but in the course of a long night's wandering, he learns love's true value and returns to her, only to find her a different woman than the one he left. A landowner, seeking to prove a principle, inadvertently exposes the ferocity of mother love. A wealthy young traveler melts the hauteur of a lovely woman by masquerading as her aged and loyal servant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shimmering and haunting, Dinesen's Winter's Tales transport us...to the mysterious place where all stories are born.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if the hype doesn't quite work, here is some critical praise from Eudora Welty:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dinesen's stories come toward one like the flashes...from a lighthouse on a strange and infrequently sighted coast--a coast beautiful and precarious, for it may be the last outreach of magic, but resting on bedrock.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you do read these stories and look forward to the discussion! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Arlinda&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223701320000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208835036000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter's Tales by Isak Dinesen</name><id>7786904</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210543200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/7786904/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/d/global_1496461.jpeg</photo_url></item>