<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>MEETUP IS BETWEEN 6:00 and 6:15, SEATING STARTS AT 6:30. GREG GIRALDO IS A VERY POPULAR HEADLINER, SO GET THERE EARLY! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FUNNY BONE REGULARS - PLEASE KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR THE NEW PEOPLE AND HELP THEM GET SEATED AT OUR TABLES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE SAVE ME A SEAT, I WILL BE THERE AFTER 7 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have guests coming from Dean's group -The South Windsor Newly Single or Just Single Meetup Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THANKS, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROB T&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wacky Wednesday At The Funny Bone Comedy Club&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Buckland Hills Mall&lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040&lt;br /&gt;(860)-432-8600&lt;br /&gt;www.HartfordFunnyBone.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is FREE every Wednesday Nite with a Funny Bone T-Shirt (T-Shirts cost $15)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for Our CTNites.com VIP Entertainment Club Table Signs, and Join Us For A Great Nite Of Comedy!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headliner: Greg Giraldo  &lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;Greg Giraldo is one of the hottest comics in the country. Socially provocative and yet broadly funny, Greg has become one of the most versatile and highly entertaining comics working today. Days after the recent release of his debut comedy album, Good Day to Cross a River, Greg starred in a pilot which he developed for Comedy Central. Earlier this year, he hosted The Stand Up Show with Greg Giraldo on Comedy Central and he appeared on the Comedy Central Roast of William Shatner. On past shows, Greg has roasted Pamela Anderson, Howard Stern and Jeff Foxworthy. Greg is well known from his stint as a regular panelist on Comedy Central's Tough Crowd with Colin Quinn. He regularly contributes a &amp;quot;rant&amp;quot; segment to Last Call with Carson Daly (NBC) where he provides his unique spin on current events, politics, and family life. In addition to his two half hour stand-up specials, Comedy Central Presents...Greg Giraldo, Greg also has performed on Late Show with David Letterman (CBS), and he has been a guest on Late Night with Conan O' Brien (NBC) a dozen times. In late 2004, Greg released an enormously successful song with producer LaZBoy entitled &amp;quot;Underwear Goes Inside the Pants&amp;quot; that has received a tremendous amount of airplay on both Modern rock and Top 40 radio across the country. Over his career Greg has created and starred in sitcom pilots for NBC and CBS, and was given the opportunity to develop and star in his own ABC sitcom, &amp;quot;Common Law,&amp;quot; which was loosely based on his experiences at a New York law firm. While in New York Greg is known to be a regular at Manhattan clubs--like Gotham Comedy Club and the Comedy Cellar. When he is not touring comedy clubs, colleges, theaters and corporate events, he can be found living in New York City with his wife and three young boys whom he believes to be his own. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTNites.com/Events/FunnyBone.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Click Here For Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193456262000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191518223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wacky Wednesday At The Funny Bone Comedy Club</name><id>6487651</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193264100000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6487651/</event_url></item>