<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Save the date and stay tuned for trail descriptions.  I may change this from the 23rd to the 24th, depending on the weather. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the parking area on 302, just south of the Crawford Depot info center and carpool up to the Edmands Trailhead.  We'll ascend via the Edmands Path to just below the summit of Eisenhower and then follow the Crawford Path over Mt. Pierce, past Mizpah Hut and down the Webster Cliff trail to the peak of Mt. Jackson.  From there, we will descend via the  Jackson branch of the Webster-Jackon trail.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite the moderate nature of the ascent and descent, be prepared for the alpine zone and for poor weather conditions as the Crawford Path is VERY EXPOSED.  Expect cold weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. While it is feasible to &amp;quot;get away with this&amp;quot; in summer, this can be dangerous in colder weather. October weather on the Presidentials IS COLDER. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. Bring plenty of water - sources on this route are scarce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views, SO if the weather looks like it will be better or clearer on Sunday, I will reschedule for Sunday instead. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/b&gt;  This is a dog friendly hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), I will not wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book time is about 9 hrs,  10 miles. Plan on it taking this long, maybe a little less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit &lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edmands Path (to Mt. Eisenhower Summit via the Eisenhower Loop)&lt;br /&gt;3.3 miles&lt;br /&gt;3 hrs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt Eisenhower Loop (from the Summit to the Crawford Path)&lt;br /&gt;.3 miles&lt;br /&gt;20 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crawford Path (from S. End of the Eisenhower Loop to Webster Cliff Trail)&lt;br /&gt;1.2 miles&lt;br /&gt;45 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Webster Cliff Trail (from Crawford Path to Summit of Jackson)&lt;br /&gt;2.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;2hr 25 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Descent Via Webster-Jackson Trail from the Summit of Jackson&lt;br /&gt;2.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;2 hr 25 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;--------&lt;br /&gt;10 miles&lt;br /&gt;9 hrs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288045869000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284930921000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eisenhower, Pierce, Jackson Traverse</name><id>14824436</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287835200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14824436/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>