<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join me for a &amp;quot;FREE&amp;quot; Comedy Show at Nicks. I had recently  won up to 30 &amp;quot;FREE&amp;quot; tickets on friday evening September 25th, 09 and thought this would be a fun idea for our group. It's a trendy cool fun place to hear three funny semi famous comedians.   &lt;br /&gt;Let's meet right outside in front of Nicks at 7:45 PM sharp and we will enter in as a group at 7:55 PM. Please note that this WILL be a free event if you enter in the comedy club with myself as a group, however if you do show up late, there is a slight chance you may have to pay the 30.00 which is normally the admission cost, so PLEASE PLEASE don't be late. Please do bring some cash to purchase drinks during the show as there will be a cash bar available. &lt;br /&gt;There are many parking garages near by if you are coming by car, or if you are coming by &amp;quot;T&amp;quot;, I believe it's the orange line, however please contact the &amp;quot;T&amp;quot; for more information on that.         &lt;br /&gt;Please note to RSVP by thursday  September 24, 09 as I do have to call and make the reservation for the final count. If RSVP'ing a &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;, PLEASE be 90 percent certain you are able to attend. If the event is full, please write a note in the &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; section saying you are inetrested and I will let you know if a space opens up.    &lt;br /&gt;Also, lastly IF there is interest, after the show is over, we can walk down to McCormick and Schmidts for some late night appetizers, however OF COURSE THIS WILL be optional as always. McCormicks had a great late night appetizer menu as one of my personal favorites is the artichoke and cheese dip. &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there!!!&lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;Krista- ast organizer Cambridge Singles&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside Nicks entrance. I will have my balloon/red meet up t shirt on</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krista</member_name><member_id>3604506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256245919000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1958</urlname><id>1096649</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge and Boston Singles Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253317524000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Free Comedy Show at Nicks Comedy Stop!!!!! </name><id>11409522</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253922300000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1958/events/11409522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/8/global_3699192.jpeg</photo_url></item>