<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>84 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.355781</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 635-2120</phone><name>Boston Common Frog Pond</name><city>Boston</city><id>848668</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071254</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join me for ice skating on the Frog Pond after work. The Boston Skating Meetup will be joining us too.  (I've run this event every year I've been an organizer except last year.) On Tuesdays admission is $2.00 with a valid student I.D. Otherwise it's $5.00 admission and a $9.00 ice skate rental fee. There's a Groupon deal at this link &lt;a href="http://www.groupon.com/deals/boston-common-frog-pond"&gt;http://www.groupon.com/deals/boston-common-frog-pond&lt;/a&gt; and a Yipit deal at &lt;a href="http://yipit.com/business/the-boston-common-frog-pond/"&gt;http://yipit.com/business/the-boston-common-frog-pond/&lt;/a&gt;. There are other deals out there too if you search and find a good one, post it below. We'll probably skate for 60-90 minutes depending on the cold.  In the past I've had trouble getting people off the ice because they were having so much fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards we'll grab some dinner in Chinatown. Each time I've run this event we've eaten at Chau Chow City, but I'm open to other places in Chinatown that people want to suggest. Chau Chow City has lots of food options and a large seating area to fit us so keep that in mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get to the Frog Pond by taking the Green or Red Line to Park Street Station. You can also drive and park around the Public Gardens. The meters run until 8:00 and have a 2-hour limit so if you park at 6:00 and feed the meter you'll be set for the night and the event starts at 6:15. We'll meet by the Frog Statues. Most likely I'll be wearing my white jacket and red hat and scarf, but I will send out an email the morning of the event day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is weather dependent. If it's really cold or snowing, I will cancel, but may still continue with dinner for those intersted. Let me know if you have any questions and as always if your plans change please update your RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dee&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be by the Frog Statues near the playground at the entrance, look for my white jacket and red hat and scarf</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358475808000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356972992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frog Pond Ice Skating &amp; Dinner in Chinatown</name><id>97199882</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358291700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/97199882/</event_url></item>