<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Allison St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.191335</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>223-0335</phone><name>Liberty Books</name><city>Concord</city><id>682917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.538397</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our monthly Concord video screening is on the 3rd Tuesday every month. We've picked something new this month that is not about 9/11, but about another false-flag terror event - you may be convinced of that by the time you get to the end of this month's movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://freemindfilms.com/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;a href="http://freemindfilms.com/"&gt;A Noble Lie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/4/6/event_86684102.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Noble Lie: A myth or untruth knowingly told by the elite to maintain social harmony, or the social position of the elite. &amp;ndash; The Republic, Plato.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 1995 bombing in Oklahoma City was a direct blow to the heart of America. 168 people were killed, including nineteen children.&amp;nbsp; For those watching the nightly news, Terrorism had come home. For years following the bombing, countless victims&amp;rsquo; family members, survivors, rescuers, and ordinary Americans, have questioned the official accounts about that fateful day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hoping to shed light on answers long ignored and censored, both by prominent media outlets and the U.S. government, A Noble Lie peels back what we thought we knew about the bombing and it&amp;rsquo;s perpetrators. This film exposes information never before examined or brought to the attention of the American public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Noble Lie is the culmination of years of research and documentation conducted by independent journalists, scholars, and ordinary citizens. Often risking their personal safety and sanity, they have gathered evidence which threatens to expose the startling reality of what exactly occurred at 9:02 am on April 19, 1995 in Oklahoma City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Utilizing footage and eyewitness testimony, previously unseen, A Noble Lie will change forever the way you look at the true nature of terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please arrive at Liberty Books at 6:30 or after and we'll begin the film screening at 7:00 with a discussion following the film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a snack to share with others, and a donation of a box of tea for our host would be appreciated. It'll help build his inventory and ease the financial burden on him.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the meeting room in the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326909068000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326221574000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concord - A Noble Lie</name><id>qmrgdcyqcbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326843000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/47525212/</event_url></item>