<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374425</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-6789</phone><name>Cambridge Center for Adult Education, Blacksmith House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>713846</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121899</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let me ask you something...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you freeze up and not know what to do when someone verbally attacks you?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you get angry later on because you didn't stand up for yourself, and then beat yourself up for it for hours after the event has passed?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have you ever felt helpless and unsure of what to do when someone makes a snippy or passive aggressive comment to you in front of others?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have you ever felt the embarrassment of somebody poking fun at you and having fun at your expense, and you wish you knew what to do about it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you answered &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to any of these questions, then this workshop is perfect for you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;In this fun and interactive event, you'll learn proven techniques for quickly disarming someone who is being snippy, rude, or flat out verbally abusive toward you.  And you can do it without getting angry, without making the other person angry, and without feeling embarrassed or awkward.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My #1 technique that automatically dissolves an attack.  Once you master this, you'll be surprised at how easy it is to quickly disarm anyone.  An interesting side effect is that this technique instantly discourages them from ever attacking you again.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The #1 mistake people make when dealing with a verbal attack that practically &lt;i&gt;forces&lt;/i&gt; the attacker to become even more of a jerk.  We often think this will stop the attack, but it almost always makes it worse.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The surprising truth about what compels people to attack you, and how to instantly put a stop to it.  And the crazy part is... the other person might not want to attack you, but they will feel compelled to if you're doing &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple technique will compel the attacker to do a full 180 degree turn and start treating you as if you are their friend.  It still boggles my mind when I see how well this works!&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members.  We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 25 people due to the size limitations of the classroom (this is an interactive seminar and we'll be moving around a lot).  Our meetings often fill up quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, November 7th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289680742000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288475448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Gentle Art of Verbal Self-Defense</name><id>15281649</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289161800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/15281649/</event_url></item>