<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>MDG January 2011 Forum: Accelerating New Technology, Minimizing Time To Market – Here’s How&lt;br /&gt;When:              Wednesday, January 5, at 5:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             1000 Winter Street&lt;br /&gt;                        Foley Hoag Emerging Enterprise Center&lt;br /&gt;                        Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;Register:&lt;a href="http://web.memberclicks.com/mc/community/eventdetails.do?eventId=288184&amp;amp;orgId=meg&amp;amp;recurringId=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.memberclic...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The sizable investments in new technologies and inherent solutions to clinical applications present medical device manufacturers with a dynamic need to get to market quickly and effectively. To exist, then to prosper, medical device companies must get a return on their new initiatives by satisfying customers. No simple task. Come join us this Forum to absorb the lessons of an accomplished market leading medical device company taking a leading edge technology - product and procedure, to market in ‘real time.’ In this Medical Development Group Forum program, Hologic Corporation, focused on women’s health, will present a case history depicting how it moved forward on a new opportunity. Acquisition of the technology, regulatory development and clinical trials, identification of its market and the introduction of the new product, which is in progress, speak to the challenge facing medical device companies in today’s market.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294322218000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292990078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MDG January 2011 Forum: Accelerating New Technology, Minimizing Time To Market</name><id>15796105</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294266600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15796105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>