<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Cloverleaf Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06812</zip><lat>41.484985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203 746 2240 </phone><name>Bruce &amp; Deb's House</name><city>New Fairfield</city><id>979077</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.515269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Short version: for those who hate to read all this stuff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween Costume Party at Bruce &amp;amp; Deb's place. &lt;br /&gt;BYO Booze, Food, Music &lt;br /&gt;Party Starts at 10/31/09 at 7PM &lt;br /&gt;Buffet put out as guest arrive &lt;br /&gt;Parking: Pull up front door, unload, drive out and find parking &lt;br /&gt;Kids welcome and can trick or treat the neighborhood &lt;br /&gt;No Drugs of any kind &lt;br /&gt;You must leave sober: Either have a designated driver or stay over &lt;br /&gt;Costume prizes &lt;br /&gt;Bring friends&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The LONG Version:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The party is at Bruce &amp;amp; Deb's house. This is a special invite to all our friends, their friends &amp;amp; members of all of our closely knit groups, Plus the throngs of our enemies, And anyone else who knows anyone either as an acquaintance, club member or in the biblical sense. As a mater of fact, this party will be of biblical proportions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It starts on Saturday, Oct 31, Halloween and runs till we kick everyone out. &lt;br /&gt;Party Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sat Oct 31. &lt;br /&gt;Arrive around 7 PM. Stay as long as you like or till we throw you out. If you drink too much you will not be permitted to dive. You must leave with someone else in the drivers seat or stay over. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ANYONE WISHING TO HELP OUT Contact us ASAP. Thanks &lt;br /&gt;Bruce &amp;amp; Deb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BYOE (Everything) Bottles of booze, a delicious dish for all to enjoy, Music etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffet dinner starts at about 7 PM in the Dining room, eat and drink and be merry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've got Karaoke CDs, bring em. We have 12,000 songs in our music library but Just in case, bring your own favorites in either CD format or iPod, 33, 45 or 78 RPM. Records. (sorry but our 8 track is broken)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be prizes for Best Costume, most original costume. funniest looking without a costume. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always ABSOLUTELY NO DRUGS, PERIOD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've got lots of advance notice. Come and be with us as we celebrate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING Send us what your best dish is in an email or in your RSVP and we'll add it to the list so others will know what to expect. We'll post it on the event calendar of Amazing Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggestions: 3 to 5 pound lobsters, Filet Mignon, Beluga Caviar. Truffles, &amp;quot;Pâté de foie gras&amp;quot; Extra handsome, smart, wealthy, educated men. (always in short supply so BRING MEN)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If You're like the us and rest of the world and in this economy you can bring Pasta, Burgers, Dogs, Caserole, Shrimp, Ribs, Salads, Chicken dishes, Deviled eggs or your own favorite speciality.. desserts, You name it, we'll all eat it. If you're staying over, eggs, bacon, ham etc. &lt;br /&gt;(bring extra men that are at least breathing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are lots of other parties that night. Make the rounds. But we warn you. Once you get here, you won't want to leave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you are in wittiness protection or on the lamb, the party will be video recorded. Persons with ankle bracelets should note that there is no cell service at our place, you should notify the authorities accordingly. Persons with heart conditions, lack of self esteem, anxiety and depression, please leave all that at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the cars parked 1/2 mile down the road...lol! Come early!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257203472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252080345000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HALLOWEEN PARTY AT BRUCE &amp; DEB'S place!!!</name><id>11289697</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257030000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11289697/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/f/global_10537455.jpeg</photo_url></item>