<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-225-0888</phone><name>Tommy Doyle's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>835734</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE: Check this page before the meetup as the venue might change!! &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This should be a famliar book to everyone, but just in case you haven't heard Sam Harris released a book last year and even came to Harvard to discuss it last fall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book, "Moral Landscape", explores the idea that science might in fact have something to say about morality. Of course a few assumptions must be made about what morality attempts to achieve, but the case is made once you set off from there. At the very least the book makes one think about morality in a way that actually places it into a context of analyzing and understanding the principles behind it. At best, the book seems to make a case that the only reason we haven't attempted to model and scientifically explore morality has more to do with our desire to mystify it - not because it can't be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is the the underlying function of moraity is to minimize suffering in the world? Can there be such a thing as the science of moraility? Could the future of machine learning and artificial intelligence be intertwined with the future of Moral thinking? Let's discuss these things and more. I have a few ideas of my own...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boston Atheists Table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303059673000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298829348000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book &amp; Brew (Sam Harris - Moral Landscape)</name><id>ggwnqypgbvb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302991200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/16723745/</event_url></item>