<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>South Main St (Rt-27)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.243397</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rocky Narrows</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1417895</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.370562</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/f/c/event_3464284.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Rocky Narrows 227 acres Views of the Charles River at its most serene as it slowly winds between granite walls. Or amble among pine groves and past wetlands along seven miles of trails and footpaths. The reservation&amp;rsquo;s blend of mixed forest and wetlands make for varied, and memorable, experiences. The reservation &amp;ndash; The Trustees&amp;rsquo; first &amp;ndash; showcases the Charles River at its best: a pastoral stream slowly moving between ancient cliff walls and steeply wooded hillsides. A mixed forest of hardwoods and evergreens once again blanket a landscape cleared long ago for farming, and the 50-foot rock walls that form the Narrows themselves date back 650 million years. On foot we can walk across miles of carriage roads and footpaths through rocky uplands and resurgent forest. A two-mile hike follows the river&amp;rsquo;s edge south before reaching successive overlooks. Rocky Narrows Overlook takes some effort to reach, but you&amp;rsquo;ll be rewarded with views of steep, hemlock covered cliffs that form a narrow river passage &amp;ndash; the landmark that gives the reservation its name. Further south along the trail is a granite bluff that bears the name King Philip, the Wampanoag chief who warred against the early settlers of the Massachusetts Bay Colony. From King Philip&amp;rsquo;s Overlook (in Sherborn Town Forest), visitors can view the marshes of Medfield and Millis, with Noon Hill on the distant horizon. If the forests, wetlands, and riverbanks you explore here seem larger than 227 acres, that&amp;rsquo;s because they are: Rocky Narrows brackets the Sherborn Town Forest on three sides. This successful model of public/private land conservation has resulted in almost 400 suburban acres protected from development. There are 7 miles of trails, including those that pass through the adjacent 150-acre Sherborn Town Forest. Moderate hiking, strenuous in places. The property is a link in the Bay Circuit Trail. DIRECTIONS: From Points North: I-95/Rt. 128 South to Exit 21A. Follow Rt. 16 East to Rt. 135 West. In Sherborn, turn left onto Rt. 27 South to 2 mi. to entrance on right. From Points South: I-95/Rt. 128 North to Ext 16B. Follow Rt. 109 West 8 mi. towards Westwood. Turn right onto Rt. 27 North for 3.5 mi. to entrance and parking (strict 6-car limit) on right. Alternate parking (recommended) on Forest St. off Snow St. at northern edge of property (6 cars). On-street parking is not permitted.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My vehicle: red jeep with big wheels</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6025746</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316362660000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Subnats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>science-88</urlname><id>1005141</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Suburban Naturalists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316112887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rocky Narrows (Sherborn)</name><id>33701172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316358000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/science-88/events/33701172/</event_url></item>