<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Asbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.636799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-887-5931</phone><name>Bradley Palmer State Park</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>694190</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.908096</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #1b2615 ; font-size : small"&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s spend an afternoon walking the trails of Bradley Palmer State Park! This 721-acre former estate features pine needled paths, acres of rolling meadows and spectacular rhododendrons which line old carriage roads. I do not know the trails here at all, so Scott from Social Fun will be my "copilot" guide for the day! We may encounter hills or some inclines, as well as rocks or roots to step around, but many of the trails are well worn old carriage trails I believe, so this should still fall under the "not too intense" hiker category :)&amp;nbsp; We&amp;rsquo;ll aim for 6-8 miles of walking (up to 3 hours, but probably covering 3 miles an hour or so), and then afterwards, anyone interested can head into to town to rehydrate and refuel with pizza and beers at (the locally legendary) Riverview (I think they open after 4 PM). &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This meetup will be weather permitting, and any necessary cancellation will be made by 8 AM the morning of. I&amp;rsquo;ll be bringing my dog, so other friendly dogs on leashes are welcomed also (please bring bags to pick up after your pooch). Bring bug spray/sunscreen, water, snacks, comfortable walking shoes or hiking boots, and a walking pole if you&amp;rsquo;d like.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This meetup was initially posted with Social Fun, but there have been some&amp;nbsp;cancellations there, so I'd like to open&amp;nbsp;8 of those spots up to this group.&amp;nbsp; Hope you'll join us!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We’ll meet in the first parking lot as you take a right after passing through the main entrance (off Asbury St.).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marilee </member_name><member_id>6596076</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1305554598000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>It's springtime...why SHOULDN'T we get out and have some fun and exercise?</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305163663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Bradley Palmer followed by dinner at Riverview Pizza</name><id>18064691</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305399600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/18064691/</event_url></item>