<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi, Sorry for the late posting. I'll  be at  Panera's Bread, directly across the street from The Coolidge Corner Theater, at 6 pm so we can get together before the film- look for a bright red Meetup sign at one of the tables. &lt;b&gt;The Man in the White Suit&lt;/b&gt; starts at 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Man in the White Suit&lt;/b&gt;  is one of the  great comedies  produced in England by Ealing Studios (The Ladykillers, The Lavender Hill Mob, etc.) starring Alec Guiness (!) during the 1950's . The film is only 82 minutes long and so even with the two guest speakers, it won't be that late of a night. For those keeping score at home, &lt;b&gt;The Man in the White Suit&lt;/b&gt; has a 100% Rotten Tomatoes score.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's link to the trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ri3JpPvplg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Science On Screen, Coolidge Corner Theater presents a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting introductions by noted scientists in a related field. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guest speakers for this event are Marc Abrahams (The Annals of Improbable Research and The Ig Nobel Prizes) and chemist Daniel Rosenberg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alec Guinness delivers one of his most beloved performances in this smart satirical comedy that pits a mild-mannered but single minded inventor against the forces of Britain's textile industry. Sidney Stratton (Guinness) is a brilliant if under appreciated research chemist on a quest to bring progress to mankind by inventing a new kind of fabric that never gets dirty and never wears out. When he finally succeeds, he is hailed a genius. But both textile manufacturers and labor unions soon come to realize that his miracle cloth could destroy their industry, and resort to desperate measures to make sure his invention never gets to market. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are Sidney Strattons everywhere—researchers and inventors who go to incredible lengths to pursue wild and often wonderful ideas, many of which the public never hears about. But guest speaker Marc Abrahams thinks we should know about the Strattons of the world and the challenges and pressures they face. In addition to being the co-founder and editor of the Annals of Improbable Research, a science humor magazine that showcases real research being done on strange or unexpected topics, Abrahams is the originator and emcee of the annual Ig Nobel Prizes, honoring unbelievable-but-true achievements that first make us laugh and then make us think. Those achievements include the development of a self-perfuming suit, which Abrahams will wear in honor of his Science on Screen appearance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Abrahams will be joined by Harvard chemist Daniel Rosenberg, who will address a key question, especially for those of us prone to spillage: Is it possible to create clothing that never gets dirty and never wears out? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The most exciting phrase to hear in science, the one that heralds new discoveries, is not 'Eureka!' but, 'That's funny...’&amp;quot; - Isaac Asimov &lt;br /&gt;Coolidge Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be at Panera's at 6pm- look for the bright red meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283554773000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science on Screen: British Comedy-The Man in the White Suit</name><id>14650444</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283810400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14650444/</event_url></item>