<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.406082</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781) 648-4340</phone><name>Capitol Theater</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Given the bad weather and lack of parking in Arlington due to Snow Emergency, the meetup has been cancelled.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After watching Ghajni &amp;amp; RNBDJ I think we are due for a silly comedy. Plus it is a long weekend for some of us and a comedy is a best way to spend the sunday afternoon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring - Akshay Kumar, Deepika Padukone, Ranvir Shorey, Mithun Chakraborty, Gordon Liu, Roger Yuan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sypnosis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chandni Chowk To China, the first ever Bollywood Kungfu comedy takes you on a madcap Journey from the by-lanes of Chandni Chowk in Delhi, to Shanghai, the Great Wall and rural China, marrying in its wake hilarious gags, breathtaking action, spectacular locations, and heart stirring emotions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our protagonist Sidhu (Akshay Kumar) is the lowest on the totem pole, cutting vegetables at a roadside food stall in Chandni Chowk in Delhi. He longs to escape his dreary existence and looks for shortcuts- with astrologers, tarot readers and fake fakirs - believing anything except himself, despite his father figure Dada's (Mithun Chakraborty) best efforts. His redeeming moment arrives when two strangers from China claim him as a reincarnation of a war hero in the past and takes him to China. Sidhu now dreams of wine, women, and a princely existence in foreign lands. Thanks to the devious translator, a conman by the name Chopstick (Ranvir Shorey), little does he know that he is being taken to the Promised Land to rid the Chinese village of the vicious smuggler Hojo (Gordon Liu)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, Sidhu blissfully sets forth to China with Chopstick who instigates dreams of a delicious future and forgets to reveal the perils, which await him. Along the way, he meets Sakhi (Deepika Padukone), Ms. Tele Shoppers Media (Ms. TSM) who has embarked on a journey to pay homage to the land of her birth and her dead father and twin. Initially, Sidhu through a series of lucky coincidences manages to sidestep being beaten by Hojo's men but finally Hojo catches up with him and exposes him as the country buffoon that he really is. Sidhu has the fire of revenge in his belly and finds the one man who will make him a Kungfu expert and set the village free. Armed with his Sifu (master), faith in himself and the love of the fair Sakhi, Sidhu sets forth to conquer all!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My cell is 5083147742. We can meet in the lobby of the cinema at 12:15</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232845153000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231472989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bollywood Movie - Chandni Chowk To China - Cancelled</name><id>9482649</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232299800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/9482649/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/9/global_4274761.jpeg</photo_url></item>