<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone - our very own Kim K creates some really fabulous artwork (some of which can be seen at www.kimsconcretedreams.com).  She has graciously decided to open up her home/studio in Middletown so that we can all enjoy it from 1pm-5pm (or so?.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;**UPDATE** At 1pm on Friday, I emailed everyone who said 'maybe' or 'yes' with Kim's address.  If you RSVP after this time, please email me to ensure that I send you the address.  Thanks! dev &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Kim:  &amp;quot;After several requests and a bit of pondering, I am staying home on a Sunday in June to open my studio for the curious and brave to come and see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, for all the garden junkies, my neighbors on either side of me will open their gardens for touring. One neighbor, (my mom) Helen, has a very eclectic and ever expanding garden with many fascinating plantings. The other neighbor, Ellie, has a garden with many earth friendly features and native plantings.  Ellie has also developed a very interesting spiral garden to walk with the story of the universe.   ??and I??.will have beer and a grill in my front yard &amp;quot;kinda sort of&amp;quot; outdoor gallery of concrete art?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All are welcome and encouraged to come with or without fathers,  family and friends?.and perhaps, but not necessary, something to add to the festivities?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!  Kim&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address will be sent within a few days of the event to those who RSVP 'yes' or 'maybe'.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213752742000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212326484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kim's Concrete Dreams Open Studio? and a bit of a party</name><id>8053451</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213549200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8053451/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/a/global_4311226.jpeg</photo_url></item>