<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Not hiking related really but a volunteer opportunity for our members. This is an opportunity to help out with remodeling, construction, &amp;amp; in some cases landscaping projects for elderly &amp;amp; disabled people in our communities. Each HomeFront Day is car­ried out by thou­sands of vol­un­teers who rep­re­sent cor­por­ations, busi­nesses, faith-based organ­iza­tions &amp;amp; civic groups coming to­gether as a com­munity to assist neigh­bors in need. I've volunteered the past couple of years for this annual event &amp;amp; this year's AmeriCares HomeFront project will be on Saturday May 3rd, from 7:30 am until 5:00pm. &lt;b&gt;I will post the location of the event &amp;amp; info about the project &amp;amp; the needs that we want to fill, as we get closer to the date.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Directions e-mailed to Yes/Maybe RSVP's, team change 4/30/08***&lt;br /&gt;We are now assigned to a crew &lt;b&gt;Team Bianchi-Gauthier&lt;/b&gt; in Enfield &amp;amp; any overflow to &lt;b&gt;Team Bianchi-Katsavage&lt;/b&gt; 7.7 miles away. I'll have direction slips from the first site to the second, if needed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, when you arrive at the workplace you must register, sign an insurance form, &amp;amp; get a HomeFront tee shirt before you can work. You must wear your tee shirt while working; no one is allowed to remain at the site or enter the premises if not wearing the tee shirt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coffee and donuts are provided in the morning. Lunch is also provided &amp;amp; snacks &amp;amp; cold drinks are available all day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;House Co-Captains (in charge of work and site):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Buchholz, cell 860-604-3288&lt;br /&gt;Bill King&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Closed to new RSVP's 4/29/08 ***&lt;br /&gt;I have to update the report of the crew we have to the Volunteer Coordinator for work assignments. Thanks all for signing up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Detail information added 4/25/08 ***&lt;br /&gt;We will be renovating 5 Enfield homes this year. One home is that of an elderly widow with a handicapped daughter; 2 others belong to single mothers who each have a handicapped child; the remaining 2 homes are those of elderly widows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The team we will be joining is the one I've worked with the couple years (address is only team host's address/phone, not work location):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;St. Patrick's HomeFront Team&lt;br /&gt;64 Pearl St.&lt;br /&gt;Enfield, CT 06082&lt;br /&gt;(860) 745-2411&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Gallagher&lt;br /&gt;Volunteer Coordinator&lt;br /&gt;(860) 745-9556&lt;br /&gt;******&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are starting work at 7:30 AM. When you arrive, please sign-in, sign the liability waiver, &amp;amp; grab your tee shirt. Every member working must be wearing an AmeriCares HomeFront tee shirt throughout the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be aware that you will need to wear sturdy shoes, and clothing you don't mind getting dirty in. Bring work gloves, hand-tools, ladders, and rakes, shovels, etc, if you have them. Please make sure to put your name on your tools so you get them back at the end of the day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please know that if you cannot contribute the full day to this proejct, it is quite ok to come for part of the day&lt;/b&gt;... That is perfectly ok and understandable... So... if you can only participate for a portion of the day, please indicate in your RSVP when you can get there, ie. full day, morning only, afternoon only, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can find out more about Americares Homefront at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americareshomefront.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americares...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General individual volunteer information is at (&lt;b&gt;you don't need any to do any of the forms, just show up at the event and you can sign in there and start helping out!&lt;/b&gt;):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americareshomefront.org/volunteer/individuals.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americares...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 1988, AmeriCares HomeFront is a community based volunteer home repair program that helps homeowners who are physically or financially unable to maintain their properties. AmeriCares HomeFront Day takes place during the first weekend of May, when teams of &amp;quot;hands-on&amp;quot; volunteers representing businesses, civic groups and faith-based organizations complete necessary repairs at no cost to homeowners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other Meetups I know who are doing the Day you might want to join in with if they are closer to you:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap Eats... and other foodie delights of Westchester (NY)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://diningout.meetup.com/219/calendar/7515859/"&gt;http://diningout.meet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be working with *Team Bianchi-Gauthier* in Enfield. Directions for the actual address have been e-mailed to Yes/Maybe RSVP's 4/30/08. Any questions, please give me a call (Cell # in my RSVP).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209987579000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>To help those who need a helping hand!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208574188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Americares HomeFront Day -E. Windsor/Enfield, CT  Area</name><id>7767624</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209814200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7767624/</event_url></item>