<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Nanotechnology - Timing is Everything : Knowing When To Start Commercializing Academic Research Projects.&lt;br /&gt;Register Online &lt;a href="http://theentretechforum.camp7.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://theentretechfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The recent and rapid development of Nanotechnology is poised to be one of the most significant developments in science of the emerging century.  As a class of technology, it is unusally cross-disciplinary.  Current applications in advanced sensor, diagnostic and materials technologies merely hint at many thousands of potential future uses.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metro-Boston's tech-oriented university infrastructure has pioneered and powered the development of advanced nanotech research locally, but it is in the commercial applications derived from that research that nanotech's future promise resides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The EntreTech Forum's December 16th panel focuses on Nanotech commercialization, and brings together some of the region's nanotech thought leaders to help the audience outline the present and future of nanotechnology, with particular interest in the supporting role player by the region's academic infrastructure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Professor Ahmed Busnaina, Northeastern University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ahmed A. Busnaina, PhD, is the William Lincoln Smith Chair Professor and Director of the NSF Nanoscale Science and Engineering Center (NSEC) for High-Rate Nanomanufacturing and the NSF Center for Nano and Microcontamination Control at Northeastern University. He is internationally recognized for his work on nano- and micro-scale defects mitigation and removal in semiconductor fabrication. He is also involved in the fabrication of nanoscale wires, structures, and interconnects. He specializes in directed assembly of nanoelements (such as nanotubes and nanoparticles), and in the fabrication of micro- and nano-scale structures. He is a prolific and award-winning author, teacher and researcher with strong links to industry. Prof. Busnaina earned his PhD from Oklahoma State University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;F. Mark Modzelewski is a technology entrepreneur, investor and pundit, and has been an early proponent of commercial nanotech applications. Mr. Modzelewski is currently involved in co-founding and developing new technology companies and was recently involved in the launch of microbial fuel cell company Trophos Energy. He is also leading efforts to launch the Water Innovations Alliance and stealth water technology company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Modzelewski’s career has crossed both private and public sectors, and today he is a member of the Nanotechnology Technical Advisory Group to the President’s Council of Advisers on Science and Technology (PCAST), Water Innovations Alliance, Health 2.0 Northeast and the University of Texas Technology Commercialization Committee..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Modzelewski earned a B.F.A in Painting from Boston University and a J.D. from University of Denver College of Law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Invited Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Brent Segal – Chief Technologist at Lockheed Martin Nanosystems&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Brent M. Segal was Co-founder and Chief Operating Officer of Nantero, a leading Nanotechnology company where he oversees operations roles focusing on partnerships, involving companies such as LSI Logic, BAE Systems and ASM Lithography. He assists Nantero with intellectual property management and government programs involving the Navy and various agencies. Nantero was recently sold to Lockheed Martin. Dr. Segal sits on the Board of Directors of Coretomic, of Burlington, Vermont and ENS Biopolymer, Inc of Cambridge, Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Segal is a highly cited author in leading nanotechnology-oriented publications and is a leader and active member of several regional nanotech community organizations. He is frequently invited to speak at conferences and seminars on the topic of nanotechnology intellectual property creation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter L. Antoinette: Co-founder, President &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer – Nanocomp Technologies, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Antoinette has more than 25 years experience in sales, marketing, and executive business management initially in Fortune 500 corporations and more recently in small companies and start-ups. Prior to co-founding Nanocomp Technologies, Peter was the President, Chief Executive Officer and Director of Cambridge Research &amp;amp; Instrumentation Inc., a Massachusetts based early stage liquid crystal technology company. As its first business CEO, he transformed a decade old, family owned, “R&amp;amp;D/SBIR shop” into a vibrant hi-tech company, commercializing major new products that positioned the company in high-value telecommunications, photonics, and research markets. Under his management he raised several rounds of investment capital, with dramatic step-ups in shareholder value, quadrupled orders, and grew the company from 12 to 60 employees in three years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nano Frontiers Newsletter:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nanotechproject.org/process/assets/files/7045/nanofrontiers3energy.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nanotechpr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trips to the Nanofrontier (5 podcast series from the Project on Emerging Nanotechnologies)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.penmedia.org/podcast/nano/Podcast/Podcast.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.penmedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232494813000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225197883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nanotechnology - Timing Is Everything</name><id>9046375</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229470200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/9046375/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_4560057.jpeg</photo_url></item>