<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group is bringing back Fit Camp!  Join fellow SSFMG Members and Guests for our first Indoor Fit Camp!  You have been asking for it and here it is!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Fit Camp is for every fitness level.  Whether you're a beginner or advanced there's always a way to modify an exercise or movement to fit your level of fitness.  This Fit Camp will be tailored to our Group based on the Poll results (vote now), fitness levels of participants and general overall health, fitness and well-being of those attending this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The session is 45-50 minutes in length and will be a combination of stretching, upper body, lower body, cardio and more!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Fit Camp will be led by Kathy Jordan (&amp;quot;KJ&amp;quot;) of Body Transformation By KJ, Licensed, Registered Dietitian, Certified Personal Trainer, and Certified Weight Loss and Fitness Coach.  Learn more about Kathy Jordan by visiting her website @ www.bodybykj.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please fill out a Medical History form which is in the Files Section.  You can email it directly to Kathy Jordan (Subject Line: SSFMG Fit Camp) or bring it with you that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indoor Fit Camp!&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 14th @ 10am&lt;br /&gt;Upham Room&lt;br /&gt;294 Pleasant Street&lt;br /&gt;Lower Level&lt;br /&gt;Stoughton, MA 02702&lt;br /&gt;W: www.bodybykj.com&lt;br /&gt;P: To be emailed to Yes RSVPs shortly after the RSVP Deadline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 6 participants including Orgs by 4pm on Tuesday, November 10th.  Max of 15 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $18pp/$15pp if at least 8 people - This includes the cost of the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: All Group Members - FREE, All Guests - $2pp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 5pm on Friday, November 13th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: This event is taking place indoors - rain, s---, or shine.  If s--- is forecast we will update with any changes around the RSVP Deadline.  All Yes RSVPs will be emailed with an update as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;294 Pleasant Street is a yellow building w/ the address listed on the sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 24:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 139 West toward Stoughton Center.&lt;br /&gt;Once you pass through the intersection of Central Street (which would tkae you to Route 138), 294 Pleasant Street is about 1 mile on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you reach Stoughton Center you have gone too far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Upham Room is on the lower level.  Enter through either door of the parking lot and it's at the end of the hall tucked away around a corner.  We will have a couple of signs posted to help you find the room.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the room.  There's a waiting area off the room and another sitting area before the room.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258415445000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256335312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indoor Fit Camp!</name><id>11696799</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258210800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11696799/</event_url></item>