<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>please contact revchristine@centersoflight.org to get the full address</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Cambridge - Close to Alewife</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10409462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/a/4/event_181696292.jpeg" width="186" height="130" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join us on December 1st to an enlightening evening with the viewing and discussion of the movie &lt;em&gt;"Where do we go Now"&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in a remote village where the church and the mosque stand side by side, this film follows the antics of the town’s women to keep their men from starting a religious war. Women heartsick over sons, husbands and fathers lost to previous flare-ups unite to distract their men with clever ruses and the unexpected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The donations accepted at this screening will be given to United Religions Initiative whose purpose is to promote enduring, daily interfaith cooperation, to end religiously motivated violence and to create cultures of peace, justice and healing for the Earth and all living beings. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Official Trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Te9c2jReOg" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Te9c2jReOg&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Official Website:  &lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/wheredowegonow/main.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.sonyclassics.com/wheredowegonow/main.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, Rev Christine will guide us through a short meditation and we will have an open discussion where we can all share our experiences in regards to the movie and the meditation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The place is easily accessible by car or public transportation. Please note that the place can only fit a limited amount of people,  so if you're interested in coming, please RSVP to the meetup and also send an email to Rev Christine to confirm. You will then receive the address of the meetup. I will also ask all of you that if after confirming, your schedule changes and you can't make it anymore, please let me know so I can give your spot to someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354417741000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353430535000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie - Where Do We Go Now?</name><id>92180382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354406400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/92180382/</event_url></item>