<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-990-7411</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213795</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It's also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people! These events are free, and if you would like to give a donation, we will send it to an organization that's truly helping the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The September Conscious Movie is Big Bucks, Big Pharma and all donations will be in support of the famine in Somalia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Bucks, Big Pharma which pulls back the curtain on the multi-billion dollar pharmaceutical industry to expose the insidious ways that illness is used, manipulated, and in some instances created, for capital gain. Focusing on the industry's marketing practices, media scholars and health professionals help viewers understand the ways in which direct-to-consumer (DTC) pharmaceutical advertising glamorizes and normalizes the use of prescription medication, and works in tandem with promotion to doctors. Combined, these industry practices shape how both patients and doctors understand and relate to disease and treatment. Ultimately, "Big Bucks, Big Pharma" challenges us to ask important questions about the consequences of relying on a for-profit industry for our health and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316909631000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315590613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie - Big Bucks Big Pharma</name><id>32907512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316905200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/32907512/</event_url></item>