<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Directed by Terry Gilliam.  Former Monty Python member, also famous for &amp;quot;Brazil&amp;quot;.  Look at the cast - Johnny Depp, Tom Waits, Christopher Plummer, and the late great Heath Ledger&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2009) Directed by Terry Gilliam. Screenplay by Terry Gilliam and Charles McKeown. Cast: Heath Ledger, Johnny Depp, Colin Farrell, Jude Law, Christopher Plummer, Lily Cole, Tom Waits. Many Heath Ledger fans know that the gifted actor died in the middle of filming The Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus. What they may not know is that, in tribute to their lost friend, actors Johnny Depp, Colin Farrell, and Jude Law took on Ledger’s role where he left off, adding a poignant tone to this brilliantly imagined fantasy. Christopher Plummer stars as a London street performer who is locked in a battle with the Devil (as played by Tom Waits). Ledger joins the Doctor’s wild troupe as a magical ringleader, who accompanies any lady willing to pay a few shillings through the looking glass and into the adventure of their own dream world. 122 min. www.sonyclassics.com/theimaginariumofdoctorparnassus, www.needcoffee.com/doctor-parnassus&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270771834000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269004601000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Imaginarium of Doctor Farnassus</name><id>12931702</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270509300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/12931702/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>