<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 White Hollow Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06039</zip><lat>41.929302</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-435-5000</phone><name>Lime Rock Park</name><city>Lakeville</city><id>350500</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.392270</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*** UPDATE *** UPDATE ********************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP to the Skip Barber Racing School at &lt;a href="mailto:ccheney@skipbarber.com" target="_blank"&gt;ccheney@skipbarber.com &lt;/a&gt;by March 30th with your Full Name, and the number of guests you are bringing.  There is no limit to the number of guests you can bring.  For the Subject Line of the e-mail you can use &amp;quot;Opening Day at Lime Rock - April 8, RSVP Requested&amp;#8207;&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gates will open at &lt;b&gt;8:30 am (first activity begins at 9:00 am)&lt;/b&gt; and the event runs until 5:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Upon arrival, please visit the registration table located near the Start/Finish Tower.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All registrations for specific activities will be handled at the track on the day of the event ONLY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Below is a summary of the activities that will be offered for the day:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free driving school exercises on the Autocross Course and on the Skidpad.  You will learn basic defensive driving techniques in our fleet of Mazda street cars, including the Mazda 3, Mazda MX-5 Miata and the Mazda RX-8.  These sessions will begin at 10:00 am and will run throughout most of the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free on-track instructor-driven &amp;quot;Hot Laps&amp;quot; in one of our Mazda MX-5 Cup race cars or our new Lotus Exige S high performance car.  Experience the adrenaline rush of riding in a race car on one of the most popular road courses in North America with some of the best racing instructors in the country.  These sessions will begin at 9:00 am and will run through the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On-track racing demonstrations operated in the classic Skip Barber Formula 2000 race cars showing the performance capabilities of our race cars and the skills of our instructors.  Two race demonstrations are planned for the day at 11:00 am and again at 2:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the late afternoon we will also be running an &amp;quot;Introduction to Racing&amp;quot; school where eight lucky participants will be provided with the opportunity to drive a real Formula race car on the track.  A raffle will be held during lunchtime for anyone interested in participating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Skip Barber will also be offering driving and racing school discounts for future programs operated at Lime Rock Park throughout the year.  Be sure to stop by the Sales Booth for more information on all our programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Additionally, lunch will be served by Fast Tracks, Lime Rock's on-site cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spring is here and it's opening day for &lt;b&gt;Lime Rock Park&lt;/b&gt; and the &lt;b&gt;Skip Barber Racing School&lt;/b&gt;.  Skip Barber Racing School is laying out something very unique and special.  The entire day (10:00 am to 5:00 pm) is completely free to show their appreciation for your loyalty and continued interest in both Lime Rock Park and the Skip Barber Racing School!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what they have planned for the day:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free driving school Skid Pad exercises in the Mazda RX-8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free driving school Autocross exercises in the Mazda 3 and Mazda MX-5 Miata&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free on-track instructor &amp;quot;Hot Laps&amp;quot; in one of our Mazda MX-5 Cup race cars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free on-track instructor &amp;quot;Hot Laps&amp;quot; in one of our Lotus Exige S&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;On-track instructor race demonstration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free van rides around the race track and tours of the Skip Barber factory building&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free food and fun for everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All activities will be filled on a first come, first serve basis.  There will be no advanced registrations accepted and all activities will be operated at no charge to the customer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skipbarber.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Skip Barber Racing School&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.limerock.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lime Rock Park Racing Track&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deepak</member_name><member_id>2592822</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239572204000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Racing Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>racing</urlname><id>1209048</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>Racing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237571176000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Racing / Driving School Experience</name><id>9997024</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239195600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/racing/events/9997024/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/5/global_7754997.jpeg</photo_url></item>