<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Francis St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02908</zip><lat>41.829306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Providence Place</name><city>Providence</city><id>1333964</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415612</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WaterFire Providence®, the award-winning sculpture by Barnaby Evans installed on the three rivers of downtown Providence, has been praised by Rhode Island residents and international visitors alike as a powerful work of art and a moving symbol of Providence’s renaissance. WaterFire’s one hundred sparkling bonfires, the fragrant scent of aromatic wood smoke, the flickering firelight on the arched bridges, the silhouettes of the firetenders passing by the flames, the torch-lit vessels traveling down the river, and the enchanting music from around the world engage all the senses and emotions of those who stroll the paths of Waterplace Park. WaterFire has captured the imagination of over ten million visitors, bringing life to downtown, and revitalizing Rhode Island’s capital city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be quite the experience. A couple of meetup groups from MA and CT are planning on attending as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fires will be lit shortly after sunset at 7:26 p.m. and remain lit until midnight. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is more description and a link about the event-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;WaterFire is an experience that embraces all of the senses and all of the City&amp;quot; &amp;quot;WaterFire is a celebration of community and beauty. There is live dancing.. and live jazz.. and an ever changing, eclectic music program all along the rivers.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;WaterFire’s one hundred sparkling bonfires, the fragrant scent of aromatic wood smoke, the flickering firelight on the arched bridges, the silhouettes of the firetenders passing by the flames, the torch-lit vessels traveling down the river, and the enchanting music from around the world engage all the senses and emotions of those who stroll the paths of Waterplace Park. WaterFire has captured the imagination of over ten million visitors, bringing life to downtown, and revitalizing Rhode Island’s capital city.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.waterfire.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.waterfire....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim </member_name><member_id>6478306</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283810411000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280329744000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waterfire- Providence</name><id>14240597</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283034600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14240597/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/4/global_15939476.jpeg</photo_url></item>