<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It is a well known fact that fearful thoughts and judgments trigger stress, and the common message is that you must banish negativity. Would you be surprised to discover that even your negative thoughts and emotions can bring your into a deeper alignment within your body? Would you like to learn how it is possible?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and join us along our journey of energetic re-integration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how important your energy flow is to your health and emotional balance. The energy flow within the body is governed by four energy gates.  When the gates lock due to trauma the energy gets blocked. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this event you will discover how each gate holds both the story and the key – the story of what is locking the gates and the key to unblock your energy flow.  You will be inspired by this process, as you discover how everything that is going on with you, everything you are feeling makes total sense.  You will begin to trust the healing nature and wisdom of the universal principles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the process you will learn how the four energy gates coincide in their placement with specific chakras. We can better understand how gates get locked when we look at the emotional and psycho-spiritual effect of those associated chakras on the body. You will begin to listen to the body cues at each gate. Even your own self-judging thoughts can be important cues for bringing you back into balance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You will discover your true voice&lt;/b&gt; that will tell you why the gate is locked. Using this information you will learn a 4-step process of how to create re-integration protocols for opening the gates locked by any fear or distress. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover and strengthen your true voice that helps you navigate today's challenging times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and join us if you’ve said to yourself &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; I need something practical that helps me live my daily life free of fear, anxiety and depression. I need a compass to guide me and tools and techniques I can use to help me when those feelings surface. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; I need a system that is simple and inspiring and that explains the reasons, meaning and purpose behind my pain and my suffering. When I'm troubled, depressed or anxious I find that complex intellectual, therapeutic or spiritual theories no matter how profound just don't help me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I want to believe that healing is possible and want a first hand experience that I actually can rely on these techniques in the midst of problems or conflicts I face at this point in my life, no matter how enormous they may feel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I really need to believe that I am not alone on this healing journey, but so often it is one of the biggest difficulties. In need a place where I can be reminded that the universe is personally looking out for me. That there is a self-help system based on universal principles that will work without fail, it give me the tools to heal my fears and change my life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I need something that helps me feel good about myself and the world I live in.  Albert Einstein was once asked what he thought was the most important question in the world. He replied - : &amp;quot;Is the universe a friendly place?&amp;quot; I too need to believe in the healing power and loving nature of the universe of which we are all a part. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255039237000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252732557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Four Gates To Recovery: Your True Voice is the Key to Unblocking Energy</name><id>11352431</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253833200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/11352431/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/2/global_10682354.jpeg</photo_url></item>