<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Front St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02066</zip><lat>42.195058</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-545-5881</phone><name>Riva Restaurant</name><city>Scituate</city><id>1335562</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.725056</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ah, summertime... The season of sun, sand and... Italian food?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Perché no?!&lt;/i&gt; After all, this is the South Shore, where we like our sauce red, our pasta al dente, and our dining al fresco! And Riva Restaurant in Scituate can provide all three.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on the Scituate waterfront, Riva has been on Mike's To-Do List for quite awhile, but he's been saving it for summer, when their patio is open. We're hoping that starting at 6:30 will give people time to get to the event after work, but still be early enough for us to be seated outside - Please be on time for this one!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope that a number of you will join us at this popular spot. If the location itself isn't enough to entice you, have a look at their &lt;a href="http://www.rivarestaurant.net/dinnermenu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;online menu&lt;/a&gt;, then plan to meet your friends at SSDOMG as we try yet another restaurant that is new to us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Riva Restaurant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;116 Front St&lt;br /&gt;Scituate, MA 02066&lt;br /&gt;781-545-5881&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.rivarestaurant.net/" target="_blank"&gt;Riva Restaurant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. Two per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact an Event Organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Prices are in line with what you might expect to pay for a nice dinner on the South Shore: Half a dozen entrees listed online are under $20.00, with most of the rest costing $25.00 or less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Current Annual Members - FREE, Group Members - $2, Guests - $2, Mid-Year Annual Membership is $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, August 11 @ 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Take &lt;b&gt;Route 3A&lt;/b&gt; into Scituate until you come to the &lt;b&gt;rotary&lt;/b&gt; where &lt;b&gt;Route 3A and Route 123 intersect&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit the rotary onto &lt;b&gt;Driftway&lt;/b&gt; - You should pass a &lt;b&gt;Dunkin Doughnuts&lt;/b&gt; on your right just after turning onto Driftway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep following the road as it heads toward the waterfront. Go &lt;b&gt;straight&lt;/b&gt; through one &lt;b&gt;traffic light&lt;/b&gt;. You may notice at some point that Driftway becomes New Kent Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After about a mile, perhaps less, you'll come to a &lt;b&gt;stop sign&lt;/b&gt;. Go &lt;b&gt;straight&lt;/b&gt; through the stop sign. This puts you onto &lt;b&gt;Front Street&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Riva will be on your &lt;b&gt;right&lt;/b&gt;, just after a &lt;b&gt;CVS&lt;/b&gt;. Turning right at the CVS will bring you into the contiguous parking area that runs behind the shops on the Scituate waterfront.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'".</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281720263000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280461833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Andiamo a Riva!</name><id>14260468</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281652200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/14260468/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/6/global_16657014.jpeg</photo_url></item>