<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Get ready for Halloween by carving a pumpkin to display outside your door for the Trick'or'Treat-ers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an evening of carving, food and fun.  We'll set up carving (or painting, if you wish) stations.  During the evening we plan to toast the pumpkin seeds, make caramel apples, and enjoy food and friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring Your Own: &lt;br /&gt;- pumpkin (if you want us to pick one up for you just let us know ahead of time and it will be waiting for you here) &lt;br /&gt;- carving knife &lt;br /&gt;- food to share  (if you would prefer to bring ingredients and prepare your pot luck dish here, you are welcome to do so - we have a large, well-equipped kitchen ready for you) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:30 pm - 9 pm  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Place: Our home in West Roxbury (bordering Brookline and Jamaica Plain).  &lt;br /&gt;***Note: I will provide the exact address and my phone number to those who RSVP.*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's easy to get here from all over Boston - we're inside the 128 corridor. Also great for those in Boston not wanting to drive - we're just 1 block from the Commuter Rail Bellevue Station (13 minutes from Back Bay, 17 minutes from South Station)! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to take the Commuter Rail? Take the Needham Line to Bellevue Station. A train arrives here at 6:21pm which will get you here just in time. There are trains back to the city at 7:43 and 9:20. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Stacy and Ingo&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacy Goodman</member_name><member_id>3216337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257028905000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252363216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pumpkin Carving and Pot Luck **Moved to THURS**</name><id>11312527</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256855400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/11312527/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_9634902.jpeg</photo_url></item>