<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1486 Hancock St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.248493</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 376-2522</phone><name>Alba Restaurant</name><city>Quincy</city><id>896285</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.001528</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cocktailers****SPECIAL UPDATE***Dr J, (from Weymouth) will be our special guest and speaker!!  Book UP FAST.  Limited to 20 Guests!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a very special/unique meeting!!! and I'm SOOO excited!!! Dr J will give us a brief 15 min preview to his upcoming book....and then we will break out into our normal groups to share our personal insights and perspectives....as well as asking Dr. J any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youractionpotential.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youraction...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Dr. J&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After years of helping his patients achieve natural solutions to healthy living, well-known and highly respected chiropractor, author and motivational speaker Dr. Jonathan Yalowchuk is about to go public with his powerful, life-altering program, “Your Action Potential”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon to be available on book stands, his first book, “Your Action Potential-A Guide to Changing Your Life Through Health”, reveals his revolutionary approach to true health and extended life long embraced by his patients, providing the information and vision needed to fulfill one’s own potential, both mentally and physically.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Utilizing the holistic techniques he developed over years of study and observation, “Your Action Potential” outlines the simple steps one can take to achieve real happiness and success in all aspects of life. His extensive research for his book, the conclusions he has drawn from that, and his own lifestyle forms the basis for his seminars, Your Action Potential-Your Perfect Beginning .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Yalowchuk’s educational background and professional/personal experiences make him eminently qualified to write this book and to teach his seminars. A graduate of Northeastern University with a Bachelor of Science degree in cardiovascular health and physiology and a minor in psychology, he went on to earn his Doctorate from Palmer College of Chiropractic West in San Jose, CA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After graduation, he served as a lead doctor at a multidisciplinary rehabilitation clinic in Los Angeles. He returned to the Boston area in 2000 to establish a private practice, Release Chiropractic in Weymouth, MA, his place of birth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Practicing what he preaches, Dr. Yalowchuk is a competitive tennis player, fitness enthusiast and a student of martial arts, living his life in the same way he advises his patients. At his Release Chiropractic, he employs a variety of holistic methods, including nutrition-and-fitness advice, counseling and motivational techniques, to help his patients take control of their own lives and achieve their life goals. Sensitive to all life forms, two-legged and four, he offers chiropractic services for animals as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Yalochuk is a much sought-after figure on the motivational speaker circuit throughout the United States, advising rapt audiences how to apply his “Action Potential” techniques to make the lifestyle changes necessary to achieve a happier, more fulfilling and productive life.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet on the lounge side of the restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin P</member_name><member_id>8297132</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Danielle Lucido</member_name><member_id>8800487</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258848519000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Personal Growth Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cocktails-Conversations</urlname><id>1372859</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>Cocktails &amp; Conversations</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257639818000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>**Motivational Speaker &amp; Author, Dr. J, author "Your Action Potential"</name><id>11821774</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258675200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cocktails-Conversations/events/11821774/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/9/global_11756713.jpeg</photo_url></item>