<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Snyder Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06438</zip><lat>41.466972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Oar</name><city>Haddam</city><id>386567</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.477295</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>How about lunch at the Blue Oar Restaurant in Haddam, right on the river, followed by a trip to Gillette Castle?  We can all meet at the Blue Oar at 11:30, enjoy a great lunch, then car pool over to the castle.  The Blue Oar is casual outdoor eating, with great sandwiches.  Admission to tour the castle is $6.00 - walking the grounds is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blue Oar:&lt;br /&gt;Visiting this fun and friendly alfresco joint with breezy music and tasty food is like taking a day-trip to the Caribbean via the Connecticut River. The Blue Oar is smack on the water, and pastel picnic tables and twinkling lights lend a laid-back island vibe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gillette Castle:&lt;br /&gt;Completed in 1919 as the home of one of the most celebrated stage and film actors of the early 20th century, Gillette Castle is a national treasure, a jewel in the park and forest system of the State of Connecticut. The unique fieldstone building looks like a medieval fortress, but a step inside the stone castle reveals the built-in couches, table trackway, and woodcarvings that all point to the creative genius that was William Gillette. The 184 acre park is situated on a hill overlooking the Connecticut River. Gillette, best known for his portrayal of Sherlock Holmes on stage, designed his house with nooks and crannies, secret passages, hidden compartments, cunning locks, and exotic wood and stone-work. The castle's buildings and estate have been newly renovated and restored to preserve its heritage for generations to come.  Along with the castle, the park offers hiking trails, amazing views, picnic areas and a gift shop.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191339341000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>BBW/BHM and their Admirers.</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BigAttractions</urlname><id>667139</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Big Attractions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190311842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Oars and Castles!</name><id>6396922</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191166200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigAttractions/events/6396922/</event_url></item>