<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per ticket</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let's walk around the inside of Fenway on Sunday afternoon!  I managed to get 8 bleacher seats for this Sunday's 1:35pm game and decided to make them available here.  They are Upper Bleacher seats, section 38, row 31.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost of each ticket is $15 ($12 plus all the fees they added on when I bought them).  I'll take cash payment when we meet up and I hand out the tickets.  Online incurs too many fees and can be a hassle and these are real tickets not eTickets, so I can't send them via email. The cheapest tickets in this section on StubHub are going for $45 right now, so this is quite a deal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please be on time.&lt;/b&gt;  I want to be inside Fenway Park before the game starts at 1:35pm.  Expect getting to Fenway to take longer than usual because of the crowds.  Parking is expensive, so I stronly suggest taking the T.   If you are going to be late, you must call me to let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The current weather forecast is 77F with a 40% chance of scattered thunderstorms.  Check the weather before you come so you know whether to bring an umbrella or sunscreen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have set this meetup to a Manual Waiting List, which means when a spot opens up, all members on the waiting list will be emailed, and it's a race to change your RSVP.  The spot will also be open to anyone who visits the website and is not on the Waiting List. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;===========================================&lt;br /&gt;Because this involves real tickets that can only be used for this game, &lt;b&gt;please&lt;br /&gt;only signup if you seriously intend on coming.&lt;/b&gt;  There are no Maybe's, and &lt;br /&gt;Yes's mean Yes.  Please don't leave me trying to sell the tickets at the last &lt;br /&gt;minute because you changed your mind or decided not to come.  If you signup &lt;br /&gt;and can't make it, please change your RSVP as soon as possible so someone &lt;br /&gt;else can take your spot.  Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;==================================================&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, I will probably go to check out my garden after the game if the weather is good, so you can come too if you want.  It's a block away at the Fenway Victory Gardens.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside Gate C.  See my profile pic &amp; put a Sox hat on top.  I'll email RSVPs with my cell # too.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug</member_name><member_id>4908818</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1247702389000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246895160000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Sox game vs. KC</name><id>10812693</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247416200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10812693/</event_url></item>