<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.summitpost.org/pumpelly-trail/157036"&gt;http://www.summitpost.org/pumpelly-trail/15...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmpumpelly.html"&gt;http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmpumpelly.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;I've never done the Pumpelly Trail before, that I can recall anyway;-), so we'll call this one an exploratory hike as many of my hikes are. Just looking for friends to explore with me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The trailhead for the Pumpelly Trail&lt;/span&gt; is located along Lake Road, near the southern shore of Dublin Lake (or is it "Dublin Pond?" Both names seem to be used). Parking is roadside, with no established parking spots, but the easiest parking is a bit west of the trailhead, on the side opposite the lake. The trail head is located on that side, as well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Here is Terry's old posting from a previous Pumpelly Trail hike for more information too...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group/events/39904262/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group/events/39904262/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The beginning of the trail, for the first 2.6 km or so, is fairly gentle, averaging a 6% grade. Much of the trail here is packed earth with occasional stretches of broken stone, crossing private land. The ascent is made through a series of steps, with some lengths descending slightly. Overall, you experience stretches that are almost level, then moderately steep, then level, then moderately steep, repeating several times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At about the 1.6 mile (2.6 km) mark,&lt;/span&gt; the trail begins its steepest ascent, climbing from about 1900 feet (580 m) to about 2450 feet (747 m) in a horizontal distance of 660 yards (600 m). About three hundred thirty yards of this consists of a 32% grade. This is similar to what you might experience on the &lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmwhite.html"&gt;The White Dot Trail or White Cross Trail&lt;/a&gt;, but for a much shorter distance. The trail is going straight up the mountain, and much of it is obviously stream bed during wet periods; some areas have been extremely eroded and bootleg trails around those sections are common. Through here, you'll have occasional breaks in the trees allowing you some nice views to the northeast. Once above 2450 feet, the trail continues a gentler climb briefly, giving you a view of the summit, about 1.25 miles (2 km) as the crow flies, through the thinning canopy. The trail takes a sharp turn to the left at about 2 miles (3.2 km), descending a rock face and for a short distance going back into the heavier tree cover. Be careful of a false trail that goes to the right at that jog. The trail continues back uphill, then descends again just before crossing a rocky uphill slope. At about this location, you can see the next steep part of the trail, its peak less than five-eighths of a mile (1 km) distant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The slope gradually becomes steeper and until you are ascending a still comparatively gentle 17% grade. The &lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmcascade.html"&gt;Cascade Link&lt;/a&gt; meets the Pumpelly at the base of several smaller peaks, about one-third of the way up the larger hill. Fortunately, the Pumpelly Trail doesn't go over the highest point of the peak, instead swinging to the north (your right) around it and avoiding a more strenuous climb. Beautiful views of the lakes and mountains to the north are presented, and watch for the summit of Monadnock ahead of you. While approaching this part of the trail, you permanently break through the treeline. The rest of the hike will be under open sky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps half a mile past the Cascade Link intersection you'll come to the junction of the &lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmspellman.html"&gt;Spellman Trail&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/images/mt20216.jpg" alt="Mt. Monadnock, on the Pumpelly Trail at the Spellman Trail junction." width="149" height="216" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;span&gt;The Spellman Trail joins the Pumpelly&lt;/span&gt; just east of a small, steep saddle in the Pumpelly Trail. The Spellman enters through a copse of pines behind which it quickly drops out of sight. In recent years, this junction has been made much more obvious. Though you may have taken a moment or two to catch your breath if you took the Spellman Trail to this point, you may think you've celebrated too soon as you continue westward on the Pumpelly Trail and immediately climb a steep and rocky slope. But the slope is brief. Under 300 yards (260 m) farther on, you can see the summit beckoning you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pumpelly Trail continues its slow climb over rock, with low bushes and flowers keeping you company. (Remember to look for blueberries and mountain cranberries in mid to late summer, especially off the beaten path. The rock cairn markers will lead you back to the trail if you don't go too far downslope.) This is breathtaking, top-of-the-world hiking that you will likely remember for some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/images/mtm0210.jpg" alt="Red Spot Trail terminator and Mt. Monadnock Summit" width="275" height="186" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;span&gt;About half way between the Spellman Trail&lt;/span&gt; junction (with the Pumpelly Trail) and the Summit, a large rock cairn with a wooden marker at its peak marks the junction with the &lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmred.html"&gt;Red Spot Trail&lt;/a&gt;. The summit now looms large beyond the marker. On a hot summer day, you'll probably be getting a wonderfully cooling breeze&amp;mdash;at least you hope that you will be. There are a few level areas and even some dips downward and the occasional steep uphill, but you're obviously on the final stretch here. While you may wander off the trail from time to time to pick blueberries or have lunch, avoid the temptation to just cut cross-country to the peak. Some of the pockets of brush that you can run into are surprisingly thick, and if you're hiking in spring or early summer, or if the summer has been rainy, you can find yourself up to your calves in mud.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a maroon Monte Carlo</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug M</member_name><member_id>7991456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333370579000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332014996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pumpelly Trail/Mt Monadnock</name><id>56750742</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333204200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/56750742/</event_url></item>