<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Beacon Hill</address_2><address_1>77 Charles St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.358330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-523-9074 </phone><name>The Sevens</name><city>Boston</city><id>684711</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070396</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Boston T Party Pub Crawl&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be a huge day, show up on time and bring your drinking shoes. We are going to try and make each new bar at the designated time but I will email some cell phone numbers out to those who rsvp so if you get lost you can find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the plan.&lt;br /&gt;2pm Meet up at The Sevens (77 Charles Street, off Charles/MGH)&lt;br /&gt;3pm Brief stop at Beacon Hill Pub (149 Charles Street, right opposite Charles/MGH T-stop)&lt;br /&gt;4pm Characters Bar &amp;amp; Grill (2 Cambridge Centre, Kendall T)&lt;br /&gt;5pm The Field (20 Prospect St, Central T)&lt;br /&gt;6pm Phoenix Landing (512 Massachusetts Ave, Central T [where we had the Australia Day party])&lt;br /&gt;7pm Tommy Doyle's (96 Winthrop Street, Harvard T: NOTE this is the one in Harvard!!!)&lt;br /&gt;8pm Tavern in the Square (1815 Massachusetts Ave, Porter T)&lt;br /&gt;9pm -- LATE The Burren (247 Elm Street, Davis T)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YOU WILL NEED TO BRING YOUR PASSPORT OR YOUR MASS DRIVERS LICENCE&lt;/b&gt;. Last time people had an early end to the night because they didn't bring the correct ID and the bars wouldn't let them in. Please please please bring your passport if you don't have a mass drivers licence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We recommend you to buy a T-Day-pass $9.00 or T-Week-pass $15.00. &lt;b&gt;Please buy your pass before meeting at the Sevens&lt;/b&gt;, 40 people trying to buy tickets will delay the pub crawl..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the 28 people that ordered t shirts, good choice. The order is at the printer and I should receive the shirts the Thursday before the pub crawl.  The shirts ended up at $15 each and I have ordered and paid for them all. It would probably be easiest to pick them up and pay for them in the first pub but if you want them before hand I work in the financial district and live in the North end so we could meet on the Thursday or Friday. KC did  a great job on the design, they are going to look good. Unfortunately I can't add and more shirts to the order now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to catch up with you all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers&lt;br /&gt;KC and Amy&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>3466832</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>KC</member_name><member_id>5408035</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210011068000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Larrikins</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aussie-145</urlname><id>222356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Aussie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204251670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston T Party Pub Crawl - Aussie style</name><id>7430283</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209837600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aussie-145/events/7430283/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/b/global_3758395.jpeg</photo_url></item>