<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;You're tearing me apart!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The summit of juvenile delinquent stories, &lt;u&gt;Rebel Without a Cause&lt;/u&gt; cemented James Dean as a star; though his untimely death four weeks before the film's premiere prevented him from seeing the final product.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dean stars as Jim Stark, the new kid in town and already he's in with a bad crowd. His love interest Judy (Natalie Wood) and &amp;quot;close friend&amp;quot; Plato (Sal Mineo) are hiding out from the cops and trying to stay one step ahead of the local goons. Romance, fast cars, real switchblade fights, and Dennis Hopper...could you ask for anything more?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Nicholas Ray, w/ James Dean, Natalie Wood, Sal Mineo, 1h51m &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/rebel_without_a_cause/" target="_blank"&gt;Rotten Tomatoes: 95% Rating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the New York Times Critics Pick Review:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This landmark juvenile-delinquent drama scrupulously follows the classic theatrical disciplines, telling all within a 24-hour period. Teenager Jimmy Stark (James Dean) can't help but get into trouble, a problem that has forced his appearance-conscious parents (Jim Backus and Ann Doran) to move from one town to another. The film's tormented central characters are all introduced during a single night-court session, presided over by well-meaning social worker Ray (Edward Platt). Jimmy, arrested on a drunk-and-disorderly charge, screams &amp;quot;You're tearing me apart!&amp;quot; as his blind-sided parents bicker with one another over how best to handle the situation. Judy (Natalie Wood) is basically a good kid but behaves wildly out of frustration over her inability to communicate with her deliberately distant father (William Hopper). (The incestuous subtext of this relationship is discreetly handled, but the audience knows what's going on in the minds of Judy and her dad at all times.) And Plato (Sal Mineo), who is so sensitive that he threatens to break apart like porcelain, has taken to killing puppies as a desperate bid for attention from his wealthy, always absent parents. . . . Released right after James Dean's untimely death, Rebel Without a Cause netted an enormous profit. The film almost seems like a eulogy when seen today, since so many of its cast members -- James Dean, Natalie Wood, Sal Mineo, Nick Adams -- died young. ~ Hal Erickson, All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll gather at the Panera Bread across the street from the Coolidge beginning 6:00 pm, and head to the theater around 6:40. Gives us a chance to catch up, enjoy some 'pre popcorn' appetizers, and pause for the cause (inside joke).  Look for John to be sitting at a table, looking like a dashing James Dean, sheepishly displaying a red Meetup Sign to everyone that passes by.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer is coming, and with it a dearth of serious film releases or willingness to sit inside movie theaters on (precious for Boston) beautiful days.  The Coolidge's &lt;i&gt;Big Classic&lt;/i&gt; series gives us a chance to catch up on some films we may have only seen 3 or 4 times, and to enjoy the experience of getting together to watch films as they were meant to be seen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for us to post the best films from the Independent Film Festival (&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Winter's Bone&lt;/span&gt; opens June 18), our annual trip to the &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Drive In in Mendon&lt;/span&gt;, and all manner of special showings at area theaters otherwise not known as cineplexes!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273018688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rebel Without A Cause</name><id>13387430</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274137200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13387430/</event_url></item>