<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's meet at 6:30 and head into get seats by 6:40.   The film time is definitely 7PM.  Buy tickets ahead of time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is playing in an upstairs theater, I will try to grab a table near the windows at the top of the escalator.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't find the group before the movie, we will gather outside the room where we have watched the movie for a bit to discuss the movie and then any who are interesed can go to the Brewery with the group for munchies, drinks and socialization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clash of the Titans&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Sam Worthington, Liam Neeson, Ralph Fiennes, Danny Huston, Gemma Arterton, Mads Mikkelsen, Jason Flemyng, Alexa Davalos, Izabella Miko, Nicholas Hoult, Pete Postlethwaite &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Action, Fantasy &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Clash-of-the-Titans.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://Clash-of-the-T...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: In &amp;quot;Clash of the Titans,&amp;quot; the ultimate struggle for power pits men against kings and kings against gods. But the war between the gods themselves could destroy the world. Born of a god but raised as a man, Perseus (Sam Worthington) is helpless to save his family from Hades (Ralph Fiennes), vengeful god of the underworld. With nothing left to lose, Perseus volunteers to lead a dangerous mission to defeat Hades before he can seize power from Zeus (Liam Neeson) and unleash hell on earth. Leading a daring band of warriors, Perseus sets off on a perilous journey deep into forbidden worlds. Battling unholy demons and fearsome beasts, he will only survive if he can accept his power as a god, defy his fate and create his own destiny. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>34</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275960692000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263406837000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clash of the Titans</name><id>12309494</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270247400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/12309494/</event_url></item>