<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come out and bring a picnic lunch, munchies, whatever floats your boat...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will meet on the lawn at the waterfront park stage where the band Jazz in the Park will play from 1-4 PM. I will have a bright turquoise beach towel spread out on the lawn and will try to find a spot along, or close to, the walkway heading down toward the water. Check out the member pictures and watch for us, we will be watching for you too. :-)&lt;/b&gt; Upbeat refreshing jazz standards and originals with a touch of RnB, latin, funk and rock. There are also many other events planned around town throughout the day. If the weather is good it will probably be crowded so I will let you know how we can find each other as it gets closer to the date. Bad weather cancels this event, check our website around 10 in the morning if unsure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if you choose to stay later, EJ Ouellette &amp;amp; Crazy Maggie perform from 7:30PM - 9:00PM.&lt;br /&gt;Led by EJ Ouellette on fiddle, guitar and vocals, Crazy Maggy rocks the roots of traditional fiddle music by blending ancient melodies with new arrangements, contemporary lyrics, and a myriad of dance grooves. The result is a mesmerizing sound which seduces audiences with its energy and invention.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check here for additional info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yankeehomecoming.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yankeehome...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Read the listing, then head toward the water (behind the fire station and Average Joe's restaurant) and watch for the bright turqoise beach towel.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248991240000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243893830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yankee Homecoming in Newburyport</name><id>10548257</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248624000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/10548257/</event_url></item>