<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>THIS IS THE FIRST OF A TWO-PART SERIES!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; How to Celebrate a Joyous Holiday Season in Uncertain Times[/b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join me as we retool Christmas (or Hanukkah or Kwanza, or Santa’s visit); changing it from a months-long orgy of conspicuous consumption to what it was intended to be – a peaceful celebration of joy, hope and love - so critical in today's financially challenging times. I'm using the framework of the Christian Advent and Christmas timeframes, but they can be easily adapted. So whether you celebrate Christmas, Hanukkah, Kwanzaa or some combination, you'll be able to use the information presented.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may be astounded by the two-part solution: the season of Advent and the Twelve Days of Christmas. [Advent is the four weeks before Christmas; the Twelve Days of Christmas are December 25 - January 6th]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This session focuses on using Advent as a time to prepare our homes and hearts for a simple meaningful holiday. We're going to take a hard look at our holiday celebrations, paring down the gift list, parties, and people - getting down to the things that are most meaningful to us. We'll use these four weeks to get ready, ridding ourselves of all the stuff that no longer gives us joy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second part of the series is on December 2nd, and it focuses on planning a joyously simple Christmas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228265716000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220145513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Celebrate a Joyous Holiday Season in Uncertain Times - Part 1</name><id>8655236</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227052800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/8655236/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/d/global_5119229.jpeg</photo_url></item>