<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I won't be asking for any donations for the meetup site. :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm going to ask this be a smaller group as Beau's having some knee issues and too many dogs will be a problem.  If anyone else wants to ever schedule meetups at Musquash that is cool with me - just please try not to have too many people so we don't overwhelm others enjoying the trails.  Also, please bring poop bags and keep the trails clean. :)  Thanks so much!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, so I am hoping the weather is nice by Sunday.  Beau's so missing socializing with dogs and their parents and this group is the best of both worlds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is on a shorter time-frame for hikes/walks so we'll do a loop that takes us roughly 35-45 minutes.  A group hike is always a little longer so prob. more on the 45 min. side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the best time of year for hikes at Musquash.  No bugs and great earthy smells.  It is however bear hunting season so be sure to put orange or other colors on your dogs and self to be safe, even though the hunters are pretty far off the trails....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet near the trail entrance under the power lines.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracey</member_name><member_id>8472167</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287448849000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287066220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Musquash - Hickory Hill Entrance</name><id>15107616</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287327600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/15107616/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/3/global_13504099.jpeg</photo_url></item>