<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>There was a lot of interest in a MFA meetup, so I've  scheduled this one for the Luis Melendez exhibit. Its a small show, so there should be time to see other exhibits as well. Wed. night is &amp;quot;pay what you can&amp;quot;, but everyone needs a ticket or a membership card.  Let's meet in the big Information Center which is accessable from either the Huntington or Fenway entrances. Hope you can come. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A splendid show.&amp;quot; —The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Luis Meléndez (1716–1780) was the greatest still life painter of 18th-century Spain. An accomplished painter of miniatures, he began creating still lifes as early as 1759. In 1771 he was awarded a commission from the Prince of Asturias (later Charles IV), an avid amateur of the new science of natural history, to paint an extensive series of works documenting &amp;quot;every species of food produced by the Spanish climate.&amp;quot; An inventive and consummate master of still lifes, the artist rendered everyday objects with exacting detail, but also created marvelous effects of light and color and a wide range and variety of textures. &amp;quot;Luis Meléndez: Master of the Spanish Still Life&amp;quot; features many of the artist's works in American collections, grouping them with relevant works borrowed from abroad, and explores some of the technical aspects of his extraordinarily realistic still life paintings.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Q.</member_name><member_id>2269958</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270249410000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268929475000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MFA - Luis Melendez Exhibit </name><id>12923574</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270076400000</time><rsvp_limit>33</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/12923574/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/2/c/global_13735068.jpeg</photo_url></item>