<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will be getting together to watch the independent documentary "In God We Teach", the story of Matthew LaClair'a First Amendment fight with is High School Science teacher.  Many of us know the details of the story. The documentary gives a much broader view with interviews from those involved and from such distinguished commentators as Alan Dershowitz, Barry Lynn, Kenneth Miller, Neil deGrasse Tyson and John Whitehead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is from the documentary's website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 60px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Are teachers allowed to express their personal opinions in the classroom?Are teachers allowed “academic freedom”?And can competing theories be taught alongside evolution in a public classroom?These and other questions are the focus of the full-length documentary, “In God We Teach," which follows the “separation of church and state” controversy played out in a very public feud between a high school student and his history teacher in Kearny, NJ, a blue-collar, all-American town within sight of downtown New York.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 60px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;While most Americans claim to understand the concept of “separation of church and state,” few are sure of what is actually legal, and what is not when it comes to the public school classroom. And the misunderstandings continue. Isn’t America a Christian state founded on Judeo-Christian values, a single nation indivisible under God and whose currency stipulates that in God we trust?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 60px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The role of religion had been central in American society from its founding to the present day, and remains a contentious topic in American life and politics. Passions run high on issues such as abortion, same-sex marriage, embryonic stem-cell research, and the “ground-zero mosque.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 60px"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;While these religion-based culture wars continue, “In God We Teach” explores the way in which diverse opinions on the role of religion in the public space conflict and clash in our everyday lives.With discussion and analysis from such distinguished commentators as Alan Dershowitz, Barry Lynn, Kenneth Miller, Neil deGrasse Tyson and John Whitehead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be time for discussion after the movie for any interested.  Feel free to bring comfy lawn chairs if you wish.  And remember, it can be warm in the hall, so bring water and dress comfortably!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345417283000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344020242000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August Meeting - Movie Night "In God We Teach"</name><id>76210092</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344985200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/76210092/</event_url></item>