<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.350399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>19 Mile Brook Trailhead</name><city>Gorham</city><id>391517</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194696</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There are so many hike options here! 3 4000 Ft summits and a very special view from Mt Hight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP and depending how energetic you are, decide on an itinerary. &lt;br /&gt;19 mile trailhead can offer you novice or expert rated hike depending on what you want to hike. One thing is true, you will be back again for more. Carter Notch Hut has bunks available if you would like to split the trip up into an overnight event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Option # 1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carter Dome (4,832 feet - #9 on AMC 4K List) and Middle Carter (4,610 feet - #15 on AMC 4K List) offer dramatic views of Mount Washington and the Presidential Range. Mt Height is the best summit for views and can be a shorter destination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our plan is to go to the hut this stretch of trail is steeper and  want to get it over with in the beginning of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Carter Notch hut Overnight hikers will plan on starting by 10 am&lt;br /&gt;(The group does have another option of going directly to Carter dome via Zeta Pass and return the same way)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail the Appalachian Mountain Club's self-service Carter Notch Hut (3,288 feet).(3.8 miles) pick up the overnight hikers in the group, take a short break,  then hike up to Carter dome..  Mount Hight, and down to the Zeta Pass. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Very strong hikers have an option to continue on the Carter-Moriah Trail to South Carter and finally Middle Carter. Return to 19 mile or descend Imp trail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAUTION: make sure you have a good water supply/last filter at zeta pass&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the group forming at the trailhead.  Diane and a few others will be meet at the Carter Notch hut.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253629242000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244672242000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Carter's and Mt Height</name><id>10624231</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253449800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10624231/</event_url></item>