<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Chapel View Blvd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02920</zip><lat>41.779533</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>REI Cranston</name><city>Cranston</city><id>1151481</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.462975</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I'm planning on posting a bunch of snowshoe events in the future so I thought this REI class might be useful. Best of all, its free! REI Cranston is offering this free class, here is the description from their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ease of snowshoeing has led it to become one of the fastest growing wintersports in the country. Simply strap on a pair and go on a winter hike, backpack, or climb! Join the staff of REI as we put on another one of our famous &amp;quot;how to&amp;quot; clinics on the basics of snowshoeing. We will focus on the appropriate selection of gear and the initial skills needed to get you outside and on the trails. In addition, we will talk about some places to go. If you ever thought about getting into snowshoeing, this is a great introduction to the sport!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you sign up you just have to register so they can have a head count, contact REI Cranston Customer Service 401-275-5250.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Just in case this is unclear, this is an indoor class...not actually going snow shoeing, just learning about it!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet 15 minutes before the class (which starts at 7) at the entrance to the store...my cell is 508-414-8544</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263668292000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262563914000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snowshoe Class</name><id>12210384</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263339900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/12210384/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/f/global_12488479.jpeg</photo_url></item>