<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3rd Floor, 1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Innovation Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1484407</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084037</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Learn from the best about how to utilize social media and marketing in our lives! There are so many ways to incorporate the many&amp;nbsp;aspects of&amp;nbsp;social media, but how do we get the&amp;nbsp;most out of it and manage it effectively? Meet the founder of Downtown Women's Club, Diane Danielson, along with Paige Arnof-Fenn,&amp;nbsp;CEO/founder of Mavens and Moguls. We will be having a panel discussion&amp;nbsp;on the topic of&amp;nbsp;social media and understand the most efficient&amp;nbsp;ways to use it. Join us to exchange&amp;nbsp;knowledge, converse, and network after. This&amp;nbsp;event will be held in the Cambridge Innovation Center and hosted&amp;nbsp;by Prompt Communications. Please kindly confirm your RSVP's in advance and respect the time of our members. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diane Danielson: Founder of Downtown Women's Club&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Diane has been in marketing and business development since 1996 when she moved from the legal world into the commercial real estate industry. She has been writing books, building online communities and working in social media since 2003 when she began blogging for the Boston Globe. In 2006, her company, the Downtown Women's Club launched the first social network for businesswomen in the US and has remained on the leading edge of social media ever since. Today, Diane uses her legal, marketing, management and social media experience to help businesses integrate new media strategies with traditional marketing and business development plan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;www&lt;a href="http://www.downtownwomensclub.com"&gt;.downtownwomensclub.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paige Arnof-Fenn: Founder and CEO of Mavens &amp;amp; Moguls&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Mavens &amp;amp; Moguls, a global marketing strategy consulting firm whose clients range from early stage start-ups to Fortune 500 companies including Colgate, Virgin and The New York Times Company. She was formerly VP Marketing at Zipcar and VP Marketing at Inc.com before the company was sold to Bertelsmann. Prior to that she held the title of SVP Marketing and was a key member of the IPO team at Launch Media, an Internet start-up that went public in early 1999 and was later sold to Yahoo. Arnof-Fenn is a founding Board member of Women Entrepreneurs in Science &amp;amp; Technology and she is currently serving as Board Chair of the Alumni Board of Stanford University. She is also the former Vice President of the Harvard Business School Global Alumni Board and the current Chair of the Board of Trustees of the Sports Museum at the Boston Garden&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.mavensandmoguls.com"&gt;www.mavensandmoguls.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Venue: Prompt Communications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Prompt Communications&amp;nbsp;enables marketers and entrepreneurs to increase their sales and marketing. It specializes in technology, sustainability, and healthcare. It helps clients through media, PR relations, copywriting, webinars, social media, video content, and customer reference programs. Founded in 2002, Prompt Communications has offices in the U.S and Europe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.prompt-communications.com"&gt;www.prompt-communications.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>First Floor: Prompt Communications</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noona Joseph</member_name><member_id>5632804</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308004876000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Learn from the best! Meet the founder of Downtown Women's Club and CEO/founder of Mavens and Moguls to have a panel discussion on how to utilize social media and marketing with business in our lives.</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandnetworkforwomen-com</urlname><id>1463004</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>New England Network for Women :: Cambridge</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305114282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Media Workshop</name><id>17962861</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306189800000</time><rsvp_limit>43</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandnetworkforwomen-com/events/17962861/</event_url></item>