<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1429 Park St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.757389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-724-4444</phone><name>Barca Tapas and Resaurant</name><city>Hartford</city><id>787490</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702313</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Authentic Tapas Night Spanish Meetup at Barca Restaurant and Tapas Bar&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, November 11th at 7 p.m.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for “un viaje” to the authentic tapas experience here in Hartford where tapas created by a chef from Spain will be served Spanish Bar/Café/ Restaurant style – on a bar counter with cañas (small glasses of Beer or wineto drink with tapas). A tapa is a small appetizer. Here’s the plan: for a cost of $12 dollars you will receive 4 tickets. You can trade your tickets for one of the tapas on the counter, one ticket per tapa.  Pay extra  and try a caña, one of several Spanish beers or wines. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the list of tapas planned for this event*:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.Tortilla Espanola – Spanish Omelett with Caramelized Onions, Roasted Red Peppers and Potatoes over Garlic Tomato Sauce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Setas del Monte Asadas con Mantequilla al Ajo – Wild Mushrooms Suateéd with Garlic and Butter servcied with Crusty Bread&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Salmon Frito – Fried Seaweed Wrapped Citrus Salmon, Seaweed Salad&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Chorizo – Spanish sausage in a tempting dish – to be determined&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Combinación de Quesos Espanoles y Carnes Curadas – Combination of Assorted Spanish Cheeses and Cured Meats&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Note: there may be some variation in the final selection of tapas for this meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eat, drink and be merry!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barca is located at The Design Center, first floor, 1429 Park Street, Hartford, CT 06106, 860-724-4444. Visit the following website for a write up of this new Hartford restaurant: &lt;a href="http://www.topix.com/content/trb/2008/04/barcas-chef-is-sweet-on-hartford-2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topix.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP by November 8th. Note: you can only RSVP Yes or No. There is not a Maybe option.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Questions: contact Karen at kdwo543210@yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Dworski</member_name><member_id>2589505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227052739000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225805225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tapas Night at Barca Restaurant and Tapas Bar</name><id>9091369</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226448000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/9091369/</event_url></item>