<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The film is at 7:15 so let's meetup at 6:45.   See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;21&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Jim Sturgess, Kate Bosworth, Laurence Fishburne, Kevin Spacey, Liza Lapira, Josh Gad, Aaron Yoo, Sam Golzari&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sonypictures.com/movies/21/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sonypictur...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Columbia Pictures' high stakes action adventure &amp;quot;21&amp;quot; is inspired by the true story of the very brightest young minds in the country ? and how they took Vegas for millions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ben Campbell (Jim Sturgess) is a shy, brilliant M.I.T. student who ? needing to pay school tuition ? finds the answers in the cards. He is recruited to join a group of the school's most gifted students that heads to Vegas every weekend armed with fake identities and the know-how to turn the odds at blackjack in their favor. With unorthodox math professor and stats genius Micky Rosa (Kevin Spacey) leading the way, they've cracked the code. By counting cards and employing an intricate system of signals, the team can beat the casinos big time. Seduced by the money, the Vegas lifestyle, and by his smart and sexy teammate, Jill Taylor (Kate Bosworth), Ben begins to push the limits. Though counting cards isn't illegal, the stakes are high, and the challenge becomes not only keeping the numbers straight, but staying one step ahead of the casinos' menacing enforcer: Cole Williams (Laurence Fishburne).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I wear a Boston Movie Group Badge.  If the movie is downstairs, I will be just inside the ropes near the concession area.  If the movie is upstairs I will be near the coffee vendor by the big windows.  I will try to snag a table there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207482687000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><why>It is so much more fun to see movies with other movie fans and this is a great group!</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200571112000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>21</name><id>7135322</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206830700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7135322/</event_url></item>