<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A roughly 3 hr., 3 - 4 mile loop hike of moderate difficulty near the south-central shore area in this 1,200 acre sanctuary with 39 miles of very interesting trails. This is my "Indiana Jones" hike which is some high adventure which will involve traversing swamp via boardwalk, modest cliffs, going through a few rockfall caves, a small bit of a rock climb, and interesting rock formations and sights! Exact path followed will depend on conditions and pace of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trails have a unique blaze system. North-south trails are marked with a circle shaped blaze. Square or triangular trails weave back and forth connecting circle trails. Crossover trails that connect two circle trails of different colors are marked with an X of the color of the circle they lead to. Complicated?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go should have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack - To carry water and keep your hands free &lt;br /&gt;

 * Hiking boots advised &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1 quart of water &lt;br /&gt;

 * Pants you don't mind possibly getting dirty from crawling &lt;br /&gt;

 * Bug spray&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meetup will be at 10 AM at the parking area. &lt;strong&gt;Parking may be limited so RSVP's are limited.&lt;/strong&gt; We would finish up no later than about 2 PM. Afterwards, we can go out to a local diner that specializes in vegetarian food but also serves meat for the carnivores among us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General directions&lt;/strong&gt; (from a trail source):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Take Exit 58 off I-95 * Take Route 77 south (toward Guilford) about 0.5 mile &lt;br /&gt;

 * Turn right (west) onto Route 1 and go 0.7 mile &lt;br /&gt;

 * Bear left onto Peddlers Rd. and drive 1.1 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 * Parking area on left just past Denison Dr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; (watch closely for dirt parking lot on south side, roughly 540 Peddlers Rd., Guilford, CT): &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://mapq.st/11k2c5m"&gt;http://mapq.st/11k2c5m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Westwoods trail map&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://guilfordlandtrust.org/wordpress/maps/westwoods.pdf"&gt;http://guilfordlandtrust.org/wordpress/maps/westwoods.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map is in " &lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Walk Book: East&lt;/strong&gt;" 19th ed., by Connecticut forest and Park Association as map &lt;strong&gt;WW-1&lt;/strong&gt; on page 80.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interactive trail map&lt;/strong&gt; (to calculate distances by trail segment): &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://guilfordlandtrust.org/wordpress/properties/westwoods/interactive-westwoods-map"&gt;http://guilfordlandtrust.org/wordpress/properties/westwoods/interactive-westwoods-map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Westwoods Reserve:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://guilfordlandtrust.org/wordpress/properties/westwoods"&gt;http://guilfordlandtrust.org/wordpress/properties/westwoods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guilford Land Trust&lt;/strong&gt; (maintains Westwoods): &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://guilfordlandtrust.org/"&gt;http://guilfordlandtrust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Ford Escape SUV, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367188597000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366080948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Westwoods Reserve Trails in Guilford CT</name><id>114561322</id><duration>14400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367157600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/114561322/</event_url></item>