<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square, Cambridge</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.367496</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Cambridge Brew Company</name><city>Boston</city><id>559881</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://iffboston.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://iffboston.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For five straight years, the &lt;b&gt;Independent Film Festival of Boston&lt;/b&gt; has brought trend-setting, eye-opening, cutting-edge indie films to ever-growing audiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you been to the festival?  Films are shown at the &lt;u&gt;Brattle&lt;/u&gt;, the &lt;u&gt;Coolidge&lt;/u&gt;, and the &lt;u&gt;Somerville Theater&lt;/u&gt; over a period 6 days, from opening night Wednesday to the closing film on Monday evening.  In between are multiple film possibilities all weekend, and an exhausting attempt to see them all, everywhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, you can attend the &lt;b&gt;International/Arthouse Film meetup group Pow Wow&lt;/b&gt; to be held on &lt;b&gt;Sunday afternoon, April 13, at the Cambridge Brew Company&lt;/b&gt; in One Kendall Square, near the Kendall Square Movie Theater.  At the Pow Wow, we plan to go over the full schedule of films, find out what the buzz is for certain films, see who is going where and on what night, organize meetups and get togethers, so that we can attend as many of the films as possible with fellow film friends and turn this festival into a community event that enables us to enjoy these great, first-run, films with friends in the audience, and stimulating discussion afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be open to as many as 60 people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come if you are a long-time member of the group and want to attend the festival with others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come if you are new to the group and want to experience the fun of seeing great independent films with others - instead of by yourself.  Walk into each theater and recognize others in the audience, sit with friends, and look forward to talking about the fims afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come if you are interested in the International/Arthouse Moive Meetup Group but haven't been to your first event.  Enjoy some microbrew, meet new friends, and look forward to the Independent Film Festival in a way that you never thought possible living in the big city.  Turns out there are like-minded film fans from all over the country who live in Boston, and this is the perfect way to connect to this community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come if you have anyting to do with the festival, have nothing to do with the festival, have been to the festival, or plan to just see one film at the festival.  Bring a guest, enjoy the discussion, and become part of this group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete list of films:  &lt;a href="http://iffboston.org/2008/films.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://iffboston.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you think of a better way to go over this list than by coming to the &lt;b&gt;Cambridge Brew Company on Sunday, April 13 at 2:00 pm&lt;/b&gt; and meeting with dozens of other film fans?&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the back room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Walter</member_name><member_id>3779246</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208283121000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><why>The Independent Film Festival is the best film festival in Boston, and one of the best in the country for independent narratives, documentaries, and short films.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206913592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independent Film Festival Boston Pow Wow</name><id>7635139</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208109600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7635139/</event_url></item>