<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>502C Commonwealth Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.348783</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-8929</phone><name>Panopticon Gallery inside the Hotel Commonwealth Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>883112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095088</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Harold Feinstein began his sixty-year career in photography in 1946 at the age of fifteen. Only four years later, Edward Steichen purchased his work for the permanent collection of the Museum of Modern Art. Feinstein became a prominent figure in the New York small camera school and his legendary photography workshops helped to launch the careers of hundreds of aspiring photographers for more than fifty years. Respected photography critic and historian A.D. Colman called him “a true photographer’s photographer. Here is New York small camera photography at it’s best. Yet there’s none of Weegee’s brashness, William Klein’s arrogance, or Garry Winogrand’s snideness here; this is the work of a man who loves people, takes unalloyed pleasure in seeing them enjoy themselves, likes to get very close to them – and, by rendering their physicality in tactile, nuanced prints, engrosses the viewer in the sensual, material world they occupy.” In the 1950’s, the New York Times photo critic, Jacob Deschin, called Feinstein’s work “the new pictorialism”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;We'll stay at the gallery until the reception ends at 7pm, and then possibly grab a bite somewhere and discuss the exhibit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.panopt.com/exhibitions.php?upcoming" target="_blank"&gt;More about the exhibit.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/visual-art-appreciators-boston/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing/carrying a purple polka dot coat.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cristin</member_name><member_id>603739</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258843465000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257526548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harold Feinstein: A Retrospective (Opening Reception)</name><id>11812268</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258669800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/11812268/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/3/a/global_11667386.jpeg</photo_url></item>