<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1151 Walnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02461</zip><lat>42.322044</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Keller William Realty</name><city>Newton Highlands</city><id>4509032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.206482</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We are&amp;nbsp; excited to have Tammy Gooler Loeb, MBA, CPCC, to present about networking and talk about building connections during the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Networking......just the thought of it leaves people feeling vulnerable and reluctant.&amp;nbsp; Too often, these thoughts create a self-fulfilling prophecy that can negatively impact the process from the beginning.&amp;nbsp; It does not have to that way!&amp;nbsp; The holidays are an especially good time to engage with people in natural ways that build interactive connections.&amp;nbsp; In this interactive forum, we will explore some of the more effective ways to access your networks and the information you need to be successful in all your professional pursuits.&amp;nbsp; You will leave this workshop with inspiration, new ideas and approaches to getting the connections and information you are seeking.&amp;nbsp; It may not be what you think....come join us and find out what you may have been missing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaker:&amp;nbsp; Tammy Gooler Loeb, MBA, CPCC, brings 25+ years experience to her work as a coach, facilitator. speaker and trainer.&amp;nbsp; She focuses on leadership, career and executive coaching, team development, school improvement planning, workshop communication. conflict management, and organizational development.&amp;nbsp; Her clients represent many areas including non-profit, education, law, biotechnology, entertainment, consulting, and executive management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Renee</member_name><member_id>9315030</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betty</member_name><member_id>10132770</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323323241000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Professional Women</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Women-in-Business-Network</urlname><id>997886</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Women in Business Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321742030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Networking:  Building Successful Connections</name><id>41763122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323214200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-in-Business-Network/events/41763122/</event_url></item>