<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Pond Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.330566</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Parking lot at Leverett Pond</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1303528</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;The Emerald Necklace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;--a chain of linked urban parks spanning 5 miles--is the only remaining INTACT linear park designed by Frederick Law Olmstead ... and it's right here in Boston! Let's take advantage of this wonderful public resource by exploring the necklace with 3 leisurely &amp;quot;hikes&amp;quot; over the course of the summer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HIKE 1 (June 26) -- The Fenway to Jamaica Pond and back&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.inquisitiveminds.org/calendar/13568833" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;HIKE 2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (July 24) -- Arnold Arboretum to Franklin Park and back&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.inquisitiveminds.org/calendar/13568863" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;HIKE 3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (August 21) -- The Boston Common to the Fenway and back&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a &lt;a href="http://dl.dropbox.com/u/904768/EmeraldNecklaceMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;map&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of the Emerald Necklace&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to 1, 2 or all 3 hikes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;This event is &lt;b&gt;HIKE 1:  The Fenway to Jamaica Pond (and back)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance = 3-4 mi / Difficulty = Easy / Time = 2-4 hrs&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE 6/21:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  I did a trial run of our hike yesterday and if the weather holds up, this will be a very enjoyable outing! I’ve &lt;b&gt;changed our starting point&lt;/b&gt;, however, because I got a better map of the “Muddy River Loop” hike from the Emerald Necklace Conservancy. So &lt;b&gt;we’ll meet at the Leverett Pond parking lot on Pond Avenue in Brookline&lt;/b&gt;. This is about the mid-point of our route. We’ll travel south and around Jamaica Pond; stop for lunch and snacks. Then we’ll proceed north to the Fenway, circling back to Leverett Pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For this hike you'll need:&lt;/b&gt; comfortable athletic shoes or light hiking boots and an extra pair of socks; sunscreen or a visored hat; bug spray (if this kind of thing bothers you); bottled water; snacks and a bagged lunch. We'll be hiking in wooded areas so be aware that we may encounter poison ivy. If you're susceptible, plan your dress accordingly. Bring your camera! There are some really interesting sights along our route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To get to our starting point:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;If you’re driving and using a GPS&lt;/u&gt; -- enter “64 Pond Avenue, Brookline MA” into your device. The Leverett Pond parking lot is directly across the street from this address (near the intersection of Pond Avenue and Washington Street).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;If you’re driving from the Fenway area&lt;/u&gt; -- take the Riverway toward JP; at the 3rd traffic light, TURN RIGHT onto Brookline Avenue; drive to the end of Brookline but stay in the left-hand lane; at the traffic light, you will be at Washington Street; TURN LEFT onto Washington then a QUICK HARD RIGHT onto Pond Avenue—do not go up the ramp or you will be back on the Riverway/Jamaicaway. The Leverett Pond parking lot will be on your left—directly across from 64 Pond Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARK AT YOUR OWN RISK -- &lt;/b&gt;The lot is free but you’re limited to 2 hours. A local told me they don’t ticket, but &lt;i&gt;our&lt;/i&gt; Saturday could be the exception. There are 24 spaces at this smallish lot (22 regular, 2 handicapped), so plan accordingly. I’m driving and I plan to be there at 9:30 am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;If you’re taking public transportation&lt;/u&gt; -- take the Green Line “E-Heath” train to the “Riverway&amp;quot; stop on S. Huntington Street (you'll be about 1,000 ft away from our starting point); WALK BACK to the intersection of S. Huntington and Huntington Streets (about 100 ft); TURN LEFT on Huntington, crossing the street (you’ll walk under the Riverway, about 450 ft); you'll now be in Brookline on Washington Street; TURN LEFT onto Pond Avenue and proceed to the parking lot (about 480 ft on your left).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;!!! Rain cancels the hike -- I will confirm cancellation via email !!!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to know more about the Emerald Necklace? Check out the &lt;a href="http://www.emeraldnecklace.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;website&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anor ... &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>An Or</member_name><member_id>8593359</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277668691000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274630009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Hiking" the Emerald Necklace -- HIKE 1:  The Fenway to Jamaica Pond</name><id>13568738</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277560800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/13568738/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/8/7/global_15221767.jpeg</photo_url></item>