<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will host a dual celebration for HumanLight and Human Rights Day which both occur this month.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This will be a potluck dinner so plan to bring some munchies!&lt;/i&gt;  A casserole, dessert, finger food or your specialty dish is appreciated.  Please note what you can bring when you RSVP!  We will also have a signup at November's meeting so get those culinary craniums cranking...  We usually start eating around 6:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also be having our annual Yankee swap.  Each person that wishes to participate in the swap should bring a small (if possible, &lt;u&gt;humanism&lt;/u&gt;) related gift (suggested target price range of about $5 - $10).  Joke gifts are perfectly acceptable, but anything at all will do.  Last year's event was a fun time, with good food and good company, not to mention some pretty interesting and humorous gifts.  To be fair only people who bring a swap gift can participate...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome! Please consider becoming a member of Greater Worcester Humanists.  Membership allows us to do all of the great programs, lectures, meetups, etc. and it's only $30 a year.  If you're not interested in membership just yet, please consider donating at the door.  The doors open at 5:30 if you would like to help set up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;____________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HumanLight" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Human Light  (sometimes Humanlight) is the Humanist counterpart to Christmas and other winter holidays. It is celebrated on December 23. Like Kwanzaa, HumanLight is a modern invention, created to provide a specifically Humanist counterpart to popular seasonal celebrations. It was established by the New Jersey Humanist Network in 2001.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Humanists have cast HumanLight as a celebration of &amp;quot;a Humanist's vision of a good future.&amp;quot; They celebrate a positive approach to the coming new year, generally through the lens of Humanist (and particularly secular humanist) philosophy--secular as opposed to religious, and with an emphasis on reason and rationality. The December 23 date allows HumanLight to connect itself to the December holiday season without imposing itself over them, since many Humanists also celebrate other winter holidays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HumanLight began with a single event in Verona, New Jersey, 2001. Since then, HumanLight has experienced much growth; in 2004, there were two dozen American events listed on the holiday's homepage, mostly on the East Coast and in the Midwest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organized HumanLight celebrations since its founding in 2001 have included guest speakers, candle-lighting ceremonies, musical and dramatic performances, dinners, dancing, and video presentations. As Humanists value creativity and an open mind, celebrations can vary from event to event or year to year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_Rights_Day" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Human Rights Day is celebrated annually across the world on 10 December. It is endorsed by the International Humanist and Ethical Union (IHEU) as an official day of Humanist celebration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.un.org/events/humanrights/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.un.org/eve...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park in the lot.  Through the double doors, hang a right.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259881513000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257710497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GWH December Meeting - Human Rights Day &amp; Humanlight Party</name><id>11826118</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259708400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/11826118/</event_url></item>