<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Burning Chair Readings present A GATHERING OF CANNIBALS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;w/ readings from Cannibal: Issue Three poets:  &lt;br /&gt;Samuel Amadon - Stephanie Anderson - -Elisa Gabbert - Erin Lyndal Martin - Ben Mazer - Christopher Rizzo - Chris Tonelli - Jared White&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Pierre Menard Gallery, 10 Arrow Street in Harvard Square&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;next to Lame Duck Books, 12 Arrow Street, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE ? BYOB&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Samuel Amadon's work has appeared recently in Boston Review, Cannibal, Colorado Review, Denver Quarterly, Modern Review, and The New Review of Literature.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie Anderson's work has appeared in American Letters &amp;amp; Commentary, Boston Review, Denver Quarterly, Spinning Jenny, and Tin House, among others.  Her chapbook, In the Particular Particular, won the 2006 DIAGRAM/New Michigan Press Chapbook Contest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elisa Gabbert's recent work can be found in Colorado Review, Eleven Eleven, Pleiades, Meridian, Washington Square, Cannibal and Diagram. She is the author of two chapbooks from Kitchen Press, Thanks for Sending the Engine (2007) and My Fear of X (forthcoming), as well as a collection of collaborative poems written with Kathleen Rooney, That Tiny Insane Voluptuousness (Otoliths, 2008).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Erin Lyndal Martin recently finished her MFA at the University of Alabama.  Her work is forthcoming in Denver Quarterly and Hotel Amerika.&lt;br /&gt;Ben Mazer is the author of The Foundations of Poetry Mathematics (Cannibal Books) and Johanna Poems (Cy Gist Press).  He is the editor of Landis Everson's Everything Preserved: Poems 1955-2005 (Graywolf Press), and a contributing editor to Fulcrum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Rizzo is a writer and publisher who lives in New York. Over the years, his work has appeared in Art New England, The Cultural Society, Cannibal, Dusie, H_NGM_N, and Spell among other magazines. Christopher has also authored several chapbooks, such as Claire Obscure (Katalanche Press, 2005), Zing (Carve Editions, 2006), and The Breaks (Fewer &amp;amp; Further Press, 2006). Full on Jabber, a collaborative work written with poet Jess Mynes, was released by Martian Press in 2007. Christopher also edits Anchorite Press, an independent poetry publisher of innovative work. He is a doctoral candidate in English at the University at Albany.&lt;br /&gt;Chris Tonelli lives in the Boston area where he runs The So and So Series. He has work forthcoming in Saltgrass, Salt Hill, Absent, and Good Foot, and is the author of three chapbooks: For People Who Like Gravity and Other People (Rope-A-Dope Press, forthcoming), A Mule-Shaped Cloud (w/ Sarah Bartlett, horse less press, 2008), and WIDE TREE: Short Poems (Kitchen Press, 2006).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jared White grew up near Boston and is currently living in Brooklyn, New York. His poems have appeared in such journals as Barrow Street, Fugue, Harp and Altar, The Modern Review and Sawbuck; they are forthcoming in Fulcrum, Horse Less Review, LVNG and elsewhere. He?s about to finish his MFA at Columbia University, where he received a prize from the Academy of American Poets in 2005. He blogs from time to time about poems and culture at jaredswhite.blogspot.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210275597000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206144318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>This week's : A Cannibal Reading</name><id>7579271</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209166200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/7579271/</event_url></item>