<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Huntington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02136</zip><lat>42.338568</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>MFA</name><city>Boston</city><id>844534</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093673</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is NOT your Disney's Sleeping Beauty, but the reviews I've read were generally positive and it sounds very interesting. It's recommended you get your ticket in advance for this one (see www.mfa.org).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the film:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sleeping Beauty (La belle endormie)&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;by Catherine Breillat (2010, 82 min.). French provocateur Catherine Breillat (
&lt;em&gt;Fat Girl&lt;/em&gt;,&amp;nbsp;
&lt;em&gt;Bluebeard&lt;/em&gt;) continues her deconstruction of classic fairytales. Cursed at birth by an evil fairy, Anastasia is destined to prick her finger and die at the age of sixteen. When three feckless fairy sisters discover this they hatch a plan to alter the curse: rather than die, Anastasia will sleep for 100 years. While in slumber, Anastasia comes of age through a series of vivid dreams, filled with charming princes, dwarves, gypsies, and magical creatures. When she reawakens a fully formed adolescent, she finds that in real life, happy endings are more elusive than in our fantasies. This constantly surprising, thought-provoking investigation of the female psyche reaffirms Breillat as one of the most inventive and risk-taking of contemporary French auteurs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Introduced by T. Jefferson Kline, Professor of French, Boston University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313947217000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310317057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sleeping Beauty</name><id>25222901</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311447600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/25222901/</event_url></item>