<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 1A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.839012</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Salisbury Beach</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>314408</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.845360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>New Location Update.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BYOB Blankets, Umbrellas, Beach Games and Food&lt;br /&gt;Into Salisbury State Beach, you enter....&lt;br /&gt;Navigate the long road&lt;br /&gt;Go ALL the way to the end, &lt;br /&gt;Open your day for some sun and sand and a beautiful beach!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event's location has been changed. Most of the Plum Island beach areas are closed due to the plovers and there were too many bugs biting there last week. Let's meet at Salisbury State Beach, go all the way to the last parking lot. As you enter onto the beach we will be toward the right heading toward the rocks. The weather sounds like it will be a good day for this. Some of us are bringing frisbees, whiffle ball, kites, etc. Don't forget your radio, towel, chair, your picnic and of course, suntan lotion!&lt;br /&gt;See you at the beach for some summer fun in the sun, maybe head out for dinner and drinks somewhere if enough people are interested in extending the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Salisbury Beach is located on the coast of north-eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;From Rte. 95: Take exit 58A to Newburyport and the intersection with Rte. 110 east. Follow Rte. 110 East to Salisbury and the intersection with Rte. 1a North. Turn right on Rte. 1a and follow it 2 miles to the Park entrance on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rte. 495: Take Rte. 495 to exit 55 and the intersection with Rte. 110. Follow Rte 110 East to Salisbury and the intersection with Rte. 1a north. Follow Rte. 1a north approximately 2 miles to the Park entrance on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking fees are charged.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183990158000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181264439000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beach Blanket BINGO...</name><id>5866992</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183816800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/5866992/</event_url></item>