<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>407 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comicazi</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1498136</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121231</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The comic book store in Davis Square has bi-monthly comic book meetings. The next book to be discussed is Planetary (one of my favorites) on Tuesday, Feb. 15 at 7:30pm.&amp;nbsp;I haven't been to one of these yet, but I'm going to try it out and thought others might want to as well. They said the length depends on how much people have to say, but typically last about an hour to an hour and a half. They also mentioned that sometimes book club members bring baked goods :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll show up at least 15 minutes early and will be milling about the store . If you haven't met me at the social meetup yet, I'm about 5'6" tall with straight light brown hair (my picture is recent) and I answer to Robyn. Please feel free to come up and introduce yourself&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
The store itself recently moved (literally) next door to a much larger location. Half of the store is comics and the other half is toys/figurine type memorabilia.&amp;nbsp;
Davis Square is on the Red Line. There is metered (bring your quarters) parking around the area. PLEASE NOTE: If you park illegally in Davis Square you will be ticketed (even if your meter runs out for five minutes)- they have multiple cops rotating around the square ticketing cars at all times- so be careful.&amp;nbsp;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn</member_name><member_id>9373103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297873711000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296698879000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comic book-club- Planetary</name><id>16421380</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297816200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/16421380/</event_url></item>