<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Dunster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-441-9797</phone><name>Finale Dessert Company</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>796663</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119213</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for the December Creative Show &amp;amp; Tell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a delicious show &amp;amp; tell, bring your art, or photos of your art to share with the group and get useful feedback on from other creative peoples! Perhaps you have an idea for something new or want to revive and old creative hobby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Folks show up with sculpture in clay, glass &amp;amp; wood, design portfolios, slide shows on computer, or come for the inspiration and desire to do those things - and leave with first hand knowledge and often new creative friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who are new to the group, Welcome! I also want to let you know that there is a $5 lifetime dues, payable at the first event you attend. This helps to cover the annual fee I pay to Meetup to have this group, also whenever possible I will chip in a to help cover tips at restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These events are always lots of fun with lots of networking and sheer talk about technique and materials, I could go on, but let those who have gone before say it..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finale won't do reservations, but I think we can find a few tables to put together - please do confirm with a yes or no as I want to try to prepare with enough seats for those attending and not hold tables that go empty - If you can't get there till 7, that's ok - just note that in the comment when you RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What people are saying about this monthly event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ Really had a fun time, great to put faces with names and see what fun things folks were doing. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“  Great group of people. I especially enjoyed viewing everyone's work. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ It was really interesting to see work of other members and their different perspective about creative ideas. The only thing I didn't like was that only 7 members showed up when till the last moment there were 17 Yes to this Meetup. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ Nice location, good size group for me since I was new. It was smaller (7 total) but easier to get to know people. Nice work shown, too. Paul was great at collecting info to send out. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ A wonderful group of people - this was my first time at a meetup - and great to compare notes on various artistic endeavors. The event was well-organized. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ Wonderful time, everyone was really connecting and showing their work. These just keep getting better and better - can't wait for the next one! ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ This is a great event and loved hearing about what everyone else is doing. Definitely spurred some creative energy! Really enjoyed meeting and connecting with everyone. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ Was fun! Nice to meet you all and see your work. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will run with a minimum of 4 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS here's Finale's site for directions &amp;amp; parking: &lt;a href="http://www.finaledesserts.com/locations-cambridge.php#directions" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.finaledess...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside the door, black hat, beard &amp; ponytail</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261523395000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258952487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Show &amp; Tell</name><id>11936719</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261350000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/11936719/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/b/global_6810507.jpeg</photo_url></item>