<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>DEAF JAM Weds, Nov 9 @ 7:00 pm 2011 Centerpiece Film; Massachusetts Theatrical Premiere, with director Judy Lieff, film subject Aneta Brodski in person and special slam poetry performance by Ayisha Knight-Shaw, deaf poet signing in ASL. Encore screening will include Aneta Brodski and director Judy Lieff in person. Teen Aneta Brodski attends a school for the Deaf in Queens and inhabits the exuberant world of American Sign Language (ASL) poetry. Filmmaker Judy Lieff chronicles Aneta's bold entry into Manhattan's spoken-word slam scene, where Aneta, an Israeli immigrant, meets Tahani, a hearing Palestinian-American slam poet. The two collaborate on a powerful duet that mirrors the complex worlds they share. Deaf Jam uses innovative film techniques to honor ASL as a three-dimensional language that exists in space - like dance. In English and ASL, fully captioned, ASL interpreted. Sponsored by Northeastern University Programs in Jewish Studies; Women's, Gender and Sexuality Studies; Cinema Studies; and ASL; and the Dept. of Languages, Literatures and Cultures.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Erika Wentworth</member_name><member_id>487803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321220576000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>ASL Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonasl</urlname><id>1298565</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston ASL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320430920000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DEAF JAM!</name><id>39965682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320883200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonasl/events/39965682/</event_url></item>