<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1820 Coyote Point Drive</address_1><state>CA</state><zip>94401</zip><lat>37.588985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coyote Point Yacht Club</name><city>San Mateo</city><id>12236302</id><country>us</country><lon>-122.320007</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our topic this Happy Friday March 15th is about &lt;strong&gt;"Blogging is the KING of Social Media!!!"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Four Concrete Steps to Get 10,000 Relevant Customers to Visit Your Web Site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://billbelew.com/subscribe/"&gt;Bill Belew&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a nationally renowned blogger who has turned this skill into a profitable cyberspace occupational. You are invited to attend his unique presentation at our lunch meeting this Happy Friday March 15th. Come hone your knowledge of how to use blogging to bring your business into the 21st century to increase your profits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://billbelew.com/subscribe/"&gt;Bill Belew&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, who's been a full-time blogger since early 2006, describes his business as an online publishing platform that serves 10 unrelated niche themes attracting one million unique visitors and more than 100 million views overall (and still counting). This allows him to make money around the clock, because he gets paid from the advertising revenue that his web sites attract with ever-growing volume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bill will answer the following questions in his talk to Successful Thinkers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His talk, &lt;strong&gt;"4 Concrete Steps to Get 10,000 Relevant Customers to Visit Your Web Site,"&lt;/strong&gt; will answer the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How much work does it take to build a quality site?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How is quality defined in a blog?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How often should a blogger post to get best results?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How long does it take before a blogger can see real results? &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Successful Thinkers Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a group of like minded professionals who believe others will buy or use products and services from people they like, know, and trust. &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building relationship&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is key to our membership and how we develop potential customers and clients. Members share ideas and information to benefit the community and their business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;Successful Thinkers Network's&lt;/span&gt; mission is to help develop relationships that will enable members to find solutions to business challenges.&lt;/strong&gt; We welcome you to join us to see how this can help you and your business.There is no membership fee. There is a $7 fee at the door that goes directly to the venue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;OUR SF/PENINSULA CHAPTER meets at a private YACHT club , overseeing the bay, with a beautiful surrounding and serene atmosphere. We are on a gorgeous walking trail with tables if you wish to meet and connect with other members after or before the lunch meeting. Please bring your lunch with you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you would prefer to order lunch from the yacht club, call Madlen at [masked]. She can reserve a salad or hamburger for you for $8.00.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;There is ample parking available. Be sure to notify the gate keeper as you enter that you are going to the YACHT CLUB, so you don't get charged.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successful Thinkers is changing the way we network and do business. Our focus is on building relationships &amp;amp; paying it forward. Please join our group, attend our lunch meetings and mixers, and bring a guest. You are welcome to put your business material on our display table for all members. We are a family and you are encouraged to check us out for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join now it's FREE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://successfulthinkersnetwork.com/?r=8744"&gt;http://successfulthinkersnetwork.com?r=8744&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Belew</member_name><member_id>15846731</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Traffic Professor Assistant</member_name><member_id>66881722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363372783000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Marketers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-SEO-small-Business-Bloggers</urlname><id>1539090</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Inbound Marketing University - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363154903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Special Event! Successful Thinkers Weekly Event This Friday with Bill Belew!</name><id>109021712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363361400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-SEO-small-Business-Bloggers/events/109021712/</event_url></item>