<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Start out the winter hiking season and find a excuse not to go shopping on Boxing Day, by climbing Mt Pierce via the Crawford Path from Rt 302. If clear, the view up the ridge to Washington is something special. Round trip is about 6 miles with a book time of 4 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is intended to be a intermediate hike for folks who want to make the transition to winter hiking. The pace will be moderate but steady going up the mountain. Crawford Path is a former bridle path for horses, so it is well graded. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traction aids, snowshoes and insulated winter boots are required for the event. As there is a short upper section of the trail that is in the alpine zone, each hiker needs enough clothing to cover every part of their exposed skin. Please make sure that you have a way of attaching the snowshoes to your pack as they will not be needed for a majority of the trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The place to meet is the Crawford Path parking lot just in on the Mt Clinton Road east of the AMC Highland Center. If the road is not plowed we will meet on the south end of the Highland Center parking lot. I will be driving a black Honda Civic Hatchback. We will leave the parking lot at 9:30 AM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The current long range forecast is up in the air and will be until Christmas day. If the projected storm moves inland, the event will be canceled. If the Saturday evening forecast for Twin Mountain NH on Weather Underground calls for more than a 30% chance of snow on Sunday, the event will be canceled. I will post the status by 9 PM on Saturday.   &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293503232000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292948552000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boxing our Way up Mt  Pierce</name><id>15789766</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293373800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15789766/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>