<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Danielson Room - La Cava Building</address_2><address_1>175 Forest Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.387332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-891-2106</phone><name>Conference Center at Bentley College</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1048857</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.219859</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CIPNE Lecture with Photographer Christopher Wilson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How Christopher Wilson Reinvented Himself As A Commercial Photographer&lt;br /&gt;After Fifteen Years As An Advertising Creative And Much To His Surprise Became Successful At It...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 15 years in the advertising world as a writer, art director and designer, Christopher Wilson jumped off a cliff in 2003 to start christopherWILSONphotography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an advertising creative, Christopher created a vast portfolio of powerful branding communications for some of the most recognized luxury brands on the planet, including Audi, Infiniti, Jaguar, Nikon, Johnnie Walker and Ritz-Carlton to name only a very few – much of which can be viewed at www.christopherWILSONcreative.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now Christopher is bringing all that experience and passion to his photography – and it shows. In five short years Christopher has leapt from agency creative to global photographer, shooting for an assortment of clients (including Ritz-Carlton, Morgan Stanley, Ford and NASCAR,) and in just about every country on the planet it seems –&lt;br /&gt;India, Singapore, South Africa, Ethiopia, Rwanda, Morocco, United Arab Emirates, Brazil, England, you name it, he’s probably shot there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christopher will spend the evening talking about how he made his successful transition from agency creative to commercial photographer, and how having an agency background has given him a distinct advantage in obtaining work as a photographer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be an excellent program, please join us for networking, food, and a great evening discussion about photography. For more details stay tuned and check out the CIPNE.org web site for all the details and how to register. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited so please RSVP - ASAP.&lt;br /&gt;You must RSVP to this event at the &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org...&lt;/a&gt; web site. This is not a worcester photo meetup event.&lt;br /&gt;Save the date!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free to CIPNE members - Non Members $35.00 (this is very worth the cost!- don't miss this!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conference Center at Bentley College&lt;br /&gt;La Cava Center- Danielson Room&lt;br /&gt;175 Forest Street&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;781-891-2106&lt;br /&gt;scott@erbphoto.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253928502000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251398495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Must See Lecture by Top Photographer and Creative Voice Christopher Wilson!</name><id>11217151</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253570400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11217151/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/global_10416090.jpeg</photo_url></item>