<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A Day with Ann Monteith&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann Monteith is the industry’s foremost authority on marketing and managing photographic studios, and she is the&lt;br /&gt;immediate past Chairman of the Board of Professional Photographers of America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;She will devote the day to providing the practical insight required to solve some of the most challenging&lt;br /&gt;problems photographers face today.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These include: establishing your business concept, perfecting your business image, how to differentiate your&lt;br /&gt;business in an age of growing competition . . . including competition from “prosumers,” understanding what it&lt;br /&gt;takes to market your business successfully in today’s evolving market: the “boutique studio” revolution and the&lt;br /&gt;“Entitlement Generation” as consumers, how to price your photography for profit, how to sell to the public with&lt;br /&gt;confidence, how to handle business finances, revenue and expense realities, how to track your business&lt;br /&gt;progress, how to assure adequate cash flow, simple ways to make goal setting pay off, and taking care of&lt;br /&gt;workflow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann Monteith has helped thousands of photographers make more money and improve their business and&lt;br /&gt;personal lives. So don’t miss this opportunity to learn!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vtprophoto.org/page7.html" target="_blank"&gt;Link for more information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269349644000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266015738000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presentation -- A Day with Ann Monteith </name><id>12591794</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269176400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12591794/</event_url></item>