<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We're looking forward to a great new guest weekend up at Wedeln! All are welcome to arrive starting at 7pm on Friday and stay until Sunday. Guest fees are just $20 per night, and to help you get a little more bang for your buck, we'll include a continental breakfast on both Saturday and Sunday (Coffee, bagels, yogurt, granola, fruit, etc), pbj makings for our Sunday hike, and we'll provide light snacks at for Friday night as we relax at the house.  I'm sure they'll be people willing to share as well. Weekend plan, must-packs, and directions can be found below. &lt;b&gt;Please RSVP by 10pm on Weds.&lt;/b&gt; Call or email me with any questions (617-640-7396).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday, we’ve planned an outing to the Woodland Valley Disc Golf course, Southern Maine's premiere disc golf course, consisting of 36 holes set on 120 acres of woodland. The PDGA rates it as the best closest Folf course to Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Sports Club (it’s just under 1 hour away, akin to a trip to Sunday River from Wedeln). It’s also super cheap:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admissions / Rental&lt;br /&gt;* 18 Holes Adult: $4.00&lt;br /&gt;* 18 Holes Junior (12 and under): $3.00&lt;br /&gt;* All Day Pass Adult: $8.00&lt;br /&gt;* All Day Pass Junior: $6.00&lt;br /&gt;* Disc Rental: $1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll leave Wedeln on the earlier side of noon, arrive at the course in the early afternoon, around 1 PM. Folf for a few hours, then head back, stopping at a wonderful restaurant called Krista’s in Downtown Cornish Village, Maine (check out their Beer List!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who have never played, if you’ve ever thrown a Frisbee, you can play Folf and have fun with it. If nothing else it provides something else to do while you walk through the lovely Maine woods in autumn. For those of you who have played at Wildcat or Bretton Woods, those aren’t real Folf courses; they’re ski slopes and don’t provide as good an experience as a place like Woodland.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ll probably find you’ll need to adjust your Frisbee throwing technique, though, because the discs are formed differently and have different weights/sizes. I’ve found it’s actually helpful to think of it as a disc instead of a Frisbee. Here’s one of many brief YouTube tutorials on how to throw a Folf disc:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday, we'll get an early start and hike up Kearsarge. Be sure to wear layers as it will be cool in the morning and also cool up top. Good hiking boots are recommended, as are snacks and water. A back pack is a good idea!  The Kearsarge mountain trail head is a quick walk from the Wedeln Lodge. The hike will take 4 to 5 hours, depending on how long we spend up top.  It's a moderate to challenging hike.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other things to pack for the weekend: Bedding (pillow, sheet, sleeping bag), towel, shower shoes (though our bathrooms are very clean), toiletries.  Accommodations are dormitory-style bunk beds, in bedrooms separated by gender.  Check out the lodge at www.wedeln.com.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You can't miss us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286892046000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284334917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Guest Fall Foliage Weekend @ Wedeln Lodge</name><id>14746386</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285974000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/14746386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/8/global_14726280.jpeg</photo_url></item>