<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll be logging in for the last time around 6pm Thursday night, and won't log in on Friday.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca has offered to host a gaming event at her place on New Years day. Here is the info.  As she has limited space, and has invited others as well, priority will be going to Yes RSVPs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the info...    The event is co-listed with Beantown Singles -- &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/calendar/12068176/"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/calendar/12068176/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  --so make sure you only sign up on one site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;Let's play some games!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You're invited to my house in Jamaica Plain on New Year's Day to play board games&lt;/b&gt;--Apples to Apples, Life, Settlers of Catan -- both party games and logic games and traditional board games. Come relax after New Year's Eve, nosh some food, and have some fun with pieces, tokens, dice, and cards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;See below for a list of games that I own&lt;/b&gt;; feel free to bring anything else you have. I'll keep a running list of games people are bringing, so we won't have duplicates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm also asking you to bring some nosh food (snacks) or &lt;u&gt;non-alcoholic drinks&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;I am a strict vegetarian, so you cannot bring cheese (cheddar popcorn, e.g.), marshmallows or gelatin (jelloMilk, eggs and butter are fine.&lt;/span&gt; Chocolate-themed food is very fine! If people are interested in making mulled cider, I have the spices; hot chocolate (milk + melted chocolate) would also be great (we can have whipped cream with it).  Cookies, chips, pretzels, cake--all good things to bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;It is rude to both the organizer (that's me) and to the other attendees (that's all of you) if you RSVP Yes and then don't show up. SO DON'T RSVP YES unless you know you can definitely make it! If your plans change--then change your RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I removed the option to RSVP as a Maybe, because I have (had) people on the waitlist; if you're not sure you can come, RSVP as No with a comment &amp;quot;want to come&amp;quot; and if spots open up, I'll change your RSVP myself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm scheduling this to start at 1pm, for after lunch/brunch.&lt;/b&gt; (Please eat a meal before you come.) But you're welcome to show up late, and jump in whenever a game ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll play at least until 5 or 6pm, or whenever people want to stop. If people love playing and don't want to stop, but are really hungry, you can order food in--but it has to be vegetarian (really! I said I'm strict!). There's an Indian restaurant down the street, among others, that has lots of vegetarian options. Ask me about this in advance so I can prepare (get you menus, etc.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I live in Jamaica Plain, off the Orange line and 39 bus; there's also free street parking. &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Exact address will be given to those who RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also note: I won't be checking my e-mail on January 1st. So get all the info you need from me by mid-day on 12/31.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Games I own:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Life&lt;br /&gt;Mastermind&lt;br /&gt;Backgammon&lt;br /&gt;Mille Borne&lt;br /&gt;Rummy Q &lt;br /&gt;Yahtzee&lt;br /&gt;Uno&lt;br /&gt;Pictionary &lt;br /&gt;Monopoly &lt;br /&gt;decks of cards&lt;br /&gt;Boggle/Big Boggle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Games others are bringing:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bang, Stone Age (RSVP is Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Scrabble (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Racko, Phase 10 (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Space Hulk (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Dalmuti, Taboo, Mars Fluxx (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Apples to Apples (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Carcassone, Settlers of Catan (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Bananagrams (Maybe) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Food/drinks others are bringing:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;chocolate and tapioca pudding (RSVP is Yes)&lt;br /&gt;apple juice (Yes)&lt;br /&gt;carrots (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;a few single-serve bottles of diet Pepsi (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;orange juice (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Chai (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;sweet potato pie (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;casserole (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;Pepsi, chips/popcorn (Yes) &lt;br /&gt;cupcakes (RSVP is Maybe) &lt;br /&gt;hummus &amp;amp; pita (Maybe) &lt;br /&gt;pie (Maybe) &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>balloons on fence to identify house</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Becki</member_name><member_id>4147212</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1262574544000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261372517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Year's Day board games (in Jamaica Plain)</name><id>12124198</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262368800000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/12124198/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>