<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For our August Meetup, we've decided to take a field trip to &lt;b&gt;Fuller Craft Museum&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Fuller is a little gem of a facility. It's one of only 8 museums nationwide specializing in contemporary crafts--more or less what we do--and it's right in our (general) area. They've got many cool exhibitions right now, and I'll bet we'll all find plenty of ideas and inspiration there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.fullercraft.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fullercraf...&lt;/a&gt; for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When: &lt;/b&gt; Meet in the museum lobby, or at the front door, at 1 p.m. *sharp.* If you arrive after that, just pay your own admission fee and wander around until you find us. We can go through the galleries, gift shop and grounds on our own or in a group--whatever people prefer. There's a guided tour of the galleries at 2 p.m. for anyone who's interested. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone's interested in meeting for lunch beforehand, let's start planning. Just start a thread on the Message Board. I don't know the area well, but the museum has a cafe and it's also not far from the Westgate Mall, which has places to eat, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt; The Fuller is located in Brockton, just over the Stoughton line. It's just off Route 24 near the Westgate Mall. For planning purposes, it's about 26 miles from our usual meeting venue in Wellesley. If you're interested in car-pooling, visit the &amp;quot;August Meetup&amp;quot; thread on the Message Board to make arrangements.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; There's no Meetup fee for this event--BUT each attendee is responsible for her or his own admission fee to the museum (see museum site for prices).  You may be able to get in free or with a discount if you have an AAA or WGBH card. If not, the usual admission price is $8 for adults, $5 for seniors and students. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Activities:&lt;/b&gt; We'll hold off on all our usual activities -- challenge cards, the games swap, background exchanges -- until our next Meetup in early September.  Watch the Message Board for further updates!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup group in the lobby. Details to come.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219861354000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208335807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August NE ATC+ Meetup: Field Trip to Fuller Craft Museum! NOTE NEW TIME</name><id>7749328</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219510800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/7749328/</event_url></item>