<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>At our April meetup, let's continue to check-in on how we're doing moving towards manifesting our &amp;quot;Be-Do-Have&amp;quot; intentions using Law Of Attraction (LOA). &lt;b&gt;Please come prepared to share so we can support and learn from each other.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have been diligently using the LOA principles in your life, you might find that you are doing fabulously well in some areas of your life and lacking in others. Or you might have good intentions but keep having resistance taking consistent LOA-related actions. You might have become frustrated and despondent and faking it til you make it ain't working.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's self-sabotaging you might be negative feelings, unproductive habits and limiting beliefs. In order to use LOA to gain inner peace, happiness, success and abundance in ALL areas of your life, you will need to &amp;quot;make peace&amp;quot; and get rid of counterproductive and damaging negative feelings etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hussein Alhadi, Graduate of Sedona Training and BostonLOA member,&lt;/b&gt; shares with us the power behind the Sedona Method releasing techniques.  Learn to ask the &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; questions to simply acknowledge and release feelings around negative or limiting beliefs and/or thoughts. You'll find yourself aligning more easily to the higher vibrations related to LOA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year, Hussein had provided a sampling of how subtle yet powerful one of Sedona Method's releasing techniques could be. This time he will provide more in-depth information of 4 techniques for you to learn and practice during our meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Sedona Method&lt;/b&gt; is a simple-to-master, very easy-to-follow, powerful tool that hundreds of thousands of people have used &lt;b&gt;to gently &amp;quot;let go&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; of painful, unwanted, counterproductive feelings &lt;b&gt;in the moment.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What makes The Sedona Method a powerful tool is that it follows a simple process &lt;b&gt;you can use anytime, anyplace,&lt;/b&gt; to improve any area of your life...&amp;quot; - Hale Dwoskin, Sedona Method co-founder, one of the teachers featured in The Secret&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you very much, Hussein, for your gift of time, knowledge and facilitation at our April meetup!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So let's not FOOL around anymore - no more excuses about why LOA is not working for you - come and learn about the Sedona Method releasing techniques to help you move forward to a great 2008!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Hussein Alhadi&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;husseincoach@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;617-304-6162&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hussein is a personal &amp;amp; business coach and an enthusiastic student and &amp;quot;practice-ioner&amp;quot; of Law Of Attraction. He is a Graduate of Sedona Training.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207600021000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204679517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction April Meeting</name><id>7465785</id><headcount>41</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207090800000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/7465785/</event_url></item>