<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Big Mouth Off - Story Slam Grand Finale, showcases winners of our September 2011- April 2012 season of slams Don't miss this unforgettable night of live story!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coolidge Corner Theater 7:00 PM, Wednesday, April 11th, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets: $20 on-line @ massmouth.eventbrite.com or $25 at the door, first come first serve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This season massmouth Story Slams have exploded in popularity and in 2011-12 took we held slams in Somerville, Cambridge, Jamaica Plain, Quincy and as far away as Lowell and Worcester. Many times people were turned away at the door because of overflow. It's clear, we are here to stay and growing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our slams attracted seasoned professionals and fledgling storytellers alike sharing their experiences and revealing their insights on themes like: emergency***supernatural***stupid-cupid***resolution***wheels***obsession*** shell-shocked home***cupid***genesis***idols***gifts***pranked***college dayz. At each slam contestants who are storytellers and lawyers, medical students, homeschooling moms, journalists, grad students, artists and professional storytellers shared real life stories and competed for a place in the semifinals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The winners of those contests will perform here as they compete for the grand prize- a week in a medieval Tuscan townhouse, yes that's Tuscany, Italy! Tickets are $20 on line and $25 at the door. All proceeds benefit the StoriesLive&amp;reg; High School Scholarship Story Slam. Last year storytellers from massmouth,inc. taught 1,100 high school students to tell their personal stories and distributed over $5000 in prizes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are more prizes for the winners chosen by the distinguished judges. In addition there will be ONE Audience Choice winner chosen by the at the end of the evening, so you get to vote! In between sets of judged stories, the audience can participate in a mini-slam of stories on the theme - "wrong turn".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come experience massmouth&amp;lsquo;s final story slam of the 2011-2012 season, live !&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334190070000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332122857000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Final Story Slam at Coolidge Corner Theater</name><id>56898002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334185200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/56898002/</event_url></item>