<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>one of my bestest friends Jilly posted this for me on my &amp;quot;meeting and greeting in so. nh and merrimack valley&amp;quot; group...geesh, who thought of that name?&lt;br /&gt;anyway, this is what jilly is doing, in my very own yard...&lt;br /&gt;WE REMEMBER LAUREN TISBERT: We have done our best to console and support our friend Susan Tisbert following the passing of her beloved daughter, Lauren, in September. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE PLAN: Lauren's favorite flowers are tulips. It would be lovely to create a garden of tulips ringing around a favorite tree on Susan's lawn. After a long cold winter will come the warmth and color of Spring! How nice to look forward to the blooming of tulips planted by friends, in honor and rememberance of Lauren!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE NEED: People!! Please bring a bag or two of tulips bulbs, and/or a bag of topsoil. Both of these items can be purchased at Home Depot or Lowes. Not expensive, and we need plenty of both! &lt;br /&gt;If you have a bulb planter, bring that too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;QUESTIONS: Tulip bulbs are favorite treats for critters. They need to be protected by either soaking them in solution that repels critters from feasting upon them, or by laying screening over the planted area, secured by stones or stakes, then removed in early spring for blooming. IF ANYONE HAS ANY IDEAS OR EXPERTISE TO SHARE, PLEASE DO!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE REST: Susan needs help with raking her leaves, so we want to do this too. Have a rake or a leaf blower? Bring them! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE FUN: We will have a potluck day, so please bring something to share. Susan will have her BBQ available. A bonfire may be possible, weather permitting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A RULE: Since this is a private home, RSVPs from members who do not have a pic. posted will not be accepted. This is for security and &amp;quot;comfort zone&amp;quot; reasons, and it will be enforced. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: Park in Susan's driveway or along Keyes Hill Road but on-street parking is only legal on Susan's side of the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: &lt;br /&gt;1) A chair &lt;br /&gt;2) Tulip bulbs or topsoil or BOTH. A bulb planter or small spade, if you have one. &lt;br /&gt;3) Food to share and BYOBeverage please. &lt;br /&gt;4) Rake, leafblower. &lt;br /&gt;5) A pretty garden ornament? Little statues, pretty stones, any creative touches you may wish to add.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'M ALMOST DONE: Please come even if you only have an hour to spare, or can stay longer. &lt;br /&gt;Post any ideas because SUGGESTIONS and FEEDBACK are welcome! &lt;br /&gt;And remember: &amp;quot;MANY HANDS MAKE LIGHT WORK&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN DATE: The following Saturday, November 13th. Can't do Sundays- it IS Patriots season!! &lt;br /&gt;a little over the top miss jilly, but who loves ya' baby!! SUZ &lt;br /&gt;email me for directions, I don't know about putting my address out there...eowwww&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289230359000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288136863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>planting tulips...</name><id>15240573</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289052000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/15240573/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/2/global_19105234.jpeg</photo_url></item>