<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a seminar that will include a discussion and experience of meditation as a way of stilling the mind.  It will include teachings from Universal truths and Jesus's own words on the subject of meditation and how he used it to rise above the frenzy of the world to reach in and up to a loving Father/Mother God, with whom he communed to the point of being one with God.  Jesus said, &amp;quot;My Father/ Mother God and I are one.&amp;quot;  Jesus kissed his cross and blessed the ones who crucified him.  How did he keep his mind on his mission so solidly?  How did he stay centered in the midst of his strife? How can we do the same in our life with wars and fighting and misunderstanding of people with people? This workshop will be a place for answers and questions of all kinds related to this topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes is a Master Teacher of Christian Mysticism for over 30 years.  His Love and devotion to God as one who has been loved and changed by God is tangible and real. His wisdom will change the way you think about who you are and what God is.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one you dont want to miss. See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://centersoflight.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://centersoflight.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://centersoflight...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540442000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1155268831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Stilling the mind to attain inner peace.</name><id>5071972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1155942000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/5071972/</event_url></item>