<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Allston  (2nd Floor)</address_2><address_1>14 Harvard Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.355206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-783-8001</phone><name>Brazilian Immigrant Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>1609586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132675</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello All,  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; I am happy to announce that the Brazilian Immigrant Center will start a Level 2 Portuguese May 5th at 7:00pm. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Instructor:&amp;nbsp; Carmem Denadai Nicoli.&amp;nbsp; Ms. Nicoli is Brazilian. She is  from Minas Gerais. She has a degree in Portuguese from two universities  in Brazil. She also has a degree in Brazilian literature. Before coming  to the United States, she taught Portuguese&amp;nbsp; in high schools for 10  years.&amp;nbsp; She is extremely excited about this course.&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Goals:&amp;nbsp; This course is for people interested in learning to speak, read, and write Brazilian Portuguese.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; First Class: If would be best if everyone came to the first course.  &lt;br /&gt; There Carmen would like to talk with you and or hear your Portuguese.  She will also pass out three levels of texts (easy, medium, and hard)&amp;nbsp;  You will be asked to read them out loud and then write something about  the text. RELAX!!!!  &lt;br /&gt; These exercises are intended to assess your reading, writing and  speaking capabilities.&amp;nbsp; At this point, based on your self assessments we  are looking at a level 2 course. However, even in a level 2 course  there will be people who are advanced at some things and a beginner at  others.  &lt;br /&gt; So, we (Professor Nicoli and I) encourage everyone to come to the first class.&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Classes:&amp;nbsp; All classes will include a speaking, writing and reading component.&amp;nbsp; They will last for one and half hour maximum.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;All classes will be taught in Portuguese&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We hope to have Brazilian volunteers coming to the classes to assist in small group discussions.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Refund Policy:&amp;nbsp; Please note if you are not satisfied after the first  class you are entitled to a full refund. You will not receive a refund  if you attend more than two classes. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Materials: Prof Nicoli has several books and resources that she will  collect and copy and have handed out classes.&amp;nbsp; Please be prepared with a  binder or folder to collect the handouts, homework assignments, and  texts.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Assessment and additional classes:&amp;nbsp; Prof Nicoli will adjust the classes  based on the needs of the majority of the students.&amp;nbsp; However, if its  clear that another level of Portuguese classes needs to start,&amp;nbsp; the  Brazilian Immigrant Center and Prof Nicoli will assess costs, interest  and sustainability at the Center.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Again, I encourage all to come to the first lesson if you are  interested. In some cases, you may be higher or lower than you think.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Please&amp;nbsp; pay in advance before the course.&amp;nbsp; The amount is $120.00.&amp;nbsp;  Please let others know about the course as well. I will send out  additional emails. You can mail your checks to The Brazilian Immigrant  Center, 14 Havard Ave, 2nd Floor Allston MA. You can also drop off  payment.&amp;nbsp; You will not be permitted to attend the first class unless you  have made payment. Again, if you do not like the course you will be  entitled to a full refund after you're first lesson.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Excited!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lydia Edwards</member_name><member_id>7660990</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304698112000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302895674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portuguese Lessons or Volunteering at the Brazilian Immigrant Center</name><id>17318751</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304636400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/17318751/</event_url></item>