<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>450 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.342730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.267.8862</phone><name>South End Art Studios</name><city>Boston</city><id>769524</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065032</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SOWA Artists Guild First Friday South End Open Studios   5:00 - 9:00 PM  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The First Friday of each month, Guild member artists and others open their studios at 450 Harrison Ave. Boston, MA 02118. Meet the artists in their element and view their latest works. The SoWa Artists Guild strives to make art and artists accessible to everyone.  The event is free and parking is available. There is also usually free wine and snacks offered too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Web Site: &lt;a href="http://www.sowaartistsguild.com/calendar.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sowaartist...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The studios open at 5:00, but I won't be able get there until around 6:30.  We'll meet at 6:30 at the entrance of the Main Lobby for the South End Art Studios at 450 Harrison Ave, Boston.  The entrance is on the side of the Building. You will have to walk along a pedestrian way that is called Thayer Street.  Its no longer a Street but it still has the Thayer Street sign to get to the Lobby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hers is the Meetup link with the Map that shows Thayer street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/venue/769524/?eventId=8807475"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;You can ask to park for Free at the parking lot next to and behind this building or at the big parking lot next to Gaslight down the street. Just tell them you are here for the First Friday Art Studio event. Make sure you DO NOT pay to park it should be free!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The silver line is your closest T bus stop! &lt;br /&gt;Its a 10-15 minute walk from other train T stops!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After visting the studios, we can go somewhere nearby for dinner or get something to drink.&lt;br /&gt;+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Fridays are an integral part of the SOWA Artists Guild mission. The aim is to give visitors access to the artists in their element – to offer a different and more personal way to experience art firsthand. By opening their working space to the public, the SOWA Artists Guild hopes to give people an avenue for viewing quality contemporary art that complements yet goes beyond the gallery experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Fridays appeal to a wide range of art enthusiasts, from seasoned collectors to first time art buyers to those who have never considered art before. Through its participation in these popular events – and by establishing itself as a presence in the SOWA artistic community – the SOWA Artists Guild strives to make its art and its artists accessible to all, working together to inspire people to appreciate art on a whole new level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Artists: The SOWA artist district of Boston has developed into a major artist community with hundreds of artists' studios and dozens of galleries. At the center of SOWA, 450 Harrison Avenue is home to 15 galleries and over 50 artist studios. The members of the SOWA Artist Guild are an eclectic group - from different parts of the world, working in different mediums, each with a unique approach to creative expression. What they share is dedication to their work and a serious pursuit of artistic quality.&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside the entrance to the Main Lobby of the Art Studios</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286063091000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285294513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Friday Open Studios- South End</name><id>14878228</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285972200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/14878228/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/2/global_13743234.jpeg</photo_url></item>