<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You need not be a  Reiki practitioner to attend.  All are welcome to receive a free hands-on Reiki session, taking turns on the table.   With several Reiki practitioners positioned around the table simultaneously, it doesn't take long to treat each person! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each of our Reiki-Share Meetups is followed by a (7-9 PM) presentation of VITAL info that we all must understand in order to prepare for planetary energetic changes arriving on Dec 21, 2012.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each month a different aspect describing the planetary changes will be covered, in addition to techniques to protect against the influx of devistating cosmic energies which will otherwise trigger irreversable changes in our DNA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The exact topic for the next month will be announced after the previous Meetup is over.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For January's MeetUp, our topic is the role played by various types of Angels.  This is very interesting, since it includes information on &lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;ANGELLIC HUMANS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In preparation, please study the definition posted on this link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.keylonticdictionary.org/Words/A/Angelic%20Humans.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.keylonticd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go up the driveway directly across from mailbox #298.  If you made a mistake and went up the second driveway (with ULCS Clinic sign), please turn around and go up the first driveway.  Enter through the front door. This has a MeetUp sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your own refreshments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;u&gt;NOTICE&lt;/u&gt;:  Don't forget to check for last minute cancellations before leaving to attend any Meetup, especially during the winter months when storms are likely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter front door with MeetUp sign and go downstairs.  No need to knock.  Have a seat in waiting room till others arrive.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295396116000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Awakening Indigoes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>IndigoInsights</urlname><id>1319438</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Indigo Insights: Awakening to our Full Potential</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293740856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NOTICE; This month's meetup is cancelled due to snow storm.</name><id>kzrcqypcbxb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295391600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/IndigoInsights/events/15861567/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/1/global_18743441.jpeg</photo_url></item>