<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>299 Harvard Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-738-1603</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1159253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122595</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will have a guest speaker, a professional organizer/life coach, named Sibel Babacan.  She is a lovely woman who used to be a scientist and changed careers now that she has a child.  I have met her personally and think she is lovely.  She will present the nuts and bolts of organizing your homes/lives. This will be a small group. I am limiting this meetup to 12 people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is her website. I think you will agree that she is fantastic!&lt;br /&gt;www.drbeeorganizingsolutions.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any ideas?  Please send them my way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am compiling questions from meetup members that I will give to our presenter. &lt;br /&gt;Sample Questions:&lt;br /&gt;What is your greatest challenge when it comes to de-cluttering?&lt;br /&gt;How do you get yourself unstuck?&lt;br /&gt;How do you organize your decluttering process?&lt;br /&gt;Do you or someone else hold you accountable? &lt;br /&gt;Do you have a friend who holds you accountable?&lt;br /&gt;Do you speak once a week with this person?&lt;br /&gt;Should I set goals for myself? &lt;br /&gt;What kind of goals are realistic?&lt;br /&gt;Having a messy home is getting in the way of me accomplishing my life goals, and I cannot relax at home since I have all this clutter in front of me.  How should I get myself past being stuck like this?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please help us find a space for a group of 12 people in Brookline or Newton on the T and with parking available.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event might fill up quickly.  We get a high turn out when we have a speaker at our events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: May 19&lt;br /&gt;Time: 7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;299 Harvard Street&lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: If you haven't attended an event, please click on &amp;quot;MORE,&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;FILES&amp;quot; to find a document that will help you find Panera and to know where you can park.  Panera is T accessible. It is a short walk from the T.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;Sibel's Biography:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sibel Babacan is the founder and the owner of Dr. Bee Organizing Solutions, a company specializes in organizing and life coaching services.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sibel holds a B.S. in Engineering and Ph.D. in Biological Sciences. Prior to founding Dr. Bee Organizing Solutions, Sibel has worked in academia and corporate R&amp;amp;D as a researcher and supervisor. At every position Sibel has hold, she made use of her organizing and coaching skills as a mentor to undergraduate students and as a supervisor at an international food company. When asked how and why she has made a career transition, Sibel says “I have walked the talk and re-evaluated my life goals after having a family, determining where I would like to be in 10-20 years. This ultimately resulted in a career transition that is more in line with my core values, passion and skills set”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sibel’s formal coaching training is through Coaches Training Institute (CTI) and she follows co-active coaching principles in her life coaching practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sibel has also conducted a number of workshops for non-profit organizations. These workshops were designed to teach the attendants unique skills to organize their homes, identify and prioritize their life goals, and simplify their lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sibel is a member of National Association of Professional Organizers, the Organizing Authority (NAPO), NAPO- New England and Coaches Training Institute Network. She lives with her husband and daughter in Waltham, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1274375904000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272410342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup with Guest Speaker-Sibel Babacan-299 Harvard St., Brookline, MA</name><id>13311853</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274310000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/13311853/</event_url></item>