<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Last night I ran into a couple that had met at the last singles dance! They seemed really happy and were so grateful for the dance and the chance to meet! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're invited to meet your new sweetie at this Meetup's &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Holiday Party Singles Dance&lt;/span&gt; on Saturday, December 10th! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can expect this dance to be very different than the others you've attended. &amp;nbsp;I have located a really nice space quip with a bartender for us. &amp;nbsp; There'll be many raffle prizes to win, delicious appetizers, and a fabulous DJ provided by The Musical Dynamo! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are also several surprises -- and one is that JENNER from Make-up Asylum will be available for FREE lipstick consultations from 8:30-9:30 pm at the dance!!! This fun service is FREE to all paid guests! &amp;nbsp;:) &amp;nbsp;Stay tuned for more gifts and surprises....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALSO beginning at 7:30 pm, Deb will be offering us a FREE SWING DANCE LESSON! So come on over early for that one! &amp;nbsp;I'm excited! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 90 tickets to the Holiday Party available so I encourage you to (a) consider if you are available to come, (b) think about who you would like to be there with you and (c) buy your ticket online. Unlike other dances, where anyone can show up at the last minute, there are a limited # of tickets available for the party. &amp;nbsp;If by chance we have a few spaces available, I will post on this site the day of the party. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be keeping track of gender balance as well. &amp;nbsp;You may find yourself temporarily on a wait-list if the balance is off...just so I can give it time to re-balance itself. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/e/6/c/event_75444172.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm very excited to get these dances going again. &amp;nbsp;I am committed to revitalizing these dances so that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a) &amp;nbsp;We have a GREAT time together; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b) &amp;nbsp;There are plenty of opportunities to meet other singles&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HERE ARE A FEW TIPS TO REMEMBER: &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;DISCOVER&lt;/em&gt; someone new and invite them into your conversation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;ASK&lt;/em&gt; five people to dance every time you attend&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;NEVER&lt;/em&gt; say 'no' when someone asks you to dance; take a risk, say YES!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;CHALLENGE&lt;/em&gt; yourself by trying something new&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;ENTER&lt;/em&gt; the dance space with your best self forward&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inspire a spirit of inclusiveness in a community of like-minded folks - be friendly, finish your conversations before moving on to another one. &amp;nbsp;Be respectful and open in your mind and heart. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DETAILS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a ticket-only Holiday Party Singles Dance&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please RSVP by December 9th and so that your spot is reserved!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Holiday Party will end at 11:30 pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be light snacks and appetizers at the dance; please eat dinner before arriving (or better yet, meet each other for dinner and then head over to dance together!)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be a cash bar; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;please do not bring wine to this event&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Thank you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm really looking forward to seeing you again!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robyn&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will welcome you at the door with a warm smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324857030000</updated><rating><average>4.21000003815</average><count>29</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>120</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317533303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Party Singles Dance</name><id>35783842</id><headcount>85</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323567000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/35783842/</event_url></item>