<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.842580</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Salisbury Beach Bandstand</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>987697</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.817250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Every Saturday night at Salisbury Beach during the summer, the Surfside Live series offers two exciting, free shows: a live concert performance on a beach stage, followed by a spectacular fireworks display launched from a barge over the ocean! What a great way to catch a live band … on a warm summer night in the fresh ocean air! Bring a beach chair or blanket and gather in front of the beachfront stage for a night of great live music, fantastic fireworks, and fun! Getting there is easy: follow directions to the beach in Salisbury, MA … then enter the beach at the Broadway Street beach access. Find a seat in the sand, and get ready for a great summer night at Salisbury Beach! Admission is FREE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet around 6 with snacks to share and cold drinks to sip while we chat for a while before the music starts at 7. Fireworks are at 10.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>MEET AT THE CORNER IN FRONT OF SAL'S PIZZA. THERE ARE SOME BENCHES THERE AND IT IS NEAR THE STAGE. LOOK AT THE PICTURES BEFORE YOU LEAVE SO YOU CAN RECOGNIZE OTHERS.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248732622000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245119347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bellevue Cadillac and Fireworks</name><id>10660324</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248559200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/10660324/</event_url></item>