<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/8/e/event_163859022.jpeg" width="240" height="215" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/b/0/event_163859312.jpeg" width="230" height="216" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/2/6/event_163859942.jpeg" width="488" height="224" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet up for a nice walk starting on Chestnut Plain Road.  We can park and meet at the Whately Center School Offices Building which is addressed at 218 Chestnut Plain Road in Whately.  It is across from the cemetary and at the intersection of Chestnut Plain Road and Christian Lane (Depot Road on google map).  I just found this loop walk today and it took myself and my little one Maggie about 1 hour to do.  What we did was start at the Center School Offices, walk around on to Christian Lane for a few hundred feet, take a trail into the woods which ended up at some farm fields, walk the dirt road around the fields, headed up a gradual hill to the main street in this lovely section of Whately, Chestnut Plain Road.  This is the same road that the Whately Inn is on and we will pass by it.  Another lovely street with 1800 period houses but also with an absolute beautiful view of the mountains, including a fantastic view of the summit house on Mt Sunderland and the road winding around up to it.  Mt Toby is also easily viewed.  What lucky people to have that as a view for their back yard! As shown in the picture above, the leaves are beginning to turn and I am hoping that by the date of the walk, we should have a spectacular colorful autumn view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This walk will have places where dogs need to be on-leash and then places where it is OK to be off-leash.  We will start out as on-leash and especially where we will be near other people's property and roads.  These roads are very low-traffic.  The main street has sidewalks on both sides of the road which are well off the road side.  Looks like a Leave-It-To-Beaver street to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to this parking spot:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Northampton, take route 91 North to exit 24, take a left at the end of the ramp and head South on routes 5&amp;amp;10.  Directions from Greenfield are to take route 91 South to exit 24, take a right at the end of the ramp and head South on routes 5&amp;amp;10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once on routes 5&amp;amp;10, continue until you see an intersection with the Castaway Lounge on your left but don't go in.  I don't want to go dancing there.  :) The Castaway is at an intersection of routes 5&amp;amp;10 and Christian Lane, take a right at the intersection.  Continue for a short time and the road will turn to a Y at the end, take a Left at the Y.  This is now Chestnut Plain Road.  The Center School Offices is immediately on the left once you get on Chestnut Plain Road. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350177484000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348946600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whately Walk</name><id>84694052</id><headcount>9</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350138600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/84694052/</event_url></item>