<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Charter Oak Landing </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.758861</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-665-9428</phone><name>HARTFORD BELLE</name><city>Hartford </city><id>970084</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.670011</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a Cross Post with THE WEST HARTFORD OVER 40 FUN BRUNCH! It is being hosted by Ira Wettenstein...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; THE PARTY AND THE SINGLES HAPPY HOUR CONTINUES &lt;br /&gt;NEW VENUE- NOT JUST A VIEW OF THE WATER, LIKE VITO’S, BUT… &lt;br /&gt;ON THE WATER!!!!!!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALMOST LIKE THE LOVE BOAT , BUT A TAD SMALLER..&lt;br /&gt;HOSTED BY THE IRA ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR SINGLES HAPPY HOUR WILL BE ON THE EVER POPULAR &lt;br /&gt;Hartford BELLE ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Friday, June 12 2009. Exclusive for our Group &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:00PM- 8:00PM on the Beautiful Connecticut River. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrival Time: Please be at the Ship between 5:30: 5:45. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our ship will be at: Charter Oak Landing located on Reserve Road. Our dock is by the gazebo, (Directions Below) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $19.00 for the Two Hour Cruise includes One Drink Ticket: Wine, Beer, Mixed Cocktail. Dry Munchies to be provided. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facts on the Booze: Mixed drinks $6.00, beer &amp;amp; wine $5.00, soda/juice $2.00, water $1.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that due to space limitations we are limited to our &amp;quot;house brands&amp;quot;. We do pour premium brands. Just a note in case you have any &amp;quot;sophisticated&amp;quot; drinkers....not to cause any alarm.. Sorry, we can not bring our own liquor aboard…… &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD: We can bring our own food aboard…….. Please be creative, and bring to share…….. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min and Max Details: We need to have a minimum of 25 Happy Singles to have the boat leave,,,,,,No more than 40, unless we want to use our life jackets……… &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Information: Please let me know no latter than June 11 Thursday at 9:00AM. It is so important that if you say yes, that a yes means yes….. mistrchrming@aol.com. 860-604-5792 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I do not get 25 yes to come, I will notify all that the event is canceled. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or Shin the Ship Leaves. They have an area that is fully covered. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS AND OTHER INFO: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Brainard Rd/Airport Rd. exit off I 91 or Rt 5 &amp;amp; 15. (Chowder Pot Restaurant). Left on Brainard Rd. and follow about 3/4 mile to light. Left on Reserve Rd. (pass Regional Market). Entrance to Charter Oak Landing is on right at RR Crossing, just under the Charter Oak Bridge. Our dock is by the gazebo, Ample free parking. See our website at www.hartfordbelle.com for complete directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Hartford Belle&amp;quot; is a beautiful 49-passenger riverboat - reminiscent &lt;br /&gt;of simpler times. She has a mahogany-trimmed enclosed cabin, but we &lt;br /&gt;like to keep the windows open to enjoy the warm summer breezes. &lt;br /&gt;A full bar is available to serve your favorite drinks and light snacks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is ample seating or you can stand on the bow to get the best views &lt;br /&gt;of your trip along the majestic Connecticut River. It is not uncommon to &lt;br /&gt;see great blue herons, red-tailed hawks and an occasional bald eagle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave Moran of the Hartford Courant said &amp;quot;This was a different part of Connecticut's capital city, even a different aspect of life, than I &lt;br /&gt;was used to seeing...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"At The Boat Dock"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1245015732000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243564438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira Happy Hours Continues on The Water!!!!!!!! Love Boat in Hartford!! </name><id>10519865</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244842200000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/10519865/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/d/global_8855373.jpeg</photo_url></item>