<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1904 Canton Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.223400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 333-0690</phone><name>Blue Hills Trailside Museum</name><city>Milton</city><id>669267</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet at 10:30 in the parking lot near the Trailside Museum. Walk starts at 10:45 and lasts 2 hours.  We will go up to the summit at some point along the way and take in the view.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Trailside Museum &lt;br /&gt;1904 Canton Ave&lt;br /&gt;Milton, MA 02186&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Take Rt I-93 to exit 2B (Milton, Rt 138 North). Follow the exit ramp to the first set of traffic lights. Go straight through the lights and the parking lot is 0.5 miles ahead on the right. The museum is at the end of the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located only minutes from the bustle of downtown Boston, the DCR Blue Hills Reservation stretches over 7,000 acres from Quincy to Dedham, Milton to Randolph, providing a green oasis in an urban environment. Rising above the horizon, Great Blue Hill reaches a height of 635 feet, the highest of the 22 hills in the Blue Hills chain. From the rocky summit visitors can see over the entire metropolitan area. With its scenic views, varied terrain and 125 miles of trails, the Blue Hills Reservation offers year-round enjoyment for the outdoor enthusiast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/blue.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scotch Bonnet Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;756 Washington St&lt;br /&gt;Stoughton, MA 02072&lt;br /&gt;(781) 344-0220 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With an emphasis on authentic Jamaican foods, The Scotch Bonnet is a casual eat-in and take-out destination. The affordable menu includes a number of lunch and dinner options, such as curried shrimp, steamed shrimp, fried chicken, and more, including a number of side dishes and the specialty jerk chicken which is spicy and especially hot. A modest lineup of beverages provides a mix of sodas and juices, ranging from Kola Champagne and ginger beer, to Ting and Limeade. The restaurant setting is simple and casually, and makes an especially appealing stop for business friendly dining. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rewardsnetwork.com/diningsearchdetails.jsp?show=menu&amp;amp;merchantId=82507&amp;amp;start=1#details" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rewardsnet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195001157000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192916889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills then Jamaican food</name><id>6586610</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194708600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6586610/</event_url></item>