<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A winter hike on the Appalachian Trail starting north of Lee, MA and heading northbound for 10.6 easy miles. There will be no significant elevation gain or loss for this section of the trail. The starting point is fixed at the small AT parking lot on Washington Mtn. Rd. (see map link below) and the endpoint is just north of Dalton, MA on Gulf Rd. at an AT trail parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** 2/23/07 -Added Mapquest locator for approximate endpoint parking lot in Dalton. We'll stop at the Key Wood Lean-to about 6.5 miles into the hike to relax a bit and eat a little of what was packed in as well as hit the outhouse if anyone needs to. **&lt;br /&gt;** 2/22/07 -I've updated the map location link and text below to better pinpoint the small parking area for the meetup. My cell for contact is 860-836-3400.**&lt;br /&gt;** 2/22/07 -I need a person to meet me at 9 AM to run up to the endpoint to leave my van there and drive me back to the starting point. If anyone can do this, please call ASAP. We will be set for transportation in any case. In the worst case I'll sleep on the AT to prep for the hike meetup.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike is to start at 10 AM and should be over by no later than 4 PM. Park at small AT parking lot (or road shoulder) on the north side **of the road somewhat northwest** of the intersection of Washington Mtn. Rd and West Branch Rd. **in Washington, MA**. I'll leave my van at the AT parking area on Gulf Rd. to suttle for the return trip. I'll have room for up to 6 additional people in my van for the trip to the starting point to pick up cars. We can stop someplace to eat in Dalton after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have:&lt;br /&gt;* A day pack -to carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water.&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots -There will be snow so it will be wet and cold!&lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks -to keep those feet warm even if wet.&lt;br /&gt;* Gators or snow pants -Strongly suggested as there will be snow on the trail and you want to keep it out of your boots!&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too.&lt;br /&gt;* Gloves -MUST have &amp;amp; warm ones too!&lt;br /&gt;* Jacket -BRIGHT color best given hunters (not advised to wear white, dark green, brown, tan, dark grey, or black if possible -see vest below if must wear). Good for 20 +degree weather but also can stow in pack if you get too hot.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat -you loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too.&lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food/lunch (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;* Orange vest, bandanna, or something bright orange, bright yellow, or bright red to wear -suggested just in case, so hunters don't make a mistake. I'll have 2 vests in the party already.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT parking lot at the starting point, north-east of Lee, MA via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=&amp;amp;address=350+Washington+Mountain+Rd&amp;amp;city=Washington&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01223" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT parking lot at the end point, in northern part of Dalton, MA via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=&amp;amp;address=2+Gulf+rd.&amp;amp;city=Dalton&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01226" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1172579894000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171629774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike on the AT North of Lee, MA</name><id>5486319</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1172329200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5486319/</event_url></item>