<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Members and Guests of the SSDOMG for our first Appetizer Social of the new year - and in a looong time!  Back by popular demand, we had so much fun at our Appetizer Socials last winter that we decided to run this event again.  Let's start off the month - and year - with a relaxed laid-back fun event where you can come and go when it suits your schedule. We'll be meeting at Ascari Cafe @ F1 Boston in Braintree, which is easily accessible from Routes 128/95 and 93. &lt;b&gt;This is a great way to squeeze in that one last event before the post holiday pot luck at Angela's place!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ascari has delicious appetizers and reasonably priced drinks.  &lt;i&gt;Plus, the SSDOMG will pay for up to 3 appetizers for the Group depending on the number of attendees.&lt;/i&gt;  As is our policy, you will still have to pay for your drinks, individually ordered food, any shared appetizers that the SSDOMG does not cover as well as tax and tip.  We will cash out between 6:30-7pm and start a new tab for those who might want to stay for dinner or to continue the Appetizer Social.  If you leave before we cash out be sure to consult a menu or ask one of the Orgs to help you figure out how much you owe and leave it with us so you can enjoy the rest of your Thursday night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;F1 Boston hosts Trivia on Thursday nights which runs from 6-8p.  Please state in your RSVP Comments if you are planning to play Trivia.  If there is enough interest we will set aside a table for those planning to play as there are limits to the number of people on the team.  In addition, F1 Boston has a Billiards/Pool Room.  If you would like to play please indicate it in your RSVP Comments.  If there is enough interest we may set-up in the Billiards Room (or send a group in to play for a little while) depending on the number of attendees and interest in both Billiards and Trivia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will run for at least a couple of hours from 5:30-7:30pm or later.  With an appetizer social you can join us whenever you can get there, whether it be 5:30, 6 or 7.  If you would let us know approximately when to expect you in your RSVP Comments it would be helpful so we can keep an eye out for you.  Over 30% of members who voted in the poll stating how early they could meetup with us said they could be at an event by 5:30pm, with another 30% stating they could arrive by 6pm.  Since the bar fills up with parties waiting to be seated the restaurant has agreed to let us socialize around a few tables in the restaurant area near the bar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a load off - it's Thirsty Thursday night and time to get a jump start on the weekend!  Join us for a fun and relaxing Appetizer Social at Ascari in Braintree!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appetizer Social!&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, January 6th, 2011 @ 5:30-7:30pm (or later)&lt;br /&gt;Ascari Cafe @ F1 Boston&lt;br /&gt;290 Wood Road&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;781-848-2300&lt;br /&gt;www.f1boston.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizer(s)&lt;/i&gt;: Alison &amp;amp; Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Min/Max&lt;/i&gt;: At least 8 Yes RSVP's by 5pm on Wednesday, January 5th (no kidding!) / Currently no max.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Guests&lt;/i&gt;: Up to 2 per member!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Event Fee&lt;/i&gt;: Org Team and Current Annual Members - Free, Members and Guests - $2pp; You can become a 2011 Annual Member at this event for $12.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Price Range&lt;/i&gt;: Appetizers, Soups and Salads range from $3 to $15, Entrees range from $10 to $28, and Desserts are all under $10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to the menu: &lt;a href="http://www.f1boston.com/f1boston/file/F1%20Boston%20Menu(1).pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.f1boston.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/i&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/i&gt;: Thursday, January 6th @ 3pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Located on Wood Road in Braintree, just beyond the hotels on the left-side of the road next to Fuzion Sports Club (gym), just off I-93, Exit #6 near Barnes &amp;amp; Noble Bookstore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from F1Boston's Website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston/Points North:&lt;br /&gt;Route 3/93 South toward Route 128. Exit at first exit # 6 (Route 37). Bear left at end of the ramp. Turn left on Granite Street (Route 37). At first set of lights (Herb Chambers Ford), turn left onto Wood Road. Race track is approximately ¾ mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North/West:&lt;br /&gt;Route 128 South to where it becomes 93 South (at Exit 12). Do not exit. Continue ahead on 93 South and take Exit #6 (Route 37). Bear left at the end of the ramp. Turn left at the lights at far end of Herb Chambers Ford and turn left onto Wood Road. F1 Boston is 3/4 mile on the left at 290 Wood Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Worcester/Points West:&lt;br /&gt;Mass Turnpike (Route 90) East to exit #14, Route 128/95 South - 95 to Route 128 South/93 North to exit # 6 (Route 37). Bear left at the end of the ramp. Turn left on Granite Street (Route 37). Drive under highway, at second set of lights (Herb Chambers Ford), turn left onto Wood Road. Race track is approximately ¾ mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Providence/Points Southwest:&lt;br /&gt;Route 95 North to Route 128 South - 93 North to Exit #6 (Route 37). Bear left at the end of the ramp. Turn left on Granite Street (Route 37). Drive under highway, at second set of lights (Herb Chambers Ford), turn left onto Wood Road. Race track is approximately ¾ mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Cape Cod/Points Southeast:&lt;br /&gt;Route 3 North toward Route 128 North/93 South to Exit # 6 (Route 37.) Bear left at end of the ramp. Turn left on Granite Street (Route 37). At first set of lights (Herb Chambers Ford), turn left on to Wood Road. Race track is approximately ¾ mile on the left&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at our tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295135170000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292626767000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st  Appetizer Social of the New Year!!!</name><id>15762042</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294353000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/15762042/</event_url></item>