<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 North Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02113</zip><lat>42.363864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mariners House</name><city>Boston</city><id>1363854</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053084</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This month we’re doing something fun and different and meeting in Boston’s North End to discuss &lt;i&gt;Dark Tide: The Great Boston Molasses Flood of 1919&lt;/i&gt;. We’ll take an insider’s walking tour of the North End with Guild Nichols and his wife Ann Nall, owners of Old Boston Tours. They’ll show us some of the key locations of the Molasses Flood, and also fill us in on the history of the North End and some exciting and little known secrets of the area (see The Old Boston Original Secret Tour on their &lt;a href="http://www.oldbostontours.com/old_boston_tours_secret_tour.html" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;)! After the tour we’ll have lunch at L’Osteria (www.losteria.com). L’Osteria is one of the North End’s many delicious Italian eateries, and serves reasonably priced, fresh, authentic Italian food in a cozy, quiet atmosphere perfect for a book club discussion! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Specifics:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our tour guides Guild and Ann will meet us in North Square on the cobblestones in front of the Mariners House (11 North Square) at 10:30 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The cost of the tour is $25.00 per person payable by check on the morning of the tour&lt;/i&gt; (a $5 discount off the usual tour price!). &lt;i&gt;Please make checks out to Old Boston Tours and bring them with you that morning.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’d like, a group of us will also meet on the steps of Quincy Market at Faneuil Hall at 10am and make the 10 minute walk over to North Square. Quincy Market is a well known spot and there’s a lot of parking in the Faneuil Hall area, so I thought that might be a good meeting place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In your RSVP please note whether you’re planning on meeting at Quincy Market at 10 or North Square at 10:30 – just so we have an idea of who to wait for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the tour, we have reservations at noon at L’Osteria at 104 Salem St, and will discuss the book over lunch and yummy Italian food! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone on the 25th!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a description of Dark Tide by an Amazon Reviewer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Stephen Puleo's non-fiction effort is truly a masterful history lesson wrapped up in a powerful story about greed, arrogance, fear, and just plain stupidity. Puleo weaves a tale around the construction and collapse of a 2.2 million-gallon molasses storage tank resulting in the Great Boston Molasses Flood of 1919. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dark Tide is a detailed look back at the time of WWI, what life was like in Boston, and the part played by both immigrants and anarchists alike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The early 20th Century comes alive as Puleio describes the U.S participation in the war effort, the part played by industrial alcohol, and the need to build a huge storage tank right under the noses of the unsuspecting and unempowered people living in Boston's North End. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not only do we learn the history of this period, but we personally experience the harrowing moments leading up to and during the actual molasses flood. People like Arthur P. Jell, Isaac Gonzales, and families like the Cloughertys, Iantoscas and Distasios come alive and virtually leap off the pages of this sad and sordid tale, with some Sacco and Vanzetti thrown in to the mix. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last part of the book describes the extremely lenghty court case overseen by the Honorable Judge Hugh Ogden. Ten years after the tank's construction, the legal wrangling was settled but the molasses forever stained the streets, wharves, neighborhoods and history of one of the most storied places in our nation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285554396000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283371600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>“Field Trip” Book Discussion – Dark Tide by Stephen Puleo </name><id>14622477</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285425000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/14622477/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/1/global_11643361.jpeg</photo_url></item>