<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 3.5 mile loop hike of moderate difficulty in south-western CT on a 605 acre state park with portions overlooking the Housatonic River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a fair chance of some ice on the trail given the cold weather and wetness of recent days but mud is likely. Rain and wind predicted for the morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have: &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots (no sneakers!) - There could be ice or it could be wet/muddy! &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - BRIGHT color better. Raincoat or rain shell may be advised as well as rain pants depending on forecast&lt;br /&gt;* Hat - optional &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 1 PM at the parking area. Park on the wide gravel shoulder left of the gatehouse where the road splits. We would finish up at about 3:30 PM and head home or have a supper out if the group feels like socializing more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aproximate location/directions via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=1550+Georges+Hill+Rd&amp;amp;city=Southbury&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kettletown State Park website (with trail maps):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325230&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/kettletown.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location. I could offer a carpool from the Ellington/Vernon/E. Windsor area but you must call me (see RSVP for phone number).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203943818000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>A warm winter hiking experience without much difficulty!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203133165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Kettletown SP in Southbury CT</name><id>7340239</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203357600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7340239/</event_url></item>