<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Across from Hilton Garden Inn)</address_2><address_1>380 Winter St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.372517</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-7800</phone><name>Best Western</name><city>Boston</city><id>408986</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079834</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>THE TIME IS NOW!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Looking for long term appreciation and cash flow?&lt;br /&gt;*Searching for the right strategy in a declining market?&lt;br /&gt;*Love the income but hate being a landlord?&lt;br /&gt;*Now is the time for real estate investors to get into the game&lt;br /&gt;*Opportunities abound for you to $CASH IN$, come and learn how!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUY AND HOLD STRATEGIES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:  Saturday, Nov. 10th 8am- 4:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Best Western Hotel,  380 Winter St, Waltham, MA, 781-890-7800 &lt;br /&gt;             (Across from Hilton Garden Inn)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: All day workshop - 6 speakers each with a unique perspective on buy-and-hold investing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: BAREIA Members pay $99.00 - includes lunch (register online at www.BostonAREIA.com)&lt;br /&gt; BAREIA Visitors pay $149.00 ? includes lunch (register online at www.BostonAREIA.com) &lt;br /&gt; (Pre-registration discount ends Monday Nov 5th ? after that date, registration is $199.00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've assembled a team of 6 speakers, each with a unique perspective on buy-and-hold investing.  This all-day workshop is jam-packed with information that will change the way you think about buy-and-hold.  You absolutely will come away with new ways to invest that you have never thought about before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Buying rental properties at 50% of market value or less, with 20% cash flow.  Impossible?  Not after you?ve heard from this investor!  Linda Huuskonen has been purchasing real estate since 1986.  She will talk about Where to invest, Analyzing the deal, Building your team, Protecting your assets, and managing your portfolio.  You?ll be amazed after you hear Linda speak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Joe Falco, VP will discuss techniques utilized by Gulfstream Realty &amp;amp; Development  in select areas of the Go Zone. They seek to develop value by building projects on inexpensive land in the path of growth. Since they start construction &amp;quot;ahead of the curve,&amp;quot; the intention is to create value and equity by developing new housing areas and/or commercial centers in select areas. And lets not forget the 50% depreciation deduction in the Go-Zone!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Stephen Martin is the owner of SMJ Martin Consulting, a unique real estate brokerage firm that specializes in income producing properties. With his mortgage background, construction background and his &amp;quot;out of the box&amp;quot; thinking he has become an investment specialist in locating and analyzing investment property.  His strategies increase cash flow and equity both at the same time using a unique financing strategy.  Learn how he does it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Lacasse is owner of N.E. Family Housing Mgt. Org., LLC , a management company that owns and manages numerous residential units.  His approach is simple ? you make your money when you buy the property!  Kevin specializes in analyzing properties for maximum profit and will share his no-nonsense approach to real estate investing.  Find out how he utilizes ?forced appreciation? to build equity and cash flow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Charlie Dobens is local to Boston Area investing and is an ardent Dave Lindahl student.  He will share his knowledge of investing in large apartment complexes and the Buy/Hold strategies necessary with large scale investing in a down turning market.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Dowd is a Commercial &amp;amp; Investment Property Finance Specialist from Drew Mortgage Associates.  He will teach you the tricks to buying both 1-4 unit Investment Properties and also Commercial Properties like Apartment Buildings and Shopping Malls. Learn valuable insider strategies that every investor should know!  You will learn how to get your deals accepted by both the seller and the bank by structuring deals around financing that gets approved!  Savvy buyers and sellers know the parameters, and so must you to compete like a Player.  Deal with unrealistic sellers by explaining to them how banks look at their information, or lack thereof.  Help them (and you) to get the most from their property by offering a Seller 2nd. Learn how to talk like a cash buyer, because the bank is on your side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194873022000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193148116000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BUY AND HOLD STRATEGIES</name><id>6601736</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194699600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/6601736/</event_url></item>