<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30PM - Power Hour Shortsale Workshop with PPNE Mentor and Shortsale Phenom Kim Harrington.  This is exclusive to members of BostonAREIA.  Visit &lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/membership.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonarei...&lt;/a&gt; for details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Main Meeting at 6:30 PM - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tim Norris &amp;amp; Alan Segal &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dodging the Bullet -&lt;br /&gt;the fancy dance we do to take cover&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;The most common questions asked at meetings are :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What's the difference between a Trust and an LLC, and when do I use them?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Doesn't a trust provide me with protection?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If I have insurance, why do I need an LLC?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If my property is in an LLC, when would I need a trust?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I know all my tenants, why should I worry about asset protection and insurance coverage?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Do I need to spend money on asset protection if I don't yet have assets to protect?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Top 10 Insurance Myths for the Real Estate Investor &amp;quot; with Tim Norris&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Where Insurance Leaves Off and Trusts and LLC's Begin&amp;quot; with Alan Segal, Board of Advisors&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;So - When is insurance all you need? And what kind? And is there a better way? And how much asset protection do you need, if you don't have any assets? And how do Trusts and LLC's relate to my protection? Am I going overboard? Am I walking around with a big red bullseye on my back?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are a few of the myths that Tim Norris will cover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I have insurance, I don't need estate, tax, and financial planning… &lt;br /&gt;Being named as an “additional insured” on the existing homeowner policy will protect my interests in a subject-to deal… &lt;br /&gt;Buying a property in your personal name and using your homeowner’s policy liability is fine… &lt;br /&gt;The “personal” dwelling fire policy is sufficient (“cheap”) to cover my non-owner occupied rental… &lt;br /&gt;I need “builders risk” coverage for a vacant or rehab project/deal/property… &lt;br /&gt;Self-insurance is too risky… &lt;br /&gt;And lots more! &lt;br /&gt;Tim isn't here to scare you into buying more insurance. But he is here to give you the real scoop on what you need and what you don't. He's an investor himself with 20+ properties, and he's been there. He left a major carrier to form him own company and focus on providing insurance to real estate investors. Get educated, and make informed decisions based on your personal situation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the most common questions that Alan will cover &lt;br /&gt;The difference between Trusts and LLC's &lt;br /&gt;When to use which one - or both! &lt;br /&gt;Assigning beneficial interest in a trust &lt;br /&gt;Role of the Trustee &lt;br /&gt;The expense of an LLC - is it worth it? &lt;br /&gt;How to keep from becoming a &amp;quot;Deep Pocket Defendent&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;These are gray areas even for very seasoned investors. So bring your questions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Location: Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;Free to Boston AREIA members (please see website for details - &lt;a href="http://www.BostonAREIA.com)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonAREI...&lt;/a&gt;, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229639370000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>83</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224196434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association November Meetup</name><id>8975672</id><headcount>115</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227220200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/8975672/</event_url></item>