<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>512 Hancock Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06605</zip><lat>41.167450</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>NEST ARTS FACTORY</name><city>Bridgeport</city><id>1557130</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.210640</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/5/d/event_21928509.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The C.A.N. ( Collective Artist Network ) Presents:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Spring Art Fest at The Nest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art, Music, Fire Dancers, and more! &lt;br /&gt;This show is stated to run for April 29th from 6pm to 2am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(there will be a submission fee for those interested in showing, see Facebook page for updates on that)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;The Nest Arts Factory &lt;br /&gt;512 Hancock Avenue&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/7/4/event_22395988.jpeg" width="69" height="54" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bridgeport, CT 06605&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Statement from the shows Director:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Nest Arts Factory&amp;rdquo; a long standing icon in the Bridgeport Art scene has been graciously donated for our use by the Nest&amp;rsquo;s Director David Flynn. This would not be possible without his help. I will be acting as Director and Curator of this project along with Assistant Director and Curator Stan Olshefski.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The primary focus of this show is the artists. I would like to personally invite everyone out to come see their work, meet them, and talk with them about their art. Ask them about their processes and what makes them tick. The primary goal of this show is for everyone to come and get together. It is after all first and foremost an art show. This means not only to come and view art but also creates an opportunity for collaborative talks between fellow artists, networking possibilities between other gallery owners and artists alike. Help me make this one of the most memorable shows to hit Bridgeport in a long time. &lt;br /&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt;J. Cusano IV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Nest" has been an icon in the art world in Bridgeport for over 10 years. We have been given the opportunity to throw the final shebang at this amazing building before they move to another location. It is a great honor and we intend to make the most of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have been granted the first and third floors to use at our disposal; About 40,000 sq. ft.  &lt;br /&gt;On the first floor there is a small stage that can be used for performance/ bands. Will have a line-up Musical entertainment of all types for which we are still looking for submissions. I have many performance artists who wish to participate including several Burlesque groups, numerous fire dancers, even aerial acrobatics artists, hoola hoop girls, etc. &lt;br /&gt;The third floor will be used as a reception area and the main gallery. There will be a second gallery on the first floor as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Thank you all &lt;br /&gt;Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;J. Cusano IV, Director /Curator &amp;ldquo;Spring Art Fest at The Nest&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For continuous updates on this event please join us at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/collectiveartistsnetwork" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3b5998"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.facebook.com/co&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;llectiveartistsnetwork&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear the bw scarf with piano keys, as time draws near I can provide my number to those who may need it.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304469520000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299797301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Art Fest at The Nest</name><id>16876919</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304114400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/16876919/</event_url></item>