<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;....And we're off...&amp;quot; Let's take a Friday off and go to one of the worlds top race tracks. Only an hour or so away. Saratoga is wonderful! Clean and has the best horse racing there is. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Work on your flying and your handicapping!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.saratogaracetrack.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.saratogara...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, Aug 20, 2010 Fabulous Fillies Day All ladies at Saratoga Race Track can enjoy a day of fashion, style and glamour! &lt;br /&gt;Head to the backyard of the Track for the Lifestyle Expo and explore displays of fashion, health care, personal improvement and leisure benefitting the Breast Cancer Research Foundation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND.... do we want to be there for the wonderful breakfast on the track? This is awesome....&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;What is Breakfast at Saratoga?&lt;br /&gt;There is a buffet breakfast every day of the Saratoga racing meet from 7 a.m. - 9:30 a.m. where you can watch the horse's morning workouts. Admission to the breakfast is free. The breakfast buffet is priced at $14.95 per person, $7.95 for children between the ages of 3 and 12. If you get to the track in the morning, you can also take a tram tour of the Backstretch Area and watch the Paddock Show and Starting Gate Demonstration free of charge. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like the KFI to 5B2 (known to ATC as five bucks on the two) 93.5 miles, 53 minutes. Can we all leave here at 7:00 to make the breakfast? Do we leave at 9:00 for just some races? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.airnav.com/airport/5B2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.airnav.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282434032000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279215189000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday's Fabulous Fillies Day at Saratoga race track!</name><id>14112437</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282302000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/14112437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/3/8/global_16444408.jpeg</photo_url></item>