<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Jfk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.491.9851</phone><name>Redline</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692091</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's meet for dinner in Cambridge at Redline and then go to the comedy show at Hong Kong Cambridge afterwards. We've heard good things about Redline and their menu looks really good. Check it out at &lt;a href="http://www.redlinecambridge.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redlinecam...&lt;/a&gt;. The comedy show at the Hong Kong starts at 8:00 and the doors open at 7:30. Tickets are only $10 and its well worth it. We've been there once and they had 6-8 comedians up for fairly short sets and they were funny - all for just $10. We're thinking we meet at Redline at 5:30 and then head over to Hong Kong (a couple blocks) by 7:30. If you want, you can buy tickets on-line at &lt;a href="http://www.thecomedystudio.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thecomedys...&lt;/a&gt; up until the day of the show. Otherwise, the tickets go on sale when the doors open at 7:30. The show goes until 9:30 or so and then we can see what we feel like from there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can RSVP and go to dinner, the show or both. We'll send out an email the week of the event to see who's planning on dinner. We'll then make reservations at Redline for the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let us know if you have questions and we hope to see a lot of you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be waiting in the lobby / bar area and will have reservations under the last name Keuning or Meetup.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247452809000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>You love food, you love comedy, you love Harvard Square or you just love late night crab rangoons and scorpion bowls!!!</why><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210208328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner &amp; Comedy in Cambridge!</name><id>7895328</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212269400000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/7895328/</event_url></item>