<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's time again for ARTWALK - Newburyport! JOIN US! &lt;br /&gt;This is a &lt;b&gt;VERY&lt;/b&gt; popular and interesting event. I have invited 4 meetup groups. It's a lot of FUN! Many of the artists are present displaying their work - and usually are very interesting to talk with! Most galleries have refershments of some kind.. and some go all out! Depending on the weather, it could be a hot day or cool. Make sure to wear appropriate clothing and comfy shoes....LOTS OF WALKING INVOLVED.   Let's hope for good weather! &lt;br /&gt;We may vote on a place to go later on for a bite or drinks, although there is no set plan. There are several possibilities. Maybe watch the boats from Waterfront Park...... &lt;br /&gt;TIME: 4:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;ARTWALK officially begins at 5 and runs until 8pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEETUP: right outside The Firehouse Center at 4:30 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: ARTWALK is FREE &lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****NOTE: Sorry folks, but - RAIN cancels this event. Please make sure to check for any updates before heading out. Also, due to this type of venue, members usually break up into smaller groups. If this is a problem for anyone, it may not be the best event to attend.**********&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Website) ArtWalk events are self-guided walking tours of the participating galleries. At many galleries artists will be in attendance to discuss their works and exhibits of new works are being presented. Light refreshments will also be available. &lt;br /&gt;Galleries are open year round and offer a brochure with map that shows a convenient walking tour of all gallery locations in town. The map may be downloaded from our website as well as picked up at galleries, the Newburyport Chamber of Commerce, and various restaurants and inns.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We Are all meeting up  outside the front entrance to the Firehouse Center</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246806225000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245513684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Artwalk  By The Sea - Newburyport</name><id>10695112</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246134600000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/10695112/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/0/b/global_4252875.jpeg</photo_url></item>