<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Admission</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Canterbury Shaker Village Celebrates 21st Annual Wool Day &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fiber Arts will be at the center of attention on Saturday, September 22 at  Canterbury Shaker Village?s 21st annual Wool Day. From 10:00 a.m. until 4:00 p.m., the Village green will be full of activity and color as we celebrate the world?s oldest sources of recyclable materials: animal fibers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission to the event is included in the price of museum admission; $15 for adults, $13 for seniors, $7 for 6-17 year olds, and free for children under 6. Members are also admitted at no charge and receive discounts at the Museum Store and restaurant. All tours and exhibits are included in the price of admission. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 1969 to preserve the heritage of the Canterbury Shakers, Canterbury Shaker Village is an internationally-known, non-profit museum and National Historic Landmark with 25 original Shaker buildings, three reconstructed Shaker buildings and 694 acres of forests, fields, gardens and mill ponds under permanent conservation easement.   The Village is located 20 minutes north of Concord, NH, and 25 minutes south of Meredith, NH, off I-93, Exit 18 or Route 106 at the intersection of Shaker Road and 20 minutes south of the Lakes Region. For more information visit www.shakers.org or call (603) 783-9511.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shakers.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;task=view&amp;amp;id=218&amp;amp;Itemid=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.shakers.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steph</member_name><member_id>4872811</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190642748000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Seacoast Knitters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>seacoastknitters</urlname><id>642244</id><group_lat>43.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Knitters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190069446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canterbury Shaker Village 21st Annual Wool Day</name><id>6377698</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190469600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/seacoastknitters/events/6377698/</event_url></item>