<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey friends - I'm running this discussion as something fun to do in August and also as a fundraiser for (hopefully) The Innocence Project - hope to see some of you there! - Jon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    See it also on Facebook: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.c.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;    Making &amp;quot;Free&amp;quot; Work for You: How Artists and Entrepreneurs Can Apply &amp;quot;Freemium&amp;quot; Business Models&lt;br /&gt;    An Interactive Discussion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    When: Monday, August 23, 6:00 ? 8:30 pm (discussion from 6:30 ? 8:00)&lt;br /&gt;    Where: Media Education Foundation, Community Room, Northampton MA map&lt;br /&gt;    Suggested donation: $5&lt;br /&gt;    Refreshments: Snacks, drinks and sandwiches can be purchased from Woodstar Café next door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    About the Event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    The &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; Internet era has powerfully impacted intellectual property and the ability of artists to monetize their ventures. But while some of the implications of diminishing copyright value, content piracy and aggregation are disturbing, &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; also offers new opportunities for creative people to generate revenue and increase their industry visibility.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    On Monday, August 23 at the Media Education Foundation, join Jon Reed, author of Free From Corporate America, for a facilitated, interactive discussion on &amp;quot;making the most of free.&amp;quot; We'll talk about some of the obstacles to monetizing and protecting copyright and share our successes with creating a competitive advantage through kickass content and/or &amp;quot;freemium&amp;quot; business models.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Some of the topics from this discussion will be inspired by Chris Anderson's Free: The Future of a Radical Price.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This discussion is a donations-optional fundraiser, with donations planned to be made to the Innocence Project, &lt;a href="http://innocenceproje..." target="_blank"&gt;http://innocenceproje...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    About Jon Reed: Jon Reed is an independent analyst and podcaster in the SAP software marketplace. He advises clients on community-based marketing and organic search. The author of Free From Corporate America: A Tactical Guide to Success on Your Own Terms, Jon is an expert in Print on Demand publishing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Community Room in Back</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Reed</member_name><member_id>9974627</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282605383000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280768749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion: Making "Free" Work for You: Artists and Entrepreneurs </name><id>14292216</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282600800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/14292216/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_1616503.jpeg</photo_url></item>