<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Three Maple Street Framingham, MA 01702 </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.296738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St. Andrews Episcopal Church</name><city>Framingham</city><id>11820672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431541</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our first program for March will be very special night of learning. We are very lucky to have here from California sponsored by Canon, Jennifer Wu, and a Canon Explorer of Light. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Photographing after the sun has set and before sunrise offers a whole new world of images and photographic opportunities for you as a photographer. Twilight offers beautiful light after sunset and before sunrise. We often think it is too dark to photograph, but the camera can pick up the subtle light that our eyes do not see. The seemingly &lt;br /&gt;

infinite darkness of the night is lit by the stars and planets. We will learn how to photograph the stars, the Milky Way, the full moon, the crescent moon and how to do long exposures of the ocean surf for that wispy effect. Our speaker will teach us about the quality of light at night and how to use that light in our photographs. It has &lt;br /&gt;

characteristics that photographers can take advantage of and Jennifer will offer tips and suggestions for photographing it. Jennifer will also discuss light painting techniques that can be used to paint light on trees, rocks and buildings to add another dimension to your night photography. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Jennifer Wu, a professional photographer since 1992, is a nature and landscape photographer with a special interest in the night sky and stars. As a “Canon Explorer of Light”, she is one of a group of 62 of the world's best internationally recognized esteemed photographers, united in their love and passion for photographic excellence. &lt;br /&gt;

They also share a common desire to contribute back to the industry with a willingness to share their vision and passion with others. Jennifer enjoys sharing her enthusiasm and passion for nature photography in lectures and workshops for Canon. Her images, featured in Canon’s professional camera brochures, numerous magazines and &lt;br /&gt;

books, have won a wide variety of prestigious awards. Whenever she is not on nature expeditions at some of the most beautiful locations in the world, she exhibits her images at galleries and art shows and lectures at seminars and speaking events throughout the USA. She taught photography and digital imaging at California State University &lt;br /&gt;

Sacramento. She currently resides in Sacramento and enjoys leading workshops for Light Photographic Workshops, Canon and “afilm International Film Workshops” Barcelona, Spain. A world traveler, she leads tours/workshops to Namibia, Death Valley, Greenland, Montana, Hawaii, Alaska and Iceland. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Join us for this visual journey through the night sky. This inspiring and entertaining presentation is a must see for anyone interested in photographing the moon, twilight, the Milky Way and night sky. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please look for more of our speaker’s work and her tour information at &amp;lt;www.jenniferwu.com&amp;gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Gateway Camera Club meets at St. Andrews Episcopal Church in Framingham: &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;lt;&lt;a href="http://gatewaycameraclub.org/index.php/directions&amp;gt" class="linkified"&gt;http://gatewaycameraclub.org/index.php/directions&amp;gt&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362795293000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361292611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jennifer Wu:Canon Explorer of Light presenting: Photographing the Night Sky</name><id>105341092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362702600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/105341092/</event_url></item>