<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 Canal Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364371</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-897-1337</phone><name>Boston Beer Works</name><city>Boston</city><id>842989</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060299</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Drop by -- this is an opportunity for you to meet group new group members, hang out with the people you already know, and perhaps vent a little of that frustration about living in a superstition- and irrationality-saturated culture. Tell that joke you know. I, for one, look forward to having a drink and relaxing a bit with a group of like-minded folks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often when we get together for pub night or brunch, I invite people to make a contribution to a charitable cause being supported by the BA outright, or by one of the members. This time around, we're going to pass the hat for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BA member Janna C. (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/members/10604433/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/members/10604433/&lt;/a&gt;) has been working with Wilderness Heals, a three-day pledge hike to raise funds for the Elizabeth Stone House. From their website: 'The Elizabeth Stone House helps individuals and families rebuild their lives after experiencing homelessness, domestic violence, mental illness, substance abuse and other forms of trauma, providing residential and non-residential programs, as well as emergency shelter for those who are in immediate need. The three-day Wilderness Heals hike covers several parts of New Hampshire's White Mountains. Wilderness Heals route options offer a range of trails accessible to individuals with varying levels of experience including a backcountry camping option. Hikers spend three days hiking and two nights at AMC huts, which provide beds, blankets, dinner and breakfast. The backcountry camping option affords hikers the opportunity to experience the wilderness in a supportive environment. Participants on this leg pitch tents and cook their own food. Round-trip transportation between Boston and the trailheads is provided.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As their largest fundraiser, the hike raises much-needed flexible funding to help the needs of the families they serve. Janna's already done the hike for this year, but she has until the end of this month to turn in any sponsor dollars, and any additional donations that have come in. That's where we come in. If you're inclined to, you can give her a few bucks at the Meetup, or a check, and that'll go toward the total she's raised. If you'd like to lend your support, but won't be able to come out this week for blasphemy &amp;amp; brews, let me know and I'll put you in touch with her directly. Alternately, visit &lt;a href="http://www.elizabethstonehouse.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.elizabethstonehouse.org&lt;/a&gt; and make a donation directly.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345127028000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344776585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August pub night at Boston Beer Works</name><id>77394102</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345069800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/77394102/</event_url></item>