<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>At this meetup, we'll review Transition Initiative Portland as a group and the Transition Towns Model, as well as discuss what we're already doing and what's next.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll talk about what brought our group together and how our understanding of Transition Towns has evolved since we started.  More importantly (and probably more interesting) we'll look at the transition model, discuss just what &amp;quot;transition&amp;quot; refers to, and talk about the core principles that comprise it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those attending this meetup will range from fully informed on the idea of Transition Towns to completely unaware.  While the event will start with an informational presentation, the idea is to keep it as concise and brief as possible.  We'd rather focus on the fun part, which is getting people talking about where to go from here.  There's no time limit (but we won't make Audrey have to kick us out!) and no limit to the potential of tonight's meetup.  We may spend the rest of the evening talking as a group, breaking into small groups, or even in a fishbowl or open space session.  As you will discover at the meetup, Transition Towns draw their greatest strength by letting the community decide what to do next.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the TIP sign on front lawn</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>matt</member_name><member_id>7777036</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226013505000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>TT'rs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>TI-Portland</urlname><id>1233823</id><group_lat>43.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2900009155</group_lon><name>Tohidu Transition - Portland Maine</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224733843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TIP and Transition - Where We Go From Here</name><id>9015988</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225319400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/TI-Portland/events/9015988/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/1/global_5989777.jpeg</photo_url></item>