<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's meet for a Walk in place of our cancelled Yoga event for the 2nd Saturday Monthly Event!  We will have our first Walk @ Webb Memorial Park in North Weymouth.  We were planning to meet here for Yoga but will instead enjoy a nice Walk to start off our weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on Boston Harbor close to the Boston Harbor Islands, Webb Memorial offers quiet enjoyment and vistas of the harbor and Boston skyline. The park is a scenic peninsula that extends nearly half a mile into Hingham Bay. Recreational activities include fishing, picnicking and walking. A large pavilion with grills is available for rent to organized groups from May through October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The two glacial hills and connecting lowland that form Weymouth Neck and Webb Memorial have been sculpted by natural and human forces for over 12,000 years. The area was used extensively by Native Americans because of its wealth of shellfish, finfish and wild fruits. European settlers used the area primarily for agriculture until the end of the nineteenth century. Boats depart from nearby Hewitt's Cove in Hingham to Boston Harbor Islands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2nd Saturday Walk&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 8th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;9:45am&lt;br /&gt;Webb Memorial State Park &lt;br /&gt;River St., North Weymouth &lt;br /&gt;781 740-1605&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: In the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: All Members - FREE, Guests - $2 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Angela &amp;amp; Elaine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: At  least 4 Yes RSVPs by 4pm on Friday, August 7th.  Attendance is unlimited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!  Up to 2 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ages: 16+ (Anyone under 21 must be a family member.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by 8pm on Friday, August 7th.  &lt;i&gt;Drop-ins welcome!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: No rain is forecast.  We will walk if it's overcast or there is a light drizzle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: TBA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Webb Memorial is located just south of Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: Rte. 3A south in Weymouth, left on Neck St. There is Dunkin Donuts across from where you take the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hingham: Rte. 3A north in Weymouth, right on Neck St. There is Dunkin Donuts across from where you take the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you make the turn on to Neck St., continue all the way to the end...a few miles. You will see the park sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check MapQuest for door to door directions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking lot.  Angela drives a Blue Toyota RAV4.  Elaine drives a Red Toyota Corolla.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250030934000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249651053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Saturday Walk</name><id>11057491</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249739100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11057491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/8/global_3818056.jpeg</photo_url></item>