<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>32 Vassar Street</address_2><address_1>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 155</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1119883</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;DEMO from 5:30 - 6:00 pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recent tragedies resulting in a major loss of life in coal mines and on oil rigs highlight the need for visibility technologies that quickly and precisely locate people in case of disasters. Beyond these lifesaving kinds of applications there are a multitude of other needs to locate people, items and assets that are often unsatisfied because of shortfalls in performance and affordability issues. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us to hear from a great group of speakers about sensor networks and locating solutions including ultra wide band technologies, cellular networks, RTLS and more. Many end users have great urgency to find affordable solutions to determine location and condition related information - indoors and outdoors - sensing temperature, light, motion, vibration, humidity, impact and much more.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PANEL&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Koudal, General Electric, Pervasive Decisions Systems Lab, Senior Research Scientist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nick Brachet, Skyhook Wireless, Chief Technology Officer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Santiago Romero, Zebra Enterprise Solutions, Product Manager - GPS and Telematics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mauro Martino, Research Affiliate: MIT Senseable City Lab &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Coyle - Moderator&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DEMONSTRATION of TagView™&lt;/b&gt; by Edward Bokhour, President of Tag Safety Systems (see below) -- the demo will be available for viewing from 5:30 - 6:00 pm and after 8:00 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nick Brachet, Chief Technology Officer, Skyhook Wireless&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 15 years of experience in software engineering, Nick Brachet has broad expertise in designing robust, scalable, and adaptable software. As CTO, Mr. Brachet oversees the design and development of Skyhook's Wi-Fi Positioning System. Prior to joining Skyhook Wireless, he was Chief Architect at Passkey International Inc., the world's leading online group reservation system, where he was primarily responsible for the development of GroupLink– a system that enables the exchange of reservations between hotels and the Passkey system. The architecture of GroupLink defined a flexible core engine and pluggable modules that allowed rapid integration of disparate hotel reservation systems. Before Passkey, Mr. Brachet was Director of Engineering for edocs Inc., where he was responsible for the architecture, implementation, and release of all new products. Prior to edocs, Mr. Brachet was Lead Architect at Gradient Technologies Inc., and represented the company at the Object Management Group (OMG). Mr. Brachet received a Master of Science in Computer Science from the University of Computer Science and Applied Mathematics in Grenoble, France.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Koudal, Senior Research Scientist at GE Global Research Pervasive Decisioning Systems Lab&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter Koudal has extensive experience in global strategy, operations, and technology research and consulting focused on identifying, designing, developing, and implementing leading-edge business technologies and systems for Global Fortune 500 companies. He has developed and managed research collaborations and alliances with industry and technology executives, consultants, academics, and other thought leaders worldwide in areas such as global business strategy, performance and financial management, supply chain management, service management, customer relationship management, and demand-supply integration and optimization. He has deep expertise in directing global research programs linking research with global benchmarking, and methods and tools to effectively develop, position, and scale existing and new technologies, systems, services and solutions.&lt;br /&gt;Peter is author and editor of numerous books, studies and articles covered extensively in leading international business media and is a frequent speaker at conferences around the world. Peter has more than 18 years of experience in global industrial research and consulting and has worked with the United Nations Centre on Transnational Corporations, the Harvard Institute for International Development, and as director of global manufacturing, supply chain and service management at Deloitte Research, the global research arm of Deloitte. He holds a Cand. Oecon. from Aarhus University, Denmark, is a graduate of the executive programs at MIT and Stanford University, and has served as board member of the Stanford Global Supply Chain Management Forum and the MIT Forum for Supply Chain Innovation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Santiago Romero, Product Manager of GPS and Telematics, Zebra Enterprise Solutions&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Santiago Romero brings over 10 years of RTLS experience.  Previously, Santiago was a Sr. Solutions Engineer with WhereNet, where he specialized in deployments of RTLS solutions in high multi-path environments.  Santiago is the first recipient of WhereNet’s “RTLS Black Belt” program, in recognition of significant RTLS algorithmic and deployment contributions.  Santiago was instrumental in growing WhereNet’s Marine Terminal RTLS business from Proof-of-Concept to a full blown solution deployed at over 15 locations.  He is co-inventor on three WhereNet RTLS patent applications.  Santiago was co-founder of ParkWatch, a WhereNet partner company targeting RTLS “Lost Child” solutions to the Theme Park industry.  Previously, Santiago was a Principal Engineer with COMSAT, specializing in mobile satellite communication systems.   Santiago started his career at Computer Sciences Corporation, designing large-scale packet data communication networks.  Santiago holds a BSEE and a MSEE, both from the University of Maryland, College Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mauro Martino, Research Affiliate: MIT Senseable City Lab&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mauro Martino is a PhD in Design and Technologies Exploitation for Cultural Heritage at Politecnico di Milano, Italy. He holds a Master in Industrial Design from the same university and has been collaborating with leading commercial research and development laboratories, including Clarion, based in Tokyo, Japan and Magneti Marelli based in Milan, Italy. Mauro is currently a research affiliate with the SENSEable City Lab at MIT, working on data visualization and his related research project, Visualizing Urban Complexity. He has developed a long experience in the visualization and exploration of massive amount of human mobility data, while working with different databases from different mobile operators (Telecom, AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, TDC, BT) and in different nations (USA, England, Belgium, Italy, Denmark). Website &lt;a href="http://mamartino.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mamartino.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moderator: Tom Coyle&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom’s career focus has been to deliver wireless technology solutions for supply chain, transportation. government and retail customers. As Vice President at Mark IV Industries Tom led business development efforts for new initiatives. Mark IV is a leading provider of RFID systems and is the largest toll tag manufacturer today best known as the maker of EZ-Pass transponders and readers.  &lt;br /&gt;Tom led Sales &amp;amp; Marketing efforts for Matrics, Inc., a leading RFID hardware provider which was acquired by Symbol (now Motorola) in 2004. At Savi Technology (now Lockheed Martin), Tom was the Director of Strategic Alliances. Savi is a leading provider of active RFID hardware and software solutions. As director of business development at Texas Instruments, Tom led efforts for RFID and GPS-based tracking solutions. Tom held consulting and management positions at EG&amp;amp;G supporting efforts at the Volpe National Transportation Systems Center. He was a supply chain analyst for General Electric. He is a graduate of West Point. He began his career as a test pilot and maintenance manager with an air cavalry unit in the U.S. Army. Tom was the founder of the Kendall Square Learning Project, an adult literacy program based in Cambridge, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Edward Bokhour, Tag Safety Systems, President&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Bokhour is President of Tag Safety Systems, Inc, a company he founded in 2003 to develop and commercialize tag-based distance measurement systems for locating, collision avoidance, search and rescue, loss &amp;amp; theft prevention, and other applications. TagView™ is his digital signal timing technique for precision real-time locating of RFID tags in logistics, materials handling, and healthcare applications. Mr. Bokhour holds three US patents. Mr. Bokhour has over 20 years experience in electronics design for spacecraft, aeronautical, and other applications, including flight hardware, software, and ground test and support equipment, for McDonnell Douglas, Boeing, NASA, MIT, Space Shuttle, International Space Station, and Russian Mir missions. Mr. Bokhour has a Master’s degree in Aeronautics and Astronautics from MIT, and was a Fellow at the Center for Advanced Engineering Study at MIT. He also holds a Bachelor’s degree in performing arts from Queens College, NY, and is an accomplished drummer and percussionist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TagView™ demonstration&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TagView™ is a new, low cost, low power wireless distance measurement technology which uses a patented round-trip time-of-flight approach.  TagView™ can 'piggy back' on most digital wireless protocols, like 802.11x, Bluetooth, and ZigBee, with minimal additional hardware, providing range information between wireless transceivers such as RFID tags, cell phones, portable computers, and handheld radios.  Because it can provide this information quickly and in GPS-denied environments (indoors, and underground), TagView™ can &amp;quot;bridge the gap&amp;quot; between GPS and RFID. The demonstration system includes a reader, tag, antenna, and laptop display. The display updates range information in real time as the tag moves at walking speeds, with accuracy of ±2 feet.  Several styles of numeric and graphical display suggest human-machine interactions in real-world scenarios.&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274453352000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258687291000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sensor Networks &amp; Real-Time Locating Systems</name><id>11917252</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274133600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/11917252/</event_url></item>