<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02543</zip><lat>41.523364</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-540-5475</phone><name>Pie In the Sky Bakery</name><city>Woods Hole</city><id>1455095</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.668822</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How About you capers getting out of bed and joining us for a scenic yet brisk walk along the beaches and through the neighborhoods of quaint Woods Hole.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to meet at the Pie in the Sky Bakery at 10 Water St. in Woods Hole MA at about 1 pm.  If you'd like to get there early and have some much needed coffee. We'll meet you there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking should be plentiful along the streets (it's not summer). In the unlikely event that you are unable to find a spot on the street, you can park for the day in the Steamship Authority Lot for $8.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always our hikes are kid and dog friendly - dogs require leashes and be prepared with a baggie or two. &lt;br /&gt;And as always it will go on rain or shine... that means you .... Jeannie and you other chickens.  If it rains... we are still walking.  Hopefully it will be snowing!  The only way I'll consider canceling is if there are gail force winds... and even then the sea will be AWESOME so I probably wouldn't.  Dress appropriately - there's an LLBean in Wareham or an EMS in Plymouth. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After our brisk walk we'll stop back in at the Pie in the Sky Bakery for some coffee, chai or hot chocolate... there food is outstanding also. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there !&lt;br /&gt;- R&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll probably be the only large red-headed guy with a goatee</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295549095000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293364049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years Day Walk on the Shining Sea Bike Path - Woods Hole</name><id>15820535</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293904800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/15820535/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/7/global_6044183.jpeg</photo_url></item>