<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Lane</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06037</zip><lat>41.628889</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ragged Mountain</name><city>Berlin/Southington</city><id>977436</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.796340</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Some places are just worth traveling to. Ragged Mountain borders Berlin, Kensington, New Britain and Southington and has westward vista views of 20 miles or more on a clear day. The trail is a moderate 6 mile loop with some strenuous areas. If you are not use to exercising regularly, this is not the hike for you. We'll meet at West Lane, Berlin, CT. Here's a link where you can get directions. Maybe some of you can coordinate a car pool. I will be driving directly there. The parking area is limited so park efficiently. &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;[311-499]+West+Ln&amp;amp;city=Berlin&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06037&amp;amp;latitude=41.6285&amp;amp;longitude=-72.80135&amp;amp;geocode=STREET And here's a link for the trail map. &lt;a href="http://www.town.berlin.ct.us/filestorage/199/2112/2276/raggedmountain_new_map_june_27_2011.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.town.berli...&lt;/a&gt; You'll want to bring water and a bag lunch or snack that we'll break to eat at the top. Hiking boots are strongly recommended. Layered clothing dependent on temperatures. Kids and dogs on leash are ok if they've done this type of hiking before and are very obedient in order to stay with the group. If you start the hike with the group, you stay with the group for the hike. No one goes off on their own. And of course each person is responsible for themselves. The Northeast CT Friends Meetup Group holds no liability for the participants. Let's Hike!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322325465000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NorthEast-Connecticut-Friends-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1330452</id><group_lat>41.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.2099990845</group_lon><name>The NorthEast Connecticut Friends Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320926909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ragged Mountain Hike, Berlin CT</name><id>40667552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322320500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NorthEast-Connecticut-Friends-Meetup-Group/events/40667552/</event_url></item>