<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>236 Patriots Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02048</zip><lat>42.010600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508.339.4810</phone><name>Davio's</name><city>Foxborough</city><id>1291450</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.172900</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The SSDOMG is finally trekking to Patriot Place!  You voted and the clear winner by a few votes was Davio's!!  Join fellow Members and Guests of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a fun Lunch @ Davio's at Patriot Place in Foxborough. At Davio's they make their own bread, desserts, ice cream and sorbets at their bakery.  There is also a gluteen free menu for customers that have special diets.  It will be a great afternoon to spend with members of the Meetup group.  I hope you can join us for a fun afternoon.  One place Jeanne plans on going to after Davio's is the Christmas Tree Shop.  Maybe you will join her for a spin at the Christmas Tree Shop or just explore what Patriot Place has to offer with others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many members of the Group have not yet been to Patriot Place so this will be a great opportunity for us to do some exploring after lunch if you so desire.  Lunchtime prices are reasonable in the $6-$25 range.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy.  This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Patriot Place Lunch! &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, June 19th, 2010 @ 12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Davio's&lt;br /&gt;236 Patriot Place&lt;br /&gt;Foxborough, MA  02035&lt;br /&gt;Tel:  1-508-339-4810&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website:  www.davios.com/fox&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: &lt;i&gt;Outside the front door if it's nice out.  We will then go in together as a Group.&lt;/i&gt;  Otherwise, inside the Lobby.  If you arrive after we are seated the reservation is under &amp;quot;Jeanne.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Angela &amp;amp; Jeanne&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 6 people 48 hours in advance.  Max of 15 people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per Member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees: Annual Members - FREE, Group Members - $2, Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 10am on Friday, June 18th.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page.  ***Extended to 6pm on June 18th as we have confirmed we will have outdoor seating!***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Event goes on rain or shine.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on &amp;quot;Weather&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Obtained from the website.  Located in between Bar Louie and Eastern Mountain Sports.  Take the P-6 entrance in to get to the restaurant.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 95: Take Exit 9 (Wrentham) onto Route 1 South. Follow Route 1 South approximately 3 miles to Patriot Place (on the left).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 495: Take Exit 14A onto Route 1 North. Follow Route 1 North approximately 4 miles to Patriot Place (on the right).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the Front Door.  Late arrivals should ask the host for "Jeanne."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>714439</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277003580000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275831389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriot Place Lunch!</name><id>13713206</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276965000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/13713206/</event_url></item>