<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Corner of Highland and Russell</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.270439</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Elm Park</name><city>Worcester</city><id>905026</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.814621</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Art in the Park Photo Contest!&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Worcester Cultural Commission and the Worcester Photography Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Worcester Cultural Commission and the Worcester Photography Center are getting together to bring you the “Art in the Park Photo Contest.” There are many events and happenings surrounding this years Art in the Park and we are hoping you‘ll all want to help capture these fun events and then share the images with the Cultural Commission. There are some very impressive pieces in the park this year and having you all show them off with your photographic creativity is a perfect challenge for a photo contest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the contests categories?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The subject matter is the Art Work in Elm Park, but these are the categories to submit your images into for the contest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Art Itself: Images of the art visibly identified within the context of Elm Park&lt;br /&gt;Daily Life: Sculpture as a backdrop in the park or of interaction of folks in the park with the sculptures to daily life in Elm Park&lt;br /&gt;Any of The Events, for example: Art in the Park Opening Ceremony or Creative Laundry&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, &lt;b&gt;August 5th&lt;/b&gt; Opening Ceremony along with ParkSpirit Concert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Rain date August 12)   5:00–6:00 PM Artists tours of works  (1st half exhibition)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30-7:00 PM Artists tours of work   (2nd half exhibition)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM Concert (TBD)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:00–9:00 PM Artist reception (TBD)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday, August 8            &lt;/b&gt; Art in the PARKing Lot festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Rain date August 15th)  11:00 AM – 3:00 PM Sole Proprietor parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sculpture tours in Elm Park, sculpture demonstrations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sunday, September 19&lt;/b&gt;    stART on the Street Festival, Park Ave. Worcester&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:00 AM – 5:00 PM   (30,000 attendance expected)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afternoon (TBD) – Awards presented to Art in the&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park winners&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Week of &lt;b&gt;September 26&lt;/b&gt;     De-Installation of sculptures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each Category Winner will receive a prize awarded for the best overall image in that category.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each entrant may submit entries in any Category he/she wishes and may submit entries at different times during the entry period, but no entrant may submit in total more than six (6) entries. Images Must be Submitted by &lt;b&gt;Oct 11t&lt;/b&gt;h 2010 Midnight&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, rules, to learn about the Judges and the prizes: please visit the Worcester Photography Center Web Site at &lt;a href="http://worcesterphotographycenter.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://worcesterphoto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you accept photos shot with a digital camera, or digitally manipulated?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes. In fact – We are only accepting digital images to be emailed to donna@erbphoto.com. Digitally manipulated photos are also acceptable, and certainly encouraged. Photographs must be in digital format. Only online entries will be eligible. No print or film submissions will be accepted for entry into this Contest. The photograph need not be taken with a digital camera; scans of negatives, transparencies, or photographic prints are acceptable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the image specifications?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Image Size: Image should have a long dimension of at least 1000 pixels and no more than 3000 pixels&lt;br /&gt;Save file as (JPG) with maximum quality.&lt;br /&gt;Color Space: Adobe1998 or sRGB&lt;br /&gt;File Size: The file should be 5×7 at 300 DPI and no bigger than 2 MB&lt;br /&gt;You MUST label you photo with your name and what category it is being submitted for. Example: DonnaDufault_Events1.jpg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where do I submit my Photos?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must email them to this email address: donna@erbphoto.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The subject line must say ART IN THE PARK CONTEST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Name, Address, Phone Number- (Why? I need to be able to get a hold of you in case you are the winner!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You MUST label you photo with your name and what category it is being submitted for. Example: YourName_Events1.jpg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who are the judges?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To determine the Category Winners and Honorable Mentions, we are employing a panel of 5 judges, all from the Worcester Cultural Arena. The Judging will take place at the Worcester Art Museum between &lt;b&gt;October 18th &amp;amp; Oct 22nd 2010.&lt;/b&gt; Everyone is invited to come see the images hanging in the Educational Wing of the Worcester Art Museum, hear feed back and comments about their entries, and view all the submissions! Awards will be given at the end of the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who can enter the Contest?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Art in the Park Photo Contest is open to all photographers, both students and non-students, amateurs and professionals – anyone that is a member of the Worcester Photography Center. Joining the Worcester Photography Center is free and you can sign up and RSVP at &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/22"&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to enter:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please complete an entry form with the required information, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, and photo caption; and submit along with your photograph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contest Prizes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first-place Winner in each Category will each receive a small gift basket containing but not limited to: 2 Passes to the Worcester Art Museum, Awards Certificate, and Photography Swag.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grand Prize Winner will receive a Photo Gift Basket-  2 Passes to the Worcester Art Museum, Awards Certificate, and Photography Swag. (We are still gathering prizes from area businesses…)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What about copyright?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copyright(s) remain with photographer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small Print: Photo Release: If any persons appear in the photograph, the entrant is responsible for obtaining, prior to submission of the photograph, any and all releases and consents necessary to permit the exhibition and use of the photograph in the manner set forth in these Official Rules without additional compensation. If any person appearing in any photograph is under the age of majority in their state/province/territory of residence the signature of a parent or legal guardian is required on each release.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By entering this contest you are giving permission to the Cultural Commission to use your images for Publicity of the Art in the Park events. Basically it is a Publicity Release and License in which the entrant warrants that he/she is the owner of the photograph and grants to WCC and its licensees the irrevocable perpetual, nonexclusive license to reproduce, distribute, display, and create derivative works of the entry (along with a name credit) in connection with the Contest and promotion of the Contest and Worcester Cultural Commission without additional compensation.  No prize transfer, assignment, or substitution by winners permitted. If a prize (or part of a prize) is unavailable, the Sponsor, in its discretion, reserves the right to substitute the original prize (or that part of the prize) with an alternative prize to the equal monetary value and/or specification, unless to do so would be prohibited by law. NONCOMPLIANCE OR RETURN OF PRIZE NOTIFICATION AS UNDELIVERABLE, WHETHER BY REGULAR MAIL OR BY EMAIL, MAY RESULT IN DISQUALIFICATION AND SELECTION OF AN ALTERNATE POTENTIAL WINNER. Any of the above can change at anytime!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Start Date: &lt;b&gt;August 5th – Sept 24th 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Deadline date for submissions: &lt;b&gt;Oct 11th, 2010 9PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Entries must be emailed to Donna@erbphoto.com with subject line ART IN THE PARK CONTEST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. FILE Set up as 5×7 @ 300DPI or 1000 Pixel on the long dimension.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Judging &lt;b&gt;Oct 18-22&lt;/b&gt; at the WAM Images will be on display there for public viewing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Winners Announced at Worcester Photo Center Meetup &lt;b&gt;October 28th, 2010&lt;/b&gt; at the Worcester Art Museum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Person:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Dufault – donna@erbphoto.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/22"&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281046820000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277749510000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art In The Park Photo Contest</name><id>13937706</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281042000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13937706/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/global_14013533.jpeg</photo_url></item>