<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;We are meeting at the Dunkin Donuts at 1550 West Main Road, Portsmouth RI 02871-1323.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im starting this ride at 0845 so that we can give a short pre-ride meetup, and get going by 0900 before traffic gets heavy. This is an all day ride for the most part, arriving home around 4-5pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This ride will be at a medium pace, nothing crazy, but there are some curvy roads to enjoy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start out at Dunkin Donuts. After a jolt of 5hr energy and/or some choca mocha latte supreme with a shot of expresso, we will head out out over the bridge following 138, to 4, to 165, to Rt 82 stopping at Gillete Caste for a break, then back down the 82 towards Mystic for lunch.  After lunch we will run up the 201, then across on the 165 back home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;The section between Rt. 2 and Rt. 165 is especially nice. It has some straights, some super twisties, and several sweeping turns. Traffic is usually very light, there are plenty of opportunities to pass, and there is some decent scenery.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be plenty of places to join up or split up, just let us know at one of our stops so we are not thinking we lost someone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will stop to re-group at all road changes, with a sweeper in the back so we will not lose anybody. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I always recommend full gear.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no reason to push hard to keep up with anybody. (We much rather wait for you than wait for the paramedics). There should be a least 100ft between bikes at all times, single file, while going through twisty sections. Please take a moment and program ICE (in case of emergency) into your phone, with your emergency point of contact numbers. We are not planning on an emergency, but in case there is one, we want to be able to react quickly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DISCLAIMER:&lt;/b&gt; By being a member of this group you hereby agree to assume all risks and liability related to or resulting from any and all group functions. You agree that neither you nor any third party will hold any of the group's Organizer or Assistant Organizers liable for any injury, loss, or damage to your own person or property arising directly or as a consequence from a group activity. You also agree that your membership of this group is based on an &amp;quot;at will&amp;quot; basis. See terms of service 6,6.1,6.2 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/terms/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please review&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MSF Guide to Group Riding&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.msf-usa.org/downloads/Group_Ride.pdf"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please review&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Google Map&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?hl=en&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;msid=107726498430591389445.000490c99c2e95fa04536&amp;amp;z=10"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The town of Mystic was founded in 1654 and quickly rose to prominence as a shipbuilding center during the clipper ship era.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nowadays, Mystic has become known for its quintessential New England charm, as well as its two world-class museums: the Mystic Seaport, the world's largest maritime museum; and the Mystic Aquarium &amp;amp; Institute for Exploration, featuring fascinating creatures from both sea and land, as well as the exhibits of Dr. Robert Ballard, discoverer of the Titanic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mystic Pizza&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;56 West Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Mystic, CT 06355&lt;br /&gt;860.536.3700&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There should be some good views, so bring a camera. There is a gas station next to the Dunkin Donuts, so be fueled up, and ready to go. We will be leaving at 0900 sharp. Dress appropriately. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;  There is a $4 charge to get over the Newport Bridge (unless you have EZpass of course).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Orange/Black CBR600RR</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Navy CFL</member_name><member_id>8858593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285533324000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><id>1535765</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280976121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mystic Seaport/Gillete Castle Scenic Ride 2.0</name><id>14324908</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285505100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/events/14324908/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/6/global_15827206.jpeg</photo_url></item>