<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-3721</phone><name>Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>875759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105592</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Inception meets Men In Black: surreal and  dreamlike &lt;br /&gt; You are Mystery Agents, individuals employed by The Company. Your work  uniform is: Pajamas. Why? Because your job is to go to sleep... and,  though a combination of holistic hoopty nonsense and pharmaceuticals,  enter the collective dream of humanity - a place called Blue City. Once  there, your dream selves, garbed in the official Imposing Black  Suit-And-Tie (Sunglasses optional), embark on missions on behalf of The  Company - either research expeditions to parts of blue city previously  unexplored, assignments to take out a Hostile Personality (These are  hostile, monstrous dream characters that were apparently the cause of  all criminal psychotic behavior in humanity - each criminal has a  corresponding Hostile Personality in Blue City that caused their  actions, and when it is destroyed, the criminal becomes a productive and  normal member of society once more), or other, more mysterious actions.  In a dream, success is easy, and the only health meter is your heart  rate - but beware, for the longer you remain, the weirder things will  get...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the April installment of our series of one-shot RPG experiences to be offered monthly over the course of 2011.  Each month will feature a different GM running a new game.  This month's GM is Konstantin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got a game on your shelf that you've been itching to run, but your regular group just isn't interested?  Why not run it for us at the Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston!  We want to continue running one-shot games throughout 2011, and you can help!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the table with sleepy looking people</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tewhill</member_name><member_id>3431516</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303657489000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>'cause games by Jared Sorensen get you street cred with the cool kids!</why><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301784886000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April One-Shot - Lacuna</name><id>17158849</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303574400000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/17158849/</event_url></item>