<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Sanford Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06824</zip><lat>41.142273</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-319-1419</phone><name>Fairfield Arts Center</name><city>Fairfield</city><id>3967502</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.257866</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ga&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/d/8/event_63310712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;llery Jazz at&amp;nbsp;Fairfield Art Center&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Set against the backdrop of the FAC gallery, this concert series by jazz impresario Brian Q. Torff, features Brian and a series of guest musicians.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;$10.00 admission at the door&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;7-9pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Brian Torff is a renowned bassist and composer, and is currently Music Program Director at Fairfield University. He is a featured bass soloist, and currently appears with many other groups. He performs in jazz festivals around the U.S., has founded the Fairfield University Summer Jazz Camp, and has served as co-chair person for the music advisory board for the National Endowment for the Arts.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Brian&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Torff's professional career began in 1974 when bassist Milt Hinton offered him the opportunity of touring with Cleo Laine. During the late 70's, Torff recorded and performed with pianists Mary Lou Williams and Marian McPartland, and toured Australia, New Zealand, and Hong Kong with violin virtuoso, Stephane Grappelli. He played in pianist Erroll Gamer's last group and worked in the big bands of Oliver Nelson, and the Thad Jones-Mel Lewis Orchestra.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;In 1979, Brian Torff joined in a duo with pianist George Shearing. In the course of their 3 1/2 year collaboration they toured throughout the U.S., Europe, Brazil, and South Africa and were featured on the NBC Tonight Show, Merv Griffin, and their own PBS special from New York's Cafe Carlyle. They received worldwide acclaim, and were invited to perform at the White House in 1982 for President Reagan. Their third album won a Grammy for vocalist Mel Torme.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Brian Torff is a noted composer who has contributed works for records with George Shearing, Larry Coryell, and his own recordings- Hitchhiker of Karoo, Manhattan Hoe- Down, and Workin' On a Bassline. He has written scores that have been performed by the Boston Pops, Los Angeles Philharmonic, and the Pittsburgh Symphony, and as appeared as conductor, composer, and clinician for numerous high school and college jazz festivals.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Brian Torff was named faculty member of the year by the AHANA students and the office of Multicultural Relations at Fairfield University. He has taught African drumming as part of the Upward Bound program for inner-city students and has recently published articles on Mary Lou Williams, Stephane Grappelli, is a regular columnist for Jazz Improv magazine, and is listed in the Groves Dictionary of Jazz.He has been featured in the New York Times, Chicago Tribune, and many other music publications.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/f/b/event_38459131.jpeg" width="46" height="43" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the front entry to the gallery, I will be wearing the BW scarf with Piano Keys!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321046002000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318521452000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gallery Jazz at FAC</name><id>37261542</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320969600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/37261542/</event_url></item>