<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dreams may contain strong emotions about people, such as attraction, romance, passion, or desire. Here's a chance to explore dreams with people in them. Sometimes these people are coworkers, sometimes friends, sometimes lovers, sometimes complete strangers, and sometimes they may be quite other worldly. Who are they and what do they want? Do they represent the heart's longing for connection? Do they represent particular people in your life? Or may they be beings from other other dimensions, with an important message for you about your life? Dreams can mean many things. It helps to have a group to consider the meaning with. This group is particularly rich and wise in interpreting the meaning of dreams. I am never disappointed. I always look forward to it. I hope you will too. You are welcome to share your dreams or you may choose not too, in our confidential and supportive group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meeting will be facilitated by Deerheart. Deerheart is a spiritual guide, visionary artist, and tantric shaman. People are drawn to him to share their life stories, life challenges, and dreams. He provides gentle guidance, understanding, and intuitive healing love energy. His heart of compassion looks upon all with unconditional love. An experienced explorer of the dream realms for for over 25 years, he has researched and studied many books and studied under many teachers. For more information about him, visit his website, &lt;a href="http://www.visionarydreamguide.com/"&gt;Visionary Dream Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For directions and other information about location please visit the Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website.For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left through angel doorway, into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330058898000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328148174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Love, Romance, &amp; Friendship</name><id>50660072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329264000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/50660072/</event_url></item>