<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As promised, I have rescheduled this event. I already have my ticket for the 4:15 p.m. show. I strongly advise you to purchase your tickets before the day of the event. The theater's website has a link called "Tickets" near the top of its homepage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Spielberg’s movie &lt;em&gt;Lincoln&lt;/em&gt; is based in part on the book &lt;em&gt;Team of Rivals: The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln&lt;/em&gt; by Doris Kearns Goodwin. What a great read! I’m looking forward to seeing how Spielberg’s adaptation fares on the big screen. And I want to see David Strathairn as Secretary of State Seward (yeah, that one: Seward’s Folly).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****From the theater website:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Steven Spielberg directs two-time Academy Award winner Daniel Day-Lewis (&lt;em&gt;There Will Be Blood&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;My Left Foot&lt;/em&gt;) in &lt;em&gt;Lincoln&lt;/em&gt;, a revealing drama that focuses on the sixteenth president's tumultuous final months in office. In a nation divided by war and the strong winds of change, Lincoln pursues a course of action designed to end the war, unite the country and abolish slavery. With the moral courage and fierce determination to succeed, his choices during this critical moment will change the fate of generations to come. Also starring Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Tommy Lee Jones, Sally Field and David Strathairn.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I will arrive at the theater at 3:30 p.m. and wait at the foot of the stairs in the theater lobby. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for me carrying a red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I strongly suggest buying your ticket online or arriving early to buy it. &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The movie starts at 4:15 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;At about 3:45, I will move into the theater auditorium so we can get seats (and I can’t miss the previews!). You can find me in the theater auditorium if you are late. Arrive early if you want to sit with the group, or if you want to sit with me in the front of the auditorium.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;After the movie, I will wait at the foot of the stairs in the theater lobby to gather everyone. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for the red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We can chat briefly about the movie then.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Going out after the movie is optional and will be decided by the group after the movie.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;If&amp;lt;&amp;lt; we decide to go out after the movie, be prepared to add 25% to the cost of your order for both tax and tip. &lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Restaurants in the area add the gratuity to the check automatically for large groups. Bring&lt;/span&gt; CASH &lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;to make division of the check easier.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend this event so I know who to look for.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Marianne&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the red backpack. See the event description for complete details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355235735000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354680626000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lincoln (the movie): second attempt</name><id>94123162</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355085000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/94123162/</event_url></item>