<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tina is a member of this group, and my Frindship group, of course other meetup groups too..but my 2 groups are to be SHAMELESSLY PROMOTED here first...LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Talk about the new places and old places to go for the spring paddling season along with meeting people who do more than just kayaking..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you can go to the Poo-Hall, its actually a good event, its indoors, not too many homless or lowlife people, and at least its a Meetup Event, but ya got to pay too much to get in the door and pay for your booze and food, do they even anything good to eat ? probbolly, but 5 bucks for a piece of greasy glop ?...LOL....you will be the one breaking or plugging the toilet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not saying its free at Tina's, you bring your own favourite good quality booze and some community food stuff and booze too......but since im such an excitement seeker, im going where the action is... &lt;br /&gt;and i/we all can enjoy ourselves much better than at a commercial event...ya cant get wet and wild at that the Poo-Hall... unless you pick up and put down your feet in a rythmetic way looking like a wild baboon frustrated at something to prevent the pee your pants thing because the toilet is broke...ya still gonna get pee...and peed off that its expensively boring there...but still, i like poking fun so it might be a good event for a few of you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not only that....REMEMBER.....&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Its not the event, ITS the PEOPLE that make the event good..and only good fun people will go to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So enough of my PROMOTION...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tina sent you this message from Activities and Friendship Group &lt;br /&gt;for Hartford County Singles on Meetup.com:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Hey Al - here's the info for New Year's Eve. No limit on the &lt;br /&gt;RSVP's. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: CAN WE LIMIT BORING PEOPLE&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Year's Eve Party&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Monday, December 31, 2007, 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Tina's Home in Meriden (address to be provided)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: Only sending it out to YESS'es RSVP's at this time unless Tina wants to send it out some others.. its easy either way...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ring in the New Year with good friends, old and new, at Tina's &lt;br /&gt;home in Meriden. Dance and party the night away, shoot some &lt;br /&gt;pool, get hot in the hot tub &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: YEH DANCING&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;shoot poo ?? ..now you are going to get POO-HALL people..LOL &lt;br /&gt;HOT TUB...now thats getting wet and wild, and sensual ? no cant do that at this kind of party..LOL.. &lt;br /&gt;no PEEING in here either.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;\. . . . Board game table will &lt;br /&gt;also be available, so bring your favorite game. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: hmm my favourite game ?? Lemme see and feel of course....well its not Kissing and Telling...Kissing maybe... im making up the game and rules right now at work... Blondies...ummm...Blondes..and Blondies with Brown Eyes only..Na dont like them any more... &lt;br /&gt;But the second part is close the eyes and guess the color while kissing....LOL. so no one gets left out.. &lt;br /&gt;Spin the bottle....LOL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh sorry, you want those other games...i really do get carried away..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Meetup&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;platter and rolls will be provided. Bring a dish for the table &lt;br /&gt;and don't forget your favorite beverage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: Bring some extra good tasting Booze just in case you desire it later..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Worried about driving &lt;br /&gt;home? Bring a sleeping bag and stay the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: well that sounds good..im bringing my sleeping stuff...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ya cant do that at that other new years event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located right &lt;br /&gt;off the Wilbur Cross Parkway in Meriden; address and directions &lt;br /&gt;will be e-mailed prior to event. (No limit on RSVP's)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tina&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;al-r: I am very happy we have such a gracious host for this kind of party, bring good stuff and bring good cheer and happiness.. or we send you to the other event(s)..LOL.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions to location mailed to Yes RSVP's</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199318982000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>This is the best party in town... but no freeloading...you bring something good or you go to the Pool Hall and pay 40/50 bucks there..</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197309701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayakers Group Meeting and Tina's New Years Party, Meriden CT</name><id>6889013</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199145600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6889013/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/9/global_2825945.jpeg</photo_url></item>