<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>238 Tolland Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.809998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Misaki sushi and seafood buffet</name><city>Manchester</city><id>7517202</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.514748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;heard so many good things about this place at work....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the all-you-can-eat Misaki Japanese Sushi, Seafood, and Hibachi Buffet, healthy eating is what's on the menu. Offering a variety of hot and cold dishes, entrees made to order on the hibachi grill, and a large sushi bar with sashimi and sushi rolls all made fresh daily by two sushi chefs. You can go back and fill your plate as many times as you like, trying everything for all-you-can-eat price. If you've been tentative about trying Japanese cuisine, this might be a good way to get an introduction. &lt;br /&gt;

 The sushi is both skillfully prepared and artfully displayed, and all the favorites are here, such as the Boston Roll, the Rainbow Roll, and the Califoria Roll. &lt;br /&gt;

 Japanese hot food include Chicken Teriyaki, Gyoza Dumplings(pork), Shrimp Sticks, Swai Filet, Chicken Katsu (chicken breast cutlet), Tempura, Miso Soup and more. You'll even find at least one american dish here among the hot offerings. &lt;br /&gt;

 At the hibachi station, the chef will make any dish you desire, all to your liking, with a combination of fresh vegetables, noodles, and chicken, scallops,salmon, or shrimp. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cold dishes, which rest on a bed of ice, include salad, shrimp, French string beans, mussels, bean sprouts, cantaloupe, sliced oranges, and honeydew melon. &lt;br /&gt;

 For desert you'll find an array of bite sized cakes,cream filled puff pastry, brownies, and ice creamyou scoop yourself with such flavors as mint chip and strawberry. The ice cream selection is soon to expand to add the popular Japanese green tea and red bean flavors. LUNCH PRICE 12.99 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 | &lt;br /&gt;

 |&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>a warm welcome by chuck 860-729-4504  my email chuckles125@att.net</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chuck</member_name><member_id>11483387</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1346622204000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Smiling Happy Faces</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford</urlname><id>1498492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Eat, Laugh, and Be Merry in West Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342265023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MISAKI JAPANESE SEAFOOD BUFFET  SUNDAY  SEPT 2    12:30 PM</name><id>73304532</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346603400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford/events/73304532/</event_url></item>