<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>232 Dudley Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.282625</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tercentennial Park</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1240261</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.433334</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like the rain and cold will make tomorrow a pretty junky day out, so let's try for May Day instead! Please be sure to RSVP for the new date!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We meet in dark places. We're inside in snowy weather, but also in sunshiney weather. We're Mole People, let's face it. So I thought it'd be fun if we could go off on a tangent and have a NoMov -- a gathering where we don't see a movie and actually get some exercise and fresh air. (Insert gasp here!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you may know that in December, my husband, Paul, and I adopted a greyhound, whom we've named &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/JacobyTheGrey" target="_blank"&gt;Jacoby&lt;/a&gt; (after Ellsbury of the Red Sox). Fewer of you know that I've started a &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/GreytFun"&gt;greyhound meetup&lt;/a&gt; to meet a few of my neighbors who also have the hounds. I thought it'd be fun to combine the two groups and have a walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can bring your dog, you can bring your neighbor's dog, you can &amp;quot;borrow&amp;quot; a dog from a random backyard, or you can come without a pup at all. &lt;b&gt;We'll welcome everyone, as long as the dogs remain on leashes the entire walk and are relatively well-behaved on a leash.&lt;/b&gt; This park is lousy with pups on Saturdays, and almost all the dogs on the trail around the park are leashed (besides, it's the law and I don't want to spend the afternoon looking for a dog that ran away).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please, for the sake of everyone in the group, human and canine, PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE make sure your dog is up-to-date on rabies shots and other vaccines.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steady rain will postpone this event, so stay tuned to your email the morning of if it looks like it could be a possibility. &lt;b&gt;RAIN DATE: Saturday, May 1.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tercentennial Park in Framingham has a very nice, wide, paved route around the perimeter. I think the circuit is a mile around. We'll probably do a few loops around the park, but you can join us for as many loops as you want to. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 2:00 by the front of the trail, right by the parking lot and some of the memorial plaques. There is a &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;ll=42.282617,-71.43335&amp;amp;spn=0.00053,0.002368&amp;amp;z=19&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;cbll=42.282617,-71.43335&amp;amp;panoid=707vOIQ0vfLL66TyHr-T2Q&amp;amp;cbp=11,279.95,,0,5.71"&gt;parking lot off Dudley Road&lt;/a&gt; that runs parallel to the road. If you can't find parking there for some reason, there is a bigger lot just to the east on the corner of Cushing Way and Dudley Rd. If you get lost, call me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP so I know who to expect and who to wait for. If you don't know me, you'll probably notice Jacoby first -- he looks like a cross between a deer and a horse (he's a big boy!) and he's insanely friendly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on 4/17!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana &lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Jacoby, the big brindle greyhound who prances like a horse, with me! (I look like my picture.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272928812000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270752560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NoMov--Hoofing it With the Hounds</name><id>13126798</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272736800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/13126798/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/c/global_14221580.jpeg</photo_url></item>