<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>72 Broadway</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06460</zip><lat>41.191471</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Costa-Azzurra Restaurant</name><city>Milford</city><id>3665592</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.084984</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THURSDAY MAY 10 - Connecticut Theatre Group COMEDY NIGHT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Theatre Group&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;for a night of great Comedy and New Friends&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ITALIAN BUFFET starts at 7pm - Only $20 - includes tax and tip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eggplant Rolotini, Chicken Francaise Penni Vodka Cream Sauce, Stuffed Fillet of Sole, Sausage, Peppers and Onions, Vegetables, Roasted Potatoes, Swedish Meatballs, Salad, Coffee or Tea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Your Advance Ticket Discount - Only&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;$15&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Online&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* Tickets at the event are $20 (cash only please)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/f/7/event_40017591.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costa-Azzurra Restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;72 Broadway&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Milford, CT 06460&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2 HEADLINERS at this show!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us in the&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Theatre Group&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Section&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George Gallo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;one of those performers that keeps his audiences riveted because they don’t want to miss a thing. Whether he is performing on stage, or directing/producing/acting in a video short, he is an entertainer to the very core.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;He began "performing" as early as the fourth grade, and says by the seventh grade even his teachers took notice. One teacher even went so far as to take George around where he impersonated all of the teachers in the school - and kept them all laughing while he did it. He was in fact voted "Most Humorous" by his high school class, but it was his talent for mimicry that has morphed into an uncanny ability to reproduce an exact sound, voice, or character.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A child of the seventies and admitted science fiction freak, his influences include Cheech and Chong, Robins Williams, Eddie Murphy and Steven Spielberg movies. His involvement as an extreme BMX bicyclist gave him the physical confidence to work in a high degree of physicality into his performances, and he soon began acting in, producing, and directing short segments for radio. These "bits" led to video segments that have since been featured on NBC, Make Me Laff, FOX, and Comedy Central, to name a few. Word of his talent for writing led to several segment writer gigs, as well as featured comic spots at some of NY’s most well-known comedy venues.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Michael Young Cho&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;born to Korean parents who immigrated to New York in hopes for greater educational opportunities for their children. Michael was the typical Korean student who was quiet in school and never a problem to his parents, teachers nor his school.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Then after his sophmore year in college, he took the challenge of telling jokes on stage. After his first performance, he was hooked. At the request of the owner of the comedy club, he was asked to return the next night. " ...if the owner didn't ask me to come back, I wouldn't be doing this today..."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terry McNeely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Long Island born and raised, Terry McNeely could easily earn the title of “Crass Critic to the Suburban World.” Terry summarizes his childhood with salty, cutting interactions experienced while living with his ornery, basketball coaching dad. Immediately out of adolescence he embraced the streets of Queens as his second home where he adopted an “Italian-by-Association” heritage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;McNeely finds his comfort zone on stage discussing his bitter disgust for women and married life while mocking husbands everywhere. He commands the stage with a with nothing short of Colin Quinn or Dennis Leary. It’s certainly no surprise that the acid humor of Terry McNeely has him rising up the ranks of comedy in leaps and bounds.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THURSDAY MAY 10 * Buffet at 7pm - Show 8pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatre.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.CTTheatre.com&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have reserved tables</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336706396000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335718630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THURSDAY MAY 10 - Connecticut Theatre Group COMEDY NIGHT with 2 Headliners</name><id>62630842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336694400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/62630842/</event_url></item>