<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;Let's have a special Seafood brunch at P-town. This place is open year round and has been on Chronicle. Check on the link below... Menu is there and all kinds of info... We'll have to do this in the summer too, but it is busy.... Right on the ocean! Usually a fun crosswind at P-Town. We might even catch a few whales breaching.... Start the new year early...  &lt;br /&gt;An Alternative would be January 4th or 11th...&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fanizzisrestaurant.com/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fanizzisrestaurant.com/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fanizzisre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A short cab ride ($6 per person) from the airport is the town of Provincetown with many restaurants and galleries. Fanizzis is right on the beach but enclosed so open year round. Great and varied food selection should cater to all tastes. I highly recommend the clam chowder and then take a short stroll up the main street into town. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awards &lt;br /&gt;Cape Cod Travel Guide – Editors Choice Award 2004 Lower Cape &lt;br /&gt;Cape Cod Life 2004 – Lower Cape Silver Medal for Best Chowder  &lt;br /&gt;AAA Approved – Diamond Rated &lt;br /&gt;Readers Choice Award 2004 – #1 Choice for Restaurant for Lunch – Provincetown &lt;br /&gt;Readers Choice Award 2004 – Honorable Mention for Restaurant for Dinner – Provincetown &lt;br /&gt;Nominated for Best of Brunch 2006 – Cape Cod Life Magazine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zagat Rated  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It feels like you're floating inside this seafooder that juts out over Provicetown Bay,  &lt;br /&gt;itself the best decor there is - whether you come for the excellent brunch on a sunny Sunday morning,  &lt;br /&gt;or arrive during a storm, when you'll see the waves swarm around the room  &lt;br /&gt;- adding a bit of excitement to the reliable, well-balanced Italian  &lt;br /&gt;and American style dishes and always pleasant service.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fanizzisrestaurant.com/information.html#hours" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fanizzisre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231891123000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228792671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>C-Food, P-Town, X-winds, G-bye 08 Sunday Brunch</name><id>9305799</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230472800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/9305799/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/0/global_6565568.jpeg</photo_url></item>