<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>735 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.376170</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-314-3425 </phone><name>Waltham Public Library</name><city>Waltham</city><id>788502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.239322</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello PANDA Massachusetts supporters!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MARK YOUR CALENDARS and get ready for PANDA’s first-ever public event in Massachusetts! On Sunday, April 14th at 1:00 PM, PANDA Massachusetts supporters from every corner of the political spectrum will be meeting at the Waltham Public Library Lecture Hall to show our 100% UNANIMOUS nonpartison support for the United States Bill of Rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PANDA Massachusetts’ Director Benjamin Selecky will detail our strategy for passing PANDA’s H.1428, the Massachusetts Liberty Preservation Act. which we have submitted to the Massachusetts House of Representatives. Benjamin will discuss and explain the many ways we can take part in PANDA’s historic and fast-growing national movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our urgent civil rights legislation will do what the US Congress should have done more than a year ago: SHRED Sections 1021 and 1022 of the 2012 National Defense Authorization Act!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In honor of PANDA’s civil rights legislation, we will be shredding the unconstitutional NDAA. What will be going into our shredder on April 14th?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, for starters we will shred the NDAA’s justice-crushing terms that effectively make every American vulnerable to indefinite detention: “Substantially Support” – Into the PANDA Shredder! • “Associated Forces” – Into the PANDA Shredder!• “Coaltion Partners” – Into the PANDA Shredder! • “Belligerant Act” – Into the PANDA Shredder!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You won’t want to miss this chance to meet like-minded friends of Due Process and the Right to a trial by jury. &lt;br /&gt;

We look forward to seeing you on April 14th in Waltham! (RSVP helpful, but not required)  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://pandaunite.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://pandaunite.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365994394000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-349</urlname><id>593245</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Libertarian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365219131000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PANDA Meeting (People Against NDAA)</name><id>112955582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365958800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-349/events/112955582/</event_url></item>