<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 1A</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.083500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 436-6507</phone><name>Odiorne Point State Park Phone: Odiorne:</name><city>Rye</city><id>1004595</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.795937</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a beautiful section of New Hampshire coast line.  The hiking trails are easy, very little elevation.  We will meet at the boat ramp parking lot and proceed to the jetty on the south side of Little Harbor.  From there we will walk south past the Science Center to Ordiorne Point where the sunken forest (referred to as the &amp;quot;Drowned Forest&amp;quot;) is.  We can then follow the paved path back to the starting point.  We will keep it about 1 1/2 - 2 miles.  There are some great places to have lunch after the hike (Petey's has great chowder).  If the weather is sunny and warm you may want to bring a lunch.  There are many tables in the park to have a picnic.  They do not allow dogs at the park.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;From 95 North or South&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 5 on Interstate 95 North or South to the Portsmouth Traffic Circle. From the Circle take Route 1 By-Pass South to Beaches/Hampton. After 1 mile the road connects with Route 1 South. Follow Route 1 South for approximately 1 mile. At the third traffic light, take a left onto Elwyn Road. Pass the Urban Forestry Center (on your left), go approximately 1.3 miles to the roundabout at Foye's Corner. Go half-way around the roundabout onto Route 1A South. Continue for 1.8 miles to the Odiorne Point State Park boat launch parking area (on left).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from the South some people may want to take Route 1A along the coast from Hampton Beach.  It's a beautiful ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some information on the area: &lt;br /&gt;Odiorne Point is the largest undeveloped stretch of shore on New Hampshire's eighteen mile coast. Located three miles south of Portsmouth on Route 1A in Rye, Odiorne offers an extensive array of habitats. On the south end of the park, sheltered tide pools of the Sunken Forest give way to an exposed rocky shore. Just north, the shore evolves into a pebble beach which shelters a fresh water marsh. Along the way to Frost Point where a jetty extends into Little Harbor, lies a small sand dune environment. At the end of Little Harbor, Seavey Creek feeds the neighboring salt marsh. Extensive inland disturbances during World War II induced the growth of dense forests in various stages of succession. Large stone walls bound open fields. Fresh water systems are represented within the park by a man-made pond and marsh. Remnants of formal gardens and wildflowers grow side by side; and the man-made military bunkers lie hidden under mounds of earth.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the boat ramp parking lot in my green Toyota 4Runner.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255789548000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254456194000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ordiorne Point State Park Rye, NH</name><id>11526638</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255183200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/11526638/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/b/global_11008251.jpeg</photo_url></item>