<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Look for High St and Glencliff home for the elderly</address_2><address_1>Sanitorium Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03238</zip><lat>43.992449</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Glencliff Trail</name><city>Glencliff</city><id>551566</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.886938</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;MT Moosilauke via Glencliff trail &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-New-England-Hiking-Meetup/pages/Mt_Moosilauke/"&gt; Trail Itinerary&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  7.80 mi To summit and back&lt;br /&gt;Time 8 hrs&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3348 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -36 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +3312 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is a great 4000 ft snowshoe hike with 360 views on a clear day &lt;/b&gt; The Glencliff trail is the best winter trail. It is quite a hike, but good footing, and never too steep. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/f/0/event_2756816.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This group will average a 12-1pm turn around time depending on the conditions. Both snowshoes and crampons/microspikes are mandatory for this hike&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will descend the same route we ascend. If trail or hiker conditions slow the group, you need to understand that the goal for the day can change and we must turn back to end the hike safely and at a reasonable hour.  We will summit if conditions allow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions to the trailhead:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; From Mooselauke Rd/RT 25 continue to Sanitorium RD (HIGH STREET). This paved road goes east from Rt 25 at the south end of downtown Glencliff. There is a sign indicating this is the way to the NH home for the Elderly. The parking lot will be on the right, just past the trailhead. A parking permit is not required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Prepare for full winter conditions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/b/7/event_3586519.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Any winter hikes will be rated higher in difficulty.&lt;/b&gt; A trail that you hiked in the summer months will be much different and a totally new experience in winter. It is an aerobic challenge but lots of fun for the prepared hiker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Every year is a new year physically.&lt;/b&gt; Hiking on icy rocks and snowy trails and colder temperatures. Gear up and let's hike one of the NH 4000ft destinations.  It will be a workout  on snowshoes and traction but lots of fun. The summit will be nice but let's start with the goal of just having a good hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We would like to see at least 4 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a Winter Meetup.&lt;/b&gt; Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup. If your plans change, please change your rsvp as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date.&lt;/b&gt; Its very important that we &lt;br /&gt;have a true headcount, and not worry that your late or lost trying to find the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into 2 groups so everyone stays warm, or if there is an injury. Every hiker is personally responsible to be prepared and understand hiker safety.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather conditions will be reviewed the week of the event. Hikers will be advised by email of any cancellations or changes. Extreme temps and high winds / official weather warnings will cancel the hike, so make sure we have a way to contact you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In parking lot  just before nursing home. Gold Honda CRV  phone  603-477-5116</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234271876000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233447186000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Moosilauke Via Glencliff Trail</name><id>9642973</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234098900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9642973/</event_url></item>