<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>108.2 mile marker 1-93 Northbound lane</address_2><address_1>Trailhead Parking</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.142196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lafayette Place Parking Lot</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>239317</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.681663</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us to hike Mt Cannon! This is the famous former home of the Old Man of the Mountain...and another one of the White Mountains 48 4000 footers.  Mt Cannon checks in at 4100 ft.  We will meet at the Lonesome Lake Trailhead...which is at Lafayette Place Campground.  We will take the Lonesome Lake trail for .4 miles to the Hi-Cannon trail for 2 miles. This intersects with the Kinsman Ridge Trail which will take us .4 miles up to the summit of Cannon. We'll have lunch there and then head back down the Kinsman Ridge Trail .8 miles to the Lonesome Lake Trail. We'll take this .9 miles down to the lake where we will do a circle of the lake on the Around-Lonesome-Lake trail (.6 miles) including a stop at the AMC Lonesome Lake Hut. Its then another 1.2 miles back to Lafayette Place Campground.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total Distance: 6.3 miles&lt;br /&gt;Total Elevation Gain: 2,400 ft&lt;br /&gt;Estimated Time: 5 hours &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Greg has agreed to lead a second group if we get more people (White Mountains limit 10 hikers per group) so I have opened up the hike to a limit of 20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Trail Head Directions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-93 Northbound through Lincoln NH, reverse direction at the Tramway Exit 34B and return southbound.&lt;br /&gt;Southbound, exit at Lafayette Campground sign and turn L before bridge for trailhead parking.&lt;br /&gt;Lafayette Campground, Franconia Notch State Park Parkway, elevation about 1740 feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lodging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start at 10 AM at the trailhead...so that gives people the option of either driving up early that morning or camping out the night before. I'm going to stay at Lafayette Place Campground, which also happens to be where the trail head is at! I have a site reserved for both Friday and Saturday nights (site 48 if you want to get one close) (I'll probably post something for Sunday too. 2 tents per site. Sites are 25 bucks per night...and that covers 2 adults...each extra adult at a site adds 10 bucks. Link to reserving a site there:&lt;br /&gt;[&lt;a href="http://www.reserveamerica.com/camping/Lafayette_Campground/r/campgroundDetails.do?contractCode=NH&amp;amp;parkId=270044" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.reserveame...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will be at an &lt;b&gt;easy to moderate pace&lt;/b&gt;. The goal will be to support hikers new to the White Mountains in achieving a 4000 foot summit.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is one spot on the hi cannon trail that involves a ladder, just as warning:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://hikenh.netfirms.com/i/02d19.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;To participate you should:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable walking at least 7 miles on uneven terrain including roots, rocks, and granite ledges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have sturdy hiking boots.  No Sneakers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have rain and wind protection.  No Ponchos!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be able to carry at least 2-3 liters of water. (3 strongly recommended.)  (Remember, 1 liter weighs 2 pounds!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be in good physical condition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Equipment List&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sturdy Hiking Boots.  &lt;b&gt;No Sneakers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rain / Wind Jacket. &lt;b&gt;No Ponchos.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Warm fleece layer (100 or 200 weight fleece is fine for summer.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Something warm for the summit.  Expect it to be very windy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-3 liters Water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Headlamp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trail Snacks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bug Repellent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Optional Gear:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hiking Poles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gaiters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunscreen / Sunglasses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Camera / Binoculars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Jeans, Sneakers, or Cotton clothing on the hike!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the bright yellow escape or call my cell 508 414 8544.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276518305000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275620255000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt Cannon</name><id>13692995</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276349400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/13692995/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/a/global_15487690.jpeg</photo_url></item>