<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekday Hike @ Quabbin Reservoir: Gate 11 (Pelham Center)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty: (Moderate, but over 7 miles, hilly)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/e/6/event_73253222.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Reservoir is, in surface area, the second-largest man-made body of water in the world. It provides drinking water for the Boston area, and is home to bald eagles, moose, bears, foxes, deer, wild turkeys, and more. It is spectacular, with old roads, natural beaches, and crystal-clear water! The entire thing cannot even be seen from the viewing tower...but on clear days, you can see Mount Monadnock from just off Route 9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuing our quest to visit every historic Quabbin gate, we'll combine the hikes from Gates 11 and 8 into one loop. It might be a little chilly, but it shouldn't be windy in the woods. Pack a lunch...we'll picnic at some beach! Parking is at Gate 11, across the street from the Pelham Historical Society on Route 202. (If there's no more room, park at the Society itself, but I doubt that will happen on a Monday.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from North-Central or Northwest Mass:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Northeast or Northwest, take Route 2 or 122 to New Salem. Turn South on Route 202. The Pelham Historical Society is about 10 miles on the southbound side of the road; Gate 11 is across the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from the East or West:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 to Belchertown, and turn North on Route 202. The Pelham Historical Society is about 7.5 miles on the southbound side of the road; Gate 11 is across the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from the South:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the nearest road North to Route 9 and follow directions "from the East or West."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Walking is on old roads (mostly dirt), no special equipment needed. It will be chilly Monday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No pets, swimming, or wading. (Quabbin Reservoir is a drinking water supply.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Carry in, carry out." Take your trash home with you. (Same reason.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322918985000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322087233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Reservoir: Gate 11 (Pelham Center)</name><id>42216622</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322668800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/42216622/</event_url></item>