<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Curzon Mill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.822050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-7223</phone><name>Maudslay State Park</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>848934</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.926670</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be an early evening walk, but we'll plan to be back to the cars around 6:30 or 7 PM. Like I told many of you last week, I missed most of the springtime blooms here last year, and want to keep a more regular eye on it this year- we saw some early bloom rhododendrons (Spelling?) last week...so it's coming!  Please bring a dollar to contribute to our meetup group fees, and parking is $2 for the parking meter at Maudslay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paths are typically level and well-cleared here- a mix of gravel, dirt, and some packed meadow trails.  There are usually a couple very short inclines- like stepping up from one trail to another or something, but these are really very easy walking trails...sneakers tend to suffice just fine.  My standard disclaimer: any walk with me is typically an "exploration" walk.  i have been to Maudslay a few times, but wouldn't say I know it like the back of my hand.  So, it's possible we may get turned around or take a new route.  that being said, it is not the sort of park we are likely to stay lost in very long!  My goal is to walk the river trail and the Mtn Laurel trail.  Anyhow, it's a pretty park, and the weather looks great, so let's get out for a couple hours and enjoy it!  I tend to walk pretty quickly- or so I'm told- perhaps 18-20 min/mile, so we'll probably cover a few miles...plan on 1.5-2 hrs...definitely back before dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This walk is dependent upon interest- I'll cancel by 1 PM if there doesn't seem to be interest.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marilee </member_name><member_id>6596076</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337000151000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336872987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maudslay Sunday evening walk- still trying to catch those blooms before rain ;)</name><id>64567012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336942800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/64567012/</event_url></item>