<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.407211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>4355392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.382439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Performing Arts &lt;br /&gt;

A group show at Worcester Academy of Music &lt;br /&gt;

Worcester Alliance of Photographers &lt;br /&gt;

June 2013 – January 2014 &lt;br /&gt;

Opening Reception June 1, 2013 at 6PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

All members of Worcester Alliance of Photographers (WAP) and other local photographers are invited to submit their work for this special group exhibit at Worcester Academy of Music, 11 Irving Street, Worcester, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The theme for this exhibit will be Performing Arts. Submitted photographs must have something to do with the performing arts, either explicitly or implicitly, and be completely child/family friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submissions for judging will be due on or before April 27, 2013 at 6 PM. Images must be in JPG format (sRGB) and sized to be approximately 5” by 7” at 300ppi. Please keep physical file sizes at/under 1MB. To submit your images, please email up to 5 images directly to Donna Dufault: Donna@ErbPhoto.com please put WAM Performing Arts Submission in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Image file names should be in the format: LastName_FirstName_ImageTitle.jpg (e.g., &lt;br /&gt;

Smith_John_ThePerfectPicture.jpg).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Selected photographers’ names will be posted on the Worcester Alliance of &lt;br /&gt;

Photographers website (www.meetup.com/photo22) on or before May 4, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All accepted photographs submitted for hanging must be matted (white only), framed and wired (no sawtooth). Please cut out and complete both parts of the form at the bottom of this page. Affix one copy securely to the back of your framed photograph, and submit the other when you drop off your artwork. We are responsible for labeling the artwork on display with artist name, title and price (if your image is being offered for sale).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rules: &lt;br /&gt;

● Each photographer may submit up to five (5) images via email for judging (no fee). &lt;br /&gt;

● All artwork submitted for hanging must be matted (white), framed and wired (no sawtooth). &lt;br /&gt;

● Indicate whether artwork is being offered for sale. &lt;br /&gt;

● Purchases will be handled by WAP and Worcester Academy of Music. WAoM will collect a 20% commission. &lt;br /&gt;

● Sold work must remain on display for the duration of the exhibit. &lt;br /&gt;

● Insurance for artwork will not be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Schedule summary: &lt;br /&gt;

04/27/2013 (6 PM) – Image submission deadline. &lt;br /&gt;

05/04/2013 – Notifications posted on meetup site.. &lt;br /&gt;

05/18/2013 (10 AM 2 PM) – Framed artwork due at Worcester Academy of Music. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Images from the last show to be picked up at this time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

06/01/2013 (6 PM) – Opening reception. &lt;br /&gt;

June 2013 to January 2014 – Show is open to the public. &lt;br /&gt;

January 2014 (exact date to be determined 10AM- 2 &lt;br /&gt;

PM) – Show closed. Pick up artwork.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about Worcester Academy of Music, please visit their website: www.worcesteracademyofmusic.com &lt;br /&gt;

For more information about Worcester Alliance of Photographers, please visit our website: www.meetup.com/photo22&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Morse</member_name><member_id>3632743</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Lane</member_name><member_id>5229126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis Ditto</member_name><member_id>13146412</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367111353000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365516859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A group show at Worcester Academy of Music - New Show Invite and Pick Up</name><id>113462862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367100000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/113462862/</event_url></item>