<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The trailhead is about 1.2 miles from Route 25 in Glencliff Village. It was called the Sanatorium Road, but is now High Street. You will park in a lot to the right where the trailhead crosses a broad field. At the end of the field, one of the Dartmouth Outing Club huts is on the left. .I will be looking into renting that hut (about 8 person capacity) if anyone is interested in staying over on Saturday night - great location, fireplace, porch, self-service. Please send me a note if you are interested in staying over on Saturday night&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When the trail enters the woods, it will be gradual for some time until it begins to gain elevation. The trail is about 3 miles long until it reaches the Moosilauke Carriage Road (that served the mountain when it was a popular hotel destination - until it burnt down many many years ago). From the Carriage Road it is about .9 miles to the summit. Rocky, broad summit with lots of wind most of the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will take about 3 hours and thirty minutes to reach the summit (3000 ft elevation gain).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the way down, we can return the way we came OR we can walk down the Carriage Road to the intersection with the Hurricane Trail that will wind around the East and South side of Moosilauke and return back to the Glencliff Trail. The length of this circuit will be about 4.3 miles and take about 3 hours. Total loop will be approximately 8 miles and 6 hours of hiking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should be prepared for late Spring conditions. There is likely to be snow left and ice and postholing will be a possible challenge. On the East side of the mountain, it catches the sun and we may see some wet conditions on the trail - be prepared with waterproof boots, gaiters, and clothing layers. Even if it doesn't rain, you will need to have a waterproof shell as well for the wind.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Don</member_name><member_id>5949952</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211204007000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207140817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Moosilauke - Glencliff Trail</name><id>7656827</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211031000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7656827/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/6/global_3677222.jpeg</photo_url></item>