<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 N Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.209446</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.224.9534</phone><name>Holiday Inn</name><city>Concord</city><id>764609</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537178</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE:  I have a table reserved for this event which seats 8 people.  If you would like to attend and sit with me (I'm not really that special!), then please get me $40 for your ticket, this is $5 off of the individual ticket price. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2008 &lt;a href="http://www.nhliberty.org/" target="_blank"&gt;NHLA&lt;/a&gt; Liberty Dinner will be held on Thursday, June 12. Mark your calendars now! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your seats now by clicking on the &amp;quot;Click and Pledge&amp;quot; box to your right!&lt;br /&gt;Individual tickets are available for $45 per person. You can upgrade your ticket by clicking on &amp;quot;Candidate Reception &amp;amp; Liberty Dinner&amp;quot; for an opportunity to meet in a small group setting with various candidates for the 2008 elections. Appetizers will be served at the reception.&lt;br /&gt;Reserve a dinner table of 8 for $320 and save you and your friends some money!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The annual Liberty Dinner will be held on Thursday, June 12 at the Holiday Inn in Concord. Besides good food and even better company, we will honor the Legislator of the Year and the Activist of the Year. We will also unveil our annual Liberty Rating, which rates all our reps and senators in relation to how pro-liberty their voting record is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Keynote Speaker will be Alex Ray, owner and founder of the Common Man chain of restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Ray is well known and respected in the state as an innovative entrepreneur and philanthropist. He has received many honors and recognition from both the business and arts communities here in New Hampshire. He has even extended his charitable work to helping victims of Hurricane Katrina.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two of his honors include being named him Man of the Year by The Northeast Economic Developers Association in 2006 and the Business in the Arts Award by The Barnstormers Theatre in Tamworth in 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Ray began his career as a business owner in 1971 with the first Common Man restaurant in Ashland. He has since grown his company into 13 restaurants up and down the I-93 corridor. These include a spa, an Inn and a country store. He is continually growing his operation and provides training and compensation to his employees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To read more about some of his charity work called &amp;quot;Do Good&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thecman.com/do-good/in-the-community.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thecman.com/do-good/in-the-community.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thecman.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact Dawn Lincoln at &lt;a href="mailto:chair@nhliberty.org" target="_blank"&gt;chair@nhliberty.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213481153000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208444501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NHLA Liberty Dinner</name><id>7757321</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213308000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/7757321/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/a/global_3188554.jpeg</photo_url></item>