<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>276 Edmands Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.330697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-405-1686</phone><name>Ann and Mark's home</name><city>Framingham</city><id>972696</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449002</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you experience stress?  If so, what kind?  How do you typically handle the stresses in your life, or when "bad" things happen?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How many days are you just operating in “survival mode”, doing your best to just get through all the commitments and demands required of you? “Life is stressful!” “Work is stressful!” Managing work, family, the house…OMG!  It goes on and on, and you just wait for relief and a moment to relax, right?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Or perhaps you have different kinds of stress in your life: business or work stress, relationship stress, financial stress, family stress, physical or health stress, stress created by not feeling good about yourself in some way, or just when those "bad" things happen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking for a way to feel better about feeling bad?  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you like a better understanding of what stress in your life means and how it can be a good thing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us as we discuss Stress and the Universal Cycles of Change and how they relate to the law of attraction perspective of expansion and growth.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You'll leave with a useful model and some tools that you can use to help you move from emotional and physical set backs, struggles and stress of any kind to new levels of happiness and growth.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thank you SO much to those of you who have RSVP'd "yes" and showed up! PLEASE, have respect for your hosts (us!) and show up if you sign up. If your plans change, just let us know!&lt;/strong&gt; We set up our space, and prepare snacks and handouts accordingly. Also, we can only take a maximum of 20 people in our space, and do not want to exclude anyone unnecessarily because of a no-show. Help us reach our goal of 100% attendance for those who rsvp "yes"!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please go to our files page (under More) to read about parking.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun! Please join us and stay "connected" by participating in our community's message board discussions and receiving our e-mails (which will include our "Good Vibrations" tips and news). To be able to do so, go to your account, and under "Your Groups", each one has an "Edit email settings". Set your preferences there. Hope to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're down a long driveway.  Look for white mailbox with our name and #276, across from large, old, white house</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338085763000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336240728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>From Stress to Success: moving beyond survival &amp; how stress can be a good thing!</name><id>dvhqscyqhbfc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337814000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/63554302/</event_url></item>