<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll meet at the entrance to the park beside the guard station.   Pack a lunch and drinks and we can eat on the beach.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Property Description  251 acres | Established 1967 &lt;br /&gt;World's End comprises four coastal drumlins -- Pine Hill, Planter's Hill, and the double drumlins of World's End proper -- all connected by over four miles of walking paths that offer dramatic views of the Weir River, Hingham Harbor, and the Boston skyline. The Reservation's hills are traversed by tree-lined roads and dotted with tree groves. In between are broad grassy fields that attract butterflies and are managed to provide habitat for grassland-nesting birds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Brewer built a mansion along Martin's Lane in 1856 and, over the next thirty years, acquired most of the peninsula as well as Sarah and Langley Islands. His farming estate was vast and varied. He produced hay and crops and raised thoroughbred horses, Jersey cattle, pigs, chickens, and sheep. To support these operations, Brewer built a complex of farm buildings that included a blacksmith shop, greenhouses, a smokehouse, and homes for farmhands and their families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1889, Brewer asked landscape architect Frederick Law Olmsted to design a residential subdivision for World's End. His plan included 163 house plots connected by tree-lined roads. The cart paths were cut and the trees planted, but the development never occurred.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the time of its acquisition by The Trustees in 1967, World's End was one of the most threatened landscapes on Massachusetts' entire coast. The peninsula had survived a 1945 proposal to construct a new United Nations Headquarters and a 1965 proposal to build a nuclear power plant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;World's End is one of the 30 islands of the Boston Harbor Islands National Recreational Area, designated in 1996. Unlike most National Parks, this park is administered by a partnership of national, state, and local representatives called the Boston Harbor Islands Partnership. The Trustees of Reservations owns and manages World's End. A Trustees representative serves on the 13-member partnership board that oversees the management plan for the Boston Harbor Islands&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245596858000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241367328000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WORLDS END HINGHAM - CHESTNUT HILL WALKERS</name><id>10325843</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244386800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/10325843/</event_url></item>