<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>75.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Love Response™: Creating Health Through Love With Eva Selhub M.D  &lt;br /&gt;February 28, 2010 10:00 - 5:00 &lt;br /&gt;Cost: $75 ($90 for non-members) -&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;If you are interested in this workshop you can either sign up here on the meet-up site or email Rain at rainhphillips@yahoo.com.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Medical doctor Eva Selhub knows an unequivocal truth: The key for a healthy, happy and prosperous life is the giving and receiving of love.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the difficult times that we live in emotions like stress, fear, anger and anxiety take over. Science proves, that with these emotions comes the breakdown of the body, the mind and social structures.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With love, the opposite happens: the body and mind's biochemistry balances out, positive emotions and thoughts come forward and social structures improve.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the Love Response, a response that shifts your body, mind and spirit from negative to positive, from fearful to hopeful, from angry to compassionate.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;In this workshop you will learn :&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; - the hard science behind the physical benefits of deliberately shifting into a place of balance by proactively creating the bonds we need to do so with others and with ourselves.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-  how the demonstration of love in the form of affection, self-nurturance and altruistic works improves health on every level.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- a set of simple practices that allow you  to find an inner stillness that enables your neurobiology to bring the body and mind into a state of flow and resilience - the hallmarks of health—while working through fear, anger and anxiety. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- to develop awareness, especially with regard to your own  physiology—to be able to discern you’re your physiology is functioning in its negative capacity, the stress response, versus in its positive capacity, the Love Response.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- how to shift from the negative physiology to the positive physiology in mere seconds.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join Harvard-affiliated medical doctor Eva Selhub and learn how to directly affect your physiology in positive ways—through the power of love—from a doctor who suffered her own major health crisis and found a way to heal. You’ll discover exactly how to create healthy changes that work, decrease stress, and let go of fear and anxiety.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;To quote Dr. Gustav Dobos, M.D., chair of complementary and integrative medicine, University of Duisburg-Essen, Germany, This &amp;quot; ...will change your life–it might even save it!”&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Eva Selhub, MD,* a trained internist and passionate advocate of mind-body medicine, is a clinical instructor in medicine at Harvard Medical School and a senior physician at the Benson Henry Institute for  Mind/Body Medicine at Massachusetts General Hospital. She is author of The Love Response/ and four audio CDs. www.theloveresponse.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267542831000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264851861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr.Eva Selhub shows how through very precise biological mechanisms love heals us</name><id>12465613</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267369200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/12465613/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>