<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Summer St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.346558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.443.0800</phone><name>M.J. O'Connor's</name><city>Boston</city><id>956019</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.042778</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Attention all Irish Pub Challengers: You’re invited to our biggest party of the summer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year’s Zoo Cruise n’ Crawl was an unbelievable event, complete with 700 of our closest friends rockin the boat (literally) to The Zoo, MTV’s Ultimate cover band. This year, we’ve made it even bigger and better, adding Fast Times, the second band for the lower deck of the Provincetown II. Add a VIP pre-party, free beer and food, and no-cover after party and it just became one of Boston’s biggest parties this summer. Double the bands, double the 80’s rock. So come one, come all, and join the Tenon Tours crew on Friday, August 6th for this epic event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s what’s happening:&lt;br /&gt;Date: August 6th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Time: 5:30pm – 1:30am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;5:30 PM – 7:30 PM:&lt;/b&gt; Exclusive Tenon Tours VIP Pre-Party @ M.J. O’Connor’s Waterfront. Included are FREE APPETIZERS, A COMPLIMENTARY COCKTAIL, and chances to win 1 of 2 $500 FLIGHT VOUCHERS TO IRELAND!*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:30 PM – 8:00 PM:&lt;/b&gt; Crawl over to the World Trade Center and join 800 others as we board the Provincetown II for the Annual Coors Light Zoo Cruise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;8:00 PM – 11:00 PM:&lt;/b&gt; On board, you’ll enjoy views of Boston like you’ve never seen before while you rock out to live performances by The Zoo, MTV’s Ultimate Cover band, and New England’s own 80’s cover band, Fast Times!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;11:00 PM – 1:30 AM:&lt;/b&gt; Hop back onto the mainland and crawl over to The Harp for the After Party. Show your Tenon Tours wristband for express line entry and no cover charge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a 21+ Event, and proper dress and ID are required. Although the Zoo Cruise capacity is 1000, the Crawl only has 200 spots available. This event sells out early every year so it is important that you purchase your tickets early!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Price: $35.00 – Limited Tickets Available! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;amp;hosted_button_id=AY52FBL79FA9G" target="_blank"&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt; to buy your ticket today!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Present your prepaid ticket at the door</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324246144000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pub Crawlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Pub-Crawlers-of-Boston</urlname><id>1391806</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Pub Crawlers of Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277906735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Zoo Cruise N' Crawl 2010</name><id>13959152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281130200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Pub-Crawlers-of-Boston/events/13959152/</event_url></item>