<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Cabot Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.581010</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>781-593-3555</phone><name>Danvers High School</name><city>Danvers</city><id>538291</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.931300</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>38.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi All!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an event coming up in April I wanted to let you all in on. Please see their web site for all the info!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yankee Photographic Society&lt;br /&gt;Providing New England with Education, Enrichment &lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp; Entertainment Through Photography&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Yankee Photographic Society&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://yankeephotosociety.homestead.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://yankeephotosoc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yankee is a diverse group of New England photo enthusiasts who meet twice a year for photographic exchange of ideas and workshops. Attendees come from Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Maine, Connecticut, Rhode Island, and New York. The seminars are scheduled in the spring: usually in March or April, and also in the fall, either in November or December. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Programs may include guest speakers, model  and child portraiture, slide, print, and digital mini salons,  The Greater Lynn International, and setups such as glassware, still life, blacklight, mylar, and pet photography. Registrants are encouraged to bring their camera, lens, and film or digital media to photograph the setups.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yankee membership is $8 for a single membership or $12 for a two-person joint household membership. You will receive a reduced registration fee to the fall seminar  2007 and the spring seminar 2008 and also  the &amp;quot;Yankee Crier&amp;quot;, a bi-annual 15-20 page publication.  The seminar registration cost is kept as low as possible. A group of about 50-60 volunteers help run the popular programs. Even the lunch buffet is a real bargain at $6.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see the seminar schedule, porfolio-hi-jinx-portraits,  registration, and directions for further information.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Information about the Photographic Society of America is available at: &lt;br /&gt;www.psa-photo.org&lt;br /&gt;Information about the  NECCC Photographic Conference, UMass, Amherst, MA, is available at: www.neccc.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MODELS AND PORTRAITS&lt;br /&gt;will be available for you to photograph 10:00AM - 3:00PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Megan, by Skip Hoyt&lt;br /&gt;Lori, by Skip Hoyt&lt;br /&gt;Sam, by Skip Hoyt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;April 12, 2008, 8:00AM (doors open) &lt;br /&gt;Program starts at 9:00AM through 5:00PM&lt;br /&gt;Models and Hi-Jinx will run from 10:00AM to 3:00PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DANVERS HIGH SCHOOL&lt;br /&gt;60 CABOT STREET, DANVERS, MA&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Scott and I will not be going to this but I wanted to put it out there for you all, if you want to meet up start a discussion about it online here and pick a place and time!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208178402000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205089935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yankee Photo Society Seminars</name><id>7497796</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208005200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/7497796/</event_url></item>