<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 Church Street</address_1><state>CA</state><zip>95062</zip><lat>36.974385</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>831.466.9870</phone><name>Pure Pleasure</name><city>Santa Cruz</city><id>884918</id><country>us</country><lon>-122.027663</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>450.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;TANTRA: THE ART OF CONSCIOUS LOVING,&lt;br /&gt;March 26-28 2010; Santa Cruz Mountains &lt;br /&gt;Transform Your Sexual Love Life in One Amazing Weekend!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles Muir and Leah Alchin will be in Santa Cruz Mountains of California to teach the world-renowned Beginners Weekend Seminar, Tantra: The Art of Conscious Loving. This seminar is a wonderful introduction to the transformative powers of Tantra Yoga. Whether you attend as a couple or a single, you can learn how to use sexual energy for increased intimacy, spiritual connection, and pleasure beyond your imagination. You will begin to master the many methods of regeneration so you can make love well into your old age, keeping you young for many years to come.  Master Charles Muir and Leah Alchin use a down-to-earth, humorous, and candid approach to creating a safe environment. No nudity or explicit sexual contact in class.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;You will learn how to be a conscious and masterful lover!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Breathing in lovemaking ~ key to ecstasy &lt;br /&gt;* Touching ~ 6 kinds of healing and erotic touch &lt;br /&gt;* Tired of dating? Discover the skills to attract the Beloved &lt;br /&gt;* Learn how your eyes, words, emotions, and vulnerability can take you to intimacy bliss! &lt;br /&gt;* Freeing the female orgasm ~ it’s easy! &lt;br /&gt;* 1,001 methods of exquisite pelvic movement &lt;br /&gt;* Sexual awakening for men, the Secret that can Quadruple the length and power of your orgasm &lt;br /&gt;* Advanced lovemaking techniques you will use forever &lt;br /&gt;* Female sacred spot massage ritual ~ step-by-step instructions to heal, awaken, and release  unlimited energy &lt;br /&gt;* Internal muscular exercises for increased energy and pleasure &lt;br /&gt;* And so much more &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt; &lt;b&gt;The Details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;March 26-28, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday 6:45 pm–10:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Saturday 10 am–7:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Sunday 10 am–8 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Santa Cruz, CA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$450 per person ($150 holds space, payment plans available) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Registration&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/tantrausa/pages/www.sourcetantra.com"&gt;www.sourcetantra.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;santacruz@sourcetantra.com &lt;br /&gt;1-888-682-6872 ext. 102 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Here’s what our students have to say…&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dear Charles and Leah...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you treated us as whole people with a full spectrum of emotions. All of the exercises were perfect and meaningful and they contributed greatly to my experience. It was so honoring and respectful, and I couldn't believe how funny Charles was. Both of you made it so much fun.  Dave and I definitely turned a corner, and are looking forward to absorbing what we learned, we plan to read over the materials and &amp;quot;practice&amp;quot; more this weekend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dear Charles and Leah...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I would like to take a moment to thank you so much for holding this weekend. I am the person in women’s group who has been married 33yrs and scared of the night’s homework on surrender. I have never experienced such a wonderful healing and it continues on! Amazing! Tears, lots of sadness, rounds of orgasms, and expansiveness! It has been a truly and wonderful feeling of aliveness! Thank you so very much for a weekend that saved us!&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah Alchin, ACTE</member_name><member_id>7260814</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269827560000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Tantric Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tantrausa</urlname><id>1157501</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Tantra USA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269292824000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra: The Art of Conscious Loving weekend seminar in Santa Cruz!  March 26-28.</name><id>12960540</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-25200000</utc_offset><time>1269654300000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tantrausa/events/12960540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/1/global_4199313.jpeg</photo_url></item>