<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>intersection of Everett Street</address_2><address_1>1175 Soldiers Field Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.364853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artesani Playground in Herter Park DCR (formerly MDC)</name><city>Brighton</city><id>738332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135521</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This walk is for a great cause.  I work for the Samaritans.  The Samaritans 5K Run/Walk is our annual fundraiser to benefit the work of Samaritans, a non-profit organization dedicated to reducing the incidence of suicide. Last year, more than 1,500 participants attended the event, and together raised more than $200,000 for Samaritans' life-saving services. Please note you do not have to register or pay the $20/25 fee (unless you want to of course and it benefits a great cause!)  You can just show up anytime before 10am (when the walk starts)  Additionally, we are also always looking for volunteers to help out the day of the event (if interested you can contact me through meet up).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortuantley, I have to work the event so I can't actually walk the 5k but hope to see you there.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.samaritansofboston.org/index.php/5k.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.samaritans...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:  &lt;br /&gt;Join Samaritans for the eleventh annual &amp;quot;Run for Someone Else's Life&amp;quot; Run/Walk along the Charles, and help us reduce the incidence of suicide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Saturday, October 2, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration: 8:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Race: 10:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;Awards: 11:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be festivities to follow, including live music, games, refreshments, a kid's race and our annual raffle. Win Green Monster Seats, an autographed Patriots' jersey or an autographed Celtic's basketball. Visit our online ticket counter!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Artesani Park, 1234 Soldiers Field Rd Road in Brighton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286030732000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284899193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Samaritans benefit walk in Brighton</name><id>14820076</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286026200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/14820076/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/1/global_3375441.jpeg</photo_url></item>