<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;FREE 45-minute live streaming video webinar with Kain Sanderson and Jenna Wayne, experts in personal and spiritual development, universal energy laws, energy psychology and ancient Eastern wisdom teachings.  Kain and Jenna have traveled to over 21 countries studying the principles of Eastern philosophy and seeking the universal truths of life and now they wish to share their knowledge with you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;How to Choose the Right Meditation for You&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Explore the differences in meditation and discover why you need to know which type is right for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;How to Connect to Your Body's Power&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Why your material and spiritual development depends on connecting to your physical body to access higher levels of consciousness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;How to Discover Who You Really Are&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;What is energy anatomy and spiritual anatomy and what are some examples of how this wisdom can help you achieve more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join this live webcast event- On Tues, Sept 23, 2008 at 6:15 pm &lt;br /&gt;1. Click on this link: &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ustream.tv/channel/energize-your-life" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ustream.tv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Enter the passcode: lifeisgood&lt;br /&gt;3. (if required) download the adobe flash 9 player&lt;br /&gt;4. Your logged in! You can use the chat feature on right side of screen to share your experience.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Contact Melissa Gurry, 860-205-8780 or Tricia Kennedy, 917-836-9575 if you need any assistance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;KAIN SANDERSON&lt;/b&gt; - Kain Sanderson is a senior certified energy management, meditation, martial arts and spiritual wisdom instructor and coach-mentor. He is dedicated to helping individuals grow and fulfill their purpose in life through spiritual development and service.  He has studied internal and external martial arts with international master expert, Del Pe and Yang Style Tai Chi with Dr. Yang Jwing-Ming.  He teaches and has helped lead retreats around the world to help people discover their real nature and the world of energy to achieve peak performance and improve their lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT JENNA WAYNE&lt;/b&gt; - Jenna Wayne is a senior certified spiritual mentor, instructor, intuitive consultant, poet and artist trained by world-renowned master of human energy science, spiritual development and martial arts, Del Pe.  After an education at Brown and Harvard Universities and a decade-long business career with top corporations, a search for life's universal truths led her to 21 countries seeking wisdom.  She now helps high-achievement professionals, thought leaders and creative people apply Eastern Wisdom to live healthier, be happier, work smarter and grow faster with achievable enlightenment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>webinar link:  http://www.ustream.tv/channel/energize-your-life</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mel Gurry</member_name><member_id>8139289</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226451378000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmeditation</urlname><id>1294140</id><group_lat>41.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7399978638</group_lon><name>Hartford Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223043742000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ENERGIZE YOUR LIFE! </name><id>8887947</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224631800000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmeditation/events/8887947/</event_url></item>