<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 Eliot St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.256287</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Broadmoor Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Natick</city><id>669274</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340240</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Broadmoor&lt;br /&gt;General Info&lt;br /&gt;News &amp;amp; Special Events&lt;br /&gt;Program Catalog&lt;br /&gt;e-News Sign-up&lt;br /&gt;Summer Camp&lt;br /&gt;School &amp;amp; Group Programs&lt;br /&gt;Adult Group Programs&lt;br /&gt;Facility Rentals&lt;br /&gt;Green Building Features&lt;br /&gt;Jobs &amp;amp; Volunteering&lt;br /&gt;Printable Directions&lt;br /&gt;Maps&lt;br /&gt;Contact Us&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Broadmoor Wildlife Sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Join us for Travel &amp;amp; Taste: Kenya, Phoenix Islands and more!&lt;br /&gt;Broadmoor’s nine miles of walking trails guide you through a variety of field, woodland, and wetland habitats. A quarter-mile, universally accessible trail and boardwalk along the bank of Indian Brook and over the marsh offers great opportunities for birdwatching, photography, and sketching. To enjoy this site in the winter, bring your snowshoes or cross-country skis. Stroll along the edge of Indian Brook, which flows into the Charles River at the sanctuary, and look for wood ducks and signs of beavers and otters from the 110-foot-long bridge. Take a tape-recorded tour of the sanctuary’s nature center, which is complete with solar heating and composting toilets, to learn about our “green” architecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;280 Eliot Street&lt;br /&gt;Natick, MA 01760&lt;br /&gt;508-655-2296&lt;br /&gt;broadmoor@massaudubon.org&lt;br /&gt;This sanctuary has the following universally accessible facilities: Nature Center, Restrooms, All Persons Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center/Trail Hours:&lt;br /&gt;Nature Center: Tuesday through Friday, 9 am to 5 pm, Saturday, Sunday, and Monday holidays, 10 am to 5 pm&lt;br /&gt;Trails: Open Tuesday through Sunday, and Monday holidays, dawn to dusk.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For Your Safety&lt;br /&gt;Do not feed any animals&lt;br /&gt;Stay on trails to avoid ticks and poison ivy&lt;br /&gt;Do not smoke anywhere on the sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;Do not pick or collect plants or crops without permission&lt;br /&gt;Avoid Conflicts with Wildlife&lt;br /&gt;Do not bring pets, leashed or unleashed, on to the site&lt;br /&gt;Picnic only in designated areas&lt;br /&gt;Do not bring motorized vehicles or bicycles onto the site&lt;br /&gt;Hunting, fishing, or trapping are not permitted&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;$5 for nonmember adults; $4 for nonmember children (2-12) and seniors (65 and over)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: Take the Mass. Turnpike (Rt I-90) west to exit 16 (West Newton/Wellesley). Follow Rt 16 west for 7 miles to South Natick Center. The sanctuary is 1.8 miles ahead on the left. From the east: Take Rt 9 west to Rt 16 in Wellesley. Follow Rt 16 west for about 5 miles; the sanctuary is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the west: Take Rt I-495 to Rt 9. Follow Rt 9 east to Rt 27 in Natick. Follow Rt 27 south for 4 miles to Sherborn. Turn left onto Rt 16 east and follow for 1.6 miles; the sanctuary is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north and south: Take Rt I-95 to Rt 16 (exit 22). Follow Rt 16 west for 7 miles; the sanctuary is on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acres:&lt;br /&gt;6&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265127062000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264427543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BROADMOOR WILDLIFE SANCTUARY NATICK MA</name><id>12415895</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264953600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/12415895/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>