<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Eastern Point Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.599048</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-283-0800</phone><name>Beauport  (Sleeper-McCann House)</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>950277</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.655506</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/5/7/event_39460791.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Enjoy touring 2 unique historic properties, and exploring galleries in the oldest art colony in the US. We'll meet at the Beauport Museum at 9:45 am, then go on a 1 hour guided tour of this national landmark with fascinating and spectacular interior design, and views of Gloucester harbor. (Tour is $10.) (www.historicnewengland.org/historic-properties/homes/Beauport) Then we'll drive 1.4 miles to Rocky Neck; a quaint historic summer community for artists, which includes many art galleries. (rockyneckartcolony.org). We'll explore some of the galleries, and then have lunch at the Madfish Grille, a Rocky Neck restaurant, which has views of Gloucester Harbor. (madfishgrille.com.) By 2:30pm, we'll drive about 15 min to Hammond Castle for a self-guided tour. (hammondcastle.org.) Admission is $10; last visitors admitted at 3:30pm. This event is limited to 12 people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logistics for event:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please allow extra time to arrive at Beauport for the tour. The museum can accommodate us all on one tour.
 &lt;br /&gt;Below are directions from the museum's website:
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.historicnewengland.org/historic-properties/homes/Beauport"&gt;www.historicnewengland.org/historic-properties/homes/Beauport&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route I-95/128 north to the end. At second set of lights after the second rotary, take East Main Street for approximately eight minutes, to the stone pillars at the entrance to&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Point Boulevard. Proceed through the pillars and follow Eastern Point Boulevard .5&amp;nbsp;mile to Beauport.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;(Please note: the stone pillars have a sign which suggests that the road is for members or residents only, and there may be a security guard stationed there. Proceed past this onto&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Point Blvd, to the museum.)
 &lt;br /&gt;The Beauport parking lot is on the left, across the street from the house.
 &lt;br /&gt;After completing the tour, we can spend some time walking on the grounds, which are very scenic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rocky Neck Art Colony is located 1.4 miles away on Rocky Neck Ave.
 &lt;br /&gt;Please park in the public lot located on the right, immediately after turning onto Rocky Neck Ave, or on the street in front of the lot. Parking is very restricted in the colony beyond this area. We will meet at the large Rocky Neck sign near edge of the parking lot before walking up to the galleries. There are Rocky Neck maps and brochures available near the sign. Our lunch reservation at the Madfish Grille is at 12:30pm, so we will have time to visit galleries before and after that. The restaurant is located within the art colony, so we will not need to&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;move our cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hammond Castle is located at 80 Hesperus Avenue, which is about 15 min away from Rocky Neck. When we arrive there, we will meet at the stairs leading down from the parking lot to the&amp;nbsp;museum grounds.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at the Beauport Museum office, where the tour will begin. I'll have a meetup sign with me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>5708116</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1311251802000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310350336000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Beauport Museum, Rocky Neck Art Colony, and Hammond Castle in Gloucester</name><id>25277121</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310823900000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/25277121/</event_url></item>