<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>561 Windsor St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.375324</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 623-0804</phone><name>Taza Chocolate</name><city>Somerville</city><id>257572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.092780</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone!&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday, December 6th the Taza Chocolate factory is having an open house.  If you like chocolate, this chocolate is really amazing and not for the weak.  &lt;br /&gt;They recommend large groups to arrive early - so the reason for setting this at 10:00am.  Please see below for details.&lt;br /&gt;From there, we can go to around the corner to Spice and Rice for lunch.  &lt;br /&gt;P.S. I’m going to set up Spice and Rice as its own meet up.&lt;br /&gt; Hope you can make it to both!&lt;br /&gt;__________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't Miss this Year's Last Opportunity to Visit the Taza Factory!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 6th, from 10am to 6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Taza Chocolate, we're proud of our certified organic, bean to bar chocolate products.  We make every one of them by hand in our small factory in Somerville, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've ever wanted to see how our chocolate is made, now's your chance!  On Saturday, December 6th, from 10 AM to 6 PM, we're opening our doors to the public for chocolate tastings and tours of the factory. Come check out our candy-apple red Barth Sirocco roaster, learn what a winnowing machine does, and examine the hand-dressed grooves in our vintage Mexican Molino.  And of course, you'll get to taste all of our products side-by-side, and quaff hot chocolate made from our Mexicano Vanilla discs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our factory is small and we anticipate a high turnout.  Because we can only accommodate a set number of people per tour, we recommend that you come early or late in the day if you mind waiting. Families are encouraged to come early, as we will be busiest from 12 pm to 4 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those visiting the factory for our tour can purchase product at the Taza Chocolate Gift Shop. If you can't make it out on Saturday, December 6th, you can always visit our website for information, a virtual tour, and purchases  www.tazachocolate.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taza Chocolate is a bean-to-bar chocolate maker located at 561 Windsor St. in Somerville. Check our website for details at www.tazachocolate.com or call 617-623-0804.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alex &amp;amp; Larry&lt;br /&gt;Taza Chocolate&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228749034000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227140380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taza Chocolate factory tour - Somerville</name><id>9196113</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228575600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/9196113/</event_url></item>