<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer - John (LAG) Lagasse  (978) 973-5022 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #634e91 ; font-size : x-large"&gt;WHEN YOU SELECT YES AND CLICK RSVP ANOTHER PAGE APPEARS WITH THE QUESTIONS YOU ARE "REQUIRED" TO ANSWER.  PLEASE TAKE THE TIME AND ANSWER THEM. AND READ THE RED TEXT BELOW :)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;read the entire event listing&lt;/span&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;answer all of the questions&lt;/span&gt; that are part of the RSVP process. If you RSVP from a mobile device you may not see them - visit the site using a computer so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of the trip; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you may put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared to respond to an emergency situation or being able to send a night in the woods if you have to. Bring your own stuff and know how to use it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be hiking two 4000 footers - Mt Lafayette (5260' #7) and Mt Lincoln (5089' #8). We will start our hike at the Lafayette Place trailhead on Rte 93.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;slowest hiker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted.&lt;/strong&gt; All participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;slower than moderate paced hike,&lt;/strong&gt; we will take &lt;strong&gt;Old Bridle Path to Greenleaf, to Fraconia Ridge, to Falling Water trail&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; We will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 8.9 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,900 feet&lt;/strong&gt; - for perspective the top floor of the Empire State Building is about 1,250 feet. It should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 6 hours 45 minutes to complete&lt;/strong&gt; this trip though I'm scheduling about &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8 hours and 30 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is considered &lt;strong&gt;Intermediate&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/photos/2030971/"&gt;Click here for information about our trip ratings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did all of my research for this trip using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (e.g. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. The higher we climb the colder, windier, and wetter it will be - we will need to be prepared. Remember, on&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;average it gets 3-4 degrees (Fahrenheit) colder for every 1,000 feet of elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt; rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or out on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the debris out of your boots. &lt;em&gt;I doubt with the early spring we will need any kind of traction but be prepared to bring microspikes, and I will update as we get closer to the date.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and conducts heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket (e.g. fleece). Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants (e.g. gore-tex). Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof over-mittens (e.g. gore-tex).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - it's time to switch from a hydration pack (e.g. camalbak) because the hose tends to freeze. Use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead (e.g. nalgene).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;: You should always be prepared to spend a night in the woods if you have to. Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in colder temperatures). Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen is important since we will be traveling on exposed trails. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The meeting spot is at the Lafayette Place parking Area. Take Rte 93 past "The Basin" parking area, next parking area is Lafayette Place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Its approximately 142 miles from Boston and 2 hours and 24 minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Either a Silver Toyota Matrix or Black Mazda MPV  Contact me at (978) 973-5022 if you are late or can't make it.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John (LAG) Lagasse</member_name><member_id>2667639</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340108092000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337215090000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH48-Lafayette and Lincoln (Intermediate)</name><id>65118752</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339850700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/65118752/</event_url></item>