<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Harbor </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.612221</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Captain Bill &amp; Sons Whale Watch Glouster Mass</name><city>Glouster</city><id>7698682</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.659637</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Whales and dolphins have the highest vibration, and are the most intelligent spiritual of all creatures on the earth...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us for a day trip to learn about and see whales on the North Shore at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Whale Aventures with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capt Bill &amp;amp; Sons&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;24 Harbor Loop&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glouster, Mass 01830&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone must arrive at the place by 1:00 pm- Bring a light jacket, and cameras are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is $30.00 per person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this rate, reservations need to be made with a credit card by Sun Sept 2nd by calling:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1-800-339-4253&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1-978-283-6995&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and stating that you are with the &lt;strong&gt;"Meetup Group reservation on Sept 15th"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trip will be 4 hours long, and we will be going to dinner to Victoria Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;in Salem following the Whale Watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If people want to make a longer day of it, Salem is about 1/2 hour from Glouster, and if you are an early bird, you can go for shopping and lunch in Salem prior to the Whale Watch, and even drive up the coast for the scenic drive to Glouster, which is about 40 mins- 30 mins up 128 N. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Whale Watch Adventures&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a well established, family owned and operated &lt;strong&gt;Boston whale watch&lt;/strong&gt; adventure company in Gloucester, Massachusetts, now in our 50th season of Cape Ann boating excursions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Join Us For An Experience You Will Never Forget!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Sail our popular three to four hour tour to view the world’s largest mammals surfacing, feeding, and breaching in the important feeding areas of Stellwagen Bank and Jeffreys Ledge. In season, these waters, a National Marine Sanctuary, provide some of the BEST WHALE WATCHING opportunities in the world. Our unique and awe-inspiring whale watching tours offer many great photo opportunities!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss the Whale Center of New England’s free exhibit, where you can get up close and personal to an actual humpback whale skeleton. To find out more about this exhibit and other attractions at our unique location on Historic Harbor Loop&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out Captain Bill's site at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.captbillandsons.com/"&gt;http://www.captbillandsons.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we set sail, you actually become a part of the research team. Our naturalists, from The Whale Center of New England, give careful instructions in the "spotting techniques" for particular species. You will also learn about whale behavior, biology, and social structure from the naturalists. As a result, you will be able to share your knowledge to help save the habitat of these intelligent, amazing creatures and marvel at their enormous size and awesome power&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are no other whale watching tours on the Massachusetts coast quite like ours!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://captbillandsons.com/articles.html" style="color : #4a6063"&gt;Whale Watching Tours&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Naturalists on board the Miss Cape Ann make the difference. Our &lt;a href="http://captbillandsons.com/whale-watching-tours-in-ma.html"&gt;whale watching tours in Gloucester&lt;/a&gt; take place on a custom designed whale watching boat that provides optimal &lt;a href="http://captbillandsons.com/whale-watching-cruises.html"&gt;whale watching&lt;/a&gt;, cruises departing twice daily, and more frequently on peak days. Located northeast of Boston Harbor &lt;a href="http://captbillandsons.com/boston-harbor-cruises.html"&gt;cruises&lt;/a&gt; are complete with the outstanding educational resources provided by researchers from The Whale Center of New England. That means every &lt;a href="http://captbillandsons.com/whale-watching-cruise.html"&gt;whale watching cruise&lt;/a&gt; with us, already inspiring and rich with the marine life sightings in the Stellwagen Bank National Marine Sanctuary or Jeffreys Ledge, is a rare opportunity to learn to latest news and more about whales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, nothing brings home the majesty of these marine mammals like viewing them in person, experiencing the sounds and sights here northeast of Boston. &lt;a href="http://captbillandsons.com/boston-whale-watching-tours.html"&gt;Whale watching tours&lt;/a&gt; with Capt. Bill and Sons are the real thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.captbillandsons.com/images_intro/horiz_spacer_intro.gif" width="744" height="11" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347840226000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339609595000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whale Watch &amp; Dinner on the North Shore</name><id>69015572</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347728400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/69015572/</event_url></item>