<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Note:   The hall seats 100. WRNEC already has over 100 reservations for The RAW-luck buffet and lecture. Only 3 of the 17 people who RSVPd from this site followed the instructions below by calling or emailing Betsy. Please call Betsy at 781-899-6664 or email her at Betsy@rawnewenglandcommunity.com to confirm your reservation. There are a number of no shows. We don't want to turn anyone away. Standing room is available. It's recommended that you arrive at 5:30 at the latest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                   GREENS CAN SAVE YOUR LIFE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Victoria Boutenko, award-winning author of several best-selling books on raw and living foods and popular speaker from Ashland, Oregon, will present her inspiring new lecture &amp;quot;GREENS CAN SAVE YOUR LIFE&amp;quot; at the next Waltham Raw New England Community dinner, on Tuesday, December 11, from 7 to 9 PM following the 5:30 PM potluck dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Victoria Boutenko's talk will be packed with revolutionary information.  &lt;br /&gt;The latest scientific research on the raw food diet; &lt;br /&gt;The signs of malnourishment and how to avoid it; &lt;br /&gt;Staying on a raw diet in the midst of temptations; &lt;br /&gt;Helping children to eat healthfully; &lt;br /&gt;Common mistakes that occur on a raw food diet; &lt;br /&gt;Green smoothies - an easy way to enjoy greens and much more! &lt;br /&gt;Come and Be Motivated To Change Your Life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All those attending are requested to bring a raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal, non-honey based ready- to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people.  Please bring serving utensils labeled with your name and a typed or neatly written recipe to display next to your dish.  For recipe ideas, go to &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawnewengl...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is $10 per person, $5 for members.   Price includes a green smoothie and handouts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For questions and reservations, contact Betsy Bragg by email at betsy@rawnewenglandcommunity.com or call 781-899-6664 or 617-835-2913. &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to give your postal address, phone number &amp;amp; email. All are invited to our buffet and lecture!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278886593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195406519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greens can Save Your Life</name><id>6764426</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197412200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/6764426/</event_url></item>