<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>500 Walk Hill St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02126</zip><lat>42.288258</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Nature Center</name><city>Mattapan</city><id>851272</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101319</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Boston Nature Center and Wildlife Sanctuary &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snowshoeing is an easy and fun way to get around and see signs of winterlife.  Every Saturday and Sunday you can borrow our snowshoes anytime from 11 am to 3 pm for a walk around our center. Or enjoy a guided tour from 12 to1  pm.  we can meet at 11 am and walk on ourown and  then join the guided walk at 12 pm.  There is parking available in a lot on the premises&lt;br /&gt;This urban sanctuary, located on the grounds of the former Boston State Hospital, offers public programs year-round. Through its Boston Schools Initiative, the Boston Nature Center provides environmental education programs to Boston elementary schools weekly. Two miles of wheelchair accessible trails and boardwalks traverse meadows and wetlands where wildlife abounds, including coyotes, pheasants, and many species of migratory birds. The sanctuary’s George Robert White Environmental Conservation Center is one of the “greenest” buildings in Boston, teaching environmentally sustainable design by example. The site also includes the Clark-Cooper Community Gardens, Boston’s oldest and largest, providing food and a green oasis for 260 local fami &lt;br /&gt; Learn more about the Boston Nature Center&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;500 Walk Hill Street&lt;br /&gt;Mattapan, MA 02126&lt;br /&gt;ions:&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Boston Nature Center is located on the grounds of the old Boston State Hospital, bounded by Morton Street (Route 203), American Legion Highway, Walk Hill Street, and Harvard Street. Many road maps and bus route maps still identify it as &amp;quot;Boston State Hospital&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;State Hospital.&amp;quot; There is ongoing construction around our borders. Please drive or walk caref&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233501385000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231802482000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chestnut Hill Meetup-Boston Nature Center Snowshoeing</name><id>9508695</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232294400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/9508695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/a/global_6852778.jpeg</photo_url></item>