<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Tremont St &amp; Park St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>710152</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061960</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I thought it would be fun to meet for a picnic at the Parkman Bandstand in Boston Commons and watch the production of Shakespear's &amp;quot;The Commedy of Errors.&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Comedy of Errors is one of William Shakespeare's earliest plays.  It is his shortest and one of his most farcical, with a major part of the humour coming from slapstick and mistaken identity, in addition to puns and wordplay. The Comedy of Errors tells the story of two sets of identical twins that were accidentally separated at birth. Antipholus of Syracuse and his servant, Dromio of Syracuse, arrive in Ephesus, which turns out to be the home of their twin brothers, Antipholus of Ephesus and his servant, Dromio of Ephesus. When the Syracusans encounter the friends and families of their twins, a series of wild mishaps based on mistaken identities lead to wrongful beatings, a near-incestuous seduction, the arrest of Antipholus of Ephesus, and accusations of infidelity, theft, madness, and demonic possession.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be in front of the Parkman Bandstand at 6:00.  We can meet there and then find a place to picnic and see the production.  Bring blankets, chairs, umbrella (in case of rain), snacks and drinks (I don't think alcohol is allowed at the Commons).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in front of Parkman Bandstand.  See photo of the bandstand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250296107000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248151423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shakespear on the Common</name><id>10921751</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249768800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/10921751/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/4/b/global_4772123.jpeg</photo_url></item>