<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Golden Hill Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.773630</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Kim and Kate's House</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>507763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053955</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Kim and her partner Kate will host a game night at their house at 105 Golden Hill Avenue in Haverhill, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can have 3 game rooms or find a way to pile everyone into one room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a number of games to choose from, and we can split into 2-3 different game rooms. Some of the games include: Poker (where Kate has volunteered to be the dealer for the evening), Trivial Pursuit, Monopoly, Backgammon, Scrabble, Simpsons Pictionary, Taboo, Hilarium and Amazing Race DVD game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also feel free to bring a game of your own that you would really love to play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The neighborhood is quiet residential, and parking will be available in the driveway, on the street in front of the house, and on Bowdoin Drive (a dead-end street to left just before you get to the house). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only drawback to Haverhill is the lack of street signs - directions will be sent closer to the event along with a phone number to call if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Allergy Alert: We do have one cat, who we will probably keep in the upstairs bedroom. FYI, Kim has an allergy to cats, and she doesn't bother her.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204774833000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202584006000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Afternoon in Haverhill</name><id>7297997</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204480800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/7297997/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/8/9/global_3094489.jpeg</photo_url></item>