<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For this meting, Kevin has volunteered to do a book review on the title "
&lt;strong&gt;If It's Raining in Brazil... Buy Starbucks&lt;/strong&gt;" by Peter Navarro... a look at the effect of macroeconomics on individual stocks and the markets in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to membership replies, we'll also take a look at some basic&amp;nbsp;technical indicators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I welcome&amp;nbsp;your ideas and thoughts regarding subjects and/or activities&amp;nbsp;for&amp;nbsp;future meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone else&amp;nbsp;has a book they'd care to recommend, or provide a review on for the group, please let me know via email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, bringing questions regarding a favorite stock from your own watchlists (or perhaps even a trade from the past) for a group critique is very much encouraged.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this meeting is after-hours, we are free to use the Library's parking lot. Our meeting room is downstairs and just to the right of the staircase (the Peace Dale Room). Newcomers are certainly welcome, so if you know of others who might be interested in joining us, please refer them to this site or just bring them along to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to see you all there, and look forward to a &amp;#65279;&amp;#65279;lively and engaging discussion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trade Green, Ray&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy working the laptop &amp; projector set up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Dreczko</member_name><member_id>4521820</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316705027000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>IBD Enthusiasts and Traders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ibd-739</urlname><id>559772</id><group_lat>41.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum Monthly Meetup</name><id>zjhdnypmbcc</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316642400000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ibd-739/events/31936002/</event_url></item>