<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Chime in&amp;quot; from 9 - 10 pm on the phone ...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- with your questions&lt;br /&gt;- to get support and suggestions&lt;br /&gt;- to share your LOA experiences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; and the telephone # to join us on call will be emailed to you&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kathryn Deputat, BostonLOA member and Clarity Coach&lt;/b&gt;, will be co-facilitating the call.&lt;br /&gt;She will share some of her WOW LOA manifestations such as meeting her beloved life partner &amp;amp; expanding her life and work to Ireland , where she will live for most of the next year.  Come and find out how she did it!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and yes, ask Kathryn how she manifested the perfect woman &amp;quot;on a dime&amp;quot; to TLC her home while she's away ... another part of the LOA story!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathryn welcomes any and all questions about her experience/process--especially if they'll move you closer to your heart's desires too. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Kathryn Deputat:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathryn is a writer, coach, photographer and clarity consultant who has been reuniting people with their inspiration, passion, and authentic expressions?in their lives and/or in their writing for more than 15 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A distinguished alumna of Wellesley College and a member of Phi Beta Kappa, Kathryn is founding owner of Claritywork.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She draws on highly attuned listening and intuitive gifts, and her techniques, rooted &lt;br /&gt;in the Goldberg writing method, combine her interest and training in psychology, Zen &lt;br /&gt;Buddhism, metaphysics, Emotional-Kinesthetic Psychotherapy, and vocal and visual&lt;br /&gt;improvisation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathryn's poetry. photos and articles have appeared in various publications, and she publishes&lt;br /&gt;regularly on www.LovesFreeway.com....&lt;i&gt;Where love has its way&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213405657000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Open Forum - Bring your questions, receive suggestions, share your LOA experiences, learn from each other, get to know each other</why><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212627545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BostonLOA Masterminding TELE- Meetup</name><id>8081196</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213232400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/8081196/</event_url></item>