<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2> Pickering Wharf</address_2><address_1> 76 Wharf Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.520065</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 744 8485</phone><name>Finz Restaurant</name><city>Salem</city><id>378258</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887909</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Call or text Tonya at (617) 445-7549 if it is after the RSVP deadline and you want to join in on the FUN!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lettie is inviting us to Salem on the North Shore for a Halloween Lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: I think it will be fun to go to Salem during Halloween Week.  This weekend We can the daytime happenings and get to see crazy  costumes without getting too overwhelmed by the night time activities. We can take a spooky tour, enter a &amp;quot;haunted&amp;quot; place or two, visit the Witches Museum IF you are willing to take the  line and House of seven Gables, to many places for me to decide so I'll leave it all up to you to vote once at the restaurant    Here you can check up places to visit:  &lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.com/attractions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hauntedhap...&lt;/a&gt;   OR if people want to stay for the witchy stuff, up to you...   Costume dress-up TOTALLY up to you... &lt;br /&gt;Finz is a GREAT Restaurant on Pickering Wharf, with VERY good food and they have the most famous Martinis. &lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  Since it is Halloween Week I'll ONLY accept RSVP's until Oct. 21 and close the RSVP's So PLEASE be 100% sure at this time, I know it is hard but it is Halloween in Salem and the restaurant needs the parties exact number for the reservation, sorry, I apologize for the inconvenience. &lt;br /&gt;At FINZ we are all about great food&lt;br /&gt;Innovative and inspired menus, a raw bar serving fresh seasonal oysters, our carefully chosen wine list all lead to an extraordinary dining experience. The menu at FINZ emphasizes seasonal, fresh seafood creative preparations. Our raw bar serves the freshest local oysters, clams and shrimp and is available until closing. &lt;br /&gt;Some of our most popular menu selections include our Buffalo Calamari, Stoli-Wasabi Oysters and our Lobster Ravioli tossed in a sherry cream sauce served with lobster meat and asparagus tips.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, for those who are feeling a little more land-based, FINZ offers an incredible Filet Mignon as well as specials such as duck, pasta dishes and the best seasonal meats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And what would oysters be without a great Sancerre from France, try our Guy Saget or a selection from our sparkling wine category with choices from France, Spain, Italy and of course here in America. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch menu available here:   &lt;a href="http://www.finzrestaurant.com/menus/salem-lunch.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.finzrestau...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Libations  menu available here:  &lt;a href="http://www.finzrestaurant.com/menus/salem-libations.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.finzrestau...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Train accessible also from North Station you can Take Rockport OR Newburyport trains they both stop in Salem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/uploadedFiles/Documents/Schedules_and_Maps/Commuter_Rail/newburyport_web.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bus service: Bus Route 450; Bus Route 455/459; Salem Depot - Haymarket or Downtown Crossing Via Loring Ave., Central Sq., Lynn &amp;amp; Western Ave. Bus Route 451; Bus Route 458/468; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING INTO SALEM IS NOT RECOMMENDED&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU MUST DRIVE, PARK AT A COMMUTER STATION BEFORE OR AFTER THE SALEM STOP&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions to the Restaurant:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from Boston (30 min.): Take I-93 North to I-95 North (exit 37-A) to Route 128 North. From Route 128 take Route 114 East Salem/Marblehead (exit 25A) into Salem. Follow the signs to Route 114 East past the Post Office (crossing Washington Street) and follow the signs for the waterfront. You will now be on Derby Street. &lt;br /&gt;The first right turn from Derby Street is Congress Street. Pickering Wharf will be on your left. &lt;br /&gt;The second right from Derby Street is Wharf Street. FINZ is at 76 Wharf Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from North Rockport/Gloucester: Take Route 128 South. From Route 128 take Route 114 East Marblehead (exit 25A) into Salem. Remain on Route 114 to North Street (at the rotary) and turn right onto North Street. One block later North Street becomes Summer Street. One block further turn left on Norman Street. Cross Washington Street (past the Post Office) and Norman Street become  New Derby Street and then Derby Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WILL MOST LIKELY BE FULL&lt;br /&gt;Parking: There is a new parking garage on the corner of Congress Street and Derby Street. There is another parking lot further down Congress Street on the right. And there is street parking on Wharf Street and all the surrounding streets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;If your name ap&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198857038000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190306799000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPOOKY HALLOWEEN LUNCH IN SALEM</name><id>6396464</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193585400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6396464/</event_url></item>