<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Market Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.812378</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-462-7336</phone><name>Firehouse Center for the Arts</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>287736</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.874626</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/7/b/6/event_220874262.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;ART WALK is a self-paced walking tour. Gallleries and studios remain open late. And, as you stroll them, they usually serve refreshments / appetizers of some kind! Touring Newburyport's galleries and artist's studios is a great opportunity to see, learn about, and maybe shop? for ART you like......&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*** PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; This is a walking tour. And, we will be doing a lot of it. If you join us, please be prepared. RAIN WILL NOT CANCEL this event - unless we have a very bad storm. Parking can be tight - so plan accordingly. I will try to have several maps - more to follow on that. AFTER the Art Walk: If the weather is good, we can take a stroll at Water Front Park.. and maybe head somewhere later on depending&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COST:  Art Walk is  Free! &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;" As the snow begins the melt and the song of a robin's sweet chirp fills our soul, the town of Newburyport awakens to a new year filled with more artistic inspiration and countless creations. Artists' pallettes change from winter to spring as does everything...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be new artists, painting demonstrations, reception times and much more. This year is going to move the mind to think about art in new and interesting ways through composition, color and community! " (website)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**** My contact # is: 508.410.4679  after 2:00 PM  &lt;br /&gt;

 This is a combined event with several other meetup groups&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will all gather at bench to the left of the building- I will wear a meetup pin &amp; also have a sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Johannah W</member_name><member_id>60834042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367156040000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364941863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ART WALK NEWBURYPORT- 1st Of The Season!</name><id>112338182</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366484400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/112338182/</event_url></item>