<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>237 Quincy Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02269</zip><lat>42.241221</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-773-9838</phone><name>China Pearl</name><city>Quincy</city><id>883920</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.990684</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join fellow Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a fun Sunday gathering for some DIM SUM at China Pearl in Quincy. DIM SUM consists of a variety of dumplings, steamed dishes and other goodies. The China Pearl is located in the Kam Man Mall. See reviews on yelp by clicking on the following link: &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/china-pearl-quincy"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/china-pearl-quincy&lt;/a&gt;  Reviews for China Pearl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The price range is approximately $11-$20 per person, including tax and tip, depending how much we all order to share.  (We paid $13pp last time.)  This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy. This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event. This restaurant does not take reservations - So all that are attending &lt;strong&gt;must be prompt for us to be seated&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dim Sum @ China Pearl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, September 23rd, 2012 @ 11:30am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;237 Quincy Ave&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quincy, MA 02169&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;617-773-9838 &lt;a href="http://www.chinapearlrestaurant.com/"&gt;http://www.chinapearlrestaurant.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Inside the lobby. We will then wait to be seated together as a Group. If you arrive after we are seated the reservation is under "Alison."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s):&lt;/em&gt; Alison&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Min of 4 people 48 hours in advance. Max of 12 people or may need to add another table. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fees&lt;/em&gt;: Annual Members - FREE, Group Members and guests- $2;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 10PM on Saturday, September 22nd. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to No after this time will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/em&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over six years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: TBD - Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather").&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Will be posted the week before the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet just inside the front door near the host station.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349030423000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347131695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join us for an early Fall Dim Sum at the China Pearl!</name><id>81480732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348414200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/81480732/</event_url></item>