<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Thanks to all who attended a great October meetup!  The group discussion format worked well and I think we all were given a lot of things to think about. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special thanks to Amy Graver of Elements for hosting and for so graciously agreeing to host again next month.  And also thanks to Liz for making the group logo - check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;November's Meetup will again be at the offices of Elements LLC (www.elementsdesign.com).   Amy Graver will lead a group discussion on Self Promotion. The group is encouraged to bring samples of past self-promotion pieces - those that worked,  those in the works, and for those who are brave enough, those that failed miserably! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to requests we will start later - mingling, food, drinks from 6-6:45, group discussion from 6:45-7:30, post-mingling from 7:30-8:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pizza will be served and drinks (soda and wine/beer) provided.   A $10 donation ($5 for students) is suggested for helping offset the costs of having the group ($20/month) plus the food. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, November 1&lt;br /&gt;6.00pm - 8.00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elements LLC&lt;br /&gt;King's Block&lt;br /&gt;20 Grand Avenue&lt;br /&gt;New Haven, CT 06513&lt;br /&gt;(Corner of Grand and Front along Quinnipiac River)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is parking on-site accessible from Front Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be there and I hope that you can all make it too!  Please RSVP so we can know how much food/drink to have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ps - Please use the message board to post resources you have found helpful - organizations to join, books, journals, etc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1162595057000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1160001335000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater New Haven Design November Meetup</name><id>5175053</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1162422000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/5175053/</event_url></item>