<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>372 Chandler Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.270000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nancy Changs</name><city>Worcester</city><id>133666</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.849998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Visit NANCY CHANG and experience the finest &lt;br /&gt;authentic, Chinese food in Central Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;Take a culinary trip through the Orient with some &lt;br /&gt;of our Thai, Malaysian and Polynesian specialties. Discover an eating philosophy that combines &lt;br /&gt;freshness and flavor with low fat, healthy cuisine. &lt;br /&gt;And, there's absolutely no MSG. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NANCY CHANG brings East and West together in &lt;br /&gt;a selection of a variety of healthy dishes. Located &lt;br /&gt;in Worcester's west side, NANCY CHANG is the &lt;br /&gt;perfect setting for relaxed dining any day of the &lt;br /&gt;week. NANCY CHANG is easily accessible to the &lt;br /&gt;handicapped and elderly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope that you, our valued customers, have also recognized our commitment to excellence. We continue to work with dieticians, health professors and doctors. For example, we created Dr. Yvonne Chen's Herbal Energy Soup with the assistance of the former professor of Health Sciences at Worcester State College, and we also formulated our own healthy cooking oil. These innovations serve as examples of our commitment to using only the freshest products and finest ingredients. We plan to continue our mission to produce the healthiest Asian cuisine available in Worcester County. It has been a privilege to serve you for the past fifteen years and we look forward to serving you in the future. We thank you for your continued patronage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have a large Vegetarian/Vegan listing and substitute veggie chicken, veggie shrimp or tofu into any of their entrees. I just ate their recently and it was absolutely delicious! Please come by and make this group grow! It's an open forum and we encourage any ideas or suggestions for topics etc.. Whether you just want to network and meet local vegans like yourself, share recipes, if you are looking for support in making or maintaining this change in your life, want to discuss challenges and success or if you just want to try some yummy food...you are most welcome! I attached a link for their online menu. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.nancychang.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nancychang...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165342230000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162753519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp December Meetup</name><id>5246097</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165168800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/5246097/</event_url></item>