<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 French Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01505</zip><lat>42.359173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 508-869-0314 </phone><name>Tower Hill Botanical Gardens</name><city>Boylston</city><id>718941</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.727748</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let's get together and check out the garden grounds. We'll meet in the at 10:30 am in the parking lot and make a plan. There is an 8.00 admission fee so please bring cash! At Tower Hill, you can stroll the many gardens and woodland trails to explore nature, take a contemplative break. There is a cafe on the grounds or we can pack a picnic. Let's wander around and maybe meet up for lunch together. We'll discuss details when we arrive...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is some info and thier web site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.towerhillbg.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.towerhillb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring sunblock, a hat, drink, lunch or snack, camera gear...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston:&lt;br /&gt;Take the Massachusetts Turnpike to Exit 11A for Route 495. Take Route 495 north to Exit 25B for Route 290 west. Follow toward Worcester. Take Exit 24, Church Street, Northborough/Boylston. Follow to Boylston 3 miles. Entrance to Tower Hill on right; dark red sign designates entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Worcester, take the exit for Route 290 east. Follow through the city to Exit 24, Church Street, Northborough/Boylston. Follow to Boylston 3 miles. Entrance to Tower Hill on right; dark red sign designates entrance.&lt;br /&gt;Garden Etiquette&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For your own enjoyment and safety, and to protect and preserve the plants, please follow these simple rules:&lt;br /&gt;? Stay on paths or lawns.&lt;br /&gt;? Dispose of trash properly. &lt;br /&gt;? Park in designated areas only.&lt;br /&gt;? Enjoy your picnic, but no alcohol, please. &lt;br /&gt;? Footwear and shirts must be worn at all times.&lt;br /&gt;? Leave all plants, flowers and wildlife undisturbed.&lt;br /&gt;? Leave pets at home. Assistance animals welcome!&lt;br /&gt;? Youths under 16 must be accompanied by an adult.&lt;br /&gt;? Commercial/wedding photography permitted by appointment.&lt;br /&gt;? Enjoy the tranquility; radios and musical instruments are not allowed.&lt;br /&gt;? No smoking in the buildings, or along trails through fields and woodland.&lt;br /&gt;? No climbing on rock walls or statuary, running, barbecuing or active sports (frisbee, ball playing, kite flying, biking etc.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a call into them to see about a group discount rate so please RSVP ASAP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks Donna&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182469703000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180101688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot: Tower Hill Botanic Garden</name><id>5817651</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182004200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/5817651/</event_url></item>