<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Plain Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02817</zip><lat>41.644005</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tillinghast Pond Management Area</name><city>West Greenwich</city><id>5145732</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.756378</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/c/e/event_85438062.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Winter is a great time to check out the Tillinghast Pond Management Area in West Greenwich. Way out there past Big John Leyden's Christmas Tree Farm, the air is a little colder and the snow (if we have any) a little brighter...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acquired by The Nature Conservancy in 2006, this 2000-acre preserve is permanently protected from development, and is open to the public for fishing, canoeing and hiking. The Providence Journal has called it "one of the wildest places in Rhode Island."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll take a roughly 5-mile hike around the property, combining all three of the Tillinghast loop trails. The route will take us in and out of the woods over fairly easy terrain, crossing hayfields and stone walls that help tell the story of rural West Greenwich, past and present. Tillinghast Pond and Coney Brook highlight the landscape... See which one you like better:&amp;nbsp; the quiet stillness of the frozen pond or the high energy of the stream as it splashes down the hillside?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am lucky enough to manage this property for The Nature Conservancy, and will be happy to talk about our vision for Tillinghast Pond and the surrounding forest.&amp;nbsp; And I promise you'll get home in time for at least 5 hours of Super Bowl pre-game.&amp;nbsp; So set the chili on low and tromp around the woods with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to Tillinghast Pond Management Area:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;From I-95, take Exit 5B - Route 102 North&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;Follow Route 102 for 3 miles, past the West Greenwich Town Hall&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;Turn left onto Plain Meeting House Road, follow for 4 miles, passing the Wickaboxet Management Area&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;Turn right at the top of the hill, onto Plain Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;Follow Plain Road for 1/2 mile to the parking lot on the right&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim Mooney</member_name><member_id>12472868</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329057814000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326411343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tillinghast Pond -- Super Bowl Sunday Hike</name><id>47886482</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328452200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/47886482/</event_url></item>