<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>For 3 Services</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>For 6 Services $150.00</description><amount>90.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;The Larches B &amp;amp; B and Wellness Center presents: &lt;br /&gt;Six Discounted Strategic Health Screening – Gives you an inside view and allows you to measure your health earlier than most conventional testing and before medications and surgery are necessary.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thurs. April 29  •  4:00 – 7:30 pm  • &lt;br /&gt;Pre-register for appointments required.&lt;br /&gt;Since specific availability of appointments is limited, early registration is recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Six Strategic Health Assessments are state-of-the-art, high-tech, and non-invasive.  &lt;br /&gt;Doing all 6 tests provide the broadest view inside your body and its function.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each service is approximately 15 minutes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fee is $90 for three services or $150 for all six services.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;(Comparable tests are $50-$125 each). &lt;br /&gt;Afterwards, recommendations will be made.&lt;br /&gt;We hope you make the decision to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cardiovascular Screening&lt;br /&gt;1. Determine the biological age of your arteries before you need intervention.&lt;br /&gt;2. Looks at influence of stress &amp;amp; the balance of your autonomic nervous system. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Live Blood Analysis&lt;br /&gt;Nutritional Microscopy enables you to see your blood live on a monitor. &lt;br /&gt;The health of your blood determines the health of your body.  (Finger prick)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Hemoglobin A1C Testing &lt;br /&gt;The gold standard blood sugar screening that more accurately evaluates the health of your blood sugar metabolism and your chance of developing diabetes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Ultraviolet Digital Facial Photography &lt;br /&gt;Allows you to see the health below the surface, dermal level, where skin damage first shows up. From this, we can see areas of concern and damage that may eventually reach the surface.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Ionic Detoxifying Foot Bath &lt;br /&gt;Our daily environment is flooded with toxins in our food, water and air. You cannot avoid it! Detoxification is a critical strategy for health. The water will actually change a variety of colors depending on the toxins that come out. This test is designed and developed to restore the body’s energy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;WHERE: The Larches B &amp;amp; B and Wellness Center&lt;br /&gt;26 South Main Street, Carver, MA 02330&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Mail checks payable in advance to &lt;br /&gt;Rain Phillips &lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Disclaimer: For educational purposes only. Not a substitute for medial advice. At no time is a diagnosis, treatment or cure of any disease made or implied.&lt;i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272930031000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271253519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Six Discounted Strategic Health Screening</name><id>13179932</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272571200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/13179932/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>