<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio (located on Trinity's campus)</name><city>Hartford</city><id>512896</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>IMPORTANT:  THE MOVIE STARTS AT 7:30 SO PLEASE ARRIVE BY 7:15.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cinestudio's UA 90th Anniversary Festival begins with a cheerfully subversive Billy Wilder comedy, rarely available on the silver screen. Tony Curtis and Jack Lemmon star as two musicians who witness Al Capone?s St. Valentine?s Day Massacre, and hide out (in drag) by joining an all-female band. Marilyn Monroe steals the show as Sugar Kane, the band?s naive yet incredibly sexy singer. While Tony Curtis poses as a millionaire to pursue Monroe, a real life sugar daddy falls for the charms of Jack Lemmon. one of the enduring treasures of the movies... that's about nothing but sex and yet pretends it's about crime and greed. Roger Ebert, from Great Movies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SOME LIKE IT HOT &lt;br /&gt;(1959)&lt;br /&gt;120 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Director: Billy Wilder. Screenplay by Billy Wilder and I.A.L. Diamond. Cast: Tony Curtis, Marilyn Monroe, Jack Lemmon, Pat O'Brien, George Raft, Joe E. Brown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  See the file in the Files section for directions to the theater.  If you haven't been to Cinestudio yet, give yourself some extra time.  There's construction on the Trinity Campus so it's not as easy to get to theater.  If you're having trouble, feel free to call me at 203-812-0705.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll meet you in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217633150000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212701855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Some Like It Hot</name><id>8087775</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217459700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/8087775/</event_url></item>