<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.381557</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn Boston-Somerville</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1618376</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Taste is produced by the &lt;a href="http://www.somervillechamber.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Somerville Chamber of Commerce&lt;/a&gt; Dining and Nightlife Group under the direction of Ray Zonghetti. It showcases Somerville&amp;rsquo;s exceptional, diverse array of dining establishments, while at the same time bringing the community- and the region- together in a festive welcome to summertime. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The beneficiary of the 2010 Taste was &lt;a href="http://www.scmtransportation.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Door2Door Transportation by SCM&lt;/a&gt;. Door2Door promotes the independence of seniors and persons with disabilities through community-based transportation. Their friendly, safe and reliable services help 3,000 of our neighbors maintain healthy, mobile and connected lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking &amp;amp; Transportation at the Taste. Free parking is available at the Holiday Inn. If the lot is full, you may park on surrounding streets without fear of ticketing. Attendees may also take advantage of a free shuttle running from Sullivan Station to the venue. Look for our green and white Door2Door van in the passenger pickup and drop-off area. Shuttles run every 20 minutes starting at 5:10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Tickets will be $30 in advance and $35 at the door.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Expect 30 restaurants to present their best fare!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich K</member_name><member_id>9340572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307486661000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Details are incomplete, but I have heard good things about this event.  Stay tuned for additional details as they become available.</why><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303487913000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taste of Somerville</name><id>17397396</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307482200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/17397396/</event_url></item>