<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>84 Inman Rd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02830</zip><lat>41.986480</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401)769 2856</phone><name>Wright's Farm Restaurant</name><city>Harrisville</city><id>327940</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.606030</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let’s have lunch together, family style, at Wright’s Chicken Farm (&lt;a href="http://www.wrightsfarm.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wrightsfar...&lt;/a&gt;) in Harrisville, RI, on Sunday, June 27th, at 12:15pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you may be familiar with Wright’s Chicken Farm. They serve one meal; a chicken dinner that’s served family style with unlimited refills on the food. The chicken dinner comes with rolls, salad, pasta shells with sauce, french fries and dessert. The cost is $10.95 per person plus tip &amp;amp; tax. Drinks are extra (no free refills on the drinks), and they also have four bars. &lt;b&gt;Please bring cash. Wright's does not accept credit cards.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wright’s gets crowded, and the wait can be long. However, if we have at least 10 people, they’ll take a reservation for us. Otherwise, we’ll wait for the next available table. They will not seat us until all of our party is present. Please arrive by 12:15pm so that we can be seated by our 12:30pm reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After lunch, we can visit Wright's Gift Shop or walk around on the grounds, if the weather is nice. We can even head up to Del's in Smithfield, RI as we meander our way home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a 'Maybe', please change your RSVP to a 'Yes' or 'No' by 3pm on Saturday, June 26th. Otherwise, I'll count you as a 'No' when giving Wright's the head count.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll gather in the lobby before proceeding to the hostess station. I look like my picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lesley</member_name><member_id>3382579</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277760804000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275418602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday lunch at Wright’s Chicken Farm, family style! </name><id>13660181</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277655300000</time><rsvp_limit>36</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/13660181/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/3/global_13367603.jpeg</photo_url></item>