<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1326 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02465</zip><lat>42.348685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-527-3203</phone><name>First Unitarian Church</name><city>West Newton </city><id>757367</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.227782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our next General Membership Meeting will be held on Thursday evening, October 30 from 7:00 to 9:00 PM. in West Newton close to Route 128. (Directions below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The subject of the meeting will be the new Child Support Guidelines. I have served on the Commonwealth’s Task Force to review the existing Guidelines and to recommend changes to them.  The Task Force has been meeting for two years, and is finally ready to make its recommendations to Chief Justice for Administration and Management Robert Mulligan. Judge Mulligan will make the final decisions on any revisions to the Guidelines. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We haven’t had a meeting in a long time, and it will be good to get together again. I will moderate the meeting on this very important topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting is free and open to the general public. Tell your friends, your significant others, and your family to come. Free refreshments will be served. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be held in the First Unitarian Church at 1326 Washington Street in West Newton. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128, travel east on Route 16 (Washington Street) for about 1 to 2 miles, passing the Newton-Wellesley Hospital, passing an entrance to the Mass Pike, crossing over the Mass Pike, and entering into a commercial area. The church will then be immediately on your right. Free parking is available in the parking lot of a bank just past the church. If you pass the West Newton Cinema, you have gone 100 feet too far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston, take the Mass Pike to Exit 16 and then travel east on Route 16 (Washington Street). You will very soon enter into a commercial shopping area. The church will then be immediately on your right. Free parking is available in the parking lot of a bank just past the church. If you pass the West Newton Cinema, you have gone 100 feet too far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I’m looking forward to seeing all of you again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Together with you in the love of our children,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ned Holstein, MD, MS&lt;br /&gt;Executive Director&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ned Holstein, M.D., M.S.</member_name><member_id>3335203</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227049005000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fathers' Rights Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fathersrights-210</urlname><id>676727</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Fathers' Rights Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223387966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fathers &amp; Families General Membership Meeting </name><id>8914606</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225407600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fathersrights-210/events/8914606/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/7/global_2531783.jpeg</photo_url></item>