<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364744</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-1580</phone><name>Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1019999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Silence covered everything like thick golden dust, except for a miniature summer concert: the thin violins of the gnats and the dusky cello of a bumblebee caught between the windowpanes."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The post-office girl is Christine, who looks after her ailing mother and toils in a provincial Austrian post office in the years just after the Great War. One afternoon, as she is dozing among the official forms and stamps, a telegraph arrives addressed to her. It is from her rich aunt, who lives in America and writes requesting that Christine join her and her husband in a Swiss Alpine resort. After a dizzying train ride, Christine finds herself at the top of the world, enjoying a life of privilege that she had never imagined. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

But Christine&amp;rsquo;s aunt drops her as abruptly as she picked her up, and soon the young woman is back at the provincial post office, consumed with disappointment and bitterness. Then she meets Ferdinand, a wounded but eloquent war veteran who is able to give voice to the disaffection of his generation. What happens next? You'll have to read the book to find out. Or will you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Caution: You might be tempted to finish the book in one sitting, so give yourself enough time when you pick it up. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331065990000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329706487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stefan Zweig: The Post-Office Girl</name><id>52993752</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330902000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/52993752/</event_url></item>