<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145-147 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02145</zip><lat>42.388291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)628-9300</phone><name>Fasika Ethiopian Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>901881</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084957</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hostelling International&amp;rsquo;s Cultural Caf&amp;eacute; series of fundraising dinners is re-visiting our first ever partnership restaurant, Fasika Ethiopian cuisine. It was a very popular event when we first started the Cultural Cafe series and we expect it to be just as popular. Join us for a night full of lively conversation and unique food and drink &amp;ndash; all while supporting a great cause!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: Tuesday, June 7th, 6-8 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Place: Fasika Ethiopian Restaurant - 145-147 Broadway, Somerville, MA 02145&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fee: $30 includes meal, gratuity, and a donation to Cultural Kitchen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You MUST pre-register for this event &amp;ndash; Cultural Cafe events have sold out in the past, so don&amp;rsquo;t miss out! Order a ticket at this link &lt;span style="color : #1f497d"&gt;&lt;a href="https://co.clickandpledge.com/?wid=39329"&gt;https://co.clickandpledge.com/?wid=39329&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or you may also buy tickets offline by contacting Laurine at &lt;a href="mailto:admin@usahostels.org"&gt;admin@usahostels.org&lt;/a&gt; or at 617-718-7990 ext 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethiopian cuisine is well know for their ingera that is known as Teff. Teff, which is similar to flat bread is made from cereal grain which is rich in iron, calcium, and potassium. Besides Teff here is a sample of a few other dishes you will see on Fasika's menu:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000cf"&gt;Y&amp;eacute;-Minchet Abish (Mild)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Finely chopped prime beef stewed with ginger, onions,cardamom &amp;amp; other spices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000cf"&gt;Y&amp;eacute;-Tikil Gomen (Mild)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Fresh cabbages,carrots,potatoes and green pepper cooked in a turmeric sauce. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000cf"&gt;Y&amp;eacute;-Atakilt kilikil (Mild)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Green beans,carrots,potatoes and onions cooked in a mild sauce.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to share this event with all your friends and co-workers on and off of Meetup.com! This is a great socializing and networking event that allows you to support a cause all at the same time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More about Cultural Caf&amp;eacute; and Cultural Kitchen:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For over a year, Hostelling International USA&amp;rsquo;s Cultural Caf&amp;eacute; has been exploring the diverse cultures and cuisines that the Boston-area restaurants have to offer. Cultural Caf&amp;eacute; is an enjoyable meal shared among fellow members of the community, and also raises funds for Cultural Kitchen, Hostelling International&amp;rsquo;s program for inner-city youth, as well as other educational and outreach programs and initiatives. For all the latest updates, consider joining the Meetup group at &lt;a&gt;www.meetup.com/culturalcafe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an afterschool activity, Cultural Kitchen teaches Boston area youth about culture and diversity using cooking as the primary vehicle - just like travelers at our hostels learn about one another while cooking together in the hostel kitchen. For more information, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.culturalkitchenboston.org/"&gt;www.culturalkitchenboston.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me near the front door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hostelling International Boston</member_name><member_id>12811800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307635581000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Support a great cause all while socializing and enjoying good food!</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Culturalcafe</urlname><id>1554280</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Cultural Café - Dine Out for a Cause</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288892731000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fasika! Where it all started!</name><id>15339490</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307484000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Culturalcafe/events/15339490/</event_url></item>