<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's start gathering around 6:15, we will want to head in for seats around 6:45.   Show time is 7:15 for the 3D version.   Make sure if you buy ahead from Fandango to select the 3D version of the movie.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, ok I give.  All the ads I have seen for this animated flick are funny and since I am going to watch it, I thought I would invite you guys to come along.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be wearing my Boston Movie Group Badge and have a small meetup sign.   If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If it is downstairs I will be near the ropes by the conession stand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we gather in a group outside the room we just watched the movie in to discuss the film and get ahead count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.   So if you miss the group before hand, look for us after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Studio: Universal Pictures &lt;br /&gt;Director: Chris Renaud, Pierre Coffin &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Cinco Paul, Ken Daurio &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Steve Carell, Jason Segel, Russell Brand, Will Arnett, Kristen Wiig, Danny McBride, Miranda Cosgrove, Jack McBrayer, Mindy Kaling, Jemaine Clement, Julie Andrews &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Animation, Comedy &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG (for rude humor and mild action) &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.despicable.me/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.despicable...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: In a happy suburban neighborhood surrounded by white picket fences with flowering rose bushes, sits a black house with a dead lawn. Unbeknownst to the neighbors, hidden beneath this home is a vast secret hideout. Surrounded by a small army of minions, we discover Gru (voiced by Steve Carell), planning the biggest heist in the history of the world. He is going to steal the moon (Yes, the moon!) in Universal's new 3-D CGI feature, &amp;quot;Despicable Me.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gru delights in all things wicked. Armed with his arsenal of shrink rays, freeze rays, and battle-ready vehicles for land and air, he vanquishes all who stand in his way. Until the day he encounters the immense will of three little orphaned girls who look at him and see something that no one else has ever seen: a potential Dad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The world's greatest villain has just met his greatest challenge: three little girls named Margo, Edith and Agnes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing my Boston Movie Group Badge and have a small meetup sign.   If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If it is downstairs I will be near the ropes by the conession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825865000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277732232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Despicable Me</name><id>13933918</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278800100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/13933918/</event_url></item>