<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As Integral Practitioners, we are often drawn to new and integrated practices.  &lt;strong&gt;Before we start updating spiritual practices and moving beyond traditional enlightenment, it is important to really understand what they have to offer and to realize not all practices are equal.&lt;/strong&gt; Arguable the pinnacle of the contemplative systems on the planet, the Indo-Tibetan Essence traditions of Mahamudra and Dzogchen, offers us precise step-by-step map of theory and practice to awakening and beyond.  These specific teachings, often unexplored, also include a perspective that embraces an intentional evolutionary unfolding. &lt;strong&gt;For us to evolve individually and culturally, we need to understand the deeper structures of the mind (Zone 1 AQAL), the different contemplative tools,  their possible flaws, and the scope of the entire contemplative journey as investigated over generations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In our evening together, we will discuss the three main journeys to awakening, stabilized awakening and Buddhahood.  This will also include making the following distinctions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;the distinction between ‘emptiness’ and ‘awareness’ teachings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;the distinction between resting in ever-present/causal awareness and awakening&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;the distinction between non-duality and awakening&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;the distinction between ‘awakening’ as a stable realization and post-awakening ‘enlightenment’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This exploration will enrich our understanding of traditional practices, and further cultivate our own Integral and Evolutionary unfolding.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;John has been practicing meditation since 1990. After leaving high school he joined Samye Ling Kagyu Monastery in Scotland where he began his studies in the Mahayana and Mahamudra. He came to the United States to study at Naropa University where he majored in Contemplative psychology with a specialization in mind/body health. During his time at Naropa he studied with American philosopher, Ken Wilber, and was a founding member of Integral Institute.  John has taught meditative and somatic approaches to awakening for the last decade. He co-founded, with his wife Nicole, Samadhi Integral, a center dedicated to the contemporary development of body, mind and spirit. He practices acupuncture and specializes in energetic psychosomatics. Since 2005 John has been a Mahamudra student of Daniel Brown, and began to study Dzogchen with Rahob Rinpoche in 2007. He was authorized in January 2012 as a teacher in the Pointing Out Way. He is deeply interested in the relationship between psychological and contemplative development, the ‘awakened sangha’, technology and dharma, and the integral evolution of humanity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;“John Churchill is now teaching the next generation of Daniel P. Brown’s brilliant and pioneering work on Pointing Out meditation (some of you might remember Daniel as one of my co-authors of Transformations of Consciousness).  John is an enormously gifted and talented teacher of Daniel’s work (as well as being fully versed in mine).  I highly recommend any of his courses or classes you might be lucky enough to take!” –Ken Wilber, The Integral Vision&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342572109000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339180617000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Integrated Approach to Awakening and Enlightenment (w/John Churchill)</name><id>68344562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341962100000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/68344562/</event_url></item>