<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>67 Kirk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01852</zip><lat>42.647323</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-970-5200</phone><name>Lowell National Historical Park</name><city>Lowell</city><id>710080</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.309705</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Am heading back to the Lowell Folk Festival this year, to get another great opportunity to experience a vast amount of truly diverse music.  The Festival runs from July 25-27th, but we're switching our day of attendance to Saturday to take advantage of the better weather forecast (please contact me directly if you still wish to attend on sunday)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the details at the website: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available at a number of garages in the area for about $10 for the day.  It's going to be a crowded day, but will provide my cell phone so folks can catch up with us as the day goes on.  There are a few spots I'm planning to be at at certain times to try and facilitate meeting.  My apologies for forcing my music choices upon you:-)  Check out the festival map to find us:  &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/festival_map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the schedule at: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And check out the performers at: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/performers.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Initial meeting spot: 10 am: Framingham Park and Ride:&lt;a href="http://www.bostonmpo.org/bostonmpo/info/pnr/Framingham-west.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonmpo....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Second meeting spot (god willing:-):  11:15-11:30 a.m:  Mack Plaza Trolley Stop, near the corner of Dutton St. and Merrimack St&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From here, we'll be heading to the Boarding House Park stage to catch Tread for Irish and Canadian Celtic Music.  This is my own personal must see for the festival, (consider yourself forewarned) but after this, I'm totally flexible.  I'll be here between 12 and 12:45 hoping to catch some sea shanties. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're running late for the park and ride or the Trolley Stop please call me, as we won't be waiting long at either location for stragglers (sorry, I've got a noon deadline:-)  but will far far more casual thereafter:-).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rest is unplanned,  and you'll have to call me to catch us (will again send out my cell number to my yes's and maybe's), but we'll probably walk around and hit upon what folks wanna see, etc.  Please RSVP ASAP....I work late tonight, and will send my cell phone number out overnight so it'll be in your inbox by morning....god willing I'm home before then:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today the festival runs right through to 10 pm, but we'll see how the folk fancy hits us.  Will probably contemplate dinner either there or around town.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet up at any of the listed spots, or call me</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217258496000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216997043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lowell Folk Festival changed to saturday</name><id>8410024</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217085300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8410024/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>