<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>34 Alder Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.366866</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-893-3087</phone><name>First Presbyterian Church</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1134863</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.235809</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>RARE OPPORTUNITY!  HEAR &lt;b&gt;FRED BISCI&lt;/b&gt; &amp;amp; ASK QUESTIONS ABOUT: Understanding &amp;quot;Your Health Journey&amp;quot;; The Raw Food Lifestyle: Why it is so confusing?; Detox: The most IMPORTANT CONSTANT! Looking at all the variables, realizing the consequences and discovering your potential; &lt;b&gt;Fred Bisci&lt;/b&gt; recognizes the value and importance of questions which he will answer from a Clinical, Practical, and Common Sense point of view from his 50 years of experience! Please come prepared with your questions!! We want people to be educated and empowered from this experience; so there will be: NO PHILOSOPHY, NO ANECDOTAL STORIES, NO PROMOTIONAL HYPE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FRED BISCI&lt;/b&gt;, born 1929, an active pioneering nutritionist for over 40 years, has discovered the key to better health, anti-aging, and a longer optimal life. IT'S SIMPLE: Leave out the manufactured foods and the habitual, chronic routines that burden, addict, and will eventually if not NOW make you sick: physically, mentally, emotionally and spiritually while being lead by a life of unprocessed foods through a Real, Clean, Fresh Food approach. He has applied this simple philosophy to his own life, as well as working with over 35,000 people with a wide range of health issues. &lt;b&gt;Dr. Bisci's&lt;/b&gt; history includes hosting his own television show &amp;quot;EAT YOUR WAY TO HEALTH&amp;quot;, which had the largest viewing audience in New York City and won the famed Nova Award for best health series. He has been interviewed and quoted in numerous books, health periodicals, Radio and TV on lifestyle changes related to health. He has completed eighteen marathons, two ultrathons, and was an Olympic style weight lifter and still leads an athletic life. In his book, YOUR HEALTHY JOURNEY, &lt;b&gt;Dr. Bisci&lt;/b&gt; offers doable, nutritious and nourishing lifestyles by inviting a person to meet themselves where they're at and LIVE A LIFE of longevity by working with the most powerful and greatest scientific, physiologic, genetic, chemical, and biological creation, the Human Body, to discover their full potential. IF YOU WANT MORE INFORMATION ABOUT &lt;b&gt;FRED BISCI&lt;/b&gt; PLEASE GO TO HIS WEBSITE AND REVIEW HIS LITERTURE AND BLOG VIDEOS &lt;a href="http://www.fredbisci4health.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.fredbisci4health.com&lt;/a&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;When:   This Thursday, February 25 at 7 pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Where:  The First Presbyterian Church, 34 Alder Street, Waltham, MA 02453 This is the same location as our first potlucks in 2006. Located just 2 blocks off Moody Street.  Parking at South Middle School on corner of Moody &amp;amp; Alder and street parking.  Come downstairs. For Handicapped entrance or questions, call Betsy 617-835-2913&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Admission:  $20 (10% is tax-deductible donation to Optimum Health Solution).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Posted by &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.essenic.org&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 11398866</member_name><member_id>11398866</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280709981000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266765430000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FRED BISCI: Waltham</name><id>12662615</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267142400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/12662615/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/3/global_13229955.jpeg</photo_url></item>