<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hurlingham Drive</address_2><address_1>Conyers Farm</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06831</zip><lat>41.119232</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>212.420.9420 x.47 </phone><name>Greenwich Polo Club</name><city>Greenwich</city><id>966773</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.641861</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NHC does Polo!  &lt;br /&gt;Join us for a fun afternoon at a truly Connecticut event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To quote the Greenwich Polo Club website: &lt;br /&gt;“The grounds open at 1pm and matches begin at 3pm. Feel free to arrive early and tailgate. Pack a picnic lunch and bring a blanket or chairs if you wish. Children as always are welcome, and so are dogs as long as they are kept on a leash. Attire is ‘Garden Party Chic’.  Tickets - General Admission $30/vehicle which includes parking and picnicking. In the event of inclement weather, the polo match is canceled but events continue as scheduled under the tents. Rain-outs are announced on the day of the polo match.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NHC will meet inside the polo club grounds at 2 pm. Bring your own picnic lunch to enjoy before the match. The website does not mention if food and alcohol are sold there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In your reply, please note if you are interested in carpooling and feel free to use the website (RSVP and comments section) to arrange carpools with other interested NHCers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you aren’t sure what to wear for “Garden Party Chic”, check out the pictures on their website…or the movie “Pretty Woman” (think Dockers, not jeans). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is raining, call the Polo Club at 212-420-9420 x47 to find out if the match is canceled for rain-out. If the match is canceled, the rain date for this meetup will be Sunday September 13th – same time, same place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenwichpolo.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Greenwich Polo Club website&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: &lt;br /&gt;Greenwich Polo Grounds  &lt;br /&gt;Hurlingham Drive at Conyers Farm, &lt;br /&gt;Greenwich, CT, 06831 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From The Merritt Parkway: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the Merritt Parkway to Exit 31 North Street. At the end of the exit ramp, follow the sign &amp;quot;To Banksville, NY&amp;quot;. Continue for approximately 2.8 miles on North Street. Turn left onto Hurlingham Drive at Conyers Farm. Security will direct you from there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 95: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the I-95 to Exit 3 Greenwich CT. At the light, take Arch Street heading north. Turn left onto Sound View Drive. Go up the hill and turn right onto Field Point Road. Proceed to the intersection with Putnam Avenue and go straight through onto Dearfield Drive. Continue north around the rotary onto Lake Avenue. Continue north 1.5 miles and turn right onto Grahampton Lane. Continue east 1/2 mile and turn left onto North Street. Continue for approximately 2 miles on North Street. Turn left onto Hurlingham Drive at Conyers Farm. Security will direct you from there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Contact numbers will be sent to YES and MAYBE RSVPs a day or two before the event. The organizors for this event are Tom and Andrea.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252433445000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249172835000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NHC does Polo! Sunday September 6th</name><id>11011595</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252260000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11011595/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/e/global_9974046.jpeg</photo_url></item>