<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Brackett Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04102</zip><lat>43.652073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ronald McDonald House</name><city>Portland</city><id>7197242</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.270325</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00 ; font-size : xx-large"&gt;Ronald McDonald House - Guest Chef&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/3/0/event_119698672.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the Ronald McDonald House?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concept of providing a home away from home for families of children with cancer and other serious illnesses began in Philadelphia in 1973, when Fred Hill, an Eagles football player, learned that his daughter had leukemia. Hill contacted team General Manager Jim Murray and together they joined forces with the medical and business community and local McDonald Restaurant owners and operators. In 1974 the first Ronald McDonald House opened its doors, today our houses are located throughout the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many families travel far from home to get treatment for their seriously ill or injured children. The treatment may last a day, a month, or even longer. It's a long time to be away from home, or to divide a family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ronald McDonald Houses around the world offer families a way to stay together, in proximity to the treatment hospital, and be comfortable and cared for during their stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the spring of 1987, a diverse group of community leaders banded together to form, Stand By Me: a group which worked tirelessly to spearhead the movement to build the Ronald McDonald House in Portland. In 2005 it became evident that our 15 guest rooms were insufficient to meet the increased need. Numerous meetings with an architect, neighbors, neighborhood associations, the Historic Preservation Board, the Portland Planning Board, and the City Council were held. Our new plan to renovate the existing House and expand into 63 Carleton Street was embraced by all neighborhood and government agencies. Since the spring of 1995, through the hard work and efforts of the Stand By Me Board of Directors, &lt;a href="http://www.mcmaine.com/"&gt;Maine McDonald's Restaurants Owner/Operators&lt;/a&gt; , the generosity of the good people of Maine and New Hampshire, volunteers, the medical community, faith-based groups, the business community, foundations, state government personnel, and civic organizations, the excellent design of &lt;a href="http://www.simonsarchitects.com/"&gt;Scott Simons Architects&lt;/a&gt;, original construction by Pochebit Construction, and the recent renovation transformation by &lt;a href="http://www.thaxtercompany.com/"&gt;The Thaxter Company&lt;/a&gt;, the 18,399 square foot facility now provides up to 21 families each night with a home away from home to families of critically-ill children receiving treatment at nearby hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the Guest Chef?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming home to a hot meal after a long day at the hospital can bring a great deal of relief to a family. This program allows you to help prepare and serve a meal to the families staying at the Ronald McDonald house. After the preparation is complete, you may join the families for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Family meals should serve approximately 20 people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dinner is served buffet style at &lt;strong&gt;6:00 p.m&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meals can be prepared in our double kitchen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do I have to do to participate in this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to have enough food to serve 20 guests, and ourselves, so we can stay and eat. We will need to bring enough of each of the following items to serve a total of 28 people.  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;Our theme for October will be early Thanksgiving, when you RSVP please sign up for one of the following:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Turkey 1 (does not have to be a whole turkey, maybe turkey breasts or cutlets, since this is an expensive item I will divide it between 2 people) Ann&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Turkey 2- Kiersten&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Potatoes for mashed potatoes- Jocelyn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Stuffing- Amber/Ann&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Rolls- Stacy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. Vegetable- Claire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7. Dessert- Claire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8. Dessert- Noel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From I -295:&lt;/strong&gt; North Bound, take the first Forest Avenue Exit.  Southbound, take the second Forest Avenue Exit.  Turn right onto Forest Avenue heading east toward Portland.  At the light, bear right onto Route 77 through Deering Oaks Park.  Go through two sets of lights.  At the third set take a right onto Congress Street.  Take the second left onto Walker Street.   At the end of Walker Street, take a right onto Brackett Street.  Ronald McDonald House is the fourth house down on the left on the corner of Brackett and Carleton Streets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;For more information about the program, please visit the link below:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rmhportlandme.org/volunteers/guest-chef-love-served-daily"&gt;http://www.rmhportlandme.org/volunteers/guest-chef-love-served-daily&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet outside the Ronald McDonald House at 5 and go in as a group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kiersten Pfeifer</member_name><member_id>5225469</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1350950692000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346167992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ronald McDonald House - Guest Chef</name><id>79733062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350939600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/79733062/</event_url></item>