<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10.00 at the door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You may have noticed that Socializing for Justice is not an issue-based organization. We host events that draw progressives of all stripes that are like-minded but not necessarily like-identified. Our philosophy focuses on creating social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections, discussion spaces that challenge our myopic view of the world and now we're introducing skillshares which will support all of us desiring to make a difference in the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're very excited that Adaora Asala, has agreed to facilitate this training. Below is the workshop description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Social Media 101&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why are millions of people using Facebook and what the tweet is Twitter? This 90-minute skillshare will cover the &amp;quot;what&amp;quot; and the &amp;quot;why&amp;quot; behind Social Media. Learn basic uses of popular tools like Twitter, Facebook, and Youtube, including how to keep up to date with and support your favorite causes, or champion your own!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCHEDULE&lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - bring your own dinner&lt;br /&gt;6:30-8:00 Training&lt;br /&gt;8:00-8:30 Q &amp;amp; A and more socializing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GLAD is physically accessible - there is a microwave and water cooler. Winter Street is between Tremont Street (Park St T) and Washington Street (Downtown Crossing T). The entrance is on Winter Place an alleyway next to Sovereign Bank.  Very limited parking nearby - best best Boston Common Garage - driving not recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adaora Asala&lt;/b&gt; is a diversity consultant and social media strategist in the non-profit sector, and an avid blogger on leadership and activism. She is the founding director of Queer Women of Color and Friends (QWOC+ Boston), &lt;a href="http://www.qwocboston.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.qwocboston.org&lt;/a&gt;, a nationally recognized social networking organization for LGBTQ people of color and allies in New England. Adaora was recently honored by the History Project as the recipient of the 2010 Lavender Rhino Award and by Fenway Women's Health with &amp;quot;The Trailblazer Award.&amp;quot; You can read more about her and her work at &lt;a href="http://www.spectraspeaks.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.spectraspeaks.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you'll join us for this and future skillshares. Is there a skill you want to learn? Is there one you can offer? Let us know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With almost 1500 members and 4+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289136863000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287767492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Social Media 101</name><id>15195253</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288648800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/15195253/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/b/1/global_18946785.jpeg</photo_url></item>