<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1657 Hancock Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.245647</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Remick's</name><city>Quincy</city><id>11322792</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.000359</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join members and guest of the SSDOMG as we discover another restaurant on the south shore!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event Title: Saturday Night Dinner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, Feb. 23, 7pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RESTAURANT INFO&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;remicksquincy.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REMICK'S RESTAURANT HIGHLIGHTS A FRESH APPROACH to traditional food and atmosphere with a distinct nod to Quincy’s historic past. With a stylish bistro atmosphere, Remick’s brings back a bit of old Quincy with historic murals and artwork complementing the modern design. Natural woods, leather and fabrics add to the comfortable atmosphere. &lt;br /&gt;

 Contemporary Comfort&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cuisine, a blend of old-style comfort foods mixed with familiar contemporary dishes, uses only the freshest, highest-quality ingredients hand chosen by our executive chef Tim Raines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: Appetizers: $9-$13&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entrees: $12-$28&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Meeting Place: Please meet inside the front door. We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizers: Debbi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event Fee: [Current] Annual Members - FREE, Members - $2 each; $5 to become an Annual Member&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maximum: 8&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No Guests&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP Deadline: Fri, Feb 22nd. 7pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our Group's No-Show Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No-Show Policy on Membership Information Page: (Please click on the following link to be taken directly to the page.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inclement Weather: Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather").&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages tab for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debbi  </member_name><member_id>22304061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361887089000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358958408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Night Dinner</name><id>101003782</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361664000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/101003782/</event_url></item>