<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>3rd Floor</address_2><address_1>80 Border St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02128</zip><lat>42.372321</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Atlantic Works Gallery</name><city>East Boston</city><id>781196</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.042312</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a closing party for this local East Boston gallery's two person contemporary art exhibition.&amp;nbsp; The Gallery is primarily for the 20 artists that create art in the building. Sounds very interesting. Let's check it out at their BYOB Closing Party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://atlanticworksartgallery.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://atlanticworksartgallery.blogspot.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what the gallery wrote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What separates inside from outside? How thin is the boundary? Once the boundary is penetrated, what happens? Chris Spuglio and Leah Grimaldi pick at, explore and transgress the border that separates the insides from the outsides in their show INN3R.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exhibit Duration: June 10 &amp;ndash; July 9, 2011
 &lt;br /&gt; Opening Reception: Saturday, June 11, 7-10pm
 &lt;br /&gt; Third Thursday Reception: June 16, 7-10pm
 &lt;br /&gt; BYOB Closing Party: July 9, 7-11PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information or to schedule a private press viewing, email Leah Grimaldi at 
&lt;a href="mailto:lgrimald@gmail.com"&gt;lgrimald@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or phone her at (774) 276-1549.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;About the Artists&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; Abstract texture painter Chris Spuglio returns to 3 dimensional sculpture for soulsearching installations for INN3R. By collecting the energy derived from dark emotions and painful experiences, he presents a powerful body of work that displays the transition from internal feelings to external perception. Leah Grimaldi deals with attraction and repulsion surrounding the insides and outsides of bodies. Leah finds jouissance in the kind of abjection that relates to the human body, its proclivity to excess and its entropy, but is also horrified by it. She deals with her ambivalence toward human bodies and having one &amp;mdash; especially in a time when not all human bodies are 100% human &amp;mdash; and the body?s treatment in fashion and entertainment. Her wall installations and prints express this ambivalence using humor and horror.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have something orange on.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Q.</member_name><member_id>2269958</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310257107000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309775432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Closing Party at Atlantic Works Gallery - East Boston</name><id>24488091</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310252400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/24488091/</event_url></item>