<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>west hartford</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.764294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>caryl's house</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>462542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.727501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. 
&lt;strong&gt;NOTE We are back at Caryl's house this month.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/7/b/event_38454651.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; At one point a few years back (BC) A friend from college days asked me to design and decorate her waiting room and office around an actual size print of van Gogh's Fishing Boats on the Beach at Saints-Maries. We built everything off the red in the front boat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picasso did Two Women Running on the Beach, The Race, which I almost posted because it is one of the Picasso pieces I actually fully appreciate. Gauguin did the Tahitian Women on the Beach and there is a good deal of red tonality in that but it always makes me a bit sad so I didn't want to post that image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fran, the friend who had me help design her office was a&amp;nbsp;physiologist&amp;nbsp;that worked with children. She was also at one time an artist and ran a&amp;nbsp;commercial&amp;nbsp;turn of the prior century typeset turning out amazingly&amp;nbsp;textural&amp;nbsp;books that are works of art in themselves. &amp;nbsp;She is also a muse for one of the top glass artists in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tells the story of a time in her life when she was so broken that suicide seemed the only option. For some reason she called me. She says that I drove to where she was picked her up and brought her home insisting that all she really needed was some lentil soup, or maybe it was onion soup. I installed her in my spare room and&amp;nbsp;apparently&amp;nbsp;proceed to feed her for a month or so. This saved her life she will tell you. Now I am using words like apparently and that "she would say" because I honestly have no&amp;nbsp;recollection&amp;nbsp;of this at all. I mean I remember her being unhappy and needing a place to stay and in those days I always had a soup, beans or stew on the stove and there was always someone in the spare room. It seems reasonable that I would have brought her home, that is what friends do after all. The point is I have no real memory of this and had no idea at the time of the crucial nature of my actions. From Fran's point of view I saved her life and this is a seminal moment of her&amp;nbsp;existence. Very different experiences of the same moment in time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason I share this story is because it occurs to me that we never know which of our actions or words will be the ones that alter the world, bring hope or save a life. I think more often than not we never know. It is a bit like that butterfly effect conversation that was so popular a few years back. It also occurs to me that most meaningful moments involve a bit of food. It&amp;nbsp;therefore&amp;nbsp;behooves&amp;nbsp;us to keep a pot bubbling on the stove, clean sheets on the guest bed and a light in the window of our hearts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh and don't forget to wear sunscreen...we don't want you red on the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313544102000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310182310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reds on the Beach</name><id>vmbmnyplbqb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313190000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/25096301/</event_url></item>