<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join fellow members of the SSDOMG as we enjoy a Saturday Evening Post-Holiday Potluck Celebration!  The Organizer Team decided this might be a less stressful and more fun and enjoyable holiday celebration for the SSDOMG.  This will allow us plenty of opportunity to socialize and interact with everyone in attendance.  So, pull out your favorite recipe or grab something from the supermarket.  Either way, be sure to have a list of ingredients for those with food allergies.  Enjoy an evening with the SSDOMG without having to figure out the tax and tip!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be gathering at Angela's home in Braintree so here are some ground rules and guidelines.&lt;br /&gt;*SSDOMG Members Only&lt;br /&gt;*You have to have attended at least 2 events w/ the SSDOMG in 2010 OR 1 event in 2010 and 2 events in 2009.  For exceptions simply email Angela.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What will be provided by your Host and Organizer Team:&lt;br /&gt;-Cups, dishes, plates, bowls, napkins, utensils (forks, knives, spoons)&lt;br /&gt;-Water&lt;br /&gt;-One other food item, tbd based on what everyone else is bringing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to optimize the food we will be enjoying here is a recommended list of items to choose from.  &lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Appetizers&lt;/i&gt;: Limit of 3, max of one hot item.&lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Beverages&lt;/i&gt;: Limit of 2 per 5 attendees.  Please bring a variety of 2 beverages.  Options include regular soda, diet soda, lemonade, eggnog, juice, etc.  (Please specify so we have enough variety.)&lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Desserts&lt;/i&gt;: Limit of 3, max of one hot item.&lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Fruits and Veggies&lt;/i&gt;: Preferably as part of a main dish.  Maximum of 3.&lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Main Dishes&lt;/i&gt;: Minimum of 3, max of 6 including but not limited to: Meat Dish, Seafood Dish, Veggie Dish, Combination Platters such as Chicken Broccoli and Ziti.  &lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Salads&lt;/i&gt;:  Maximum of 2.  (If you are bringing a garden salad please specify which salad dressing you will be brining.)  (Please specify type.)&lt;br /&gt;-&lt;i&gt;Condiments&lt;/i&gt;: Mayo, ketchup, relish, salad dressing (1-2, please specify), etc...  based on what others are bringing and the need.  We have salt but not pepper. 1 person to bring 3-4 items based on need.&lt;br /&gt;*Please bring proper serving utensils.&lt;br /&gt;*Cold items should be brought cold and hot items should be brought hot.&lt;br /&gt;*Please contact the Host/Organizer if you need to heat an item with all pertinent information.&lt;br /&gt;*&lt;i&gt;Please state the category of the item you are bringing in your RSVP Comments.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please state in your RSVP Comments the category of the item you are bringing and please be as precise as possible by stating the name of the item so as to avoid having too many of any dish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: &lt;br /&gt;1. Everyone will start on the Wait List and will moved to a Yes once the Organizer has confirmed your past event attendance.  (We will start confirming attendees in mid-to-late December once we have the minimum number of attendees.)&lt;br /&gt;2. Please advise what you are bringing no later than January 12th.  &lt;br /&gt;3. If anyone shows up empty-handed please be prepared to pay $8 cash to help cover the cost of expenses.&lt;br /&gt;4. The Host lives in a secure building.  Please plan to arrive no later than 6:30pm so the Host can enjoy the event and not spend the entire night letting people in.  If you are going to arrive later than 6:30pm please contact Angela directly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allergies: If you have an allergy please note it in the Talk About It Section.  Even though my home is non-smoking, neighbors are allowed to smoke in their individual units.  I can attest that I do smell cigarette smoke on occasion.  In addition, even though my home is animal-free, neighbors are allowed to have small pets (although none currently do).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to join us on Saturday, January 15th, 2011 @ 6pm to approximately 9pm for a fun evening of socializing and eating in a relaxing environment!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post-Holiday Potluck Celebration!&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 15th, 2011 @ 6pm&lt;br /&gt;Angela’s Condo&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers/Hosts:&lt;/b&gt; Angela and the SSDOMG Organizer Team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Minimum and Maximum number of attendees:&lt;/b&gt; We desire a minimum of 8 attendees by Wednesday, January 5th.  The maximum number of attendees is approximately 20 people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, January 14th @ 6pm / No new RSVPs will be accepted after 10am on Saturday, January 15th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Members Only for now.  We will check the RSVP List and update right after the first of the year if there is enough space to allow one Guest per Member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Late Arrivals:&lt;/b&gt; So that we may all enjoy the food and each other’s company without having to “wait a few more minutes as another dish is on the way” we ask that you please arrive within 1/2 hour of the start of the event.  Please call if you will be any later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Whatever you choose.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; NONE!  The only cost is the items you bring.  You can become a 2011 Annual Member at tonight's event.  Please bring $12 cash if you would like to become an Annual Member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/b&gt; TBD - Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on &amp;quot;Weather&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Directions, including address and phone #s (to be used only if necessary) &lt;b&gt;will be emailed to all Yes RSVPs&lt;/b&gt; a few days prior to the event and then again shortly after the RSVP deadline.  Located near Exit 17 on Route 3, the Braintree T, and along a bus stop.  Please be sure to read the Directions email as it will include parking information.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You will have directions right to my door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296518177000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290288572000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Post-Holiday Potluck Celebration!</name><id>15511394</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295132400000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/15511394/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/b/global_14765243.jpeg</photo_url></item>