<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hilldale Lane</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03070</zip><lat>42.982098</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hillsborough County 4-H Youth Center (Fairgrounds)</name><city>New Boston</city><id>1339916</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.682395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/1/c/event_160540732.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/b/c/event_160540892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will do a easy line hike 3 miles one way (6 miles round trip) off leash once we are away from the fairgrounds.  As it is a relatively straight easy to follow trail anyone wanting to turn back earlier could do so.  By the time we get back Pet Step will be in full swing and it would be too late to participate in the Pet Step 2 mile walk.  Anyone wanting to do the Pet Step walk could simply turn back earlier and only walk for 1 and 1/2 hours.  If you are not going to participate in the Pet Step walk (on leash) it doesn't cost anything to attend the event itself, although you could register if you wanted to simply as a way of supporting the fundraiser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may have to park where told to by the Pet Step Staff then walk to the rear of the fair grounds where the rail trail starts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pet Step is a fundraiser for the Animal Rescue League of New Hampshire. . There will also be vendors there and other activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to the event: &lt;a href="http://rescueleague.org/petstep.cfm"&gt;http://rescueleague.org/petstep.cf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking for the Pet Step event starts at 9:30 AM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to bring a guest for the rail trail walk have them sign up on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After parking we will gather at the back of the fairgrounds where the rail trail starts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348889828000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347669599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Piscataquog Rail Trail 6 mi. Line Hike - Pet Step ARLNH Fundraiser</name><id>82465202</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348320600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/82465202/</event_url></item>