<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/d/a/event_82048122.jpeg" width="239" height="360" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is going to be busing this weekend on the red line from Kendall to Broadway, so plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oooh!  This sounds fun and creepy!  Love Poe, and the idea of a serial killer using his work to plan his crimes is simply delicious!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Showtime is at 6:40PM. I will be at the theater by 5:45 and we will head in for seats by 6:10 PM.&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;/strong&gt; I will update closer to the event when actual movie times become available.  Usually the theaters release the times on Wednesdays.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The movie is showing upstairs, so look for the group at the tables by the windows at the top of the escalator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have been hearing a lot of buzz about this movie, so it would be a good idea to buy your tickets in advanced. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after and bring cash.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Release Date is Now: April 27, 2012&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Relativity Media &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt;James McTeigue &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Ben Livingston, Hannah Shakespeare &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt;John Cusack, Luke Evans, Alice Eve, Brendan Gleeson, Oliver Jackson-Cohen &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Thriller &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; R (for bloody violence and grisly images) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.relativitymediallc.com/film_details.asp?projectId=%7B7A58AC96-0D4A-4990-B107-9CB1013B2499%7D" target="_blank"&gt;RelativityMediaLLC.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt;In this gritty thriller, Edgar Allen Poe (John Cusack, "Being John Malkovich") joins forces with a young Baltimore detective (Luke Evans, "Immortals") to hunt down a mad serial killer who's using Poe's own works as the basis in a string of brutal murders. Directed by James McTeigue ("V For Vendetta"), the film also stars Alice Eve ("Sex and the City 2"), Brendan Gleeson ("In Bruges") and Oliver Jackson-Cohen ("Faster"). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

When a mother and daughter are found brutally murdered in 19th century Baltimore, Detective Emmett Fields (Luke Evans) makes a startling discovery: the crime resembles a fictional murder described in gory detail in the local newspaper—part of a collection of stories penned by struggling writer and social pariah Edgar Allan Poe. But even as Poe is questioned by police, another grisly murder occurs, also inspired by a popular Poe story. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Realizing a serial killer is on the loose using Poe's writings as the backdrop for his bloody rampage, Fields enlists the author's help in stopping the attacks. But when it appears someone close to Poe may become the murderer’s next victim, the stakes become even higher and the inventor of the detective story calls on his own powers of deduction to try to solve the case before it's too late.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335976503000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325007087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Raven (6:40PM Show)</name><id>45591432</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335649500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/45591432/</event_url></item>