<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AMC Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;4 Joy Street, Boston MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM potluck, 7:00 PM slideshow&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking to hike amoung glacier-capped mountain peaks, turquoise-blue glacial lakes, thundering waterfalls and multitudes of wildflowers? Have you been wanting to spy on charismatic mega-fauna,  such as grizzly &amp;amp; black bear, mountain sheep, elk and moose? Join two of AMC August Camp hike leaders, Michele Grzenda &amp;amp; Julie LePage, for a slideshow about these things and more during their 2010 trip to the Canadian Rockies w/AMC's August Camp. During their two week stay, they lead day hikes and backpacks in the Canadian Rocky Mountain National Parks of Banff, Yoho, Kootenay, Glacier and Jasper.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the show, you'll learn more about the 125+ year history of AMC August Camp, a nomadic 64 person basecamp that moves to different mountainous locations each year offering a variety of hikes, backpacks, car camps, water trips and mountain bike rides for a four-week period from mid-July to mid-August. Each week offers something for everyone, from an arduous day of hiking, to a cultural museum tour, to an afternoon at the hot springs. This year, the folks that run August Camp decided the Canadian Rockies had so much to offer, they're staying put for 2011! So get the inside scoop on this magical area and learn about signing up for a week or more next summer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you plan to attend, please RSVP to AMCBostonSlideshows@gmail.com. For those who wish to participate in the potluck at 6:30, feel free to use the following guidelines for what to bring: Last names beginning with J-Z bring a main dish or side dish, A-I bring an appetizer or dessert. Homemade dishes are great, store bought goodies &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome:) Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (stovetop, oven, microwave, sink, fridge, etc).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292080587000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287627752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canadian Rockies (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>15178917</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291851000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15178917/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/d/global_18921341.jpeg</photo_url></item>