<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Storrow Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.355885</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>DCR Hatch Shell</name><city>Boston</city><id>616724</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.074165</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>America with Marty Balin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first free Oldies 103.3 concert of the summer! Remember what a great time we had last summer! We will bring a picnic, get there early, visit the booths, and enjoy the music! We will carpool and park on Storrow Drive-or some will take the T-More info to follow! Check the website: www.oldies1033.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2008 Free Summer Concert Series Parking &amp;amp; Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here to return to the Summer Concert Series Homepage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Line&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take any train to the Charles Street/MGH station. Take the footbridge over Storrow Drive to the Charles River side and go West along Storrow Drive. The DCR Hatch Shell is a short walk from here. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take any train to the Arlington Street Station. Walk along the Public Garden/Arlington Street to Beacon Street. Cross over Beacon Street and take the Arthur Fiedler Footbridge over Storrow Drive to the DCR Hatch Shell. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here for more MBTA infomation or call 617-222-3200.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The DCR Hatch Shell is located on Storrow Drive. You can access Storrow Drive from Routes 93, The Mass Turnpike, Route 2 and many other roadways. The DCR Hatch Shell is located on the East End of Storrow Drive not too far from The Mass General Hospital. Handicapped parking is located in the lane closure, lane closure parking fills up quickly so plan on taking the MBTA or parking in a Garage. The lane closure is limited to the coned off marked area. Do not park on the median or past the coned marked off area on Storrow Drive or you will be towed. Parking on Storrow Drive is also limited to 1/2 hour after the concert ends, if your car is still on Storrow after the 1/2 hour is up it will be towed. Parking is very limited, so unless you show up early plan on parking in a garage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local Parking garage&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Prudential Center Parking Garage&lt;br /&gt;800 Boylston Street&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;617-236-3060 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Common Garage&lt;br /&gt;Charles Street&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;617-954-2096&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tips &amp;amp; Notes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Grills &lt;br /&gt;No Alcohol &lt;br /&gt;Handicap accessible seating area first come first serve (1 Person with 1 assistant) &lt;br /&gt;Buy T passes on your way in so you will avoid the crowds when leaving &lt;br /&gt;Bring a picnic lunch, but leave the alcohol at home &lt;br /&gt;Bring blankets and lawn chairs &lt;br /&gt;Come early to get a good spot on the lawn, it fills up quickly&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>4148667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213657393000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211327929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>America in concert on the Esplanade!</name><id>7978568</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213484400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/7978568/</event_url></item>