<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Values: To be nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and to be respectful to everyone. We utilize private house parties or dance parties as a vehicle to meet other singles. Purpose is to socialize with similar people of your age (30-50) who are searching for a lifetime partner. Have fun meeting old and new friends. Circulate, talk to everyone. If someone is alone go up to them and say hi! Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Yes Dance - I ask you to be respectful and say yes to anyone who asks you to dance ONCE. Please understand this is our number one value. If you are able to say yes, then this is a great event for you to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are coming because you got this email, and this is your invitation. Please invite other friends, particularly men. Our goal is to have an equal amount of men and women. Last dance in the 40-65 age group, we had more men than women.(62 men-55 women) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $5.00 plus wine or food assignment &lt;br /&gt;DJ - Dancing will be available &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wine and food selections change monthly: &lt;br /&gt;Men bring a bottle of wine this party&lt;br /&gt;Women- bring a food selection- appetizer or entree&lt;br /&gt;No chips or crackers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Format: &lt;br /&gt;Location is in a safe, warm, loving and relaxing environment. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dress code - &amp;quot;business casual&amp;quot; – NO JEANS OR SNEAKERS &lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 9:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, October 11, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open Bar - wine/beer/soft drinks/water that you are assigned to bring&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can sign up on &lt;a href="http://dance.meetup.c.." target="_blank"&gt;http://dance.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You do not need to email me personally. &lt;br /&gt;50 guests only&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions &lt;br /&gt;44 Pickman Drive&lt;br /&gt;Bedford, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128 -Exit 4 and 225 toward Bedford- 3.9 miles&lt;br /&gt;stay right at two forks past VW Dealershipo&lt;br /&gt;left Dudley Rd. (sign Huckins Farm)&lt;br /&gt;left on Pickman&lt;br /&gt;Right 44 Pickman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay off grass when parking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the time, the location and what you should bring so let’s have fun! &lt;br /&gt;See you on Saturday, October 11th at 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe watch Rd Sox game in one room if you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be! &lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcoming you at the Door</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345157309000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217878656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles House/ Dance Party</name><id>8475349</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223766000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/8475349/</event_url></item>