<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1525 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.339706</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stella Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>1499122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072403</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Bryan S. is again hosting this event...thanks Bryan!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Stella Restaurant and Bar is located in Boston at 1525 Washington Street, at the corner of W. Brookline Street in the South End, near the Blackstone Park. The telephone number is 617-247-7747.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Stella Restaurant and Bar offers Italian cuisine and an energetic ambiance. The décor is white-on-white resulting in a unique, stylish space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Light appetizers will again be provided courtesy of the Sitz group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Directions to Stella Restaurant and Bar After Work / April 10, 2013 @ 6:00 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The restaurant is easily accessible from the north and South (Expressway/Route 3/93); and, from the west via the Mass Pike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;From the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;south&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; take the Southeast Expressway to Exit 18. At the top of the ramp take a left at the second set of lights towards Roxbury (Melnea Cass Blvd.) and the Boston Medical Center. Then take a right at the next set of lights onto Massachusetts Avenue. At the 3rd set of lights take a right onto Washington and go 6 blocks. Stella Restaurant will be on the left-hand side, adjacent to the Blackstone Park at the corner of West Brookline Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you are driving in from the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;west&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, take the Mass. Pike to the Copley/Prudential exit. Take the ramp to the Prudential and exit onto Huntington Avenue. Go through the first set of lights, keep right, and take a left onto Massachusetts Avenue. Take Mass. Avenue to Washington Street (5th set of lights), go left onto Washington Street, go 6 blocks and Stella’s on the left.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;From the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;north&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, take the Southeast Expressway to the Melnea Cass Blvd. exit. Go right at Massachusetts Avenue and at the 3rd set of lights take a right onto Washington Street, go 6 blocks and Stella’s will be on your left at the corner of West Brookline Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The restaurant is also accessible by MBTA at nearby stops on the Green Line (Copley); Orange Line (Mass. Ave.); and, Silver Line, which runs along Washington Street in front of the restaurant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stella’s has valet service for $16 per car, cash only. There is also limited metered parking on Washington Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Questions, please call Bryan Stevens at 617-472-2770 (days), or 617-262-6396 (evenings)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the back room...follow the happy sounds</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365732950000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363833926000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Afterwork in the South End!</name><id>110291482</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365631200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/110291482/</event_url></item>