<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Near Tremont Street and Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356514</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fountain in Boston Common by Park Street T</name><city>Boston</city><id>9369412</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE&lt;/a&gt; IS CO-SPONSORING THIS EVENT WITH OUR FRIENDS AT &lt;a href="http://www.thedefinitionofnyce.com/"&gt;THE DON&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://wonderwomenboston.com/"&gt;WONDER WOMEN OF BOSTON&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://laced569.com/"&gt;LACED BOSTON&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://voltcrowd.com/"&gt;VOLT CROWD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/2/event_160920722.jpeg" width="228" height="230" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 10,000 Hugs Event, Supporting Our Youth:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us on a walk from Boston Common to the South End to create a positive atmosphere in our city. The walk will be about an hour long, stopping to hug everyone we find on our way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you arrive at 11am you'll be provided a Hug T-Shirt (if you have made a donation, see below) and some flyers. As we walk together we'll be providing people we meet on the way a flyer, explain to them the 10,000 Hugs Event and how we are supporting the youth by raising awareness and giving them shirts. Then offer the people we meet a friendly hug - and ask them to hug another five people today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DONATE via our &lt;a href="http://search.voltcrowd.com/campaign/detail/328"&gt;Volt Crowd page&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; We want to see our youth engaged in their communities. We want the adults in those communities to encourage and empower the youth. The DON (Definition of Nyce) produces shirts that spread positive messages - and we want to be able to give these shirts to youth at no cost to them. By joining our hug chain, they've certainly earned it! So donate to this Hug Chain today, and not only get a shirt for yourself - but for one of our youth, as well! We'll also be contributing to &lt;a href="http://www.thecityschool.org/"&gt;The City School&lt;/a&gt;, an organization developing &amp;amp; strengthening the power of youth to work toward building a just society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Itinerary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:00am - 11:15am&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Receive a T-Shirt (if applicable), Get Hug Flyers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Begin walk -- Some people might want to linger in Downtown Crossing area while others go through the park toward Newbury Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1pm- Arrive at Laced Boston (569 Columbus Ave), for an after party with music &amp;amp; food.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who prefer not to go on the walk, Huggers can choose to stay in one place and offer hugs to potential huggees at our Hug Stations. The first one will be in the North End, just outside, North End Fish Market at 99 Salem Street. The second will be in Dorchester, just outside of Stitch House at 846 Dorchester Ave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATTENTION YOUTH HUGGERS&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Each Hug Station will have a set amount of clothing inventory to donate to youth huggers. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are a youth hugger, please register by October 5th&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; to be added to the list of youth who will receive a t-shirt on the day of the event - t-shirts are limited and will be given out on a first come basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/#JoinTheHug"&gt;#JoinTheHug&lt;/a&gt; all about?&lt;/strong&gt; Conceived by The DON (The Definition of Nyce), we're a community oriented clothing brand dedicating the profits to charities. We're labeled as a "streetwear" brand; outshining others in our genre as we support a non-violent culture; we believe in changing the current language - from Thugs to Hugs, in a sense. Same people, same style, slightly different script.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We Are&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The DON is a community oriented clothing brand dedicating its profits to charity. A brand with substance – a brand you’re proud to wear. We have the same style &amp;amp; attitude as other streetwear brands but we're changing the script, sharing positive messages on our shirts. The brand represents a positive lifestyle; one of honesty, integrity, compassion, humbleness, and overall kindness. Those who live The DON Lifestyle are energized by the idea of making a difference, who understand that we cannot wait for other people to do the good that needs to be done, and who know that change from within is the only change that can stand the test of time. The underlying premise of The DON is that every company can make a positive social impact. Businesses in every industry can set forth to achieve philanthropic goals and - even fashion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DON is a call to social action, offering to break down social barriers and unite communities. With this unity, we sanction society to battle the greater challenges facing our citizens today. Those who join The DON Family walk the talk by being open-minded, honest, maintaining their integrity, and living their daily lives full of love &amp;amp; compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DON's &lt;a href="http://www.thedefinitionofnyce.com/index.php?page=keep-love-alive"&gt;Keep Love Alive collection&lt;/a&gt; was created as an avenue to spread love. None of the world's problems will ever be solved without love! The DON uses fashion and it's Keep Love Alive collection as a way to spread encouraging messages and create a positive atmosphere throughout our communities. To date, over 2 dozen shirt designs for both women &amp;amp; men have been printed and sold.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>8714250</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daniel Rechel</member_name><member_id>10433469</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350757172000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348154269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>#JoinTheHug - 10,000 Hugs, Supporting our Youth</name><id>83280392</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350745200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/83280392/</event_url></item>