<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305225</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>3825562</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.818054</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for GWH nonmembers</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;James Croft, a candidate for an Ed.D in Human Development and Education at the Harvard Graduate School of Education (HGSE), and a vice-chair of the Humanist Graduate Community at Harvard, will deliver a talk entitled, " The Symbolic Poverty and Potential of Humanism." Lecture Abstract: Art. Ritual. Narrative. Music. Organized religion harnesses all these symbolic resources in order to build strong communities, persuade others, and encourage congregations to act on their values. Organized Humanism and Secularism, in contrast, too often shies away from these powerful mechanisms, even viewing appeals to the emotions as morally suspect. In a lively and challenging presentation, James will demonstrate the importance of symbolism and argue that Humanism, despite it's current symbolic poverty, has great potential to become a more effective social movement by harnessing the symbolic power of the arts. The program is scheduled to start at 7 at the UU Church of Worcester, with doors opening at 6:30 for socializing and conversation. Guests who are not members of the Greater Humanists of Worcester will be asked to make a $5 donation at the door. Please watch &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/24260341/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/24260341/&lt;/a&gt; for changes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318378977000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317757917000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A talk by James Croft, on the use of symbols in Humanism</name><id>36138432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318374000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/36138432/</event_url></item>