<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>To be celebrated according to your conscience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the official description: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;International Blasphemy Rights Day takes place September 30th to commemorate the publishing of the Jyllands-Posten Muhammad cartoons. The purpose is not to promote hate or violence; it is to support free speech, support the right to criticize and satirize religion, and to oppose any resolutions or laws, binding or otherwise, that discourage or inhibit free speech of any kind. While many perceive blasphemy as insulting and offensive, this event is not about getting enjoyment out of ridiculing and insulting others; rather, it was created as a reaction against those who would seek to take away the right to satirize and criticize a particular set of beliefs given a privileged status over other beliefs. Criticism and dissent towards opposing views is the only way in which any nation with any modicum of freedom can exist. Without this essential liberty, those in power are those best able to manipulate others will suppress and silence dissent by labeling it &amp;quot;defamation&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;blasphemy&amp;quot; or whatever other bogey words they can use to stifle opposition by turning popular sentiment against it. Please, do not let them do this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you support free speech, and the rights of those who disagree with religious views to voice their opinions peacefully, celebrate International Blasphemy Rights Day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;International Blasphemy Rights Day is a volunteer-coordinated campaign administered by the Center for Inquiry as part of its Campaign for Free Expression. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.centerforinquiry.net/cffe" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerfori...&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285892032000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285617911000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International Blasphemy Rights Day</name><id>14914717</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285887600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/14914717/</event_url></item>