<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Renowned English video artist Steve McQueen's feature film debut, HUNGER, is a cinematic punch to the gut. McQueen brings a visceral intensity to his retelling of the hunger strike instigated by Bobby Sands (Michael Fassbender) and several other detained Irish Republican Army members in the early 1980s, who were determined to live in a Northern Ireland free from British rule.   It's impossible not to make a political film out of this furiously political material, but McQueen chooses to concentrate on the more visceral, tactile elements of the story to drive his point home. HUNGER is one of the more exciting directorial debuts of recent memory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With an epic eye for detail, the drama provides a timely exploration of what happens when body and mind are pushed to the uttermost limit. Directed and co-written by acclaimed British artist Steve McQueen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ifcfilms.com/viewFilm.htm?filmId=1197" target="_blank"&gt;Hunger Official Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showing exclusively at The Kendall for one week only, this film won the Camera d'Or at the 2008 Cannes Film Festival.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start time for the film is approximate.  Exact time will be posted once the Kendall releases its schedule.  After the film, we'll go to Tommy Doyle's for discussion and a well earned meal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As this will be opening night of a highly regarded film, it is strongly suggested that tickets be purchased in advance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will stand near the front of the theater holding a Meetup Sign after the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237504954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hunger</name><id>9991928</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238195700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9991928/</event_url></item>