<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Las Vegas Blvd S</address_1><state>NV</state><zip>89101</zip><lat>36.164035</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>N/A</phone><name>Las Vegas</name><city>Las Vegas</city><id>809103</id><country>us</country><lon>-115.144124</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join the Arizona, California and Utah fans of Red Sox Nation in a special weekend of Sox Watch parties!&lt;br /&gt;RSVP here to show your support, but you must RSVP on either the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NESNN33/"&gt;New England Sports Nation-Nevada &lt;/a&gt;(NESNN) MeetUp Page or on the &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=1219423424&amp;amp;v=app_2344061033&amp;amp;ref=profile#!/event.php?eid=195029678817&amp;amp;index=1"&gt;Facebook Event Page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since December of 2009, Arizona and Nevada have been working together on an event where RSN members from all over the country are invited to Sin City for a set of wicked cool game watch parties (In fact they have invited the Governors' from all 50 states plus Washington DC and all their local fans). Well, the day is almost here! The meeting will be in Las Vegas over Memorial Day weekend which is May 28th-31th. Monday the 31st is Memorial Day, so you'll have added time to have fun and enjoy &amp;quot;Sin City&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some details:&lt;br /&gt;FRIDAY @ 7 PM: We are kicking the weekend off at Cashman Field. The Las Vegas 51's (Toronto's AAA affiliate) will be taking on the Tacoma Rainer's (Seattle's AAA affiliate) and it is FIREWORKS night. The venue is small and the fireworks are spectacular! Easy cab/bus ride and NESNN peeps will pick people up too. Pick-up will be at 6PM, location TBD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY @ 4 PM: Our 1st Red Sox game watch with the RSN gang! NESNN is going to host all of our RSN Friends from out of town at our favorite Irish Pub, McMullan's while the Sox flush the Royals from Fenway Park. Yes, it is &amp;quot;Royal Flush&amp;quot; weekend. There will be $1 off all pints, clam chowda and a few other specials put together by the chef team at McMullan's. Easy cab/bus ride and NESNN peeps will pick people up too. Pick-up will be at 3PM, same location as Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY @ 10:30 AM: ESPN Zone at NY-NY OR &amp;quot;The Pub&amp;quot; at The Monte Carlo! We have it narrowed down and will select the exact location in a few weeks but we need your help. We need a real head count to make the proper arrangements. A message relative to that is forthcoing so please respond. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPECIAL NOTICE: The Natives will be joining NESNN &amp;amp; RSN live from the Bleacher Bar on Sunday via Skype!. Very, very cool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We recommend staying on the south end of the strip (Mandalay Bay, Luxor, NY-NY, Monte Carlo, MGM, etc.) or close to it as we are setting up watch parties around this area. We have been doing a lot of research on this, so if you need tips or updates on good deals, let us know. We will update the deals as we come across them as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DISCOUNT OFFER- If you have not yet reserved a room, Kelly has an employee discount code to be used at The Luxor. This gets you a room for the entire 3 night for $350 with taxes included. Please e-mail him to acquire the code.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GO SOX! &lt;br /&gt;Kelly T.&lt;br /&gt;The Green &amp;quot;Building&amp;quot; Monstah!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly T.</member_name><member_id>8856197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275164605000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>58</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273274038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Sox Nation Invades Las Vegas! </name><id>13418246</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275087600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/13418246/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/1/global_14887297.jpeg</photo_url></item>