<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>No doubt, this discussion could open up the Pandora’s box of opinion in the philosophy of mind from the extremes of “reductionism” (that the mind is purely reducible to material and causal factors as much as is any phenomena of nature) to Cartesian dualism or immaterialism (that mind is a function or aspect of metaphysical and/or spiritual reality that inter-reacts with physical reality).  But this discussion could also be a bit different.  The focus of this discussion, at least initially (because our discussions invariably take on a life of their own once we get going) will not so much concern technical topics similar, for example, to those sometimes entertained by my friends over at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/philosophy-185/"&gt;The Boston Philosophy of Mind Group&lt;/a&gt;.  Equivalencies or similarities with schemas of artificial intelligence are, I think, important and revealing but there is a question about how much it reveals about aspects of the mind as opposed to the brain.   And pure reductionism seems to invariably reach a dead end when it comes to the existential subjectivity of consciousness.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A mind means intelligent consciousness, and “what it is like to be a human being” and to have a human mind would seem to entail many more permutations than do questions concerning “what it is like to be a bat” (referencing Thomas Nagel).  It is hard to think about what a mind is without also considering the meaning of such things as wisdom, self-reflection, emotion, pain, suffering, joy, free will and the relationship of all of  these (and much more) to morality.  Posing the question, “What is it like to have a mind?” opens up a vast realm  of qualitative considerations as opposed the more quantitative comparisons with computers or machines.  I actually believe that machines possessing minds may someday exist, but that will happen only when technology succeeds in making the linkage with consciousness that nature has evolved, in other words, a machine that knows “what it is like” to be what it is.  That will most likely entail pain and emotion and, at more advanced levels, the mental states that are associated with the human mind.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The metaphysical question of whether mind is purely reducible to material facts continues on, but I wonder if the quantitative arguments and techno comparisons sometimes lose sight of the forest for the trees.  Much as arguments over the existence of ‘God’ are literally hopeless and meaningless when the parties do not even agree about what the term ‘God’ means, we may first need to better understand the qualitative argument of “what it is to have a mind&amp;quot; before we can determine whether or not understanding the brain is sufficient for understanding the mind.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture (to the left!)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286641638000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280687240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Are ’Mind’ and ‘Brain’ the Same?  </name><id>14281765</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284159600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/14281765/</event_url></item>