<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As you know summer is Carnival season so it seems timely for us to get in the spirit by heading to Johnny D's once again, to enjoy the lively powerful sound of &lt;a href="http://www.afrobrazil.org/index.php?CLm=07&amp;amp;CLd=31&amp;amp;CLy=2010&amp;amp;c_num=AB&amp;amp;PHPSESSID=182ba1d1520ba57353b2cee3ce72b7c5&amp;amp;CLmAB=8" target="_blank"&gt;Marcus Santos and Bloco AfroBrazil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another reason for the party is to celebrate, fellow Meetup member &lt;a href="http://tomnmusic.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tomn aka Tony Maiella&lt;/a&gt; CD release of Brazilian inspired music&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local band &lt;a href="http://rayhendricksrevival.com/fr_home.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;Ray Hendricks Revival&lt;/a&gt; is also performing original music, which sounds real cool&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to get in the mood, try a refreshing Guarana, Caipirinha, Caju Amigo....well known Brazilian beverages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's yet another chance for you to experience the baddest, loudest, funnest indoor carnival around. Yes, I am a GIGANTIC fan which is apparent because each time this group parties, I place it on the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/"&gt;Portuguese &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonOnyxbirds/"&gt;Onyxbirds&lt;/a&gt; Meetup calendars. Since dinner is an option, I've also invited the Meetup dining group, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/"&gt;Breakfast Brunch Lunch &amp;amp; Dinner&lt;/a&gt;.  Let's pack the place again, because the more the merrier and also your presence will convince Johnny D's to keep the Bloco AfroBrazil party on their schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil is a 12-piece percussion ensemble that always puts on a spectacular show combining traditional Brazilian grooves like Samba and Axé with Funk, Rock, Jazz and even Hip Hop; add to this, (who will get you in rhythm)and you got a recipe for FUN, Brazilian style!! Bring your dance shoes or socks and leave your worries at the door!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your friends....I guarantee a funtastic time, that is if you like your music strong and your party loud.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You must be at least 21&lt;/b&gt; but you don't have to drink, just enjoy each others company and an AMAZING! show.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once the drumming, singing and dancing start, group conversation is difficult. Let's just enjoy the party!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;$10 cash cover charge at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you want to be included in the 8:30 PM dinner reservation you must also order at least $10 (this is in addition to $10 cover) in food and/or drink....otherwise you're welcome to enjoy the show from the bar or dance floor.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you come for just the music, stop by the dinner table to say hello and so you can meet folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/menus/dinner.html"&gt;Johnny D's Dinner Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/parking.html"&gt;Map of Nearby Municiple Parking Lots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WARNING------SOME METERS ARE OPERATIONAL UNTIL 10 PM------WARNING&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge (Harvard Square):  &lt;br /&gt;From Harvard Square travel north on Massachusetts Avenue and pass the porter Square T-Station and the Porter Square Shopping Center on the right. From Porter Square, continue on Massachusetts Avenue through seven traffic lights; at the seventh light turn right onto Cameron Avenue. At end of Cameron turn right onto Holland Street. 5 streets down on the right hand side, turn onto Buena Vista Road. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West (Route 2 or Route 16 Watertown):  &lt;br /&gt;Head west on Route 16 past the Alewife T-Station and continue to the intersection of Massachusetts. Turn right onto Massachusetts Avenue. At the third set of traffic lights, take a left onto Cameron Avenue. *Follow Cameron Avenue directions below. At end of Cameron turn right onto Holland Street. 5 streets down on the right hand side, turn onto Buena Vista Road. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North (traveling South on Interstate 93):  &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 32 (Route 60, Medford Square). Bear right at end of ramp proceeding through Medford Square and follow signs to Route 16 West. Follow Route 16 (for approximately 2 miles from the Route 93 exits) until you reach the intersection of Route 16 and Broadway (Somerville). Turn left onto Broadway. At the second set of traffic lights (Teele Square), bear right onto Holland Street. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South (traveling North on Interstate 93):  &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 31 (Route 16 West/Mystic Valley Pkwy). Follow Route 16 (for approximately 2 miles from the Route 93 exits) until you reach the intersection of Route 16 and Broadway (Somerville). Turn left onto Broadway. At the second set of traffic lights (Teele Square), bear right onto Holland Street. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East:  &lt;br /&gt;Travel on Route 16 West (Revere Beach Pkwy ? Mystic Valley Pkwy ? Alewife Brook Pkwy). Follow Route 16 (for approximately 2 miles from the Route 93 exits) until you reach the intersection of Route 16 and Broadway (Somerville). Turn left onto Broadway. At the second set of traffic lights (Teele Square), bear right onto Holland Street. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Create your route at &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;http://mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;http://www.hopstop.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Subway - Red line to Davis station and exit from the Holland Street side (just turn right after you've exited the turnstiles). Johnny D's is directly across the street as you exit the station.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bus -  Routes: 87, 88, 90, 94 and 96&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Details will be emailed to all those who've RSVPd YES &amp; MAYBE </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282997600000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282818683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brazilian Happy Hour Party at Johnny D's Friday August 27th 8:30 PM</name><id>14547738</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282955400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/14547738/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/3/global_16501411.jpeg</photo_url></item>