<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.367571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-723-2500</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>731371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070306</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: I have been advised that this event is sold out. Also, Ed Wilson will not be present. However, some of the same issues will be discussed at another event on the 16th at the HMNH. See: &lt;a href="http://diningout.meetup.com/362/calendar/8524487/"&gt;http://diningout.meet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The state of the planet is now of major concern. How did we get to where we are today? And where are we headed? With all the attention, effort and expense directed at our environment, it seems astonishing that the root cause of the problem has been largely ignored; that we have, for too long, seen ourselves as being separate from the natural world. - S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Museum of Science's &amp;quot;Celebrity Science Series will explore these questions in this special event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/events_activities/lectures&amp;amp;d=2813"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sustaining Life: A Conversation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;From &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/"&gt;The Museum of Science &lt;/a&gt;event website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Earth's biodiversity — the rich variety of life on our planet — is disappearing at an alarming rate. And while human health depends, to a larger extent than we might imagine, on biodiversity, this essential relationship is rarely addressed. Join this lively discussion about why we can no longer see ourselves as separate from the natural world, nor assume that we will be unharmed by its alteration. Discover why former vice president Al Gore said, 'Sustaining Life is the most complete and powerful argument I have seen for the importance of preserving biodiversity.' Book signing to follow. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lecture with: Eric Chivian, MD, founder, director, Center for Health and the Global Environment, Harvard Medical School; Nobel Peace Prize Laureate; author, Sustaining Life: How Human Health Depends on Biodiversity; Edward O. Wilson, PhD, University Professor Emeritus, Harvard University; world-renowned research scientist; two-time Pulitzer Prize winning author; moderated by Noel Michele &amp;quot;Missy&amp;quot; Holbrook, PhD, Charles Bullard Professor of Forestry and professor of biology, Harvard University.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission: $15. Seating limited; advance purchase is strongly recommended. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy tickets &lt;a href="http://store.mos.org/?action=showevent;event_id=456"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the MFA event. An ad-hoc organizer is needed for this event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224013470000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218137929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Humankind &amp; Biodiversity: What's the connection?</name><id>8498538</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223074800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/8498538/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/6/global_5574950.jpeg</photo_url></item>