<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our August pick is Water for Elephants by Sara Gruen.  Here is the synopisis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As a young man, Jacob Jankowski was tossed by fate onto a rickety train that was home to the Benzini Brothers Most Spectacular Show on Earth. It was the early part of the great Depression, and for Jacob, now ninety, the circus world he remembers was both his salvation and a living hell. A veterinary student just shy of a degree, he was put in charge of caring for the circus menagerie. It was there that he met Marlena, the beautiful equestrian star married to August, the charismatic but twisted animal trainer. And he met Rosie, an untrainable elephant who was the great gray hope for this third-rate traveling show. The bond that grew among this unlikely trio was one of love and trust, and, ultimately, it was their only hope for survival.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in August and I hope you enjoy the book!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the entire room downstairs so you will know us when you come in!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218755615000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Enjoy a relaxing evening out and away from the kids, meet people, talk about fav</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216166849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club August Meetup</name><id>8348194</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218582000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/8348194/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/6/global_4811782.jpeg</photo_url></item>