<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Is your New Year's Resolution to bring in more money from your artwork? If so, this is the class for you! You'll learn how to scan and upload your images to Zazzle. Zazzle is a Print on Demand company, offering artists the opportunity to sell their artwork on a wide variety of products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You upload your artwork to their site, and use their web-based program to fine-tune how you'd like it positioned on various items such as t-shirts, mugs, iPhone cases, posters, and lots more. They have the products made, and you make a royalty - this price is set at 10% by default on most items, but many people find they have the best success adjusting their prices to more like 25%-30%. No hassles with getting the products made or ever shipping anything, you simply get a check whenever you reach their minimum payout of $25. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 In this class you'll learn the basics of setting up a Zazzle shop, creating products and "Quick Create Templates" to create several products with the same artwork at once, and marketing strategies. We'll cover how to market the art you already have, and how to make art that sells. Even if you already have a Zazzle shop, there will be a lot to learn here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $20.00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; Laptop computer, with at least a few high-resolution (600dpi or higher) scans of your artwork. Dinner, if you won't have time to eat before class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*If you don't have a laptop, you may still attend, but you will have an easier time following along if you can do things on your shop as we go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone (18+ only, please).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt; Reserve a place for yourself and any guests by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; If we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons, we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT YOUR INSTRUCTOR:&lt;/strong&gt; A lifelong artist, I've been internet savvy since before most folks knew what the internet was. I've been selling on Zazzle for about a year, but really only devoted about two months to it in that time, and I have brought in over $300. With my advice and whatever time you are able to devote, you can earn money with your artwork too.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through front door or door off parking lot; proceed up stairs to ArtStudio 360 (unfortunately, no elevator)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsi</member_name><member_id>5074581</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332469762000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330642180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Making Money With Your Artwork On Zazzle.com - rescheduled at last! :)</name><id>54567852</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332090000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/54567852/</event_url></item>