<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All,  &lt;br /&gt;Hope everyone is having a smashing summer.  As you all know, we continue to host two locations for our summer season Chi Meetups.   &lt;br /&gt;All future meetings (June and onward) will be held in two locations for the summer season.   &lt;br /&gt;TIME: 1:00PM   &lt;br /&gt;1. Boston Common (near the Boylston T stop/Lowes theater side)   &lt;br /&gt;2. DOGGIE DAY PLAYCENTER (Tremont Street, South end, Boston ...our usual location   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have rec'd some feedback as to a possible 11AM time slot for the BOSTON COMMONS Meetup ONLY!! I have posted a poll on our meetup site to see what the group as a whole prefers. At this time Doggie Day meetup will remain at 1PM and can not be changed. However, if most members prefer we meet at the park at 11am instead of 1PM, we can certainly accommodate for our future meetups. However, the only way to do this would be if there is a reasonable amount of feedback. So please take a moment to vote!  &lt;br /&gt;FYI: Many of our members continue to give charitably to worthy causes in order to aid other animals in need. Most recently, our very own Leticia (Luke an Liea?s mom) has set up the &amp;quot;Happy Tails&amp;quot; Chihuahua group to help raise funds for the MSPCA Walk for Animals to be held on Sept.9th, 2007. This Walk helps benefit over 250,000 animals that the MSPCA-Angell cares for each year. We encourage all members who would like to participate this year and join HAPPY TAILS to help raise funds for a good cause. (For those of you who will be in the commons for the Sept. meetup, this event will also be taking place in the park that day) So, break out those tennis shoes (if you haven?t already) and join us!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE VISIT.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mspca.org/.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mspca.org/...&lt;/a&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the team page for Happy Tails   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mspca.org/.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mspca.org/...&lt;/a&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;Also, congrats to  &amp;quot;DUCKY&amp;quot;  who is now in the Guiness Book of World Records as  The smallest dog living, in terms of height, is a short-coat, male Chihuahua who measured 12.38 cm (4.9 in) tall on 4 June 2007 and is owned by Lisa Messier of Charlton, Massachusetts, United States.  &lt;br /&gt;Ducky and Lisa a members of our group. Kudos!! please keep in mind that Ducky was a product of genetic variation  and was NOT bread to be small or as some like to term &amp;quot;teacup&amp;quot;....he's just a cute little one....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I mention this b/c our site has rec'd some requests and interest about &amp;quot;teacup&amp;quot; breeding....keep in mind &amp;quot;teacups&amp;quot; do not exsist and to breed in terms of size is a terrible unhealthy practice especially for Chihuahuas who ulitimatly suffer from complications. Ducky is just lucky and cute....:)  &lt;br /&gt;See you all next month! Stay well. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184087207000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181498851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua July Meetup</name><id>5875670</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183914000000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/5875670/</event_url></item>