<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Loew's Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>223313</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064316</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As promised, I've re-scheduled David Cronenberg's latest .  A chilly character thriller set in the Russian underworld of London, has elements of murder mystery and gangster melodrama. But in director David Cronenberg's hands, it's a search for moral bearing in a dark and desperate world.&lt;br /&gt;Naomi Watts plays Anna Khitrova, a midwife who works in a London hospital. When a newborn girl and a Russian-language diary come into her possession (the baby's drug-addicted teenage mother dies in childbirth on Anna's watch), she's determined to do right by the baby. But her routine diligence turns into a dangerous ordeal when she meets Semyon (Armin Mueller-Stahl), a Russian restaurant proprietor who seems unusually motivated to translate, and keep, that diary. After uncomfortable run-ins with Semyon's sidekicks, his perpetually besotted son, Kirill (Vincent Cassel), and Nikolai (Viggo Mortensen), his severe, laconic driver, Anna realizes she's dealing with a criminal enterprise.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; Washington Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The actors and the characters merge and form a reality above and apart from the story, and the result is a film that takes us beyond crime and London and the Russian mafia and into the mystifying realms of human nature. &amp;quot; Roger Ebert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.killermoviereviews.com/main.php?nextlink=display&amp;amp;dId=901" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.killermovi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film Tom will be holding a meetup sign and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. Shots of vodka are optional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191876770000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190675004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eastern Promises</name><id>6420400</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191703500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6420400/</event_url></item>