<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>23 Turnpike Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01772</zip><lat>42.296249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cherubino Whole Health Center</name><city>Southborough</city><id>3597242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.497299</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;We have another sponsor, providing space for this great opportunity for you!&amp;nbsp; Thank you Cherubino Whole Health Center!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;If you've been wanting more instruction, tips and techniques for making meditation easy, then this is for you.&amp;nbsp; This is one of the greatest tools for being a successful deliberate creator with law of attraction principles.&amp;nbsp; Hope you'll join us! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;A FREE Class: Meditation Can Be Easy!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Thursday evening, October 6th, 7:15 &amp;ndash;9:00pm, at Cherubino Health Center &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Are you aware of the benefits of meditating, but can&amp;rsquo;t get yourself to do it or you think it&amp;rsquo;s too difficult?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meditation can be one of the easiest and most effective means to living with greater harmony, happiness and well-being. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to peacefully transform your problems, your fears, and any pain and stress in your life into something more positive. And, it's a great way to set or shift into the perfect mood for your day, feeling perfectly aligned with all that you desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t have to sit in silence for long periods of time to gain the multitude of emotional and physical benefits!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come to this Free Introduction to Meditation Class and experience how simple and delightful it can be. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some simple techniques you can do for yourself for any length of time that is comfortable for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to easily get into a meditative state and create pleasurable, "connected" feelings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The difference between active and passive meditation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What you can use meditation for.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will not be doing traditional silent meditations. The class will consist of 2-3 &lt;em&gt;guided&lt;/em&gt; meditations, with discussion and instruction in between. All you have to do is let go and listen to Ann&amp;rsquo;s voice as she leads you through the process, like listening to a good story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;The meditations will leave you totally relaxed with magnificent feelings of peace, love, happiness and hope- essentially feeling really, really good!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 All are welcome. This is a public service event. Please share this with your e-mail lists and groups, your friends, and your family! It's a wonderful evening - like going on a mini retreat! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have never meditated before. It has always been hard for me to get difficult thoughts out of my head. Tonight I really relaxed and seemed to go into another world. It was great. Thanks!&amp;rdquo; Susy C.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Your meditation showed how easy it can be to focus &amp;ndash; something I usually think of as an effort. Thanks, it was very nice!&amp;rdquo; John H.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Space is limited so an RSVP is required.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also, &lt;em&gt;please,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;be considerate of your hosts (that's me and the folks at Cherubino Health!) and honor your "yes" rsvp&lt;/span&gt; by either showing up or letting us know if your plans change by changing your rsvp. Many of you have been wonderful about this, and we very much appreciate your understanding, consideration and support!&amp;nbsp; Thank you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann can coach you to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, you&amp;rsquo;ll become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness you desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class is co-sponsored by Cherubino Health Center and New Possibilities Coaching as a free service to their clients and the surrounding communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Really easy to get to, on Rt. 9 west, on the Framingham/Southborough border; free parking lot, too</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318017154000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316536862000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meditation Can Be Easy!  Free class!</name><id>34270422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317942900000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/34270422/</event_url></item>