<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A winter hike on the Appalachian Trail starting near Lee, MA. The starting point is fixed (see map link below) but the route isn't quite fixed yet but anticipated to be roughly 10 miles. I already have one person who will hike this with me and if there are others game for a winter hike that is a bit ad-hoc you are welcome to join.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call my cell at (860) 836-3400 if you plan to join in and also register here at the hiking site. Since this hike has been opened up to the hiking club last minute I won't be able to check online before it starts. I'm staying in Lee overnight to get an early start. The hike should be over by roughly 4 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've hiked the section of the AT to the south and it would be about 10 miles +/-. I would rather do the section to the north but I have not completed looking at the maps for logistics and will complete that later today. The intent is to hike to the next road crossing to the north that falls somewhere near 10 miles out +/- (with daylight for a maximum of 14 miles out, or 7 hours out).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll position my van at the endpoint to shuttle up to 5 additional people back to the start at the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have:&lt;br /&gt;* A day pack -to carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water.&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots or comfortable winter boots.&lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks -to keep those feet warm even if wet.&lt;br /&gt;* 1 - 2 quarts of water&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food (e.g. G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too.&lt;br /&gt;* Gloves -MUST have available!&lt;br /&gt;* Jacket -BRIGHT color best given hunters (not advised to wear white, dark green, brown, tan, dark grey, or black if possible -see vest below if must wear). Good for 20 - 30 degree weather but also can stow in pack if you get too hot.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat -you loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too.&lt;br /&gt;* Orange vest, bandanna, or something bright orange, bright yellow, or bright red to wear -suggested just in case, so hunters don't make a mistake. I'll have 2 vests in the party already.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snow should not be a big issue due to lack of snowstorms but you might bring gators if you have them to keep your lower legs dry just in case. Ice is more likely to be an issue and any ice gear you have might help out. This includes instep crampons (preferred) or crampons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT parking lot off of the south side of Rte. 20 east of Lee, MA via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=%5b2156%2d2199%5d%20Cape%20St&amp;amp;city=Lee&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01238&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=h0UZsDXphfpgCKqxeORaPmnJxRG1FeGecblSmpdP4%2bmmsAc5oVgSVFpN8%2b7UQvTQ4oDNCd9Ougpn8EOTjBVSzHdv5TTKUSTI53DhqyXBtfw1gvAZwwKzjDzJKCTySSmFtCNM35rCvQ8nVcQG6MEV%2bA%3d%3d&amp;amp;ambiguity=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171466550000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171045942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter hike on the AT near Lee, MA</name><id>5467358</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171116000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5467358/</event_url></item>