<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Millbrook Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03582</zip><lat>44.579847</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(FR 11) 4.5 mi. south of NH 110.</phone><name>Mt Cabot Via The N. Unknown Pond TH</name><city>Stark</city><id>727921</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.397678</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://farm1.static.flickr.com/70/186981878_98449e0b71.jpg?v=0" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This  hike to Mt Cabot will start  on the &lt;b&gt;Millbrook Rd, Stark, NH/ North Unknown Pond trail&lt;/b&gt;,including the trail-less &lt;b&gt;Unknown Pond Peak&lt;/b&gt;, this route takes in the classic reflecting-pool view of the Horn from Unknown Pond, and also climbs the Horn itself, which provides the best views in the Pilot-Pliny Range.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unknown Pond Peak is on the New Hampshire 100 Highest list, which is just east of the pond on Kilkenny trail and the campsite on a southern spur. then back over the &lt;b&gt;Horn&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;the Bulge&lt;/b&gt; (two peaks on the NE Hundred Highest list) to &lt;b&gt;Mt. Cabot&lt;/b&gt;, elevation 4,170 feet,  by the Kilkenny Ridge trail, returning by Bunnell Notch trail(lp: 10.9 miles, 2,800 feet, 6:50). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt; : trailhead is on Mill Brook Rd. (FR 11) 4.5 mi. south of NH 110. There is a sign (hiker symbol) on NH 110 at the beginning of Mill Brook Rd. and a trail sign at the trailhead, which is just east of a bridge across Mill Brook. Parking is available beyond the bridge on the right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mt. Cabot is the most northerly 4000 footer in New Hampshire. Please add time to your driving trip to arrive on time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that  your late or lost. Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury. Waiting for the group at junctions and difficult sections is the rule and makes for a better hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219153100000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217374120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Cabot Via The North Unknown Pond Trailhead</name><id>8437729</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218979800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8437729/</event_url></item>