<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>207 Agnes Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03102</zip><lat>42.993187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Goffstown Rail Trail</name><city>Manchester</city><id>5420022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.497650</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/a/6/event_89692902.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last fall or even the fall before that Liz Peterson was interested in checking out the trails here in order to schedule a future meetup and was looking for some company to go with her. &amp;nbsp; Although it didn't happen&amp;nbsp;then&amp;nbsp;with renewed interest in this hike recently posted by members becoming more active in suggesting hikes a time and date has been picked. &amp;nbsp;This hike will explore all of the Goffstown Rail Trail that runs in between the Henry Bridge Road near the&amp;nbsp;Woman's&amp;nbsp;Prison and Agnes Street near the Nazaire Biron Bridge (Kelly St. Bridge).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;207 Agnes Street is the street address of one of the Piscataquog River Apartment Buildings off of Pinard Street in Manchester, NH. &amp;nbsp;The rail trail is accessible at the end of Agnes St.at the bottom of the hill. &amp;nbsp;Once you turn on to Agnes St. continue straight ahead without turning into any of the Apartment Building parking lots. &amp;nbsp;Parking will be on the roadway. &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Although I know the roadway to the Apartment Buildings is plowed the roadway to the bottom of the hill may not be so we may have to play that part by ear depending on what recent snowstorms do just before the hike. I will check that out if needed and let people know.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As this is a line hike on an easily followed trail anyone not wanting to do the whole 5 miles could turn back early if they start getting tired. &amp;nbsp;It would also be possible with a little prearranging to only do the hike one way (2.5 miles) if another car were parked at the turn around point on Henry Bridge Road before the start of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing the hike one way there are 4 road crossings where there could be vehicular traffic while crossing the road. &amp;nbsp;Doing the hike round trip makes that 8 road crossings. &amp;nbsp;At the turn around point there is a convenience store with bathrooms if anyone wanted to buy something or use the facilities. &amp;nbsp;Doing that would make an extra 2 road crossings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you click on this link you can download and print a trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://goffstownrailtrail.org/"&gt;http://goffstownrailtrail.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329156850000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251817561000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk part of the Rails to Trails in Goffstown 5 mile line hike (2.5 mi. one way)</name><id>16207199</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329062400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/16207199/</event_url></item>