<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On Thursday evening, June 4th, I'll be leading a guided meditations session from 7:15 -8:30 pm, at our usual meetup location, Wayland Wellness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free event for the public, co-sponsored by myself and Wayland Wellness as a public service - our gift to you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Meditating is my number one tool for connecting to Source, creating, and allowing. I can't recommend it strongly enough; so I'll also give you some guidance as to what you can do on your own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven’t experienced my guided meditations, I invite you to experience my unique way of bringing you to a place of total serenity, inner wisdom and alignment. If you have experienced them before, I invite you to experience more again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a chance to take some time to nurture yourself in a deep, expanding way, and to peacefully transform your problems, and any pain and stress in your life into something more positive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These will not be traditional silent meditations. All you’ll have to do is let go and listen to my voice as I lead you through the process, like listening to a good story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;The evening will consist of 2-3 guided meditations, leaving you with magnificent feelings of peace, love, happiness and hope- &lt;b&gt;essentially feeling really, really good and putting you in a great vibrational, allowing state.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;All are welcome. The class is appropriate whether you are a beginner to meditating, or experienced. Please invite others to sign up and join you. Forward this to your friends, family and groups.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required. Please only RSVP if you know you can attend, so no one will be left out unnecessarily, and let us know if your plans change, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;To register, reply to Ann with your name, e-mail, and phone number.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** If you prefer to meditate lying down, please bring whatever you might need to be comfortable: mat, pillow, blanket, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Free evening of Guided Meditations&lt;br /&gt;Thursday evening, June 4th, 7:15 -8:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;Wayland Wellness, 15 East Plain St., Wayland, MA 01778&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245191350000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243741685000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Evening of Guided Meditations</name><id>10533772</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244157300000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/10533772/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>