<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>257 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 629 8717</phone><name>Diesel Cafe</name><city>Somerville</city><id>705077</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Can an ESFJ love an INTP?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003300"&gt;Can a woman who is an introvert and intuitive find love with man who is an extravert and sensing?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;People who prefer sensing like concrete tangible evidence. &amp;nbsp;Those who are intuitive are comfortable with hunches, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Myers-Briggs Type Indicator is a way to look at personality by 4 dichotomy pairs. &amp;nbsp; The Myers-Briggs questionnaire is used to determine where an individual falls on these 4 pairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introvert &amp;amp; Extravert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sensing &amp;amp; Intuition (N)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thinking &amp;amp; Feeling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Judgement &amp;amp; Perception&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Wikipedia explaining introversion and extraversion: &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;"People who prefer extraversion draw energy from action: they tend to act, then reflect, then act further. If they are inactive, their motivation tends to decline. To rebuild their energy, extraverts need breaks from time spent in reflection. Conversely, those who prefer introversion expend energy through action: they prefer to reflect, then act, then reflect again. To rebuild their energy, introverts need quiet time alone, away from activity. The extravert's flow is directed outward toward people and objects, and the introvert's is directed inward toward concepts and ideas. Contrasting characteristics between extraverts and introverts include the following:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Extraverts are action oriented, while introverts are thought oriented. Extraverts seek breadth of knowledge and influence, while introverts seek depth of knowledge and influence. Extraverts often prefer more frequent interaction, while introverts prefer more substantial interaction. &lt;strong&gt;Extraverts recharge and get their energy from spending time with people&lt;/strong&gt;, while &lt;strong&gt;introverts recharge and get their energy from spending time alone&lt;/strong&gt;.[21]"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you can be an ENFP, ISTJ or ESFP, etc. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each letter indicates your preference of the pair. &amp;nbsp;You can be, for example, strongly extraverted. Depending on your test results, you might only slightly more F than T.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These personality traits influence how you see the world, how you relate to others, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Are certain types romantically incompatible? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are certain combinations ideal?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Should you look for a girlfriend or boyfriend &amp;nbsp;based on your Myers-Briggs preferences? &amp;nbsp; How can you make your existing relationship better by knowing your partner's personality preferences better?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start the evening with a review of the characteristics of the dichotomy pairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The date for this Meetup is subject to change.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The date for this Meetup is tentative.  Look for us at the large table all the way in back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim B</member_name><member_id>1113365</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>8</waitlist_count><updated>1321718442000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320468860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Can an ESFJ love an INTP?</name><id>40020582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321660800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/40020582/</event_url></item>