<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte. 66</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06455</zip><lat>41.537853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Higby Mountain</name><city>Middlefield</city><id>138268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.725807</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a nice mostly clifftop hike of about 4.5 miles total or in other words about 3 - 3.5 hrs. This hike is an &amp;quot;out and back&amp;quot; style. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out at the Route 66 parking lot at the western end of Middlefield at 2:00 PM and hike somewhat steeply in places up to the cliffs. Then things mostly level off as we hike the cliffs for about 3/4 mile with occasional descents and ascents. We pass through Preston Notch and hit some more cliffs for about 1/3 mile. We then turn around and return the way we came with some possible quicker bypass trails if time is running short.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are good views to the West. Not as good as the views from the shorter Chauncey Peak and its associated cliffs. Higby Mt. is about 300 feet higher than Chauncey Peak. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring 1 qt. of water and a small backpack to keep layers, snacks, and the water so your hands are free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; to small paved parking lot and starting point (North side or westbound side of Rt. 66/Meriden Rd., Middlefield): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Middlefield&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=%5B625-681%5D+Meriden+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06455&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.5303&amp;amp;longitude=-72.73965&amp;amp;geocode=STREET" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=41.5302, Long.=-72.73965] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions from the Hartford area&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;* Take I-91 South  &lt;br /&gt;* Take the MIDDLE ST./COUNTRY CLUB RD. exit- EXIT 20  &lt;br /&gt;* At the stop sign turn LEFT onto MIDDLE ST and go only a hundred yards or so to another stop sign at COUNTRY CLUB RD.  &lt;br /&gt;* Turn LEFT (East) onto COUNTRY CLUB RD. crossing I-91.  Go, a  &lt;br /&gt;couple of miles to HIGBY RD. which is opposite Moody Elementary School on the right. &lt;br /&gt;* Turn right onto HIGBY RD, going South. &lt;br /&gt;* Go a couple of miles - through a stop sign and to the traffic light at the intersection with ROUTE 66. &lt;br /&gt;* Turn RIGHT (West) onto ROUTE 66/MERIDEN RD. (It's the first intersection where you can go right.)  &lt;br /&gt;* Go what seems like a couple miles - (about 1/2 mile past Guida's Restaurant which is on the right).   &lt;br /&gt;* On the right will be a small parking area at the TRAILHEAD. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map&lt;/b&gt; can be found in the &lt;i&gt;Connecticut Walk Book&lt;/i&gt;, 19th Ed., in either the East or West editions, as map &lt;b&gt;MB-8a&lt;/b&gt; as published by the Connecticut Forest and Park Association. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Topographic map of the area centered on the southern part of Higby Mtn.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.topozone.com/map.asp?lon=-72.73965&amp;amp;lat=41.5350&amp;amp;datum=nad83" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topozone.c...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289070799000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288202568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Higby Mountain in Middlefield CT</name><id>15248752</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288548000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15248752/</event_url></item>