<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Criteria: &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NO WHINING, COMPLAINING, ETC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;ALL HIKERS WILL SHOW UP AND BE READY ON TIME.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All hikers must be able to maintain a minimum pace of three miles an hour for a minimum of four hours. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;starting at Air Line Trailhead (Appalachia) and Valley Way Trailhead (Appalachia) Back to here hike 0.03 mi/1 min/+15 ft on the Air Line The Air Line and Valley Way Trails begin together at Appalachia and cross the Presidential Range Rail Trail to a fork near the edge of the power-line clearing, where the Air Line leads right and Valley Way left. to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+15 ft on the Air Line In 40 yd., just after the Air Line enters the woods, the Link diverges right. to the junction of The Amphibrach and The Link hike 0.15 mi/6 min/+58 ft on the Air Line The Air Line crosses the Sylvan Way. to the junction of Sylvan Way hike 0.40 mi/21 min/+300 ft on the Air Line The Air Line crosses the Beechwood Way and Beechwood Brook. to the junction of Beechwood Way hike 0.20 mi/10 min/+144 ft on the Air Line The Short Line diverges from the trail on the right. to the junction of Short Line hike 0.10 mi/8 min/+173 ft on the Air Line There may be water in a spring 30 yd. left (east) of the path (sign). The trail, continuing south, meets the Randolph Path. to the junction of Randolph Path hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+17 ft on the Air Line The Randolph Trail coincides with the Air Line for 20 yd., then the Randolph Trail leaves on the right. to the junction of Randolph Path hike 1.48 mi/1 hr 35 min/+1673 ft on the Air Line From here the path becomes steeper then eases up and reaches an old and now completely overgrown clearing known as Camp Placid Stream (water unreliable), where the Scar Trail enters on the left, coming up from the Valley Way. to the junction of Scar Trail hike 0.70 mi/41 min/+673 ft on the Air Line The Air Line emerges from the scrub, and, the Upper Bruin comes up left from the Valley Way. to the junction of Upper Bruin entering alpine zone hike 0.10 mi/6 min/+81 ft on the Air Line The Air Line now ascends over the bare, ledgy crest of Durand Ridge known as the Knife-edge, passing over crags that drop off sharply into King Ravine on the right and descend steeply but not precipitously into Snyder Glen on the left. Just south of the little peak called Needle Rock, the Chemin des Dames comes up from King Ravine. to the junction of Chemin des Dames hike 0.30 mi/19 min/+325 ft on the Air Line The Air Line now climbs steadily up the ridge toward Mt. Adams. From several outlooks along the upper part of this ridge, one can look back down the ridge for a fine demonstration of the difference between the U-shaped glacial cirque of King Ravine on the left (west), and the ordinary V-shaped brook valley of Snyder Glen on the right (east). The Air Line Cutoff diverges left (southeast) to Madison Hut, which is visible from this junction in clear weather. to the junction of Air Line Cutoff hike 0.17 mi/14 min/+298 ft on the Air Line The Air Line now departs a little from the edge of the ravine, going left of the jutting crags at the ravine&amp;rsquo;s southeast corner, and rises steeply. There is no single well-beaten footway in this section, so following the trail in poor visibility requires great care. to the junction of King Ravine Trail hike 0.03 mi/2 min/+51 ft on the Air Line The trail passes the Gateway of King Ravine, where the King Ravine Trail diverges right and plunges between two crags into that gulf. Here there is a striking view of Mt. Madison. to the junction of Gulfside Trail hike 0.06 mi/2 min/+10 ft on the Air Line The Gulfside and Air Line coincide for less than 100 yd., then the Air Line branches left toward the summit of Mt. Adams. to the junction of Gulfside Trail hike 0.54 mi/36 min/+641 ft on the Air Line After coinciding with the Gulfside Trail for 70 yd., on the high plateau at the head of the ravine, the Air Line diverges to the left (southwest), passing northwest of Mt. Quincy Adams, up a rough way over large, angular stones to the summit of Mt. Adams, where it meets Lowe&amp;rsquo;s Path and the Star Lake Trail. to Mt Adams Totals Distance 4.30 mi Time 4 hr 23 min Elev Gain +4517 ft Elev Loss -44 ft Elev Change +4473 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.54 mi/36 min/-641 ft on the Air Line The Air Line path begins on the summit of Mt. Adams, at a junction with Lowe&amp;rsquo;s Path and the Star Lake Trail. It travels down a rough way over large, angular stones, diverges to the right (southwest), and passes northwest of Mt. Quincy Adams. The path then enters the Gulfside Trail, turning to the right. to the junction of Gulfside Trail hike 0.06 mi/2 min/-10 ft on the Air Line At the end of this section, on the high plateau between King Ravine and Mt. Quincy Adams, the Air Line enters on the right, descending from Mt. Adams, and the trails coincide for less than 100 yd. to the junction of Gulfside Trail hike 0.30 mi/20 min/-357 ft on the Gulfside Trail Then the Air Line branches left at the top of the steep, open north slope of Mt. Quincy Adams, and just below this junction, the King Ravine Trail branches left from the Air Line. Here there are striking views ahead to Mt. Madison, and into King Ravine at the Gateway a short distance down on the left. to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+13 ft on the Gulfside Trail The Gulfside then descends the slope and passes through a patch of scrub to a junction with the Valley Way and Star Lake Trail about 30 yd. from Madison Hut. to AMC Madison Spring Hut hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+13 ft on the Osgood Trail The Osgood Trail begins at Mt. Madison hut. Then, in 30 yd., the Pine Link joins on the left. From Madison Hut until it reaches the Osgood Tentsite, the Osgood Trail is part of the AT. to the junction of Pine Link hike 0.48 mi/14 min/+546 ft on the Osgood Trail It ascends steeply along the north side of the ridge. It ascends eastward just below the ridge crest and above the steep slopes falling off into Madison Gulf on the right. It then follows the crest of the ridge past several large cairns. to Mt Madison Totals Distance 5.72 mi Time 5 hr 37 min Elev Gain +5116 ft Elev Loss -1078 ft Elev Change +4038 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.30 mi/21 min/-410 ft on the Watson Path The Watson Trail begins at the summit of Mt Madison. Id descends over rough and shelving stones, crosses the Pine Link and traverses the grassy, stony back of the ridge before entering the scrub. to the junction of Pine Link hike 0.90 mi/1 hr 17 min/-1637 ft on the Watson Path The trail soon attacks the steep flank of Gordon Ridge on a very steep and rough footway. to the junction of Lower Bruin leaving alpine zone hike 0.10 mi/4 min/-9 ft on the Watson Path The Watson Path crosses brook at the foot of Duck Fall and the Lower Bruin branches to the right toward the Valley Way. to the junction of The Brookside hike 0.50 mi/30 min/-506 ft on the The Brookside The Brookside Trail diverges from Watson Path a short distance north of Bruin Rock. It descends sharply then climbs toward the brook. It continues along a wild and beautiful part of the brook, with cascades and mossy rocks in a fine forest. Below this point, the Brookside becomes steeper and rougher (though recent intensive trail work has significantly improved the footing). Again, the trail runs close to the brook, passing Salmacis Fall (limited view north from the top). to the junction of Kelton Trail hike 1.16 mi/1 hr 3 min/-871 ft on the The Brookside The Kelton Trail leaves to the right as the Brookside begins to climb along the west bank with good footing, rising well above the brook through a fine birch forest, with occasional views through the trees to cliffs on the valley wall on the other side of the brook. to the junction of Inlook Trail and Randolph Path hike 0.01 mi/1 min/0 ft on the The Brookside The Brookside and the Randolph Path cross the brook together on large stepping-stones (the former bridge at this crossing was washed out in 2005 and will not be replaced). to the junction of Randolph Path hike 0.03 mi/1 min/-13 ft on the The Brookside The Brookside ends at Valley Way about 30 yd. above the Valley Way&amp;rsquo;s junction with the Beechwood Way. to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.02 mi/1 min/-25 ft on the Valley Way The Valley Way is soon joined from the left by the Beechwood Way. It then leads nearer Snyder Brook. to the junction of Beechwood Way hike 0.20 mi/11 min/-178 ft on the Beechwood Way Beechwood Way begins at Valley way. It crosses the Air Line. to the junction of Air Line hike 0.40 mi/21 min/-300 ft on the Air Line The Air Line crosses the Beechwood Brook and Beechwood Way. to the junction of Sylvan Way hike 0.15 mi/6 min/-58 ft on the Air Line The Air Line crosses the Sylvan Way. to the junction of The Amphibrach and The Link hike 0.02 mi/1 min/-15 ft on the Air Line The Link diverges right and Air Line leaves the woods to the junction of Valley Way hike 0.03 mi/1 min/-15 ft on the Air Line Air Line passes through a power-line clearing and reaches a fork where the Valley Way joins from the right. The two trails coincide and cross the Presidential Range Rail Trail before terminating at Appalachia. to Air Line Trailhead (Appalachia) and Valley Way Trailhead (Appalachia) Totals Distance 9.54 mi Time 9 hr 35 min Elev Gain +5213 ft Elev Loss -5213 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A CAR</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308489444000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307378143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TO KNOCK ANOTHER ONE OFF THE LIST</name><id>21170851</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308400200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/21170851/</event_url></item>