<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>An Impromptu Philosophizer is a casual meeting at a cafe or pub that may or may not have a specific topic, and may even be scheduled “on the spur of the moment!&amp;quot;  It's great to know that there is now a way for philosophically minded people to meet but with no particular agenda other than that of satisfying the need to talk about what's on your mind.  Whether the interest or concern involves current events or politics, cultural or intellectual issues, personal stuff, pure philosophy or whatever else is on your mind we can all benefit from sharing philosophical perspectives.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fred or I announce IP meetups as they materialize from the flow of our respective schedules, but please feel free to let either of us know if you have a hankering for an IP because we just might be able to accommodate your need to philosophize!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Therapy for the sane,&amp;quot; a term used by Gerd Achenbach (founder of the modern &lt;a href="http://www.integralhypnosis.com/philosophical_counseling.htm" target="_blank"&gt;philosophical counseling&lt;/a&gt; movement), may partially suggest the Impromptu Philosophizer concept but it is more multifaceted than, say, an occasional &amp;quot;therapy&amp;quot; session after a trying day.  IPs are designed to be fun, engaging and unique opportunities for creating a near spontaneous venue to meet other group members for the purpose of sharing thoughts, ideas and concerns from a philosophical perspective.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Impromptu Philosophizers are spontaneous, existentially driven meetings and discussions.  Of course, continue to check back often for the scheduling of the somewhat more structured, topical meetings  that are regularly scheduled by Boston Area Philosophy Discussions!     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPECIAL NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;  By its very nature, an Impromptu Philosophizer may often have a small turnout. Accordingly, in order to prevent situations in which the event host arrives and there is no one else who shows up, in some cases those who 'Yes&amp;quot; RSVP may be asked to email a further confirmation.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture (Look for the Meetup sign).  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282094091000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280334706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Impromptu Philosophizer (IP)</name><id>14241450</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281999600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/14241450/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/a/global_15047834.jpeg</photo_url></item>