<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi, Everybody -     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a great hike and picnic lunch at Mount Agamenticus (actually just a hill with an elevation of 692 feet!). We'll hike the Mount A area and then head for another hiking trail and picnic in a quiet wooded area a short distance away. I'm estimating the combined hike and picnic will last about     &lt;br /&gt;3 - 3 1/2 hours or so with about 6 miles of total hiking.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The directions are at the end of this listing:&lt;/i&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to the Mount Agamenticus Conservation Area:     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.agamenticus.org/recreation.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.agamenticus.org/recreation.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.agamenticu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just click on the various tabs in the left column for more details.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who choose to do so, you can head to the beach after the hike and continue to enjoy the rest of the day near the ocean (although the beach area is super crowded at this time of year).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pack along a nice, big picnic lunch, beverages - and a can of bug spray!    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For your picnic lunch, I would recommend packing it in a cooler with ice and leaving it in the car for the first part of the hike.   We will come through the parking lot again before heading off to the picnic.  You can pick up your lunches then and they will still be cold.  Bring beverages though for the entire hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy     &lt;br /&gt;RandyS@maine.rr.com    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions:&lt;/u&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 95 north over the big bridge to Exit 7 just before the    &lt;br /&gt;toll booths. (NOTE: There are two Exit 7s -one in Portsmouth,    &lt;br /&gt;NH before the bridge and the one in Maine before the toll    &lt;br /&gt;booths. It‘s that second Exit 7 - the one in Maine - that we're    &lt;br /&gt;looking for).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 7 - bear left to end of the ramp - stop sign - take    &lt;br /&gt;left - and then the next immediate available right (the road    &lt;br /&gt;ends at that point, so you have to turn right), and go    &lt;br /&gt;approximately 6.3 miles (the name of this road is Chases Pond    &lt;br /&gt;Road which becomes Mountain Road - same road; just keep going    &lt;br /&gt;straight). You will come to a small parking lot at the base of    &lt;br /&gt;Mount Agamenticus (the paved road ends at this point).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the lot is full (and it’s small so it usually is), you can    &lt;br /&gt;park on either side of the road. I’ll be waiting in a silver    &lt;br /&gt;Subaru Forester across the street for the first couple of    &lt;br /&gt;hikers, then after that we will gather at the back edge of this    &lt;br /&gt;parking lot, towards the large boulders under the trees.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to meeting you on Sunday.   Weather looks to be perfect!    &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For the first few hikers, we will meet near my vehicle (silver Subaru Forester) across the street from the parking lot. After that, we will gather at the edge of the parking lot near the big rocks</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281378297000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278407278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and Picnic Lunch in York!</name><id>14013717</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281276000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/14013717/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/a/global_8053098.jpeg</photo_url></item>