<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>137 Barton Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01775</zip><lat>42.403980</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Collings Foundation</name><city>Stow</city><id>2035621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.507484</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The only event of this type - in the world. &amp;ndash; Don&amp;rsquo;t miss it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an event for all ages and genders!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Battle for the Airfield Picture this: Allied Forces knew the exact coordinates of the German encampment. The night before an elite German force over took a small grass airstrip just a few hundred feet away. The Allied Forces had to gain control of this airfield so they could fly in much-needed supplies. - It was going to be a tough fight. How will the battle end? Will the Allied troops be able to gain control of the airfield and further their advancement? You will have to be here to find out. The Collings Foundation will host a Living History event you will never forget. You will be able to see original equipment from WWII in action. Everything from the cooking utensils to M1 rifles is original.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost at gate: $20 Adults. Paypal is NOT available for this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 1:45, tour the auto and airplane museums and then catch the 3:00 show (early arrivals are recommended). Afterward, we will regroup and travel to Nancy's Airfield Cafe for a 5PM Gourmet Dinner!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP for show and/or dinner by Oct 6th!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318280984000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315239888000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Collings Foundation Hosts: WWII Reenactment and WWII Living History Weekend </name><id>32315642</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318182300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/32315642/</event_url></item>