<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.316738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Vibrant Health Family Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>10954002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363457</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>396.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;Inner Way Weight Loss Group:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;A special focus group and class for aligning your mind, body and spirit to allow for a lasting, happy, healthy, satisfied, naturally slender you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Note: Please do not just use the RSVP meetup feature. Because of the various options, registration must be done directly with Ann, as described below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to lose weight and be more healthy and slender?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does it seem like the only way to do so will mean deprivation and effort, needing will power and discipline, and that it will be hard and unpleasant?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It doesn’t have to be that way; and it’s certainly not the law of attraction way!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;As you’re probably well aware, most weight loss is approached by changing outer behaviors only, changing what and how you eat and getting you to exercise. Motivation is often handled by having you pay, having structure, and having some accountability, or by using will power and discipline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But, as you may have also discovered, these strategies alone are not typically lasting or easy or pleasurable!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;This is because your inner emotional factors involved and the necessary mental strategies are not adequately taken care of. Nor is effective,lasting internal motivation created. When getting and staying slim and healthy means deprivation and endless effort, the weight eventually comes back; and you’re not very happy in the process, either! In the law of attraction world, we call this inner resistance, and a lack of being aligned with and not allowing what you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;I want to offer you the external structure, support and motivations AND to use my coaching expertise to address your inner needs for an easier way to a lasting, happy, healthy, satisfied, naturally slender you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this Inner Way Weight Loss group, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;create lasting, intrinsic motivation strategies that work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;resolve any internal “tug-of-war” conflicts that make your weight loss an unnecessary struggle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;learn and use effective mental strategies to make your weight loss easier&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;learn forgiveness and unconditional love and acceptance of yourself&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;learn how to effectively overcome your triggers and challenges with food, and to change your habits that don’t support what you want&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;change your beliefs that are contributing to being overweight to ones that support you in being naturally and easily healthy, happy, and slender&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;learn and adopt eating strategies of naturally slender people so you can become one, too&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;learn more effective strategies for preventing and dealing with the stress and emotions that can lead to unhealthy habits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;And, of course, being who I am, we’ll be adding in some guided meditations and spiritual components, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;This isn’t about what foods you should and shouldn’t eat or measuring this and that (aren’t you sick of that?). We’ll be using some of the world’s most advanced mind and behavior-changing techniques and you’ll have practical steps in an easy-to-follow program to permanently change how you think about and behave around food from a new, natural, inner way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you approach weight loss in this deep and profound way, not only will you drop pounds, you’ll also become happier and more fulfilled in general. Inner Way will bring about a powerful transformation that will leave you deeply satisfied on the inside and slim and healthy on the outside.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I’ve started this adventure for myself, and it has been so insightful, life changing, easy and effective! I’m so excited about continuing it with you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The on-line program I took that I’m drawing this from (with the leader’s blessing and support) was only six weeks; and it was way, way too short and too impersonal. This is why I’ve designed the Inner Way class to take place over 12 weeks and in-person. &lt;em&gt;Mind you, this can all be pleasurable and easy; in fact, very much so!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Each week, we'll be doing exercises together from a fantastic book, along with some of my own additions, share and support one another and develop close relationships, and we’ll grow and succeed together! I love it! I’m feeling so much positive energy around this. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;I promise you that this will do way more than just change your relationship with food and your body. It will change your life.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Logistics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When: Thursday evenings, 7:00 - 8:30pm, January 24th through April 11th (12 weeks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where: Dr. Annie Jackman’s Vibrant Health Family Wellness, 33 Main St., Wayland, MA (out back, between Rite Aid and JJ McKays, at the intersections of Routes 27 and 30, with lots of easy parking)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tuition options: $396 if paid in full, or $145/mo. for 3 months.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus options to further guarantee your success:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discounted private coaching sessions with me for $125/session &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;OR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*** &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; private coaching sessions for only $300 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;if paid with tuition&lt;/span&gt;, which comes to: $696 if paid in full, or $245/mo. for 3 months.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Group sessions will be recorded and sent to you in MP3 format, in case you have to miss a session or want to listen again (like my guided meditations!).&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;We’ll have a private on-line group discussion forum for ongoing connection and support.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please share this information with anyone who you think might be interested and would align with this approach! (Doing this with a friend would be super awesome!) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I’m limiting the group size to 20 max., so if you’re interested, I encourage you to sign up asap. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are the steps to take to register.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This is not a week by week meetup. We want a consistent group of people following the course structure for maximum support and results. Thus, you must commit to participating in the full 12 week program, other than occasional exceptions: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;1. E-mail me at &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com&lt;/span&gt; with your name, address, and phone numbers where you can be reached in case of any unforeseen class changes (i.e. stormy weather or illness)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;2. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Let me know which option you’d like&lt;/span&gt;. I’ll send you the appropriate PayPal link and instructions.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;3. Make your payment to reserve your spot!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Let’s do this together! To a naturally happy, healthy, slender you! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Warm heart, &lt;br /&gt;

 Ann &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>at intersection of Rt. 27 and 30, in back parking lot, between Rite Aid and JJ McKay's</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359078011000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357236818000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inner Way Weight Loss Group: To align and allow a happy, naturally, slender you</name><id>dczjcfyrcbgc</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359072000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/97708412/</event_url></item>