<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth&lt;/b&gt; will begin its meeting is from 6:00pm to 6:45pm. Discussion for our agenda is welcome. You can write to members at this meet-up site by emailing - 9-11-270@meetup.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginning at 7:00 pm, Valley 9/11 Truth is publicly screening a 2008-released film, The Reflecting Pool, but not the film itself, but its DVD';s bonus feature, &amp;quot;Revealing the Sources.&amp;quot; This includes a commentary track revealing the sources used in making &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;the first investigative drama to challenge official version of 9/11&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.reflectingpoolfilm.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Reflecting Pool&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/a&gt; is about an investigation of the 9/11 events by a Russian-American journalist and a father of a 9/11 victim implicates the US government in the attacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALEX PROKOP (Jarek Kupsc), a successful journalist, receives a rare 9/11 video tape revealing new information about the attack. The footage was sent by PAUL COOPER (Joseph Culp), a driven researcher, whose daughter died on 9/11. Sensing a good story, Prokop travels with Cooper to New York and Washington, DC, where they uncover suppressed information implicating the US Government in the attacks. As Cooper introduces Prokop to key eye-witnesses, the façade of the &amp;quot;official story&amp;quot; begins to crumble. Prokop hears accounts of underground explosions in the Twin Towers moments before their collapse and discovers that the firm providing WTC security was run by the President's brother.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We follow Alex and Cooper as they investigate the inexplicable collapse of the 47-story WTC Building Seven, disprove the implausible airliner &amp;quot;attack&amp;quot; on the Pentagon, and uncover the illegal destruction of physical evidence from Ground Zero.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The pressure builds as the FBI intimidates Alex's editor, McGUIRE, (Lisa Black) to reveal key sources ? while the magazine's corporate investors threaten to kill the entire story. Plagued by the ghosts of his Communist childhood and trying to uphold the independence of American journalism, Alex's search for the truth leads to a dangerous and shocking realization!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE REFLECTING POOL is an intense, sobering investigation into the most controversial tragedy of our time. Drawn from established sources and based on verifiable facts, THE REFLECTING POOL is a thought-provoking study of a search for truth and the profound consequences of not looking for it any further than the nightly news.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the bonus feature, revealing the sources, which has a running time of about one hour and forty-five minutes, open discussions will take place. People can &lt;a href="http://www.reflectingpoolfilm.com/reflectingpoolbuydvd.htm" target="_blank"&gt;purchase a DVD of the film for $15.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a list of films, many screened by Valley 9/11 Truth, see Flyby News' &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1053728158,12232," target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;FILMS THAT MAKE A DIFFERENCE!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, for a good overview, see: &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1014738186,11057," target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Bush Conspiracy &amp;amp; 9/11 Investigative Reports&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The community meeting space is in the back of the building of the Woodstar Cafe.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209766003000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Unity and support for such a critical issue could be key for our survival, freedom, and well being.</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203029619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Reflecting Pool - Revealing the Sources</name><id>7332819</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209592800000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/7332819/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/5/global_3479317.jpeg</photo_url></item>