<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A 6.0 mile loop hike of moderate difficulty mostly on the Ragged Mountain Preserve Trail but also a little under a half of the hike on a part of the Metacomet Trail. There will be cliffs, water views, and a modest amount of up/down on the traprock ridge. Plenty of angular rocks as is common on these ridges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go should have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack - To carry water and keep your hands free &lt;br /&gt;

 * Hiking boots &lt;br /&gt;

 * 2 quarts of water &lt;br /&gt;

* Bug spray - Ticks &amp;amp; mosquitoes are out &lt;br /&gt;

* Hiking poles would be helpful&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM at the parking area off of West Lane in Berlin. &lt;strong&gt;Parking may be limited so RSVP's are limited.&lt;/strong&gt; We would finish up no later than about 1:30 PM but a good chance we will be done a bit earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;(watch for dirt parking area on north side shoulder, roughly 499 West Ln, Berlin, CT): &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://mapq.st/15zzx1M"&gt;http://mapq.st/15zzx1M&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Map is in "&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Connecticut Walk Book: West&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;" 19th ed., by Connecticut forest and Park Association as map&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ME-3b&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;on page 180.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Ford Escape SUV, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368996875000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368305027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Ragged Mountain in Berlin CT</name><id>118919992</id><duration>16200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368968400000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/118919992/</event_url></item>