<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 New Park Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.747871</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bow Tie Cinema Palace 17 &amp; Odyssey Theater</name><city>Hartford</city><id>10782802</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.712669</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You and a guest are cordially invited to a complimentary special advance screening of Fox Searchlight’s upcoming film TRANCE, a thriller directed by Academy Award winner Danny Boyle and starring James McAvoy, Rosario Dawson and Vincent Cassel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, April 9 &lt;br /&gt;

7:00pm &lt;br /&gt;

Bow Tie Palace&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To download a complimentary pair of passes, click here: &lt;a href="http://ow.ly/jKSe7" class="linkified"&gt;http://ow.ly/jKSe7&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

or go to www.gofobo.com/RSVP and enter the code: S5ZGND16&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are complimentary, but expected to go quickly as there are only a limited number available. Please arrive early as seating will be available on a first come, first served basis and is not guaranteed. This film is rated R, no one under 17 will be admitted without a parent or legal guardian. &lt;br /&gt;

 Running Time: 101 minutes &lt;br /&gt;

Rating: R for sexual content, graphic nudity, violence, some grisly images, and language. &lt;br /&gt;

Visit the official website: www.trancethemovie.com &lt;br /&gt;

Directed by: Danny Boyle &lt;br /&gt;

Screenplay by: Joe Ahearne, John Hodge &lt;br /&gt;

Produced by: Christian Colson &lt;br /&gt;

Cast: James McAvoy, Vincent Cassel, Rosario Dawson &lt;br /&gt;

Simon (James McAvoy), a fine art auctioneer, teams up with a criminal gang to steal a Goya painting worth millions of dollars, but after suffering a blow to the head during the heist he awakens to discover he has no memory of where he hid the painting. When physical threats and torture fail to produce answers, the gang’s leader Frank (Vincent Cassel) hires hypnotherapist Elizabeth Lamb (Rosario Dawson) to delve into the darkest recesses of Simon’s psyche. As Elizabeth begins to unravel Simon’s broken subconscious, the lines between truth, suggestion, and deceit begin to blur. &lt;br /&gt;

 TRANCE Opens in Select Theatres April 12 &lt;br /&gt;

 Rated R for sexual content, graphic nudity, grisly images, violence and language.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365560257000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365105213000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Complimentary advance screening passes TRANCE </name><id>112707622</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365548400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/112707622/</event_url></item>