<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>One of the most effective ways to get into a positive vibrational alignment for deliberately creating is to be in a state of appreciation.  November seems like a most appropriate month to make this the focus topic for our meeting!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll begin the meeting leading everyone through a gratitude meditation which, of course, is sure to leave you feeling good and is always the main intention of our meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we'll talk about how and why to practice appreciation as a key means to feeling good and manifesting what you desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, we'll also spend time on group support and coaching on questions and issues you want to bring to our meeting.  This has been a most valuable time for everyone at our previous meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're also going to try something new this month regarding our schedule.  Since it has seemed like we could go on all night with more group discussion time, we're offering the option for you to arrive a 1/2 hour early with your own dinner (or not) so we can have extra time to chat as a group while we eat.  So we'll have a dinner/discussion time from 6:30 -7:00 pm, and have the &amp;quot;meeting&amp;quot; from 7:00 - 9:00pm.  If you can't make it at 6:30, it's okay.  We'll still be having our group coaching time during the last part of the meeting, too.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Waiting a full month to do this again has been too long! Can't wait to be and create with you all!  Please RSVP asap, and also PLEASE invite others to join you!  &lt;i&gt;If&lt;/i&gt; your plans change after RSVP'ing, please be considerate enough to e-mail us so we won't be unnecessarily waiting for you to arrive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With appreciation and joy,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be upstairs.  Go to back of front lobby for stairway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229475727000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224634015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metro West Law of Attraction/"Good Vibrations" November Meetup</name><id>9006524</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227052800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/9006524/</event_url></item>