<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;August 15th, 1971. The United States of America changed on this date. Richard Nixon removed all ties of the U.S. Dollar to any tangible standard and Dr. Ron Paul decided to run for a seat in the United States Congress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This date, in two forms, changed our culture. One for setting up the cycle of booms and busts, inflation and debt, while the other split the kindling for the fires of Liberty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The "Resulting Flames" still burn today. Our global and domestic financial structure is crumbing, yet the notions o...f Liberty flare stronger than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between August 13th and August 15th we now have a chance of giving Concord, New Hampshire a voice for Liberty in the State House. Ron Noyes (National Delegate for Ron Paul) and his candidacy for State Representative faces a steep climb, one that will be difficult at every step but a climb that we in the Liberty Movement have gladly grown accustom to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With your help, we can throw water on the negative "Resulting Flames" of broken monetary policy and throw gasoline on the genuine and lasting "Resulting Flames" of liberty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join me by contributing any amount you are able to during these three days. Please do so, not only for the campaign, but also the "Resulting Flames" of Freedom, Prosperity and Liberty that were set in motion on August 15th."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://noyesfornh.chipin.com/noyes-for-nh-money-bomb" class="linkified"&gt;http://noyesfornh.chipin.com/noyes-for-nh-money-bomb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345057884000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344463785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Noyes for NH Rep "Resulting Flames" Money Bomb </name><id>76924342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345046400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/76924342/</event_url></item>