<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Lexington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.503330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Temple Shalom Emeth</name><city>Burlington</city><id>2858801</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.200432</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This dance is cancelled due to lack of enrollment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minimum attendance to schedule dance party is 80. Minimum of 30 men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Values: To be nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and to be respectful to everyone. We utilize private dance parties as a vehicle to meet other singles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purpose is to socialize with similar people of our age (30-65) who are searching for a lifetime partner. Have fun meeting old and new friends. Circulate, talk to everyone. If someone is alone go up to them and say hi! Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a Yes Dance - I ask you to be respectful and say yes to anyone who asks you to dance once. Please understand this is our number one value. If you are able to say yes, then this is a great event for you to attend. You are coming because you got this email, and this is your invitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please invite other friends, particularly men. My personal goal is to have an equal amount of men and women. We are very close on equal numbers of men and women. The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable dance party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***The entry fee is $15.00 plus wine or food assignment listed below. Pay at door. Of course if you are unable to bring anything, then your entry fee will be $30.00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti Location is in a warm, loving and relaxing environment. "Dress code - "professional casual 7:30PM - 11:00pm Sat. August 20th, 2011 Temple Shalom Emeth, 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minimum attendance to schedule dance is 80&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- DJ will be present&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pizza Buffet[/b] which will start at 8:30PM&amp;nbsp; Open bar- wine/beer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your last name begins with the following letter please bring the following.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food assignments will be given two days prior to dance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either Pizza, bottle of wine or dessert I will ask you to bring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location and Directions Temple Shalom Emeth, 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;128 North Exit 32B Middlesex Turnpike (Burlington/Arlington) At the end of the ramp turn right onto Middlesex Turnpike - on the left is Barnes/Noble After the Burlington Mall turn right on to Burlington Mall Rd. - on left is Longs Jewelers Take left after you pass Kohl&amp;rsquo;s on your left which is Lexington Street Temple Shalom Emeth is on your left at16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two parking lots on the right side of building. Enter through the side entrance at the end of the building. Third parking lot is two houses up at Church - we have permission. Fourth parking lot is across the street - McGinnis Ave., - Mt Hope Church. See you on Saturday, August 20th at 7:30pm---- 7:30pm Party begins Food served at 8:00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best is yet to be!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313952166000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306354809000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Private Singles Dinner Dance Party 30-65</name><id>19719871</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313883000000</time><rsvp_limit>105</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/19719871/</event_url></item>