<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am planning a&amp;nbsp;looping 6.7 mile hike through Bigelow Hollow and around Breakneck Pond to the north-east. I haven't offered this version of the hike in a couple years or so and it would be great to offer it to you. This is a familiar area with beautiful rolling terrain, many water features,&amp;nbsp;and a fairly high and thin ridge. If time and conditions allow,&amp;nbsp;those inclined&amp;nbsp;might take a quick dip in the pond to cool off at the half-way point. This is also a great place for lunch. We should be out for about&amp;nbsp;5 hours so done by about 3 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please plan on bringing water, snacks, sunscreen, and a lunch for this adventure. Hiking&amp;nbsp;boots are strongly recommended. We usually can expect a good deal of bugs so bug spray is a must! You might want something to wear for the fairly quick dip if you are inclined or at least something that dries quick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bigelow Hollow State Park and the adjoining Nipmuck State Forest offer over 9,000 acres of recreation opportunities, including miles of hiking trails and an 18-acre pond in Eastern Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is likely that there will be a charge to enter the park which is $9.00 per vehicle. I will see if anyone wants to condense at a carpool location&amp;nbsp;leaving Vernon, CT&amp;nbsp;at 9 AM. Watch for comments on this event for this carpool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you enter the park, head up the road and we will meet at the 2nd parking area along the road from the entrance, which is a picnic area. It will be on your left side as you drive in (it has the water pump, 2 dark colored outhouses, and a bulletinboard). On the map, it is the 3rd marked parking area from the entrance. If you reach the boat launch and the end of the accessible road you've gone one parking area too far. In the event the parking area is full, we will still meet at that location as the trailhead we are using is there. Please allow some extra time in case you need to walk to this area from available parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that there is virtually NO CELL reception at the park!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Location/directions for entrance to Bigelow Hollow State Park&lt;/strong&gt; (off of Rte. 171 in Union, CT):
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Bigelow+Pond&amp;amp;city=Stafford+Springs&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.99204&amp;amp;longitude=-72.131743&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=13881594"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Bigelow+Pond&amp;amp;city=Stafford+Springs&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.99204&amp;amp;longitude=-72.131743&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=13881594&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Hiking map&lt;/strong&gt;:
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/big_nipm.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/big_nipm.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Rough indication of topography&lt;/strong&gt; via Google Maps (click Terrain button, if needed): 
&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=Bigelow+Hollow+State+Park,+Union,+CT&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.002908,-72.132711&amp;amp;spn=0.016775,0.023947&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=A"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=Bigelow+Hollow+State+Park,+Union,+CT&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.002908,-72.132711&amp;amp;spn=0.016775,0.023947&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=A&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;More information on the park&lt;/strong&gt;:
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325174&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325174&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Count Me In" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a dark green Dodge Caravan minivan with CT plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311055311000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309996400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Bigelow Hollow SP &amp; Nipmuck SF, Union CT</name><id>24823041</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310824800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/24823041/</event_url></item>