<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Meetup Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Cumberland Farms, 2643 Hartford Ave, Johnston RI&amp;nbsp; at 0800am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guys, I'm going to plan a day trip to the scenic Litchfield Hills in Northwest CT. 
&lt;strong&gt;Several portions of this ride were called some of the most scenic rides in America!&lt;/strong&gt; We will ride through long rolling hills, beautiful farmland, quaint small towns, lakes/rivers, and of course nice twisties!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will take Route 6 through RI and across CT almost entirely to Litchfield. I take Route 6 very often to Hartford for my job and it's a nice country road where we can really twist the throttle to Hartford. From Litchfield we'll take 202 west to 45 north to 341 west to 7 north and then finally on to 44 east. Once we reach 44 we'll take that back across CT to RI. Route 44 from Hartford to RI is also designated as a scenic road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Basically this whole ride will be backroads and country settings!!&lt;/strong&gt; We will be riding over 400 miles, so I'd like to meetup early. We'll meet at 7:00am and kick stands are up by 7:15am. This is an all day ride, I'm planning to be back in Boston by 6 or 7pm. Any questions or suggestions call me 617 817 1136. Don't miss out! Check out the Google Map below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?msid=205405326991230603662.0004a6e930b475522bb81&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;ll=41.965617,-72.298279&amp;amp;spn=0.896514,2.463684"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?msid=205405326991230603662.0004a6e930b475522bb81&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;ll=41.965617,-72.298279&amp;amp;spn=0.896514,2.463684&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason Kuriakose</member_name><member_id>14553066</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310396139000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><id>1535765</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309521308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lovely Litchfield Hills and Central CT Tour Joint Ride w/Boston Tier 1 Riders</name><id>24207821</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310299200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/events/24207821/</event_url></item>