<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In this meeting of the Boston Dreamers, acclaimed Boston area author and astral traveler Kurt Leland will share tips and techniques for remembering and recording dreams, interpreting dreams, and becoming lucid in dreams, based on nearly thirty years of keeping a daily dream journal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kurt is a veteran explorer of the worlds of dreams and afterlife. In 1996 Kurt was featured in the Top 100 Psychics in America. Kurt's 2001 book &amp;quot;Otherwhere: A Field Guide to Nonphysical Reality for the Out-of-Body Traveler&amp;quot; layed out many of the ground rules for understanding the symbolism and levels of lucidity found in dreams, astral travels, and other adventures in consciousness. This was followed in 2002 by &amp;quot;The Unanswered Question: Death, Near-Death, and the Afterlife&amp;quot;, which made fascinating comparisons between the cosmologies of the Tibetan Book of the Dead, the Egyptian Book of the Dead, Emanuel Swedenborg's visions, and the NDE accounts of people who have clinically died and returned. Kurt's extensive research into Seth, Theosophy, and the planes of existence has led to a soon-to-be self-published book on the multidimensionality of our humanness and how to develop the inner senses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kurt's website at www.kurtleland.com features several valuable articles on working with your dreams and dream interpretation. His system for identifying the eight archetypal dream characters is both unique and remarkably useful, so questions on that and other topics will be welcomed. For the record, the eight characters are: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Numen: a representation of the soul, often appearing as a wise older person, sometimes as one's parents&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soma: a representation of the body consciousness, often appearing as an animal, such as a horse or a dog&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Witness: the part of you that watches the dream action, sometimes from within the dream itself, often appearing as a neutral observer, sometimes as a teacher or other person who represents memory &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participant: the part of you that acts in the dream--the hero &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Counterpart: reflections of you in other people, including past, present, and future selves, also your essential selves (those associated with activities that are related to your life purpose or are especially important to you), close friends, people you admire, etc.--this is the largest category of dream character&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anima/Animus: a representation of your sexuality, usually taking the form of whatever sort of person you find sexually attractive&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shadow: the portion of consciousness that resists the learning required of you by the soul, often represented by a criminal type, an antagonist, a dark or sinister person, a dictator, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Delimiter: the portion of consciousness responsible for establishing, maintaining, or dismantling belief systems, or identifying and eliminating problems created by the shadow, often represented by the legal profession, government officials, judges, the police&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting: Tuesday, November 3, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;7 pm - 9:00 pm (Two hours)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is a sliding scale - $10-$20. Anyone who cannot afford to pay should contact the group organizer Deerheart, to arrange alternatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 25 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by car: Very limited parking at chapel, otherwise nearby streets such as Broadway and Mass Ave. There is a free small parking lot on Kirkland Street side of chapel, up to 8 cars. Coming from either direction on Massachusetts Ave into Harvard Square, turn onto Cambridge Street, then onto Quincy Street and around the corner onto the parking lot on Kirkland Street. The chapel is right on the corner of Quincy Street and Kirkland Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by T: The Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel is a lovely Gothic-revival stone chapel located at 50 Quincy Street in Cambridge, Mass. Please note that the official and historical name as may be found on maps and church directories is The Cambridge Society of the Church of the New Jerusalem (Swedenborgian). We are located at the corner of Quincy and Kirkland Streets, across from Harvard's monumental Memorial Hall/Sander's Theatre, which is behind Harvard Yard in Harvard Square. Access is an easy 5 minute walk from the Harvard Station MBTA stop on the Red Line and buses - just walk through Harvard Yard and ask anyone for Memorial Hall if you don't readily see the large fancy tower, then walk around the Hall to the chapel. &lt;br /&gt;For more information and directions for the Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, check out their website: www.swedenborgchapel.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257608419000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256353118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tips and Techniques: Beginner to Advanced</name><id>11698437</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257292800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/11698437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/8/c/global_11373980.jpeg</photo_url></item>