<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 44</address_2><address_1>1721 Boston Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06238</zip><lat>41.798228</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Highland Park Market</name><city>Coventry</city><id>1114934</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.374872</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We haven't done this in a couple of years, but the chance is back to help with Foodshare's Turkey and a Twenty drive.  The Turkey and a Twenty campaign is a region-wide effort to collect enough donated turkeys to make sure that everyone who needs a little help gets it this Thanksgiving and to raise money to help Foodshare feed people in need all year long.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, we will cover the collection point at the Highland Park Market in Coventry from 11:00 to 2:00.  This drive is in conjunction with WDRC-FM, the oldies station, and some of the station personnel should also be on site with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be working in the front of the store, accepting donations from people, and putting the turkeys in bins, the other food in separate bins, and the cash donations in a cash box.  We'll also hand out thank you cards and stickers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not clear if we will be inside or outside the store, but will update if I find out.  Otherwise, dress in layers and warm enough to work outside if need be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those interested, we might stop for a late lunch when we are done.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258993021000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-28</urlname><id>364032</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Heights Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257718572000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Foodshare's Turkey and a Twenty drive</name><id>11827023</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258819200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-28/events/11827023/</event_url></item>