<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bennet Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Regattabar at the Charles Hotel</name><city>Cambridge, Harvard square</city><id>3395632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Cross-posted with the Boston Culture Club: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/events/101631252/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/events/101631252/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you caught the Atlas Soul show in mid Jan, then you already know how incredibly talented Ali Amr is and you'll do everything you can to catch this amazing act. And if you weren't there, then now is your chance to hear one of the most remarkable young musicians out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's how it works. Order your tickets in advance at &lt;a href="http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2813" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2813&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do this NO LATER THAN Feb 14th, and then email me (Kenny Hyde) that you are planning to attend. I will make arrangements with the Regattabar for everyone who has emailed me to sit together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Featuring: Ali Amr - Qanun, Vocals, Compositions &lt;br /&gt;

Izaac Haselkorn - Drums &lt;br /&gt;

Christian Li - Piano &lt;br /&gt;

Jared Henderson - Bass&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ali Amr is a vocalist and Qanun performer. His compositions contemplate Arabic &amp;amp; Jazz music while embracing different textures &amp;amp; styles within. Amr was honored with 3 advanced Marcel Khalife Competition Awards including the National Heritage Award as the Music Performer of the Year, 2004-2007. Since then he has been touring worldwide with different acts to include his own group “Ali Amr Experiment". &lt;br /&gt;

Amr’s childhood was steeped in music as he began playing the Qanun and singing at the age of five at the Edward Said National Conservatory of Music and has performed in countless artistic events throughout the Middle East and in Sweden, Norway, Germany, Holland, Japan, Spain, Turkey among many other concerts worldwide. &lt;br /&gt;

In 2002, he was invited by Arabic music virtuoso Simon Shaheen to the Arabic Music Retreat in Massachusetts, where he earned accolades from leading musicians and Arabic music specialists. In 2006, he completed a two-month tour in the United States, starting at the United Nations in New York, and ending with an audience of 85,000 at San Antonio’s Alamo Dome. Since then he has begun his professional career performing in world-renowned venues such as the Boston Symphony Hall (Massachusetts), Carnegie Hall (New York) Kennedy Center (Washington D.C.), Hollywood Bowl (Los Angeles), Auditorio Nacional (Madrid) and Koerner Hall (Toronto).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His most recent appearances includes the Festival de Peralada in Spain where was invited by 27-time Grammy Award winning producer Quincy Jones as part of the Global All~Stars Group with Lionel Loueke, Esperanza Spalding and Antonio Carmona. Amr also performed at Monterey Jazz Festival, North Sea Jazz Festival, The Istanbul Jazz Festival, with 7-time Grammy award-winning producer Javier Limon, The Bean town Jazz Festival and the Newport Jazz Festival, Puerto Rico Heinken Jazz Festival, Lotus World Music Festival among many Berklee College of Music festivals at Berklee Performance Center, including the International Folk Music Festival and The Middle East Music Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to performing with his own group “The Ali Amr Experiment", Ali Amr has appeared in different multiple acts, managed and produced by EMI and Universal Studios and performed with amazing and world-renown artists such as Jack Dejohnette, Chick Corea, Esperanza Spalding, Alejandro Sanz, Concha Buika, Quincy Jones, Javier Limon, Simon Shaheen, Husnu Senlendirici, Dhaffer Yussuf, Aaron Goldberg, Omer Avital, Jamey Haddad, Eric Harland, Avishai Cohen, Glen Velez, Joel Smirnoff, Carmen Linares, Aynur Dogan, Glykeria Kotsoula, Elefteria Arvanitaki, Ritta, La Shica, Leo Blanco, Robin Eubanks, Eguie Castrillo, Sandra Carrasco, Bassam Saba among many others. Amr had the honor of performing for the Princess of Jordan (2010) and the President of Palestine (2008), Paco de Lucia (2010), Lang Lang (2011) and Brian O’Neil (2012) in Los Angeles. &lt;br /&gt;

Ali Amr wants to create a world of music that is exceptionally satisfying to the ear and the soul. This is why he selected New York City as his base to meet all virtuosos in their own musical forms, and whose expertise and knowledge raise the music and the group's performances to spectacular levels.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kenny Hyde</member_name><member_id>11634784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364569144000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359458841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Listen to the Ali Amr Group</name><id>101938552</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361491200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/101938552/</event_url></item>