<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Saturday as of Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt;Independence Day: Mostly sunny, with a high near 75. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Saybrook Jetty starting with July 4, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa   4      Low   3:13 AM     0.4   5:22 AM     Set  2:42 AM      89&lt;br /&gt;     4     High   9:16 AM     3.0   8:26 PM    Rise  6:40 PM&lt;br /&gt;     4      Low   3:05 PM     0.9&lt;br /&gt;     4     High   9:31 PM     4.2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Independence Day:  W wind around 13 kt. Mostly sunny. Seas 1 to 2 ft.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Water temp ranging between 61 to 68..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for a bit colder water if you want to go for a swim..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last Year we all found this to be a favourite spot for a Barbie-q and paddle event(s)..&lt;br /&gt;And last wekend it was good too...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an area that is good for both recreational and sea kayakers..&lt;br /&gt;But recreational kayaks should have a blow whistle, float bags, a paddle leash, a paddle float , pump and...shouldnt go out in the deep too far. BUT RIDE THE INTERESTING WAVES HERE.&lt;br /&gt;BUT REMEMBER you seen a recreational kayak sink before your eyes at Bolton lake..the body has never been recovered either, no PFD was worn either.&lt;br /&gt;for sea kayakers..well you know what its like out here..so i dont have to tell you anything,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DONT FALL IN, JELLY FISH, Ells, and Big Fish ARE HUNGRY....&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;we will have a flotilla of stuff to bring out there..so if you fall in..good luck...&lt;br /&gt;you are on your own.. we will grabb the food and bugg juice though..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to barbie q on the island this time for lunch....bring a sun umbrella for the sand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DISCLAIMER:&lt;br /&gt;IM OLD, HAVE NO ASSETTS, a big ass though, CANT HEAR OR SEE, AM WEAK AND THINK SHARKS ARE PETS..&lt;br /&gt;SO YOU should BE ABLE TO DO SELF RESCUE.. YOU CAN PRACTICE THAT HERE ALSO in real ocean conditions..&lt;br /&gt;im not going in the water to save you, i knowe there are giant blood suckers, monty pythons, piranahs, brain invading amebeas, and SHARKS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great Island area provides paddling in the secluded back channels, side rivers, and coves that parallel the lower Connecticut River near the mouth on the east side. You wind through 10-foot-tall marsh reeds and generally avoid the voluminous summer boating traffic. Whereas deeper-draft boats have to pay attention to the charts, kayaks can wander all over the place in the shallow waters here. Another advantage of the lower Connecticut is that three-quarters of the 1-mile?wide mouth averages a few feet in depth, which serves to keep motorboats to a minimum or forces them into the west channel, which exits through two stone breakwaters beyond Saybrook Point Lighthouse. The water just off the breakwaters is also very shallow? even small boats sometimes get grounded. Great Island offers good summer sea kayaking amid marsh grass, seaside goldenrod, glasswort, sea lavender, and water hemp.&lt;br /&gt;This popular launch site, located less than 500 feet from the Great Island Wildlife Management Area, provides visitors with opportunities to explore tidal marshes and a barrier beach. It is important to note, however, that motorized vessels must remain a reasonable distance away from the Great Island Wildlife Management Area upon launching. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; LOCATION ...APX  #95 (use whatever the gps indicates) Smith Neck Road&lt;br /&gt;Old Lyme, Connecticut for GPS users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from hartford:  Apx 45 minutes.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Take rte 9 south past Essex to 95 North , rte 9 ends here, stay to the left fork&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Take I-95 North to Exit 70. (Its right over the CT river bridge)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp, turn right onto Route 156/Shore Road &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.7&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; miles. to Smith neck rd  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;as you go along, Count 3 streets on right,   ( look for Jonny cake Hill rd is on left) DIRECTLY across is the next right 3rd one = Smith Neck Road, (you cant see the name its occluded by the Yellow Left turn arrow Diamond Sign)  &lt;br /&gt;turn right onto Smith Neck Road, and proceed 0.7 miles (to its end at the boat ramp).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have the Avalon with the kayak trailer and most likely i put the orange cones somewhere visible.&lt;br /&gt;I dont expect this area to be filled..but dont know..our group Should doubble park with each other to save room for other boaters if you want to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Rain or high wind (10+) , High seas (3+) canceles the event......The back up plan is to do the Blackhall River&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics on maybe 1 to 4 or so foot waves..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 20 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this ocean all day trip and new carbon paddles &amp;amp; paddle leaches..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub, Recreational Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed=    SAUSANNE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Short Sea Kayak = Riot Tourlite 15'=     AL-R&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Long SOT Sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', =  ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner, Long sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'=   BILL &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenlander, Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Fiberglass or Greenland Paddle= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= DURELLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susanne,  Durelle, and Bill can switch yaks if need be based on the paddle skill/comfort and conditions.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring extra food, or adult Bugg Juice for later at the 7 Falls Site on the return trip also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya all soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Orange Cone on Roof of PIMP GOLD Toyota Avalon &amp; Kayak Trailer Behind</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247332243000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246471378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> *PADDLE FOR INDEPENDANCE @ GREAT ISLAND *  Sea &amp; Rec Kayaks OK</name><id>10780175</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246726800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10780175/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>