<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 Arborway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.308380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-1718</phone><name>Arnold Arboretum</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>595034</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In The Groves: A Summer Solstice Journey with Diane Edgecomb accompanied by Margot Chamberlain on Celtic Harp&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, June 15th and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, June 16th,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$20 -- Please Register Online at &lt;a href="https://my.arboretum.harvard.edu/Info.aspx?DayPlanner=1024&amp;amp;DayPlannerDate=6/16/2012" class="linkified"&gt;https://my.arboretum.harvard.edu/Info.aspx?DayPlanner=1024&amp;amp;DayPlannerDate=6/16/2012&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;This enchanting evening of tree myths from around the world was designed specifically for the Arnold Arboretum. It starts at the Arnold Arboretum’s Hunnewell Visitor’s Building, 125 the Arborway and continues along tree-lined paths with story and music accompanying the way. As twilight descends the audience visits cherry, evergreen, ash and birch groves ~ celebrating nature with tree legends, songs and music from many lands. Pieces and music are drawn from the rich cultural traditions of Japan, Wales, England, Australia, Russia and Native America. The evening culminates with the haunting Czech legend “The Wild Woman of the Birch Grove” told among the birches of Bussey Hill at sunset. Appropriate for adults and for children eleven years and above. Bring a cushion to sit on if you wish. The journey will be approximately two miles on and off trails. The performance takes place rain or shine. In the event of rain, it will be held indoors and additional Solstice legends will be added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339807997000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>storytellers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>storytelling-28</urlname><id>1247871</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Greater Boston and MA Storytelling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339000868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>In The Groves: A Summer Solstice Journey with Diane Edgecomb </name><id>68009392</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339799400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/storytelling-28/events/68009392/</event_url></item>