<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>HURRICANE ROAD</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03845</zip><lat>44.075188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MOUNT KEARSAGE NORTH</name><city>INTERVALE</city><id>1141137</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120163</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WE WILL BE HIKING TO THE TOP OF MT. KEARSAGE NORTH.  ALL ATTENDEES MUST READ, UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO THE WAIVER &amp;amp; LIABILITY DISCLOSURE BELOW AND ALSO LOCATED ON THIS WEBSITE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A WAIT LIST HAS BEEN ESTABLISHED FOR THIS HIKE.   IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO ATTEND, PLEASE SIGN UP ON THE WAIT LIST.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE WILL BE STARTING PROMPTLY AT 10:00 SO PLEASE BE THERE NO LATTER THAN 9:45.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL ATTENDEES MUST BE PREPARED FOR WINTER CONDITIONS.  THIS INCLUDES NO COTTON, FOOT TRACTION (YAK-TRAXS, CRAMPONS, MICROSPIKES).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE KNOW YOUR LIMITS PRIOR TO SIGNING UP.  WINTER HIKING IS MUCH MORE DIFFICULT THAN SPRING/SUMMER/FALL HIKING.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance Time Elev&lt;br /&gt;Change&lt;br /&gt;Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude&lt;br /&gt;starting at Mount Kearsarge North Trailhead 44° 04' 31&amp;quot; 71° 06' 33&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;This trail ascends Kearsarge North from a small parking area on&lt;br /&gt;the north side of Hurricane Mountain Rd., 1.5 mi. east of NH 16&lt;br /&gt;near the state highway rest area at Intervale.&lt;br /&gt;3.10 mi 2 hr 52 min +2587 ft on Mount Kearsarge North Trail&lt;br /&gt;3.10 mi 2 hr 52 min +2587 ft This trail is a very popular and relatively easy trail to the&lt;br /&gt;magnificent views of Kearsarge North, but inexperienced hikers&lt;br /&gt;should not underestimate the total climb of 2,600 ft., which is&lt;br /&gt;comparable to the ascent required for many much higher peaks.&lt;br /&gt;Leaving the road, the trail runs level for a short distance, then&lt;br /&gt;climbs rather easily past a summer residence on an old road well&lt;br /&gt;up on the bank above a brook. It passes several boulders, and the&lt;br /&gt;old road starts to become rougher. It climbs steadily into a ledgy&lt;br /&gt;area, where there are views to Mt. Chocorua and Moat Mountain,&lt;br /&gt;crosses the crest of the ridge connecting Kearsarge North to&lt;br /&gt;Bartlett Mountain, then swings right and ascends mostly along the&lt;br /&gt;north side of the ridge. The trail makes a sharp right turn at a&lt;br /&gt;steep spot, then angles upward, circling to the left around to the&lt;br /&gt;west edge of the summit ledges, and climbs to the tower.&lt;br /&gt;to Kearsarge North 44° 06' 21&amp;quot; 71° 05' 39&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;3.10 mi 2 hr 52 min -2587 ft on Mount Kearsarge North Trail&lt;br /&gt;6.20 mi 5 hr 44 min 0 ft The Mount Kearsarge North Trail descends from the summit fire&lt;br /&gt;tower. It circles around to the west ledges then descends the&lt;br /&gt;ledges. It then swings to the north side of the ridge and crosses&lt;br /&gt;the crest of the ridge connecting Kearsarge North to Bartlett&lt;br /&gt;Mountain. It enters another open ledgy area where there are&lt;br /&gt;views to Mt. Chocorua and Moat Mountain. It descends steadily&lt;br /&gt;down the mountain. It passes several boulders then joins an old&lt;br /&gt;road and the grade eases. It passes a summer residence and&lt;br /&gt;descends easily to the road.&lt;br /&gt;to Mount Kearsarge North Trailhead 44° 04' 31&amp;quot; 71° 06' 33&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;This trail ascends Kearsarge North from a small parking area on&lt;br /&gt;the north side of Hurricane Mountain Rd., 1.5 mi. east of NH 16&lt;br /&gt;near the state highway rest area at Intervale.&lt;br /&gt;6.20 mi 5 hr 44 min 0 ft Totals&lt;br /&gt;2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has signed up for The New England Hiking and Adventurer's group is probably fully aware that there are risks involved with outdoor activities. Needless to say, we want everyone to have a safe and pleasant experience while participating in our events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hiker Responsibility Code is a set of principles that all hikers can look to before they hit the trail. Similar to the Skier's Responsibility Code endorsed by the National Ski Areas Association, the Hiker Responsibility Code was created to help hikers become more self aware about their responsibility for their own safety every time they are on a hike. It also acknowledges the inherent danger of hiking in the backcountry, and encourages hikers to be better prepared every time they are on the trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are responsible for yourself, so be prepared:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. With knowledge and gear. Become self reliant by learning about the terrain, conditions, local weather and your equipment before you start.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. To leave your plans. Tell someone where you are going, the trails you are hiking, when you will return and your emergency plans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. To stay together. When you start as a group, hike as a group, end as a group. Pace your hike to the slowest person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. To turn back. Weather changes quickly in the mountains. Fatigue and unexpected conditions can also affect your hike. Know your limitations and when to postpone your hike. The mountains will be there another day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. For emergencies. Even if you are headed out for just an hour, an injury, severe weather or a wrong turn could become life threatening. Don’t assume you will be rescued; know how to rescue yourself&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;# Be knowledgeable of what to prepare for.&lt;br /&gt;# Contact the event organizer about any concerns and event challenges.&lt;br /&gt;# Every participant needs to come fully prepared.&lt;br /&gt;# Disclose any medical conditions before the event.&lt;br /&gt;# pack to survive the event and for &amp;quot;what if&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more about Hike Safe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We expect for you to read the following and understand its terms. Feel free to contact us with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•  We ask that any member who does not agree to the below terms to leave The New England Hiking and Adventurer's Group (NEHAAG). Your remaining a member states that you do agree to the above terms. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Risks and Disclaimers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  When you sign up for Meetup.com, all members of Meetup must agree to their Terms of Service . Section 5.2 specifically releases the Organizer and Assistant Organizers from any liability related to incidents that occur at Meetup gatherings. &lt;br /&gt;  This is an online adult based group. You agreed when you joined Meetup that you were over the age of 18. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the NEHAAG is an adult group members and guests must be 18 years old to participated in an event. Guests over 18 are welcome, but must join Meetup and this group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only exception to this will be when an event is designated as &amp;quot;all ages welcome&amp;quot;. In these instances the parents and/or legal guardians are responsible for the care and supervision of their guests under the age of 18 years old. By signing-up for an &amp;quot;all ages welcome&amp;quot; event the member acknowledges and agrees that the Meetup and the NEHAAG terms apply to the guests as well.&lt;br /&gt;  All members will complete their personal profiles on the website. These profiles verify your hiking history and helps us get to know who you are. The organizers can then advise you a hike is too hard, and for security we can help identify each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Waiver of Liability.&lt;br /&gt;  The New England Hiking and Adventurer's Group (NEHAAG) is volunteer organization.&lt;br /&gt;  NEHAAG is a group of persons who share a common interest in the pursuit of outdoor recreational activities. Members of this group individually agree to pursue outdoor recreational activities with other Members and their guests(Events/Meetups). Meetups are organized by other members who have volunteered to lead the event. While event organizers may possess specialized skills or training, neither NEHAAG nor its members represent that they have any specialized training or skills relating to the event, wilderness safety or first aid.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Weather plays a big factor in the mountains. &amp;quot;the summit will be there another day.&amp;quot; We may cancel or change an event due to weather conditions. It is up to the member to keep track of event cancellations, posted by the organizer.We can not guarantee what trail conditions will be, only to advise members to prepare for all conditions. Communicate with other members who are participating in that event. &lt;br /&gt;  Outdoor sports are inherently dangerous and accidents will happen. It's a reality that if your miles or hours out on a trail, it might not easy to seek medical care right away. If you chose to explore, you do so knowing that there are risks.&lt;br /&gt;  It is wise for everyone of us to have regular medical checkups and to be fit to hike. It should also be noted that if you have a &amp;quot;minor&amp;quot; medical condition that your hiking partner know of any special needs. Are you on blood thinners, diabetic, asthma, allergic to bees, etc? Remember that the most we can do for you in the woods is basic first aid, and try to get you to safety.&lt;br /&gt;  By joining the group or participating in any events posted on the web page you are taking responsibility for your own safety and well-being. NEHAAG does not certify or confirm the identity or qualifications of any of its members to lead or participate in trips. Member personal information is voluntary. A minimum number of RSVP's will be met to insure the safety and comfort of all hikers and organizers. We remind all members that in an internet group it is difficult to verify anyone's reputation. Exercise common sense in meeting up with people you don't know. There is safety in a group.&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be familiar with the hike plans- do your own homework. Here are some links to what you should know. There are also checklists in the files section for you to print out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Trail ratings and Trail rules&lt;br /&gt;  Guide to Map and Compass&lt;br /&gt;  Book Time: How long will this hike be?&lt;br /&gt;  OA Guide to Water Purification&lt;br /&gt;  Trail Blazes&lt;br /&gt;  When lightening strikes&lt;br /&gt;  Picking and Packing Backpacks and Backpacks and what to put in them&lt;br /&gt;  What to wear on a hike&lt;br /&gt;  Nutritional issues Staying hydrated,&lt;br /&gt;Food as fuel, and hey sugar&lt;br /&gt;  First Aid A First Aid Kit In Every Backpack&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  We follow the Seven Principles of Leave No Trace, which can be summarized as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>DIANNE AND I WILL BE IN A BLACK FOUR DOOR ECHO</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261408282000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260819566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT. KEARSAGE NORTH</name><id>12083411</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261234800000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12083411/</event_url></item>