<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 State St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076996</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-9715</phone><name>The Rosa Restaurant</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>260717</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.754150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/c/e/event_55805582.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Our October pick for the Portsmouth Book Club is &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incongnito: The Secret Lives of the Brain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;by David Eagleman.&amp;nbsp; Another great non-fiction book for our bookshelf!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Here is a brief synopsis of &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incognito&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; from the editor:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If the conscious mind&amp;mdash;the part you consider to be you&amp;mdash;is just the tip of the iceberg, what is the rest doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this sparkling and provocative new book, the renowned neuroscientist David Eagleman navigates the depths of the subconscious brain to illuminate surprising mysteries: Why can your foot move halfway to the brake pedal before you become consciously aware of danger ahead? Why do you hear your name being mentioned in a conversation that you didn&amp;rsquo;t think you were listening to? What do Ulysses and the credit crunch have in common? Why did Thomas Edison electrocute an elephant in 1916? Why are people whose names begin with J more likely to marry other people whose names begin with J? Why is it so difficult to keep a secret? And how is it possible to get angry at yourself&amp;mdash;who, exactly, is mad at whom?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking in brain damage, plane spotting, dating, drugs, beauty, infidelity, synesthesia, criminal law, artificial intelligence, and visual illusions, Incognito is a thrilling subsurface exploration of the mind and all its contradictions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;And a review from Barnes and Noble:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This book helps answer the question that is frequently asked when an expert tells us that our conscious mind comprises only a tiny fraction of our working brain: What are the rest of my 160-190 billion brain cells doing? Neuroscientist/author David Eagleman (Sum; Wednesday Is Indigo Blue) is superbly positioned to plumb the depths of our subterranean mental processes. Drawing on cutting-edge research, his exploration illuminates real world decision-making, with examples that include everything from the mortgage meltdown and mating preferences to the fluctuating incomes of pole dancers. A provocative read for fans of Malcolm Gladwell.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318461300000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299638953000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club October Meetup - Incognito</name><id>mbhqqypnbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318374000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/32507692/</event_url></item>