<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi incubators!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of our regulars Ziad is off to start a new life in Germany thanks to a sweet grant he's gotten!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So instead of our usual incubator this week, he has invited all of us to his going away party which will include tons of improvised games as well as a performance by the troupe Ziad is is and I direct, Laughing Matter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, email me!  It's not too far from my place&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host:   ziad ganim&lt;br /&gt;Location:  &lt;br /&gt;80 pleasant st&lt;br /&gt;cambridge, MA 02139 US&lt;br /&gt;When:  Thursday, July 29, 7:05PM    Add to my Outlook Calendar&lt;br /&gt;THE LAST TIME I had a party my bathroom was trashed, someone puked on the carpet, and all the gummy bears went in the salsa. 15 years later, I'm ready to throw another one and expecting around the same level of maturity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COME MEET all the depraved freaks I hang out with when I'm not around you. Lots of social circles spilling together; now that I'm leaving you can finally mingle. (Play nice. I'm gonna ride this chemistry thing out, but I want politics as backup.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DO YOU WANT a piece of me? Seriously. Rather than giving presents, buy my stuff. Everything will have a price tag on it. Show up early for select items such as: Combo DVD/VCR player, Henckels Knives, Bathroom Scale (features lbs and kgs), The Eating Bowl (good for any meal), Pressure Cooker, Garlic Press, Garlic Press #2 (that I bought when I forgot about #1), and Gently Used Kitchen Towel. FREE giveaways if you prove you need it by showing up with Top Ramen breath.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GAMES. Improv games led by Laughing Matter; the whole evening is a game of party quirks so come with one. We will also have an OPA alignment competition, a Dark Sun campaign, handstand olympics, the mangina semi-finals, and a panel on Jarzinsky's Inequality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THERE may be a keg. Did you know that there are 124 pints in a keg? (Auf Deutsch: Wir konnten bis zu fünfzig acht Litern trinken. Bitte bringen Sie einen Liter Stein, wenn Sie eine Tasse, weil ich nur einen haben.) There will be plenty of dinner, drinks, and perhaps some surprise treats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Promise to use your inside voice, we can play all nite.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280962070000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280255591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ziad's going away party!  An incubator at Ziad's!</name><id>14230743</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280446200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/14230743/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>