<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you always loved nighttime street shots but never knew how to make them? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is all about taking photos in low light situations and getting great results. The advantages that digital cameras provide when compared to film really stand out with this type of photography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop begins with a classroom discussion that covers technique, exposure, camera settings and working with long exposure times.  After the discussion we will move outside to do some actual shooting of an urban environment during twilight and into darkness.  For the most part we will be working with available light only but we will touch upon adding electronic flash to the mix.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Almost every digital camera (point and shoot) has the capability to set long exposure times so not think you need the top of the line Dslr for this class.  Besides your digital camera the only other equipment I would suggest (not required) is a tripod.  If you do not own or cannot borrow a tripod you will also learn some great, easy alternatives.  A tripod is your best choice so make an effort to have one for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a good and fun class for beginners and more advanced photographers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285452987000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281806691000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LOW LIGHT and NIGHT PHOTOGRAPHY- Shooting in the dark!</name><id>14421943</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285448400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/14421943/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/e/global_16414110.jpeg</photo_url></item>