<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Henry Hobson Richardson was born on September 29, 1838 in New Orleans.  Meet us on the steps of his masterwork, Trinity Church, as we salute this great American architect on the 170th anniversary of his birth.  The tour will take in four of Richardson buildings and discuss the evolution of this brilliant architect's work to the culmination of his style, the Richardsonian Romanesque.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From its inception, Trinity Church  has been hailed as a superior American building by the American Institute of Architects. In the AIA's recent poll of the top 150 buildings in America (for their 150th anniversary) Trinity was Boston's highest ranked building.  The tour will also include several other buildings that made their list -- the Boston Public Library and the John Hancock Tower.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us as we stroll through Copley Square and the Back Bay relishing the architectural wonders to be seen and celebrating the life and work of the phenomenal Henry Hobson Richardson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour costs $12 for the general public, free for &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot members&lt;/a&gt;.  Purchase tickets directly from the guide at the time of the tour. Meet at the steps of Trinity Church on the side facing Copley Square (see photo above).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boston By Foot guides will be on the front steps</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223130499000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220311535000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tour to Celebrate the Birthday of Henry Hobson Richardson</name><id>8665654</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222723800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/8665654/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/8/global_5373704.jpeg</photo_url></item>