<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for a talk given by Greater Worcester Humanist's own David Miller.  He will be speaking to the group about things teachers wont teach you about America's founding fathers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The men who made the American Revolution, wrote the American Constitution, and founded the United States Government, men like Tom Paine, George Washington, and Thomas Jefferson, are routinely lionized as national heroes in our history textbooks and history classes.  That they were radical thinkers in the context of the political thought of their times is hardly mentioned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totally ignored is the inconvenient and embarrassing truth that they were also radical and unorthodox thinkers in matters of religion.  In fact the first six presidents, whose terms spanned the first forty years of the nation’s history, rejected orthodox Christianity and various of the central dogmas of the Christian faith.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rev. David J. Miller, Minister Emeritus of the Unitarian Universalist Church of Worcester, will give a talk illustrating the non-belief of the Founding Fathers by means of quotations from their writings along with commentaries gleaned from contemporaries who knew them and their convictions and from historians and biographers who wrote about their religious views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is free and open to the general public.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will probably be setting up some piece of equipment....</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244564257000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236257369000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GWH April Meeting - What Your Teachers Won’t Tell You about the Founding Fathers</name><id>9886750</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239748200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/9886750/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/2/global_7423922.jpeg</photo_url></item>