<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Taza Chocolate Demo and Tasting&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store and Somerville's own Taza Chocolate are happy to invite you over for a little wine, some conversation, and an in-store demonstration and tasting with Taza, the only maker of 100% stone ground chocolate in the United States. Taza Chocolate also happens to be one of the only independently owned, socially and environmentally responsible chocolate makers in the country. What's not to love?!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come hear Taza's inspiring story from the &amp;quot;Masters of the Dark Arts&amp;quot; (Boston magazine). And then there's the dark matter itself: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Instead of a refined, buttery smoothness, Taza chocolate reveals the natural essence of the cacao bean, resulting in a raw chocolate flavor unlike any available locally.&amp;quot; - Boston magazine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;'What most people don't know is that chocolate is a fruit,' says Larry Slotnick, Taza's co-owner. 'If you were to slice a cantaloupe in half, you'd see seeds and pulp. It's the same with cacao.' Every month, ten sacks, weighing 150 pounds each, of this fruit - fermented and dried - arrive at Taza's warehouse outside Union Square to feed the roasters, grinders, and refiners that turn bitter, almond-size cocoa beans into Taza's organic dark chocolates.&amp;quot; - Boston Globe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taza is a true bean-to-bar chocolate maker located in Somerville, Massachusetts, and is the only maker of 100% stone ground chocolate in the United States. Taza sources organically grown cacao beans directly from small farming cooperatives ensuring those farmers receive more than fair trade prices for their high quality cacao. Taza is uniquely positioned as one of the only independently owned, socially and environmentally responsible chocolate makers in the country. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taza's chocolate making process is designed to capture the true flavor of the cacao bean by minimally processing the chocolate every step of the way. By putting care into the entire process, from the sourcing of ingredients from our proud farmers, to molding finished chocolate bars, Taza is dedicated to quality, and to serving our customers and the environment every step of the way. Taza Chocolate holds periodic open houses at our factory in Somerville, Mass. that are free and open to all. To learn more about tours at Taza, click &lt;a href="http://www.tazachocolate.com/tour.php" target="_blank"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Book Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215314236000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206908642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chocolate Tasting (Taza)</name><id>7634616</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208818800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/7634616/</event_url></item>