<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Meet earlier to chat at the Congress, around 9/9:30 (easier to park at that time for those who need to).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then move over to the Salon basement to listen (and dance) to TANGLED, between 10:30/11 estimated arrival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Per the Salon website: "Union Street Collective is an all-female DJ collective that includes DJ AMac, DJ Kasumi, LaRochelle, and DJ Mercedes mixing house, tech house, deep house, electro, and electronic beats. Recently nominated for best DJ's in the Providence Phoenix's Best Music Poll."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My less than technical review of their music is that it is foot-tapping, danceable, and the beats switch a bit as each DJ takes her turn spinning. This is less drum/base or hard techno ear-bleeding repetition, although the volume could be loud. They usually project a movie or videos on the wall. There's a bank of booth style seating at the far corner when you enter the room. That's probably a better spot for a small group like ours to find each other. The bartenders are nice. The scene in the basement tends to be of various ages, while upstairs seems to be mostly college crowd.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332792287000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331249568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday night / TANGLED</name><id>55571582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332638100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/55571582/</event_url></item>