<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello RIRUGgers. Please mark your calendar for the July meeting of the Rhode Island Revit Users Group. We will meet once again at the new JTJ Investments building at 28 Wolcott Street. We plan to continue to try to provide a non-revit related incentive for these meetings - so for those of you who did not attend last time, we will ask John Jacobsen to provide another brief tour of the Net Zero Energy Office Space at the end. If you attended this before - you are exempt from this part! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a very informal kick-off discussion last time. At the upcoming meeting we will ask attendees to briefly discuss their relationship to the software (avid user, transitioning, consultant etc). I'd also like to branstorm some topics that the group feels would be beneficial to have a focused presentation on. Please try to attend, guys - we need to build up the momentum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, this Friday 7/10 I will be presenting at the 2009 AIA RI Corporate Affiliate Fair and Summer Conference as part of this:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;B2 Technology: BIM – Is Now the Time?&lt;br /&gt;It’s said that when you have the money you don’t have the time, when you have the time you don’t have the money. Participate in this honest discussion about the pros and cons of a technology transition in a challenging business climate with fellow professionals who have been through it.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the upstairs space - entrance off of Wolcott St or through the courtyard and up the stairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Wade Keating</member_name><member_id>8961244</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256224375000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Revit Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Rhode-Island-Revit-Users-Group</urlname><id>1414420</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Revit Users Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246912779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RIRUG July Meeting</name><id>10815382</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248384600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Rhode-Island-Revit-Users-Group/events/10815382/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/0/global_7803696.jpeg</photo_url></item>