<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather isnt looking real good for either weekend day and just to get in a paddle event i think this location is sort of local for most of us, it also has the possibility for exploration till the weather changes with a reasonable return time or at least some escape areas if Thunderstorms do occur Later in the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im not sure if Weslean has any activities for the day, i didnt see any listed so parking should be easy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one of the more early events only because its bad weather questionable in the afternoon ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This time i chose 10 am or so at the ramp and hope to get going about 10:30 OR SO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN CANCELS THE EVENT IF THINGS LOOK IMMINENTLY NOT FEASIBLE FOR A FEW GOOD HOURS OF PADDLING.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUT AS USUAL THE WEATHER REPORTS AND PREDICTIONS ARE SO UNPREDICTABLE SO I REALLY DONT KNOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday may look better, i just cant say based on all the mixed weather reports i have seen so far..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update in the morning before the event. If it dosent look like a good paddle day but ok for some other thing, 7 Falls is nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip involves Play around in the METABASSETTE area(s) TillL the we are done one way or the other ...then head back to the Weslean boat ramp for a simple Lunch/Dinner if its still nice out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its the usual kind of event if the weather holds out so bring some Barbie-Q food and your favourite bugg juice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to the Weslean boat ramp...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford: Points North of Middletown via Route 9 South:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 14. (DeKovan) Make 3 consecutive lefts (off of exit left on Dekoven, left on Union, then left on Harbor ) and A RIGHT AT the WESLEAN boat ramp (ITS BEFORE the Harbor Park Restaurant) is on the right. &lt;br /&gt;You may have to park wherever you can because the drunks go to the harbor rest...so look around..but you can drop off your boat by the boat ramp before parking..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points South of Middletown via Route 9 North:&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 12. At first stop sign go straight. At second stop sign go left. At first stop light go right and at first stop light again go right. Go under overpass and bear left. WESLEAN boat ramp (BEFORE Harbor Park Restaurant) is on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points North of Middletown via I-91 South:&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 22S. This puts you on route 9 south. Follow directions from 9 South. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Points South of Middletown via I-91 North:&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 22S. This puts you on route 9 south. Follow directions from 9 South. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest or GPS just use 80 Harbor Drive Middletown CT to get you close enough..&lt;br /&gt;compare your directions to mine..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics ..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub, Recreational Kayak= Pungo 12' with floataion bags 1nstalled= &lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Sea Kayak= Riot Tourlite 15'= AL-R&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Sea Kayak= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = &lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner, Sea Kayak= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= KAREN ?&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenland, Sea Kayak= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 10 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for ORANGE STRIPED TRAFFIC CONES @ parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246730570000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246020998000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak trip up the CT RIVER to the METABASSETTE RIVER AREAS</name><id>10740393</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246111200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10740393/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/global_474104.jpeg</photo_url></item>