<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>873 Whalley Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06515</zip><lat>41.326642</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.389.9555    </phone><name>Kehler Liddell Gallery</name><city>New Haven</city><id>800189</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.959489</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;WOW three gallery openings today all in Westville Village!!!  Lets start at Kehler Liddell&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Streetwise Americana at Kehler Liddell,&lt;br /&gt;Wunderlee Arts, and DaSilva Gallery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Streetwise  America&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Artist talk at 4:00&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hank Paper and Friends&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kehler Liddell Gallery is pleased to present Streetwise America, a group show of photographs, paintings, collage and installation that documents contemporary America and facilitates a conscious consideration of what&amp;#700;s happening on our streets. The exhibition features over 40 color photographs by New Haven-based artist Hank Paper, shot over the past five years.  A selection of works by Peter Bosco, John Columbus, Steve DiGiovanni, Graham D. Honaker II, Robert Lisak, Maryann Ott, David Ottenstein and Suzan Shutan accompany Paper&amp;#700;s work, offering chance similarities and juxtapositions that create new points of departure for reflection on our national identity.  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Hank Paper&lt;/b&gt; shoots fast with a handheld Leica camera and crops with his lens in the straight, photojournalist style of New York&amp;#700;s street photographers of the 60&amp;#700;s and 70&amp;#700;s; Robert Frank, Garry Winogrand, Diane Arbus, and Vito Acconci. The invention of digital film in the 80&amp;#700;s did not fundamentally change his craft.  Major themes in his work are evident in the patterns and behaviors that appear in his images time and time again: Sexual Role Modeling, Aging, Immigration.  His subjects are the people that play out these themes: preoccupied businessmen, wild hookers, concerned parents, assimilated immigrants, museum-going elders.  For Paper, the challenge is to puncture the viewer&amp;#700;s preconceived notions of his fellow man by making works that reveal his subjects&amp;#700; ever-changing dimensions: the posture of a Hell&amp;#700;s Angel walking a toy poodle or the isolation of a lonely schoolgirl at a Christmas pageant.  &lt;br /&gt;    Paper has dedicated the past 35 years to documenting contemporary society, mining the streets of North America, The United Kingdom, Western Europe, the Middle East and Cuba in search of capturing what he describes as “that revelatory action, or gesture, or face.”  His work has been exhibited in museum and gallery shows around the world, including The African American Museum in Philadelphia (2006), The Hebrew University in Jerusalem, Israel (1999), The Jewish Museum of New Jersey (2008), the High Point Historical Museum in North Carolina (2001), the Tamarkin&amp;#700;s and the Leica Gallery in New York City (2002) and the Morgenthal-Frederics Gallery in New York City (2000).  He received the Piedmont Award from the Somers Juried Photography Show for his Terminal Series in 2009 and a grant from the CT Commission on Culture and Tourism for his Ascension Series in 2006.  &lt;br /&gt;    Together, the artists in this show hope to penetrate mass media image saturation and mitigate the pressure of electronic assault in order to fix on what is elusive and infinitely moving in the face of America today. A fully illustrated, hardbound catalogue with an introduction by Hank Paper will accompany the exhibition.&lt;br /&gt;    Peter Bosco&amp;#700;s photographs come from a larger body of work titled Fading Places, which attests to the impermanence of things, both animate and inanimate.  Bosco photographs many places that are no longer extant, intending to show things as they are and to render them in the most literal way possible.  His work has been described as “hymns of sadness”, and while they are often about loss, his works ultimately serve to sustain time, place and memory.   &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;John M. Columbus&lt;/b&gt;&amp;#700; interest in photography began as a boy in 1960&amp;#700;s New Jersey when his parents gave him a Polaroid/Land camera. He studied with photographer Marc Cohen, who influenced his street photography style of “seeing the unusual.”  Columbus, whose photo assignments have taken him throughout the U.S., the Caribbean, and Europe, currently concentrates on event and magazine photography, exhibiting his work, and drumming in a ska/jazz band.  &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;b&gt;Steve DiGiovanni&lt;/b&gt; blurs the line between painting and photography by incorporating digital photography in his paintings.  DiGiovanni culls Internet images, old magazines and personal photographs, all of which he incorporates in his works in acrylic on canvas.  Inspired by his imagination, his compositions are often free associative and improvisational, reflecting his ongoing interest in the wide range of painting&amp;#700;s possibilities.  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Graham D. Honaker&lt;/b&gt; II is an Abstract Expressionist whose paintings comment on contemporary society, with subjects ranging from potentially harmful political structures to the simple poetics of everyday life. Influenced by Existentialism, which emphasizes the act of creating, Honaker exercises his subconscious through “auto-painting.” At the same time, his observations of the perpetually shifting world around him and his place in it are conveyed in his often-intricate and highly conceptual subject matter.  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Robert Lisak&lt;/b&gt; is a photographer based in New Haven, who recently published a catalogue on the architecture of his city&amp;#700;s historic churches. Lisak received his MFA from the Yale School of Art, and is currently a member of ASMP and an adjunct Professor of Photography at Sacred Heart University.  &lt;br /&gt;    Maryann Ott is inspired by dreams, hallucinations, flights of imagination, and the mind&amp;#700;s eye. She feels that if she could map the streets, alleys and hidden pathways of her inner life, she&amp;#700;d be a wiser person. Instead, she is a photographer, capturing what she can and making it hers.  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;David Ottenstein&lt;/b&gt; has been pursuing fine-art/documentary photography, exploring interiors of abandoned and decaying buildings in the northeast and the vanishing agrarian landscape of the Midwest.  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;b&gt;Suzan Shutan&lt;/b&gt; is a New Media Sculptor, Installation and Video Artist straddling the worlds of two and three dimensions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wunderlee Arts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Painting, Prints, Photography: Don Wunderlee, Oi Fortin, &amp;amp; Catherine Fisher  Opening reception at Wunderlee Arts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wunderlee Arts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;924 WHALLEY AVENUE &lt;br /&gt;NEW HAVEN, CT 06515&lt;br /&gt;203-387-3537&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wunderleearts.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wunderleea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3-6&lt;br /&gt;    &amp;quot;My new images are born out of my summer Cape series and I am pushing further into textured linear shape and as much density as I can get into the surface...&amp;quot; - &lt;b&gt;Don Wunderlee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &amp;quot;Oi Fortin - SomnambulistMy Monotype prints are contemporary abstract expressions of the depth and spatial relationship of color, form, texture and size. My work ranges from four square-inch iniatures to three square-foot prints. The piece &amp;quot;Somnambulist&amp;quot; is an example of my latest work with limited hues - Black &amp;amp; White with little red series.&amp;quot;  - &lt;b&gt;Oi Fortin&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &amp;quot;I find abstractions on rusting surfaces, peeling dumpsters, weathered boats and broken windows.  Texture, color, pattern and light combine to find beauty in ordinary and often abandoned objects.&amp;quot; - &lt;b&gt;Catherine Fisher&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FERNANDO DASILVA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OPENING RECEPTION AT DASILVA GALLERY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome DaSilva Gallery as they open the inaugural show in their new space next to The Frame Shop: Fernando DaSilva, presenting new mixed media acrylic works on canvas. Meet the artist at the opening reception.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Da Silva Gallery&lt;br /&gt;897 Whalley Avenue&lt;br /&gt;New Haven,CT&lt;br /&gt;06515&lt;br /&gt;203-387-2539&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will wear the BW scarf with Piano keys, check all attending faces so we connect, also ask gallery director to point me out if needed.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268941945000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265134582000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Streetwise America Reception and more!</name><id>12497491</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268593200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/12497491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/3/4/global_13330148.jpeg</photo_url></item>