<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Stone Ridge Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.568957</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beverly Commons</name><city>Beverly</city><id>710187</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.821632</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Beverly Commons is partly owned by the city of Beverly and the Greenbelt. There are several trails, some of them are very rocky so wear hiking boots or sturdy walking shoes! There are no steep grades, the trails meander here and there, passing through a beautiful hemlock forest and mixed pine and oak forest and wetlands. Bring binoculars if you have them, because we will stop to look at any birds. I've seen barred owls and pileated woodpeckers there.  Dogs are welcome on this walk! Please bring plastic bags for pick up.  The hike will take about one to 1.5 hours, depending upon our pace. There are no restrooms. We can go to downtown Beverly later for some refreshments at one of the nice little eateries if people are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Walk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiker Code of Conduct&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please follow the leader. I don't want to lose anyone. Please be sure your dog comes when called.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Take Route 128 to Exit 17, Grapevine Road toward Beverly Farms. Grapevine Rd becomes Hart St. Go approximately two miles on Hart St. and take a right onto Greenwood Ave, (look for Chapman's Greenhouse on the corner of Hart and Greenwood). Follow Greenwood to the end and park near the fire road at the entrance to the Commons but do not block the fire road entrance.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be there with my dog, Sophie. Our picture is posted on this website.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debora</member_name><member_id>11719701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1289058360000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288105694000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Hike at Beverly Commons</name><id>15233627</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288531800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15233627/</event_url></item>