<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>249 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yoga In The Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>941611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121885</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Embark on a profound journey of healing and integration. Address the core limiting beliefs, conditioning, and habit patterns which block you from having the life you truly desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each Chakra stores the collection of our core beliefs, emotions and experiences in correlation to seven fundamental themes in our life: survival, creativity, power, love, self-expression, wisdom, and divine connection. By deeply exploring your relationship to each of these central themes, you will clear out negative accumulations and revitalize the positive attributes and creative potential of each chakra.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through guided meditation, visualization, movement, breath, sound, drawing, creative writing, and interactive exercises you will release what no longer serves you and experience healing and integration of your whole being. No prior experience necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9 Wednesdays: Sept 23 - Nov 18, 8:00 - 10:00pm, $160/series, $20 drop in&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't paid for the series, you may pay per class via PayPal or cash or check at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Note: There is a hot yoga class before us. You may wish to bring cool, loose, comfortable clothing to change into and a water bottle.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Week 1: Overview of Your Life, Setting your Intentions for Manifestation&lt;br /&gt;Week 2: Root Chakra - Feel Safe and Grounded in the World, Tap into Abundance Consciousness&lt;br /&gt;Week 3: 2nd Chakra - Access your Creative Power and Ability to Experience Pleasure&lt;br /&gt;Week 4: 3rd Chakra - Increase your Self-Confidence and Effectiveness in the World&lt;br /&gt;Week 5: 4th Chakra - Open your Heart to Receive Unconditional Love and Acceptance&lt;br /&gt;Week 6: 5th Chakra - Find your Authentic Voice and Express your Truth&lt;br /&gt;Week 7: 6th Chakra - Develop Trust in your Inner Guidance&lt;br /&gt;Week 8: 7th Chakra - Experience your Direct Connection with the Divine&lt;br /&gt;Week 9: 8th Chakra - Access your Higher Power of Manifestation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Tantric Educator and Intimacy Coach. She has been studying and practicing in the fields of Somatics and Consciousness since 1984. Brynn draws on her training in Taoist and Hindu Tantric Practices, Hakomi Method of Body-Oriented Psychotherapy, Mindfulness Practices, Chi Gong, Authentic Movement and Expressive Arts Therapy in her classes and private sessions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Brynn is available for individual healing and coaching sessions, should you desire greater support around any of these themes.*&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter through the door to the left of the Burren. We are upstairs at the end of the hall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256862346000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253131321000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chakra Integration Series, Week 5: Awakening the Heart</name><id>11389899</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256169600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/11389899/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/3/global_10606195.jpeg</photo_url></item>