<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358894</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Central Wharf/New England Aquarium </name><city>Boston</city><id>3036611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050827</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The New England Aquarium is concluding its spring lecture series this week with what looks like an interesting talk:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/index.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/education_and_activities/programs_and_classes/aquarium_lecture_series/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Dinner Matters: Lobster Love, Sushi Secrets and How We Can Help Save the Seas with Smart Eating&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Trevor Corson, bestselling author of The Secret Life of Lobsters and The Story of Sushi&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Trevor Corson draws on his experiences researching and writing his two bestselling books —The Secret Life of Lobsters and The Story of Sushi—as well as his two years as a full-time commercial fisherman, his current work as the only "Sushi Concierge" in the United States and his appearances as a judge on Food Network TV's Iron Chef America, to share his passion for marine science and fishing, the amusing social life of lobsters, the surprising secrets of sushi and the current plight of the endangered bluefin tuna. Using stories, photos, and videos, Carson ties his far-flung subject matter together with an empowering message about how our choices at the dinner table and the ways we harvest our seafood can help save our oceans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've been to a few talks at the Aquarium and they've generally been pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is happening at the Imax Theater right next to the Aquarium. I'll wait outside until 6:45 and then go in to grab seats. It might be crowded so we might not all be able to sit together. After the talk I'll go down and wait by the exit to catch people who came in late. Don't be shy - say hi! I will do my very best to remember my meetup pin that day too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the talk we can grab an ice cream and hang out at the park or go to grab some grub at a local spot like Jose McIntyres.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait outside the Imax theater until 6:45 and then go in and get seats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>2367399</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339772765000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339467451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Talk at the Aquarium: Lobster Love, Sushi Secrets</name><id>68783932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339713900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/68783932/</event_url></item>