<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of State and Pleasant Streets</address_2><address_1>26 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Richdale Food Store</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1126642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Calling all goblins, witches and warlocks for a &amp;quot;spooktacular&amp;quot; event in downtown Newburyport &amp;amp; The Tannery Marketplace. Enjoy merchant and restaurant hospitality while shopping and meeting your favorite witch or warlock. Many participating businesses will be decorating their stores in the best of Halloween finery, serving light refreshments, having a costume contest and offering a reverse trick or treat to benefit Pennies for Poverty: 2 Cents for Change. For information on the 2 cents for change go to &lt;a href="http://www.witchesnig.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.witchesnig...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Witches Night Out attendees are encouraged to dress as a witch or warlock to add to the festivity’s of the evening. Costumes are suggested you don’t have to dress up to attend, but if you do it will just add to the fun. So grab your best witch or warlock getup and come cast your spell in Newburyport.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an Adult Event For The Night. Costume Contest Will Be Held At The Black Dog At 8:00! Winners Will Receive a $50.00 Newburyport Gift Certificate From The Newburyport Chamber!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't be scared come prowl along with the rest of the creatures of the night that will be around town. Right now there are over 45 stores/restaurants (and they will be adding more) that will be joining in on the fun of this event, so come to this event to hang around with some great friends, shop, get a bite to eat, check out some great costumes, and get/give some treats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note we will only wait for 15 minutes after scheduled meetup time to head out into the night, if you are running late, get lost or not able to find us call the Meetup phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 3 municipal lots downtown – parking is FREE in these 3 lots.&lt;br /&gt;They are located at Green &amp;amp; Merrimac Streets, State and Harris Streets (next to the Library) and on Prince Place. There are 2 lots run by the Newburyport Redevelopment Authority They are located at either side of Waterfront Park along Merrimac Street Between The Black Cow and Not Your Average Joe’s (West Lot) and Water Street (East Lot). You may also park in legal spots on the street. If you park in a nearby neighborhood, please be respectful of residents and all parking laws - do not block fire hydrants or driveways. Police will ticket or tow all cars which are parked in illegal spaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to getting spooked with you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet shock&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in front of the entrance</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287880814000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286416444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Witches Night Out....</name><id>15029464</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287788400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/15029464/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/6/d/global_18543181.jpeg</photo_url></item>