<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>You may have heard about this place on Chronicle or the Phantom Gourmet.  Word is, it's well worth the trip to Newton....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Local, a West Newton gastropub, promises to live up to its name with New England–brewed beers on tap and sustainable, moderately priced New American comfort food; sleek and open yet invitingly dark, it’s the kind of upscale watering hole where you can settle into the dining room for a meal or catch a game on TV at the bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the dark wooded, tall-candled former R.J. Crowley space, The Local is a gastropub stripped of Brit in favor of New Englandness, serving locally sourced grub/brews that seek &amp;quot;to celebrate all that is good in our region&amp;quot;. The menu starts with native favorites like PEI Mussels (Bass Ale broth, Dijon, grilled bread), Homemade Chowdah, and Brahmin-esque Warm Potato Chips w/ French Onion Dip, then moves on to &amp;quot;Small Things&amp;quot;: three types of Mac and Cheese (Peas/Ham, Lobster, Truffle/Chive), Crispy Calamari (jalapenos, sweet &amp;amp; sour onions, &amp;quot;real soy&amp;quot;), and a Lemon Chicken Soup w/ Orzo credited to &amp;quot;Skinny Dan&amp;quot; (&amp;quot;The Cueeervo Gold, The Leeeemon Chiiiicken Soup...&amp;quot;). For the more heartier appetite, there're three types of Flatbreads (Kobe Beef, Iceberg, &amp;amp; Cheddar; Roasted Tomato, Basil, &amp;amp; Pecorino; Italian Sausage, Broccoli Rabe &amp;amp; Crushed Red Pepper Aioli) and &amp;quot;Bigger Things&amp;quot; like T.W.'s Marinated Steak Tips, Hanger Steak w/ Warm Soba Noodle Salad, and an &amp;quot;American Kobe&amp;quot; Burger (plays here, but beloved in Asia!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's check it out for some appetizers and cocktails and take in a movie across the street at the West Newton Cinema.  We can choose a movie as we get closer to the date.  We will go to see The Informers at 8:35 - if you want to go to the movie, I suggest you buy your ticket before getting to The Local.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my picture on the site</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1242593988000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Baby Boomers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun</urlname><id>1347228</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Baby Boomers Meetup Group-Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239149971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drinks/Appetizers at The Local and optional movie at the West Newton Cinema</name><id>10139772</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240700400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun/events/10139772/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/6/global_8048502.jpeg</photo_url></item>