<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Activate supporters in NH (And Beyond) to SHOW their support for Ron Paul! Tons of voters are on &amp;quot;the fence&amp;quot; about him and often convey that they don't think he has enough support. The election is decided by voters, not the media, and Ron Paul can win if we SHOW IT. ... From now until the next debate (Nov. 9th) we're making a big push to encourage ALL Ron Paul supporters in NH to put up those Ron Paul signs, apply those bumper stickers, throw on those Ron Paul shirts, knock on some doors, come into HQ to make some phone calls, talk to a friend, family member or co-worker... whatever you do, SHOW IT! Take pictures/write descriptions and post them on this site: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=279863038701942" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; and let's SHOW the great amount of support Ron Paul has. It is time to get those undecideds off the fence and we need your help! Post your photos and descriptions here, encourage others to do the same. SHOW IT is all about you and we can't wait to see your pictures, let's make this big... SHOW IT! If you need signs/bumper stickers let us know! Send an email to RonN@ronpaul2012.com. Or stop in to Ron Paul HQ: 128 Hall St, Suite D, Concord, NH 03301 Or go to &lt;a href="http://www.RonPaul2012.com/store/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.RonPaul201...&lt;/a&gt; Help spread the word by re-posting this event/spreading the word on Facebook!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320903448000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319560441000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deadline to submit photos to campaign!</name><id>38655172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320899400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/38655172/</event_url></item>