<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>41 Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.048241</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-745-9911</phone><name>Alpine Adventures</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>341994</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.662804</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Alright zippers, I spoke with Jennifer Duffy from Alpine Adventures. She is reserving space for our group and giving us 10% off!! Please call her to make your reservation. You can either reference the invoice # included in her letter (which I will copy below), or tell her you are from the RI Outdoor Adventure Club. I think her letter will address any questions but please email if I can offer further info. Their website has local lodging suggestions. Check it out. &lt;a href="http://www.alpinezipline.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you rsvp I can forward the waiver of liability which she sent as an attachment. You can probably get it off their website as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to zipping with this group. Thanks for your interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Jenn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Jennifer,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Attached please find invoice # 122936 for your group this January.  As we talked about today November 25th we are going to be holding your reservation for 13 people with the VISA card that was given. Your group will call in separately and will all receive the 10% discount, if spots are not paid for by January 2nd, 2010 they will be reopened to the public with out the $10.00 fee per person. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a 72 hour cancellation policy that can be viewed on the website.  There are also age and weight restrictions and other helpful information on the website at www.alpinezipline.com, including a weight requirement of 70 - 240 lbs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have also attached our waiver of liability.  Please print and have parents sign for the kids under 18 years of age.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We meet for the tour 40 mins. prior in the office&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group Check-in Procedure:&lt;br /&gt;40 mins. prior to tour time group leader(s) come in to the office at 41 Main Street, Lincoln, NH  preferably without the group to alleviate confusion and crowding, with completed waivers for each guest.  Parents sign for their children.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is more than one group, please make a list of participants in each group and attach to corresponding waivers. Payment reconciliation if any would be taken care of at this point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;30 mins. prior to tour time, participants arrive dressed and ready to go. They should use the facilities and take any sharp objects from their pockets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;20 mins. prior to tour time we gear 'em up and get prepped for their adventure with harnesses, lanyards, carabiners and their pulley and a brief orientation from our knowledgeable &amp;amp; friendly staff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10 mins. prior to tour time the van arrives to transport the group to the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't hesitate to call or email with any questions.  We're looking forward to your Zip-line adventure!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jenny Duffy&lt;br /&gt;Office Manager &amp;amp; Group Adventures&lt;br /&gt;Alpine Adventures Outdoor Recreation&lt;br /&gt;41 Main St / POB 1059&lt;br /&gt;Lincoln, NH 03251&lt;br /&gt;Office:(603)745-9911&lt;br /&gt;Fax:(603)745-2630&lt;br /&gt;jenny@alpinezipline.com&lt;br /&gt;www.alpinezipline.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am in the office Wednesday through Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;If you are in need of immediate assistance please call Alpine Adventures Headquarters at (603)745-9911.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264723663000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259186991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zip Lining</name><id>11956434</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263666600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/11956434/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>