<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>403A Centre Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.311988</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 522-2393</phone><name>JuneBug Cafe</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>843073</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114820</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;Thank you to those who e-mailed me--we now have enough board games!  (Taboo, Guesstures, Pictionary, cards, cribbage, Uno, Trumpet, Jenga, and Scrabble)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reservations are now closed.  However, you can try to get on the waitlist, and I'll check my e-mail in the morning.  You will receive e-mail notification if you are moved to YES.  However--you &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;MUST pay by noon in order to come to the event&lt;/span&gt;.  If you don't pay, then I'll allow someone else on the waitlist to come instead.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come have fun with other singles on Valentine's Day!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt; (and help Nerd Fun raise money for Haiti, too!)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;Join us at the June Bug Cafe in Jamaica Plain on Sunday, February 14th, from 2-5pm. &lt;/b&gt;  &lt;i&gt;(directions below)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:  June Bug Cafe only takes cash!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (no credit cards--but there's an ATM next door)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It'll be a relaxed event. We'll have the entire cafe to ourselves!  We'll schmooze (chat), nosh on the muffins, cookies, bagels, sandwiches, soup, tea, coffee, bubble tea, and hot chocolate the cafe will have for sale*, and play board games &lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;(UPDATE:  cafe owner thought she had a bunch of games in storage, but really doesn't--so please bring any group-oriented games you have, such a Pictionary, Taboo, Fluxx, etc.)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;*Be generous with what you buy!  The owner gave me a good price because this is a fundraiser.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus, we'll play custom-made game show games, $20,000 Pyramid and Jeopardy, in a round-robin fashion that will let people get to know each other.  Prizes will be given out! (of course, since this is a fundraiser, the prizes will be very small--or at least, very inexpensive!)  &lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;i&gt;So &amp;quot;Send in the clowns&amp;quot; because &amp;quot;Mona Lisa Smiles&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Land of the lost&amp;quot; (hint: these are categories in the game show)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:  $20, split between venue and donation for Haiti, to be given to &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/12362411/"&gt;Partners in Health&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt; You must pay to RSVP Yes.  If you'd like to make a larger donation, you're welcome to do so.&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because it's Valentine's Day, and this event is for singles, I will do my best to ensure there is an even gender balance.  &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Gender balance is pretty equal, which is great!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So take this day to enjoy being single, hang out with friendly folk, maybe meet someone you like, and know that you're making a donation to people who are in dire need of our help.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to help me?  Are you interested in making a pretty game board? Coming a little early to help me set up?  Decorating the site?  Greeting people the day of?  Have a brilliant idea of something fun we can do?  Let me know!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, thank you to the many people who filled out my survey about what type of event to hold; I ended up not booking a bowling alley because they all charged more than I wanted the event to cost (even with a discount for it being a fundraiser).  But I got other good ideas from reading your comments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=junebug+cafe,+centre+street,+jamaica+plain,+ma,+usa&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;cd=1&amp;amp;ei=5CBiS-qqFYy6zgTzlbzWDg&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;view=map&amp;amp;cid=5717067922432661949&amp;amp;iwloc=A&amp;amp;ved=0CB8QpQY&amp;amp;sa=X"&gt;Go to Googlemap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;By car:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  There is plenty of street parking, especially in the Hi-Lo supermarket, or try surrounding streets.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the Arborway/Jamaicaway.  From Brookline, turn &lt;u&gt;left&lt;/u&gt; onto Perkins Street at the top of the hill (just before Pond starts); from Arborway/Morton St/Centre Street (e.g., via VFW Parkway) -- go past Jamaica Pond, and at light at end of pond turn &lt;u&gt;right&lt;/u&gt; onto Perkins Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go through next light (South Huntington Avenue).  Go down side of Angell Memorial Animal Hospital (lovely murals on wall to right--NW Indian style).  When you come to rotary, turn right and June Bug is a few doors down on right side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or:  from Centre Street/Forest Hills--go down Centre Street to 7-11; stay straight; cafe is two blocks down on left side.&lt;br /&gt;Or:  from S. Huntington Street -- at 7-11, turn left (around the wedge of the parking lot), and cafe is two blocks down on left side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;By MBTA:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Take Orange Line&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to Jackson Square and walk up Centre Street (come out of station and turn right), walk half mile up Centre St.; at rotary, turn left--cafe is a few doors down on right side.  Or go to Stony Brook; come out of station, turn right and walk up Boylston Street.  When you get to Centre St, turn right; cafe is 2 blocks down on left side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;39 bus:&lt;/b&gt;  Take 39 bus from Forest Hills; get off at 7-11 (Moraine St); continue on Centre Street (right side of 7-11), cafe is 2 blocks down on left side.  &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/schedules_and_maps/bus/routes/?route=39&amp;amp;direction=I&amp;amp;timing=U&amp;amp;RedisplayTime=Redisplay+Time"&gt;inbound schedule&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or: Take 39 bus from Back Bay; get off at Perkins Street.  Turn left and walk up Perkins Street.  Go down side of Angell Memorial Animal Hospital (lovely murals on wall to right--NW Indian style).  When you come to rotary, turn right and June Bug is a few doors down on right side.  (Or get off Moraine Street, and turn left to other side of 7-11 parking lot, and walk down 2 blocks) &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/schedules_and_maps/bus/routes/?route=39&amp;amp;direction=O&amp;amp;timing=U&amp;amp;RedisplayTime=Redisplay+Time"&gt;outbound schedule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Need a ride?  Post in your RSVP &amp;quot;need a ride from _____(town)&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup sign on cafe door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6019932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266495255000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264642281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nerd Singles' Valentine's Day Lollapalooza</name><id>12444917</id><headcount>39</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266174000000</time><rsvp_limit>41</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12444917/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/5/e/global_11354654.jpeg</photo_url></item>