<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Thanks to those (5) who showed up for our October meeting, nice discussion on moral objectivity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic: Our topic for November will focus on the worry about reductionism, free will, and responsibility as expressed by British progressive Raymond Tallis in two articles &lt;a href="http://www.spiked-online.com/index.php?/site/article/3893/" target="_blank"&gt;Free will is not an illusion&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.timesonline.co.uk/tol/comment/columnists/guest_contributors/article2726643.ece" target="_blank"&gt;Why blame me? It was all my brain's fault&lt;/a&gt;. Tallis thinks we have to deny neural determinism and be skeptical about &amp;quot;neurolaw&amp;quot; to suppose we are real agents that can be held responsible. Is he right? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another relevant story is here: &lt;a href="http://daily.stanford.edu/article/2007/11/5/profExploresLegalRoleOfNeuroscience" target="_blank"&gt;http://daily.stanford...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;best,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org&lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195085240000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192493286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reductionism and responsibility: did my brain make me do it?</name><id>6556250</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194912000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/6556250/</event_url></item>