<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Live With Passion!&lt;/b&gt;  A Passionate life of endless possibilities for personal and professional success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us for this &amp;quot; Life Changing&amp;quot; 1/2 day seminar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will teach you how to align with your own personal vision, then guide you through a powerful four-step process for creating anew.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An engaging, interactive seminar, we work together a small interactive group to learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•How to stay powerfully aligned with your unique gifts, talents  and to define your purpose that you want to bring forth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•How to understand what stops you (your fears) and clear internal blocks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VISION BOARDS are great for helping us see our potential and believe attaining it is possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yet, need to go deeper, and EMBRACE WHO YOU NEED TO BE to manifest your vision and CLEAR SUBCONSCIOUS limiting beliefs that block the full expression of our highest selves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Without having a vision, a vision has us.  There is a vision that is just outside our conscious awareness…we need only listen long enough to allow it to reveal itself.   Once we glimpse the possibility, we simply say yes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rather than forcing our will upon the Universe, we yield ourselves to become OPEN and AVAILABLE to that which is birthing itself through us.  We SURRENDER completely and ALLOW the vision to take us over.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY BELIEFS need to be addressed, along with vision boards and intentions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--you must believe in the possibility of a particular intention before it can come to us…so clearing any blocks to belief must be addressed first….focusing on the vision board will be meaningless if you don’t believe you can have what you put on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Consciousness precedes matter.”—Albert Einstein.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, you set your intention to put on vision board.  Then, you take the actions that support the manifestation of the intention.  Surrender and have faith.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So four steps (and most people ignore the crucial first one, which is critical to other three working):[Soft Break][Soft Break]    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Clear limiting beliefs (often requires the help of another who can mirror where you are blocked at a subconscious level)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.Set you daily Intent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.Take supporting actions and find people that will help you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.Surrender, ACT and trust, have faith….timing is not yours to determine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“There is a mystery that unfolds when you are simply standing inside the intention you set.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--you must also DEVELOP A CONSISTENCY BETWEEN WHAT YOU SAY AND THE ACTIONS YOU TAKE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•How to set clear intentions for new outcomes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•How to bring forth new dreams, visions or pupose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•How to set this in motion everyday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COME DREAM NEW DREAMS…and LEARN HOW TO BRING THEM TO THE WORLD IN SERVICE TO OTHERS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is it time again! &lt;br /&gt;Are you starting over again?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or do you feel stagnant, like you are just spinning your wheels?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;October 16th, This event is always weel attended so call, email or respond ASAP. &lt;br /&gt;This event is $25.00 for 3 1/2 hour that could very well change your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are not meant to do this alone! Join this amazing group of support, friendship and successful people WANT to give back and help other succeed! This is our way of giving back!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well here it is! Something that could change your life. This Vision Voice and Message workshop is designed to help you create your Purpose in LIfe, Your New Beginning starting now! Let's work together and start now to put your best Life ever into ACTION. This is opportinity is here, now, so nothing is stopping you from your GOALS in life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have been here before and created a Vision Board please bring it with you. If you have not don't worry about it, this workshop is about creating it and writing it down, making it part of your everyday life and to work it into your New Morning Routine (NMR) and your New Evening Routine. We shall create together a seven sentence statement that will keep you focused on your dreams in life and work on getting it to appear daily. So make that step, get in touch with me and say &amp;quot;YES I am Ready&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Mindful Wealth Seminar reveals the most powerful laws in the universe. &lt;br /&gt;The knowledge of these laws have run like a golden thread through the lives and the teachings of all the prophets and through the lives of all truly great men and women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All that they have ever accomplished or attained has been done in full accordance with this most powerful law&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ The Laws of Intent. Purpose and Attraction&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Folks, YES! WE are back! Anthony Pasquale will be holding This Vision Board/Statement Workshop! Specializing in &amp;quot;how to put it into action&amp;quot; workshop. Finding the Purpose within!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All are welcome! If you have attended these events in the past, it was such a success we had to book four other workshops&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have been to one of these workshops, Bring your Vision Board and either finish it or update it with new goals in your life. If this is your FIRST time, WELL you are in for an amazing life changing event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also Anthony J. Pasquale will be there to teach you his Five Pillars to Mindful Wealth Everyday! &lt;br /&gt;Anthony will be sharing his Goal Setting Vision Statement processes that he says &amp;quot;will put your life on course&amp;quot; and help you find your CHIEF AIM in life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be held October 16th 1:30pm to 4:30pm for the workshop PLUS: from 445pm to 530pm we may have a special guest drop by.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do Not Wait to book your space we only have 25 seats and six are already taken.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to change your life!!! Things to Bring to this Visioneering Workshop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Imagination &lt;br /&gt;2. Desire (write it out) &lt;br /&gt;3. Your &amp;quot;Why&amp;quot; in Life (write it out) &lt;br /&gt;4. Persistence &lt;br /&gt;5. The life style you want. (write it out) &lt;br /&gt;6. Where and with who. (write it out) &lt;br /&gt;7. What you are willing to give in return for your goals. (write it out) &lt;br /&gt;8. The Date that you want your goals done by! (write it out) &lt;br /&gt;9. 5 x 8 index cards, Markers. Glue stick (mini Vison Board) &lt;br /&gt;10. Any decorative items you may want to put on your board. Most importantly anything that, &amp;quot;Speaks to you!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;11. Open Mind to Adunance and Wealth. &lt;br /&gt;12. Sense of Humor. &lt;br /&gt;13. A willness to be coachable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some of the things that will be covered:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Awakening, Voice, Vision, Message!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fear and how to filter and use it the right way!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Seven Daily Steps through Mindful Wealth Living.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating your Vision. (Your Vision Board)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating your Voice. (Your Vision Statement)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creating your message in life. (Your Vision Symbol)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Vision in life will determine your decisions in life! &lt;br /&gt;(You will do this excerises for the rest of your life!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sifu Anthony Pasquale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AJP Enterprise &lt;br /&gt;United Martial Arts Center &lt;br /&gt;Osanna Seminars &lt;br /&gt;Mindful Wealth Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Live with purpose and passion everyday&amp;quot; !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.umachealth.com &lt;br /&gt;www.danversmartialarts.com &lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street, Suite 100 &lt;br /&gt;Danvers MA 01923 &lt;br /&gt;(978) 836-6501&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain &amp;quot;average&amp;quot;. These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287771016000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Practicers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-732</urlname><id>1196018</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Danvers " The Secret  "Vision Board Workshop Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283449119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mindful Wealth! Beyond the Vision Board!</name><id>14634116</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287248400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-732/events/14634116/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/e/b/global_4551819.jpeg</photo_url></item>