<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;CT REIA and Robyn Thompson presents:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson – Learn how to buy, renovate, and sell single and multifamily homes for huge profits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson is the leading expert in buying, renovating and selling single and multifamily homes for huge profits. Robyn has renovated and sold over 235 homes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;January 25, 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crowne Plaze Hotel&lt;br /&gt;Cromwell, CT&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm-9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;FREE for CT REIA members&lt;br /&gt;$30 for not-yet-members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register now for this monthly meeting at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=224" target="_blank"&gt;ctreia.com/events.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Are you tired of having more month than you have money?&lt;br /&gt;* Are you looking for financial independence?&lt;br /&gt;* Are you ready to start a business that will generate huge chunks of cash?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you answered yes to any of these questions, retailing ugly houses is for you! Robyn has taught thousands of students how to achieve financial independence by investing in distressed properties. Robyn has made retailing homes a science and she knows every technique imaginable to locate profitable deals, renovate distressed properties at lightning speed, minimize holding costs, and qualify good credit buyers and expedite closings so you can collect a big check.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn Robyn’s trade secrets for buying and repairing distressed homes, as well as selling and cashing out investment properties, designed for both novice real estate investors and seasoned professionals! Robyn has taught hundreds of students already, and now you have the opportunity to learn everything you need to know to begin retailing houses and making money in your hometown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who Is Robyn Thompson?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson real estate Robyn Thompson is the nations leading expert on buying, renovating and selling homes for huge chunks of cash and is known throughout the United States and Canada as “The Queen of Rehab”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After spending 9 years working a dead end corporate job, Robyn realized that her hard work and dedication for IBM was not going to provided financial independence. She walked away from her secure paycheck and never looked back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the past 11 years since Robyn left IBM, she has bought, fixed and sold 260 homes with price ranges as low as $8,000 to as high as $4,000,000. She has spent as much as $2,100,000 in labor and materials in one year to renovate properties with more than 22 contractors working full time to take the ugly homes she bought and turn them into little castles at lightening speed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn will be sharing her strategies on: 1) How to find the profitable homes that need renovated, 2) How to find and control the contractors to get the job done and 3) Selling houses quickly for huge chunks of cash.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn has taught thousands of students throughout the United States how to become financially independent. She has shared the stage with Donald Trump, Dr Phil, Mark Victor Hansen, Ron LeGrand, Marshall Sylver &amp;amp; many more legends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn uses her success in the real estate business to help those less fortunate. The most recent construction project that Robyn completed was an orphanage in Haiti for 165 children that opened on February 21st, 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 – Members Workshop&lt;br /&gt;5:40-6:40 – Network with investors, vendors, and professionals&lt;br /&gt;6:40-7:00 – Member Deals and Announcements&lt;br /&gt;7:00 – Guest speaker: Robyn Thompson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register now for this monthly meeting at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=224" target="_blank"&gt;ctreia.com/events.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264631964000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261438853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. January Meetup</name><id>lvqfjyncbhc</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264458600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12128264/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/5/global_12369445.jpeg</photo_url></item>