<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://www.coolidge.org/sites/default/files/images/banners/storieswetell_banner.jpg?1366209561" width="606" height="340" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v9AJgNqsxQA"&gt;Watch Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;1hr 48mins&lt;/span&gt; // directed by:&lt;span&gt;Sarah Polley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=f740e0c1-ba1c-4632-b43d-0f9f0a474d69&amp;amp;evtcode=33971~2227d6a5-68f5-41c2-b22e-813c872c64f4&amp;amp;"&gt;Stories We Tell Tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Always better to reserve tickets ahead of time, unnecessarily, than to get shut-out at the theater when you arrive on Opening Weekend expecting to get a ticket at the last minute to a popular film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this inspired, genre-twisting new film, Oscar-nominated writer/-outdirector Sarah Polley discovers that the truth depends on who’s telling it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Polley is both filmmaker and detective as she investigates the secrets kept by a family of storytellers. She playfully interviews and interrogates a cast of characters of varying reliability, eliciting refreshingly candid, yet mostly contradictory, answers to the same questions. As each relates their version of the family mythology, present-day recollections shift into nostalgia-tinged glimpses of their mother, who departed too soon, leaving a trail of unanswered questions. Polley unravels the paradoxes to reveal the essence of family: always complicated, warmly messy and fiercely loving. &lt;span&gt;Stories We Tell&lt;/span&gt; explores the elusive nature of truth and memory, but at its core is a deeply personal film about how our narratives shape and define us as individuals and families, all interconnecting to paint a profound, funny and poignant picture of the larger human story.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the AV Club: &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;there’s much more to &lt;em&gt;Stories We Tell&lt;/em&gt; than navel-gazing. Polley’s fledgling foray into documentary filmmaking is also an investigative mystery, a real-life soap opera, and—most compellingly, perhaps—a searching “interrogation” (the director’s word) of the hows and whys of storytelling itself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;From the NYT: "Building on the interest in narrative form that she expressed in earlier movies like “Take This Waltz,” she explores storytelling itself and the space between a life lived and its different, at times conflicting representations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #263469"&gt;Following the film, we have reservations at Pho Lemongrass (Banh xeo crepe and Fisherman's Hot Pot highly recommended) for post-film discussion.  Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend ASAP as we have several people on the Waiting List.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To be Continued,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will gather the group AFTER close of credits in the lobby area holding an authentic, antique, Meetup Sign, so that we can use the restroom and go to a nearby eatery</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1369009889000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368399844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stories We Tell</name><id>119058372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368918900000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/119058372/</event_url></item>