<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Walnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02460</zip><lat>42.346506</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>United Methodist Church</name><city>Newtonville</city><id>1280079</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.206274</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>Online/$15Door</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Optimum Health Solution &amp;amp;   &lt;br /&gt;Raw New England Community Dinner Speaker Series   &lt;br /&gt;welcomes back:  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Adiel Tel-Oren (Dr. T), MD, DC, LN, CCN, DABFM,  &lt;br /&gt;DACBN, FABDA Nutritional, Environmental &amp;amp; Functional  &lt;br /&gt;Medicine Public &amp;amp; Professional Lectures Worldwide  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Explore a Revolutionary New Scientific System  &lt;br /&gt;to Boost Every Aspect of Your Health!  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Speaking on  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;IMMUNE HEALTH MICROBIAL BALANCE, INFECTIOUS AGENTS,  &lt;br /&gt;ANTIBIOTICS, &amp;amp; FLU PREVENTION WITHOUT VACCINATIONS  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;When: Sunday, May 8th at 7&amp;ndash;9:30PM including Q &amp;amp; A  &lt;br /&gt;Come Early to Register at 6:30PM and assure a seat.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Where: United Methodist Church, 430 Walnut St. Newton MA  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Skin Clinics - Consults Available&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A skin tag is a common, acquired benign skin growth that looks like a small piece of hanging skin. Skin tags are often described as bits of skin- or flesh-colored tissue that projects from the surrounding skin from a small, narrow stalk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nutritional/Clinical CONSULTATIONS  &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, May 8 &amp;amp; Monday May 9  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot;Consults are held at Betsy's (my) home, 126 Myrtle St., Waltham, MA. 02453  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;For Appointments and Questions, call Betsy 617-835-2913    &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Tickets $12 on line at &lt;a href="http://www.OptimumHealthSolution.org"&gt;www.OptimumHealthSolution.org&lt;/a&gt; or $15 at door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HAVE YOUR SKIN LESIONS REMOVED BY DR. TEL-OREN  &lt;br /&gt;MAY 8 OR 9&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sign up today or call 617-835-2913 for an appointment now with Dr. Adiel Tel-Oren to remove Skin Growths &amp;amp; Blemishes.  Limited space on Sunday, May 8 afternoon and Monday, May 9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How are they removed?  Dr. Tel-Oren lightly applies to the lesion his safe, effective non-medical liquid &amp;ndash; modified trichloracetic acid (similar, yet gentler than the one mentioned in the AMA Journal, April 8, 1972, p 210; and Obstet &amp;amp; Gnec. Audio-digest Vol 20 #2, Jn 23, 1973).  Even small children can tolerate the slight burning sensation (similar to a mosquito bite).  The lesion&amp;rsquo;s nutrition is restricted by the liquid, which causes the circulation to constrict.  A scab forms in a few days, then drops off in a few weeks, leaving esthetically pleasing skin.  The best results are achieved with growths on the face (any size!).  Mild de-pigmentation may occasionally occur on the arms, legs &amp;amp; torso, especially when  melanin-containing or cancer-prone flat areas are treated.  Any deeper layer of pigment that might remain can be safely retreated, as no blood vessels are penetrated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DR. TEL-OREN&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. T. is a sought after holistic scientist who educates medical professionals and the general public about functional medicine and disease prevention via truly natural lifestyle and dietary modification.  He is a licensed European Medical Doctor, Licensed Nutritionist and is American Board Certified of Functional Medicine, of Oxidative Medicine and of Chelation Therapy.  Founder of several holistic non-profits in US  and Nepal, Asia, Africa &amp;amp; Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. T has treated 36,000 patients in over 22 years and when he was here on January 15th he healed 30 of our members of skin lesions.   Make your appointments NOW for May 8 &amp;amp; 9 since Dr. T's time is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. T promotes "EcoRaw Living" as a model for optimal cellular health and the principles of sustainability.  He is the owner and manager of a raw, organic restaurant, Ecopolitan, in Minneapolis. Dr. T  offers nutritional medical care  in Africa, East and South Asia, Europe, the Americas, and the Tropics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is the Founder and Co-Founder of several non-profit Health and Sustainability Programs Worldwide. This includes the Center for Community Development in Nepal (with its Community Health Program that cares for 200,000 Nepali villagers); The Israeli Center for Functional Medicine; The Eco-Sphere Green Community Project in Wisconsin; and the Ecopolitan Eco-Health Network with its numerous communities in the USA - supporting healthy lifestyle, Intensive Healing Retreats, Tropical Escapes, Foraging trips, Eco-Raw Restaurants, Clinics, University Degrees and Certification Programs, and Humanitarian Eco-Trekking adventures. Dr. T is also founder of the world's first hypoallergenic GF/DF vegan bakery (www.greenbakery.net)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;European &amp;amp; US-Trained MD &amp;middot; European Medical License 1996 &amp;middot; USA Nutrition License 1997 &amp;middot; MN Board of Nutrition &amp;amp; Dietetics &amp;middot; USA Doctor of Chiropractic, practiced 1990 through 2001 &amp;middot; Professor &amp;amp; Board Certified Clinical Nutritionist with the IAACN &amp;amp; CNCB &amp;middot; Board Certified, American Board of Functional Medicine, American Clinical Board of Nutrition, American Board of Oxidative Medicine, American Board of Chelation Therapy; Fellow, American Board of Disability Analysts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President &amp;amp; Founder: &amp;middot; Ecopolitan Eco-Health Network, Ecopolitan Restaurant and Non-Profit Community (www.ecopolitan.com); &amp;middot; The Eco-Sphere Green Building Project &amp;middot; The Green Bakery (Beyond Gluten Free&amp;trade; ) - The First Hypoallergenic Bread (www.greenbakery.net) &amp;middot; Co-Founder: CCODER Nepal's Health Plan (CCODER.org), caring for 200,000 villagers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President Emeritus &amp;amp; Professor of Nutrition and Functional Medicine: &amp;middot; University of Natural Medicine, Santa Fe, NM &amp;middot; Functional &amp;amp; Dental Health (FDH) Foundation, Founder &amp;middot; Bio-Mental Health Foundation, Founder &lt;a href="http://www.ecopolitan.com/doctor-t" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ecopolitan.com/doctor-t&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to print a name tag and carpool.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/d/3/event_20759347.jpeg" width="108" height="163" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Feel free to print name tag and carpool. www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 11398866</member_name><member_id>11398866</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304899735000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302539672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS/RNEC: Dr. Adiel Tel-Oren (Waltham)</name><id>17263662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304895600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/17263662/</event_url></item>