<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Lansdowne St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 693-2583</phone><name>House of Blues</name><city>Boston</city><id>924938</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The award-winning producers at Teton Gravity Research (TGR) present their newest ski film, Light The Wick. Shot using film, HD and 3D technology, Light The Wick is about sparking the flame and watching the world's best athletes blast off. This winter the TGR crew of athletes and cinematographers captured the most jaw-dropping footage ever witnessed. The team traveled around the world to uncharted destinations, as well as some of their favorite stomping grounds. Follow the crew as they discover the previously unskied big mountain playground of Petersburg, AK, find the best snow Croatia has seen in fifty years, ski deep pillows in undiscovered Italy, hit full throttle riding in British Columbia, and experience epic free-riding at Ripley Creek and North Cascades Heli. Don't miss Sammy Carlson and the Stevens Pass 3D experiment, the first ever 3D ski segment. The groundbreaking dual RED One slow motion arial shots will make you want to reach out and touch the action. Light The Wick showcases the most talented and well-rounded athletes in skiing together in one must-see film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Athletes: Sage Cattabriga-Alosa, Seth Morrison, Kye Petersen, Ian McIntosh, Dana Flahr, Dylan Hood, Sammy Carlson, Dash Longe, Rachael Burks, Callum Pettit, Wiley Miller, Erik Roner, Cody Townsend, Todd Ligare, Chris Benchetler, Shroder Baker, Daron Rahlves, Byron Wells, John Spriggs and friends&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Locations: Croatia, La Thuile Italy, Petersburg AK, Pemberton BC, Last Frontier Heli Skiing, Jackson Hole WY, North Cascade Heli Skiing, Idaho, Oregon, Utah, Grand Targhee WY and Stevens Pass WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Every attendee will receive a 2 for 1 lift ticket for Sugarbush Ski Resort***&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will meet in the restaurant at 5pm.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tetongravity.com/tour/lightthewick/" target="_blank"&gt;Teton Gravity Research &amp;quot;Light the Wick&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tetongravity.com/tour/lightthewick/event.aspx?tid=764" target="_blank"&gt;BUY YOUR TICKET!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will call tickets will NOT be available until 1 hour prior to door time.  Doors open 7pm, show starts 8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.houseofblues.com/tickets/eventdetail.php?eventid=65971" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to buy tickets via HOB website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll have a booth set up on the ground floor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Buckley</member_name><member_id>3881633</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Krissie</member_name><member_id>6035276</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sara Hickson</member_name><member_id>7424991</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ken Simon</member_name><member_id>8614118</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nung</member_name><member_id>8898177</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289692207000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286995056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Teton Gravity Research "Light the Wick" at House of Blues</name><id>15098450</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289599200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/15098450/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/4/global_18718356.jpeg</photo_url></item>