<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Stevie from the &lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Providence French Language Meetup Group&lt;/span&gt; on &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;March 26 at 6.45 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; for &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&amp;quot;La Faute a Fidel/Blame it on Fidel&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, the 3rd film of the &lt;b&gt;Salve Regina French Film Festival held in Newport RI&lt;/b&gt; between &lt;b&gt;22 March to 2 April 2009&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films are being shown to the public for no charge thanks to the support of the French American Cultural Exchange (FACE), the Cultural Services of the French Embassy and the French Ministry of Culture (CNC). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An &lt;b&gt;RSVP limit of 15&lt;/b&gt; will ensure we have enough seats in the theater given its freely available to all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the film&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Salve Regina French Film Festival website shows the following details for the screening of this film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;La Faute a Fidel/Blame it on Fidel&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date &amp;amp; Time&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;b&gt;7 p.m. Thursday, March 26&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Bazarsky Lecture Hall, O'Hare Academic Center&lt;/span&gt;  - Ochre Point Avenue Newport RI - see campus map for precise directions &lt;a href="http://www.salve.edu/academics/SRU-CampusMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;SRU-CampusMap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;A charming comedy of manners, class and politics that takes place during the political revolution sweeping France during the 1970s.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Further details about the film (taken from the FACE Tournées Festival information at &lt;a href="http://www.facecouncil.org/tournees/fichesfilms/lafauteafidel.html" target="_blank"&gt;FACE/tournees/fichesfilms/lafauteafidel.html&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Anna is a nine-year old precocious girl. Her life is rather simple and comfortable, regulated by habits and order. Her family is wealthy, she goes to a private religious school and often visits her grandparents who have a wine estate in Bordeaux. One day, her father's sister is forced to leave Spain - her husband has just been killed by Franco's police force. This event is experienced as an electroshock by Anna's parents and they change their political views radically. Both become left-wing revolutionaries and Anna's stable life goes awry. Women's rights, freedom of speech, democracy and demonstration are now at the forefront of Anna's parents lives. At first, Anna is not interested in any of it. She strives to hold on to the comfort she is used to and she is very unhappy when the family moves to a smaller apartment. She also has to adapt to her parents' new lifestyle as they have less time to take care of her. Yet, she also tries to make sense of the larger political events that shake her life and she does not settle for the simplistic answers that adults give children.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTOR&lt;/u&gt; - Julie Gavras&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;SCREENPLAY&lt;/u&gt; - Julie Gavras, Arnaud Cathrine. Based on Domitilla Calamai's novel Tutta colpa di Fidel.&lt;br /&gt;CAST&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna: Nina Kervel-Bey&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Marie: Julie Depardieu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fernando: Stefano Accorsi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;François: Benjamin Feuillet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bonne Maman: Martine Chevallier&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bon Papa: Olivier Perrier&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Running time&lt;/u&gt;: 99’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Production&lt;/u&gt;: France / Italy, 2006&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rating&lt;/u&gt;: Not rated&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gauge&lt;/u&gt;: 35mm, DVD (color)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;GENRE&lt;/u&gt; - Drama&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DISTRIBUTOR&lt;/u&gt; - Koch Lorber Films&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of those rare films that maintain unwavering fidelity to a child's view of the world (a lineage that includes 'The 400 Blows' and 'Lukas Moodysson's Together'). It's not [merely] a snapshot of the revolutionary politics of 1970-71; it's about the upheavals of childhood, which are timeless and universal.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Beer, Time Out New York&lt;br /&gt;______________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is being organised by Stevie Worthington as part of a &lt;b&gt;6 part Meetup event&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Providence French Language Meetup group&lt;/span&gt; held in &lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;NEWPORT RI&lt;/span&gt;. If you can't make this night, hopefully you can make it to at least one of the other films in the Film festival on either &lt;b&gt;22 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;24 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;29 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;31 Mar&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;2 April&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, send Stevie an email - merci!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be inside the lobby from 6.30pm wearing a pink jacket holding a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238350133000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236709426000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Film Festival in Newport - Film 3 "La Faute a Fidel/Blame it on Fidel"</name><id>9924392</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238108400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/9924392/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/6/4/global_7623940.jpeg</photo_url></item>