<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Wilkins St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01749</zip><lat>42.395193</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wilkins Street Parking lot</name><city>Hudson</city><id>960779</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537024</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I just heard about this trail today and want to check it out. Its a short one, but sounds nice. Please let me know if you know any nearby places to extend the ride or to stop for a snack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.arrtinc.org/index.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.arrtinc.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Assabet River Rail Trail provides a forested escape from the surrounding urban bustle. Traveling 5.6 miles (with plans to expand it to 12 miles, the trail connects the towns of Hudson and Marlborough, and parallels the scenic Assabet River. The trail crosses the Assabet River five times, the last crossing on a refurbished, historical wrought iron railroad bridge. The 12-foot-wide corridor makes an excellent cycling route-just take care maneuvering between bollards located at the intersection of trails and roads; they are closer together than most. The trail begins along Route 62 in Hudson, marked by a trailside, restored, 1921 blue caboose across the road from an ice-cream store. Look for the trailhead parking area. Passing through downtown Hudson, the trail weaves through the awkward three-way intersection of Villa do Porto Boulevard, Broad Street, and the South Street extension. Returning to the rail corridor, you'll cross a wooden bridge, followed by more trailhead parking on your right. The forested trail here provides a welcome buffer from the surrounding residential and urban landscape. At mile 2.4, you'll cross the Marlborough town line through a tunnel. The onward trail skirts a main road north, passing the Boston Scientific medical research and corporate center before reaching Fitchburg Street. Be careful at this intersection, as there are no bike lanes and the traffic light cycle doesn't allow much time to cross. Beyond the crossing, there are no bike lanes. Look for the trail sign after the intersection, and you will find yourself leaving the traffic behind. As the path diverges from the road, the adjacent, landscaped swathes on either side of the route shield trail users from the busy urban environment. Side trails connect to the Assabet along this stretch. Eventually, the trail will extend to South Acton along the Marlborough Branch Railroad corridor, which connected the Fitchburg and Massachusetts Central railroad lines. The five communities along the corridor are working together to develop the rail-trail.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Parking &amp;amp; Trail Access:&lt;br /&gt;To reach the Wilkins Street trailhead in Hudson, take Interstate 495 to State Route 62 toward Hudson. Once in town, continue through the rotary to the parking lot on Wilkins Street.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244995652000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Leisure Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-235</urlname><id>527341</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Boston Leisure Bicycling</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242527757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Assabet River Rail Trail - Memorial day</name><id>10428689</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243270800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-235/events/10428689/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/1/global_1549089.jpeg</photo_url></item>