<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2nd floor Suite 6B - (take elevator)</address_2><address_1>201 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518875</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-240-3671</phone><name>A Higher Balance </name><city>Salem</city><id>848691</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895309</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Color as a Portal to Profound Intuitive Insight &lt;br /&gt;

Drawing on the energy-filled images of the Aura-Soma® ‘New Aeon’ Tarot deck, we will consider the richness of information available in viewing ourselves through the lens of color. We will start with basic chakra colors and expand to include the aura. Each attendee will receive a mini-consultation during the workshop. $35 advance reg by Jan 10, $40 at door. Register: Barb_Ducharme@Yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;

Individual readings with beautiful cards depicting beings of light will be available following the workshop. Learn about the symbolic meanings of your color selections. Experience colors and the Aura-Soma Tarot deck as a gateway to deep insight into your innate gifts and talents, your deep inner resources for meeting life’s challenges, your Soul’s perspective on your life path, and what’s next in your relationships, career, personal and spiritual development, and more. Book your private session directly: Barb_Ducharme@yahoo.com. $30 for 20 minutes, $45 for 30 minutes. &lt;br /&gt;

 Barb is a long-time student of theories and techniques of personal development and well-being, including Life Energy Alignment Process, Dowsing, Aura-Soma®, and Labyrinths.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara Ducharme</member_name><member_id>3582123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358010727000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Women Supporting Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Women-Social-Network-Group</urlname><id>1379831</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journeys</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356714631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Color Workshop and Private Readings with Barb</name><id>96829662</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358002800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-Social-Network-Group/events/96829662/</event_url></item>