<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Friday nights should be a good time to share a few laughs and drinks with friends and what better way to do it than hanging out at a Comedy Club. Motleys Club was voted Best of 09 by Phoenix magazine(No idea what the heck that is but who cares). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Myq Kaplan is the featured comic for the day and there will be several others. You can find more info about him at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myqkaplan.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myqkaplan....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also reserve your tickets online for $20  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mottleyscomedy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mottleysco...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure to buy tickets for Myq Kaplan performance on 10/02/2009. It almost sounds like I am promoting the guy, but really not, just trying to make sure you get tickets for the right show since there are a few lined up. Please update the discussion board once you have bought the ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the show for those who are interested we can hang out at a local bar/club/lounge whatever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discount parking is available at 75 State Street Garage, you can print out a coupon from Comedy Clubs website.Closest T stop would be State Street on Orange line/ Blue Line, you can walk from there in about 5-7 mins Please get there at least half and hour early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karan&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karan</member_name><member_id>8985082</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255651463000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254368259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mottley's Comedy Club!!!</name><id>11515666</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254528000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/11515666/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/c/global_10053356.jpeg</photo_url></item>