<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>311 Temple St</address_1><state>CT</state><lat>41.309502</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Downtown Evening Soup Kitchen</name><city>New Haven</city><id>682661</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924713</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us as we help one of &lt;a href="http://www.downtowneveningsoupkitchen.com" target="_blank"&gt;New Haven's finest (and most critical) non-profit organizations&lt;/a&gt; serve dinner to 150-200 of New Haven's hungriest.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We usually only do this once a year, but DESK is in critical need of volunteers right now!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The homeless population of New Haven increases greatly in the summertime, just as the school, church, and civic groups that normally assist the &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=77929646515#/group.php?gid=46316116888" target="_blank"&gt;Downtown Evening Soup Kitchen (DESK)&lt;/a&gt; are away on vacation.   There has been an increase in demands for services due to the current economic situation as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be serving a massive amount of fresh food (no food prep necessary for this commitment) for the 5:45-6:45pm meal.  We'll need to arrive at 5:30 to help set up, and then will man the stations to dole out the offerings of the evening as efficiently and kindly as possible.  Cleanup (sweeping and wiping down tables, and running&lt;a href="http://www.newhavenindependent.org/archives/2009/03/greening_the_op.php" target="_blank"&gt; DESK's exciting new dishwasher&lt;/a&gt;) is done by 7pm or so, leaving plenty of time for any plans you already have (or may want to make as a group) afterward for dinner, beer, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact is Michelle.  Feel free to email with any questions or concerns.  I'll be emailing out my cell phone number as a contact to the YES people the day before the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special note: because of the nature of this event, it's very important that you show up, if you've RSVPed!  If you can't make it, please change your RSVP in time to allow someone else to sign up, or for me to twist some arms to replace you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one in latex gloves and a hair net (and so will you at some point)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1250345043000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248260025000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The NHC Volunteers: Serving Dinner at D.E.S.K.--S.O.S. edition!</name><id>10931007</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250026200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/10931007/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/2/6/global_9806086.jpeg</photo_url></item>