<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01864</zip><lat>42.577489</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kittys Restaurant</name><city>North Reading </city><id>795105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111330</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is going to be a double Workshop for the price of one!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first hour of the Workshop will focus on the techniques and tips on street photography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Workshop will consist of :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finding the best locations &lt;br /&gt;Which Camera should you use &lt;br /&gt;Camera Settings &lt;br /&gt;Becoming invisable &lt;br /&gt;shooting from the hip &lt;br /&gt;legal aspects of street photography &lt;br /&gt;Getting up close&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is great for those of you with DSLR but also with simple point and shoots! Street photography involves using less equipment and leaving all those expensive toys at home or in the store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Next hour of the workshop we will look at how to take great photos of Holiday lights and scenes!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will cover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Lighting circumstances &lt;br /&gt;Filters &lt;br /&gt;Using your Flash - Built in or external &lt;br /&gt;Inside scenes and Portraits &lt;br /&gt;Outside Lights and Holiday Landscapes &lt;br /&gt;Using ISO or ASA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bonus!! Come practice what you learned!! On Saturday November 21st(earlier each year) we will be heading into Boston for the annual Tree lighting Ceremony. This event starts with at 11am with events running all day long.. The tree itself will be lit at 5:30pm.. This is going to be a open event as some members may want to arrive later or earlier then others. If you do want to meet up with the group we can form some meetup locations and times.. A seperate listing for this event will also be posted for the rest of the group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258762128000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257441389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Street Photography and Holiday Lights Workshop</name><id>11803483</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258588800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/11803483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/1/global_11655521.jpeg</photo_url></item>