<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>west hartford</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.764294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>caryl's house</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>462542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.727501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am extrodinarily late in posting a writeup for March's theme. One of the reasons is that there is so much in the news right now that seems, to me, connected with long marches. The main reason though is that I have written about long marches before back in the summer of 2001 for a magazine that no longer exsists. There are personally a lot of connections and associations to the the words "long march" for me. So below is a updated reprint of one of the articles I wrote over a decade ago. I offer it because I can. The Avon 3-Day no longer exists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;7/10/2001 (publish date)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the end of July, I will be joining 4000 others in the long walk from San Jose to San Francisco. I have been writing about why I am doing this and whom the walk supports for several months now. I have detailed my experience at different levels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 13px"&gt;This month I have noticed that many of the people with whom I have corresponded or walked in preparation of doing this 60 mile journey through Northern California have begun to withdraw or find themselves challenged to participate in the event even after months of training and raising $6.7 million for the Avon Breast Cancer Crusade. My regular walking partner, for example, was out one evening and somehow managed to fracture a bone in her foot while dancing. She went to the doctor and was told she couldn't do the walk. Bless her; she went to another doctor for a second opinion, and again she was told she had a fracture. This doctor, however, said she could do the walk if she wore hiking boots and listened to her pain, allowing the "sweep van" to pick her up and carry her into camp rather than try and push herself too hard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I was shopping for furniture last week and walked smack into a knee-high coffee table. The result is a doozy of a black and blue bruise, and an ice bag on my raised right knee every day after a walk. I have also noticed my toenails darkening on three toes. I too decided to consult a physician, and, taking a lesson from my walking partner, I called two doctors. Both said the same thing to me. If I have my toes treated now I run the risk of making them tender. They both suggested I do the walk and seek treatment afterwards. Both said I would in all likelihood lose those three toenails. Showering this morning I noticed a fourth turning black - due to my 20-mile walk yesterday no doubt.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Yesterday, my current favorite shoes had the shank break through the bottom and press into the ball of my foot every step beginning around mile 18 and continuing through the end of my walk. The wonderful people at Fleet Feet are replacing my shoes (thanks to them!). After going there, I came home, by then barely able to walk, and put my left leg up with my right, an ice pack now resting on the left leg shin splint caused by walking in the defective shoe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Driving home from a meeting, I was thinking about what a pain this walk was and how I am tired of it all and how much time this is all taking from my life. I was thinking about my walking partner and others who have real injures from doing this and how we haven't even gotten to the walk yet. I was thinking about those friends and family of mine who haven't come through with as much of a pledge as I had thought they would. I thought of the friends I have who almost won't speak to me they are so tired of hearing about my "walk." I had a life once, I thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I was on my way home thinking about all these things when I tuned into &lt;a href="http://www.thislife.org/"&gt;This American Life's&lt;/a&gt; Fourth of July show on the car radio. Writer Sarah Vowell was narrating a trip she and her twin sister took to retrace the &lt;a href="http://ngeorgia.com/history/nghisttt.html"&gt;Trail of Tears&lt;/a&gt; - the route their Cherokee ancestors took when expelled from their land. Much of the ambivalence she expresses in this piece I found reflective of my own mood. Yet in the end I cried.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I thought about what it meant to me. I had heard the story of the Trail of Tears many times before. Now though, I understood the story from a very different place. For the first time I understood this piece of history not just from the wildly unjust historic point of view or the emotional or mental anguish. Now I understand this story from the physical aspect. What I understood immediately was that my physical experience when I do my 3-Day Walk will be to the people who were made to walk the Trail of Tears a mere taste from the plate they were served. And so I reflected on other Long Walks and thought about the complexity of our lives and our history.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;One of the questions that Sarah Vowell raised in her radio story was "What is history good for anyway?" I think I know the answer in part. History changes our own experience of life. It is the window in the room of the present allowing us a vista beyond the four walls of now. It changes our perspective and allows us to know and therefore recognize what is best and worst in others and ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I dried my tears, turned off the radio and thought about how good my legs are looking, how strong I feel. I remembered the dress size I've come down. I reflected on the opportunities that have opened up for me directly from participating in the 3-Day Walk. I smiled over the deeper friendship that has developed between my walking partner and myself and the wonderful people I have met on my training walks, the new friends I have made. I thought about how two years ago I was so physically damaged that a half block walk slowly down to the corner store and back again to the house was a big accomplishment for my day. I thought about how strong and confident I felt in general even when limping a little. I thought about the friends, family and strangers who have given to this cause so very generously. I thought about people like my son who not only contributed to my fund raising but also gave me a wonderful sleeping bag for my birthday so I could be comfortable during the nights of my walk. I thought about my friends who have offered to walk a few miles with me at the start of one of my longer solo walks just to keep me company. I considered the people I have touched by writing of my experience. I thought about my effort toward saving those 41,500 individuals who otherwise might die from breast cancer this year. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I still have a life. Only now it is a better life, and I walk through it softly, with fuller awareness and an &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/photos/263619/#21773834"&gt;old dog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just a few more historic long walks: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As white settlers and prospectors pushed westward in the latter half of the 19th century, displacement of Native Americans from their ancestral homelands became commonplace. One of the most tragic episodes of exile was the Long Walk in 1864, when Kit Carson rounded up 8,000 Navajos and forced them to walk more than 300 miles from northeastern Arizona and northwestern New Mexico to Bosque Redondo, a desolate tract on the Pecos River in eastern New Mexico. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At 12:30 p.m. on April 9, 1942, Brigadier General Edward King, commanding officer at Bataan in the Philippines, surrendered to the Japanese. The victorious Japanese then forced more than 10,000 American and 65,000 Filipino survivors of Bataan's garrison to march 100 kilometers in blazing heat from Mariveles to San Fernando. Already weary from months of fighting, the Filipinos and Americans also suffered from malaria, hunger and thirst. Those who fell along the way were beaten and clubbed - often to death - by their captors. Six hundred to 650 Americans and five to ten thousand Filipinos died on the trek.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Palestinian Refugees were forced to march to Arab Legion lines in the foothills to the east through the heat of the day. As many as several hundred died on that march.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;###&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Throughout history oppressed people have been forced to march great distances. Over and over again their humanity wins out over the stress. Traditions, food, music all travel with them, allowing for their personal recreation. We all have journeys to mourn and celebrate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn&amp;rsquo;t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300064295000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Please do not use the google map forced on us by Meetup Management</why><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271720908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Long March</name><id>vmbmnypfbpb</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299888000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/16510675/</event_url></item>