<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187114</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>Richard Tosti Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>826225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236877</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Values:  To be nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and to be respectful to everyone.  We utilize private dance parties as a vehicle to meet other singles.  Purpose is to socialize with similar people of our age (40-65) who are searching for a lifetime partner.  Have fun meeting old and new friends.  Circulate, talk to everyone.  If someone is alone go up to them and say hi!  Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Yes Dance - I ask you to be respectful and say yes to anyone who asks you to dance once.  Please understand this is our number one value.  If you are able to say yes, then this is a great event for you to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are coming because you got this email, and this is your invitation.  Please invite other friends, particularly men.  My personal goal is to have an equal amount of men and women.  We are very close on equal numbers of men and women.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable dance party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will supply the wine and beer- Open bar&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***The cost is $15.00 plus  food assignment listed below.&lt;br /&gt;Of course if you are unable to bring anything, then your entry fee will be $30.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host - Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Format:&lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, loving and relaxing environment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dress code - &amp;quot;business casual&amp;quot; – NO JEANS OR SNEAKERS&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm - 11:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, June 27, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth, 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA&lt;br /&gt;Maximum attendees 175&lt;br /&gt;Dancing will be available - DJ&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No pork or shellfish&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffet which will start at 8:00&lt;br /&gt;Open Bar - wine/beer that you are assigned to bring&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your last name begins with the following letter please bring the following.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A-L  Healthy Entrée’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;M-N- appetizer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dessert O-V&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;W-Z 2 bottles soda (1 diet &amp;amp; 1 regular) and 2 gallons of water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You do not need to email me personally.&lt;br /&gt;170 guests only&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions&lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth, 16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128 North&lt;br /&gt;Exit 32B Middlesex Turnpike (Burlington/Arlington)&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the ramp turn right onto Middlesex Turnpike - on the left is Barnes/Noble&lt;br /&gt;After the Burlington Mall turn right on to Burlington Mall Rd. - on left is Longs Jewelers&lt;br /&gt;Take left after you pass Kohl’s on your left which is Lexington Street&lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth is on your left at16 Lexington Street, Burlington, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are two parking lots on the right side of building.  Enter through the side entrance at the end of the building.  Third parking lot is two houses up at Church - we have permission.  Fourth parking lot is across the street - McGinnis Ave., - Mt Hope Church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the time, the location and what you should bring so let’s have fun!&lt;br /&gt;See you on Saturday, June 27 at 7:30pm----&lt;br /&gt;7:00-free 30 minute lesson&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm Party begins&lt;br /&gt;Appetizers served at 8:00&lt;br /&gt;Entree served at 8:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be!&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339201545000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>74</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241444104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Private Singles Party 30-65</name><id>10332590</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246145400000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/10332590/</event_url></item>