<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Andover Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03257</zip><lat>43.399567</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Flying Goose Brew Pub</name><city>New London</city><id>5594202</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.960350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Show: 8 p.m. Dinner: doors open at 6 I think for dinner Concert ticket: $25 from the Flying Goose website: Cheryl Wheeler has to be seen to be appreciated. Nothing you read and nothing you hear from her albums prepares you for how good a performer she is. You may not be familiar with Cheryl, but you have probably heard her music. She is very respected as a songwriter by her peers, which can be seen by how many of them record her songs. Chery's songs have been covered by artists as diverse as Dan Seals, Peter Paul and Mary, Kenny Loggins, Garth Brooks, Suzy Boggus, Melanie, Bette Midler, Maura O'Connell, Sylvia, Kathy Mattea, and Holly Near. If they think she is great, then you owe it to yourself to learn more if you aren't familiar with her. From her albums you can tell that she is a gifted songwriter with a beautiful voice. From other people's comments about her you can learn that she is a natural story teller with a fantastic sense of humor. But until you see her in person, you never really believe what you've been told about her. Besides, almost half of the songs she does during her shows haven't been recorded! Cheryl's concerts are more like what you would find at a comedy club than expect to find at a folk music concert. She will tell a story that has you rolling in the aisles, and then sing a song that leaves you wiping tears from your eyes. She will talk about some serious current event, and then sing a song that will have you howling with laughter. Her entire concert is a emotional roller coaster.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329445403000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328728258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cheryl Wheeler at the Flying Goose, New London NH</name><id>51576472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329440400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/51576472/</event_url></item>