<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boston, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02109-3502</zip><lat>42.360008</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Prudential Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>4635912</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056740</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Date and Time: Thursday, December 22, 2011 (4:30pm- 6pm) Location : The Shops at The Prudential Center For further updates, join us on Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/221562927917487/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook....&lt;/a&gt; The Shops at Prudential Center has chosen Association for India's Development (AID) as the lighting partner for 2011. &amp;quot;31 Nights of Light&amp;quot; is a Boston Holiday Tradition, created to bring awareness to participating non-profit organizations during the month of December. On the night of 22 December, the top of the Prudential Tower will shine Indian Tricolor on AID. A large symbolic switch is staged at The Shops at Prudential Center, providing additional awareness and a photo opportunity for us. This event is free of cost and do join us for quiz/ raffle to win coupons at the event. Festivities will take place in the Center Court at the Prudential. Please drop by to show your support towards all the development work that is being done back in India. Save the date and join us! The lighting ceremony will take place at 4:30 pm. This event is brought to you by AID, MIT &amp;amp; Boston Chapter along with the Shops at the Prudential. About AID: Association for India's Development is a volunteer movement promoting sustainable, equitable and just development. AID supports grassroots organizations in India and initiates efforts in various interconnected spheres such as agriculture, energy, education, health , livelihoods, natural resources including land and water, women's empowerment and social justice. Contact AID at : events@aidboston.org More Information: www.aidboston.org or www.aidindia.org One for India Campaign: www.oneforindia.org 800 Boylston Street, Boston, MA 02199-8001 Free for all&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324593742000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322696999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>31 Nights of Light - Indian Tricolor on top of The Prudential Center</name><id>42962572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324589400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/42962572/</event_url></item>