<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWER STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:10, so &lt;b&gt;let's meet at 6:30&lt;/b&gt; (few minutes earlier than usual because it's a Saturday night show) right inside the theater ticket lobby doors. Then we'll get our tickets and snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget the book swap. Let us know in your comment whether you'll be bringing a book to swap (and how many). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm still running the matching fundraiser for Haiti and accepting Paypal and checks and cash and email receipts to the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/pages/Haiti_relief_efforts/"&gt;five charities mentioned here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on Saturday! Lemme know if you'll be late or get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since Sherlock Holmes is such a beloved literary character, this movie's after-movie get-together is perfect for a book swap!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a book you don't want to keep around on your swelling bookshelf? Bring it to this meetup and give up a book you don't want to get a book you do want! After all, one man's trash is another man's treasure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only those who bring a swapable item can participate in the swap. (Bring one item, get one item. Bring 2, take 2, etc.) Stay tuned for more swap days in the future!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please indicate in your Yes RSVP if you'll be bringing something and how many something's you'll bring so we know how many people can swap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810045845/details"&gt;Sherlock Holmes&lt;/a&gt; is bringing the cultural icon to a whole new generation. As if Robert Downey, Jr., Jude Law and Rachel McAdams weren't enough of a reason to go see a movie these days. Join me in the adventure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert Downey Jr. brings the legendary detective to life as he has never been portrayed before. Jude Law stars as Holmes' trusted colleague, Watson, a doctor and war veteran who is a formidable ally for Sherlock Holmes. Rachel McAdams stars as Irene Adler, the only woman ever to have bested Holmes and who has maintained a tempestuous relationship with the detective. Mark Strong stars as their mysterious new adversary, Blackwood. Kelly Reilly will play Watson's love interest, Mary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Sherlock Holmes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264464582000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262392560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sherlock Holmes</name><id>12193204</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264291200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12193204/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>