<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>256 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395573</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Joshua Tree</name><city>Somerville</city><id>7409032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122154</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;The below event has been cancelled to avoid overlap with the Central Square Pub Crawl. Please sign up for the Crawl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SATURDAY NIGHT SOCIAL IN SOMERVILLE!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Joshua Tree is letting us have an area next to the bar for the evening at no charge. There will be a DJ and dancing later in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have a menu and cocktails. &lt;a href="http://www.joshuatreesomerville.com/content/joshua-tree"&gt;Click here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVER:&lt;/strong&gt; The GM told me there was no cover. In my experience, bars will institute a cover later on even if it is not advertised, which is why I encourage you to get there close to the start time of 6pm. If you arrive late and they try to institute a cover charge, try saying that you're with the group at the bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINE:&lt;/strong&gt; I do not know if lines form, but I assume they would seeing as it's Davis Square on a Saturday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CHECK THIS SITE BEFORE YOU LEAVE YOUR HOUSE AS I MIGHT HAVE TO CHANGE VENUES!!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DATING:&lt;/strong&gt; This is not a dating event - this is a social event centered around dancing and mingling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;: I've never been here, so if anyone has any advice or info please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FACEBOOK:&lt;/strong&gt; Copy and paste this as an event on your FB and invite your buddies. The more the merrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOUBLE BOOKING:&lt;/strong&gt; Only RSVP to one site so I can have a correct head count (I'm posting this on Social Fun, Fun with Alcohol, and Boston Happy Hour).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OTHER ORGANIZERS:&lt;/strong&gt; Please feel free to post this on your meetup groups (Just let me know!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have our own area next to the bar</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave </member_name><member_id>10064486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348362854000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344097798000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joshua Tree Event Cancelled-Sign up for Central Square Pub Crawl</name><id>76318142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348351200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/76318142/</event_url></item>