<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>260 Willow St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06890</zip><lat>41.128992</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Likins PHome</name><city>Southport</city><id>780676</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.288624</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing a new Meetup for The Hartford Cooking And Recipes Meetup Group!&lt;br /&gt;Location &lt;br /&gt;Likins Home  &lt;br /&gt;260 Willow Street&lt;br /&gt;Southport, CT 06890 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: Southport Seasonal Local Brew Tasting and Dinner &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: October 5, 2008 4:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: (A location has not been chosen yet.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Description: Please join us for a local seasonal brew tasting and dinner, along with an October Garden tour. The menu for the evening is being prepared by the illustrious caterer, Marianne Wilson of Wilton, CT, and consists of a succulent pumpkin soup with fresh crusty bread and a fall salad followed by apple crisp dessert. Platters of gourmet cheese and snacks selected by the buyers for &amp;quot;Say Cheese&amp;quot; in Simsbury will circulate to compliment the brews. Wine will also be served. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be live music by a local artist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is being held in a lovely Southport home. The address will be made availabe to those who RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This home is being opened up and the tasting and dinner are being provided as a fund raiser for my organization Covenant to Care for Children. www.covenanttocare.org There is no cost to attend but a donation per person is requested and expected. Donations above $35.00 are deductible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our goal is to raise $15,000.00 from our guests. The host and owner of the home will match whatever we bring in up to $15,000.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an opportunity to visit a beautiful home and garden, meet new people, support an important organization for CT, taste some local seasonal brews and fine wines and have a yummy dinner. What better way to spend a Sunday evening? Please spread the word to people you know, especially in Southwestern CT. Please plan on attending and bring a friend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a well-behaved kid friendly environment. &lt;br /&gt;Any questions just email or call me. Thanks for helping make this event a success!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://cooking.meetup.com/505/calendar/8462754/"&gt;http://cooking.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>CARPOOLING IS RECOMMENDED</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223411955000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220836356000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SOUTH PORT  Seasonal BrewFEST Local Tasting and Dinner</name><id>8710866</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223238600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8710866/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>