<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Stoneham</address_2><address_1>4 Woodland Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02180</zip><lat>42.480000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Middlesex Fells</name><city>Stoneham</city><id>188710</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Middlesex Fells Reservation walk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10 at the Sheepfold parking area, next to large meadow.  We will follow the bike path trails around the reservoirs and back.  There are lots of wide trails throughout, so we could change route if we want.  The sheepfold is a fun place to start out.  It?s a large meadow where everyone lets their dogs run free, one big dog party!  The trails are likely to be a little muddy, so dress appropriately.  Afterwards we will take a short drive over to JJ Grimsby &amp;amp; Co for lunch at 12:30 (1 Lynn Fells Pkwy, 781-1123).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those coming by T ?  I can pick you up at Oak Grove station at 9:30.  You can also post a message asking for a ride. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Car ? there is a sign for the Sheepfold on Rte 28.  Complete directions and a park map on the site below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/fells.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Middlesex Fells Reservation's 2,575 acres offer a welcome retreat for city dwellers and a suitable terrain for hikers, horseback riders, rock climbers, cross-country skiers and picnickers as well as natural and cultural history buffs. &amp;quot;Fells&amp;quot; is the Saxon word for rocky, hilly tracts of land - an apt name for this scenic area which is rich in local history. This picturesque area was once favored for timber, granite quarrying, ice industry, and water power for the many mills including one that manufactured some of the first vulcanized rubber products.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Botume House at 4 Woodland Road is the Middlesex Fells Headquarters and will soon house the Middlesex Fells Visitor Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special features for visitors include the Sheepfold picnic area, Bellevue Pond, Virginia Wood, and Spot Pond. The Sheepfold is 10 acres of open field, ideal for picnics, frisbee playing and informal games. Bellevue Pond is a seasonal pond surrounded by trails and wide fire roads, some leading up to Wrights Tower which looks out over the Boston Basin. Virginia Wood, the site of a vanished mill village called &amp;quot;Haywardville&amp;quot; is now a dense hemlock enclave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spot Pond&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spot Pond is a picturesque body of water, centrally located in the Middlesex Fells, just east of Routes 28 and 93. With a surface area of 340 acres, and a capacity of 1.8 billion gallons of water, it serves as a backup reservoir to the Quabbin, located in central Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;The area was first explored by Governor Winthrop and his men in the winter of 1632: &lt;br /&gt;...they came to a very great pond, having in the midst an island of about one acre and very thick with trees of pine and beech and the pond had divers small rocks standing up here and there in it, which therefore called Spot Pond.&amp;quot; (quote from Gov. Winthrop's private papers) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spot Pond Boating offers sailing, kayak, canoe and rowboat rental from Memorial Day through Labor Day. Sailing lessons are provided throughout the season as well. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1163095555000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1161645250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middlesex Fells walk</name><id>5218204</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1162652400000</time><rsvp_limit>19</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5218204/</event_url></item>