<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the movie's  playing at 7 and 8. Let's head to the 7:00 one, which means we'll meet at 6:30 inside the theater doors. (We're going to the 7 show and not the 8 show bc it's a loooong movie.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exact change ($8.50) makes me like you more. Be sure to change your RSVP if your decision to attend changes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll head out to Fridays after for a drink or a nibble if anyone's still awake. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you tonight!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Hey, all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a desolate February, let's get back into the movie-watching mayhem with &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1808406490/info" target="_blank"&gt;Watchmen&lt;/a&gt;. It's sci-fi meets comic books, I think. It does run 163 minutes, so be aware of that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;In an alternate 1985 America, costumed superheroes are part of the fabric of everyday society, and the &amp;quot;Doomsday Clock&amp;quot; - which charts the USA's tension with the Soviet Union - is permanently set at five minutes to midnight. When one of his former colleagues is murdered, the washed-up but no less determined masked vigilante Rorschach sets out to uncover a plot to kill and discredit all past and present superheroes. As he reconnects with his former crime-fighting legion - a ragtag group of retired superheroes, only one of whom has true powers - Rorschach glimpses a wide-ranging and disturbing conspiracy with links to their shared past and catastrophic consequences for the future. Their mission is to watch over humanity...but who is watching the watchmen?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's plan on the 7:00 or 8:00ish show. I'll update a few days before with exact times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome. Just be sure to include them in your RSVP so that I know how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And we'll head to Friday's after the movie, if anyone's game for that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call me with any last-minute RSVPs (after 5:00 on the 11th) or directions if you get lost. 508-308-4897.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237593444000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236376171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watchmen</name><id>9898556</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236812400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/9898556/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>