<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1660 Litchfield Turnpike (Rte. 69)</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06525</zip><lat>41.360000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-392-0283</phone><name>Starbucks Coffee</name><city>Woodbridge</city><address_3>near Yarn Barn</address_3><id>151123</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.010000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>August 18th to the 19th (rain or shine) - this will be an easy-to-moderate 4-mile hike. Destination is Sage's Ravine on the Appalachain Trail in the Northwest corner of CT (there is a possibility of a more difficult climb (not technical) to the top of Bear Mountain, which could be a separate hike for those who want more challenge, but that will be a game-time decision and needn't include everybody, if some choose not to).  The hike will take 3-4 hours from the trailhead to the campsite.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The campsite is not a traditional &amp;quot;car-camping&amp;quot; sort of comfort.  Folks who want to do this will be using an outhouse and setting up camp in the woods.  If there is a campfire, campers would create the pit.  We need to be sure to pack out any trash we create.  This is not for experienced hikers only, but it could be classified as &amp;quot;roughing it&amp;quot; and will challenge those who have never backpacked. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Supplies should include: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Backpack (doesn't need to be fancy, but should be comfortable and accomodate the   &lt;br /&gt;  essentials listed below)&lt;br /&gt;- Sleeping bag (and pad, if desired)&lt;br /&gt;- Tent (and willingness to share, if needed)&lt;br /&gt;- Flashlight&lt;br /&gt;- Comfy Hiking shoes&lt;br /&gt;- Food and snacks for a day and a half&lt;br /&gt;- Water/Fluids for 2 days&lt;br /&gt;- Some First Aid provisions&lt;br /&gt;- Bug spray&lt;br /&gt;- Toilet Paper&lt;br /&gt;- Rain gear (in the event of inclement weather)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It would be a good idea to try to water proof your gear by throwing sleeping bags into a trash bag then bringing  a spare bag to put over your pack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A small water filter and camp stove will be brought along, but you should bring food that you can prepare on your own with use of this equipment if necessary - there are no camp &amp;quot;Cookies&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling might be necessary, depending on interest - the rendevous point would be the Starbucks Parking lot in Woodbridge (on Rt. 69, just past the underpass of the Merrit Pkwy).  We should meet at 11:00 am on Saturday (8/18).  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve (resident outdoorsman) is the contact for this event:&lt;br /&gt;203.954.9362&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187661703000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185541822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sat. 8/18 &amp; Sun. 8/19 - Overnight Backpacking Trip to Sage's Ravine on the AT</name><id>6084742</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187449200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6084742/</event_url></item>