<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Just 1 1/2 hours from Boston, Waterville Valley offers some great hiking opportunities.  Our easy / moderate hiking adventure will climb three peaks:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt. Tecumseh&lt;/b&gt; (4003)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Mt. Tecumseh has the distinction of being the shortest official 4,000 footer.  Views to the immediate north include Mt. Osceola, the highest peak in the region. East, across the valley, is the Tripyramid Massif, which includes North Tripyramid and Middle Tripyramid.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Route Level:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will ascend the 2.5 mile Mt. Tecumseh Trail to the summit. We will descend via one of the ski trails.  For fun we will have a Treasure Hunt to look for items dropped from the ski lifts over the winter.  Prizes will be awarded for the best loot!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time/Distance:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5 miles round-trip, 3 1/2 hours book time (probably will take less)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Welch-Dickey Loop&lt;/b&gt; (2605 &amp;amp; 2734)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Eighty percent of the trail features great views, a rarity in the wooded Northeast.  Its one of those modest effort-great reward hikes.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Route Level:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Easy/Moderate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will make the loop counter-clockwise to allow for an easier return trip. From the trail head parking on Orris Road, we will follow the trail to the right, toward Welch Mountain. We will start heading uphill after about half a mile, then traverse flat, open ledges, amidst scrubby jack pine and dwarf birch, to reach the summit of Welch and views of Mad River and Campton Meadows. Note: a few rock scrambles will be encountered on this section. We will then drop back into the woods before continuing up and over more exposed ledge to the summit of Dickeys summit. After a great ridge walk, with one stunningly sheer drop-off, we will descend to a logging road for the final hike out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time/Distance:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;4.5-mile loop, 3 hours book time (probably  will take less)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weather Note:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Currently there is a 30% chance of rain on Saturday.  The order we do this hike will be adjusted based on Saturday's forecast.  This will allow us to safely hike the many open slab crossings found on the Mt. Welch &amp;amp; Mt. Dickey Loop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpool - I -93:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those hikers traveling I-93 to Waterville Valley, I am organizing a &lt;b&gt;7:45 am carpool&lt;/b&gt; at the L.L.Bean in Concord. If interested in carpooling from here please email me at: tourbusiness@altazone.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;L.L. Bean Street Address &amp;amp; Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;55 Fort Eddy Road&lt;br /&gt;Concord, NH 03301&lt;br /&gt;North (from Boston, MA)&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 North to Exit 14. Take Exit 14 and pass through the light at the bottom of the ramp. At the next light, turn left into the L.L. Bean parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the Disclaimer and things you must know.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214226628000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213934784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Tecumseh, Mt. Welch &amp; Mt. Dickey, Waterville Valley, NH</name><id>8177635</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214053200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8177635/</event_url></item>