<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Junction Rt 147 and Rt 157 / Middletown</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06455</zip><lat>41.520000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lyman Orchards</name><city>Middlefield</city><id>381548</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.720001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>When: Sunday, October 7. Meet at 11:30 in New Haven to carpool otherwise meet at the Orchards at 12:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpool meetup spot: The Yale parking lot next to 302 Temple Street, across from the New Haven Public Library. It's on your right after Wall St. I will meet you at the orchard as I will not be carpooling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: A corn maze in the shape of a windy, twisty spider web.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Lyman Orchards in Middlefield, CT (about 40 minutes from New Haven)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why: Because it's a fall activity every good New Englander does. If you have never experienced one before, now is your time to try!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $9 (or $8 if you print off the $1 off coupon on their website). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;Lyman Orchards is located in Middletown, CT, approximately 40 minutes from New Haven. This Corn Maze covers 4 acres of land and is craftily carved into a spooky spider web.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Poor sense of direction? No need to worry. Lyman Orchards provides maps, educational materials, 'interactive passports', and trivia questions to help you through. If you really suck at reading a map and don't know a lick of trivia, you can always talk to a 'corn cop' to help you get out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the corn maze doesn't interest you whatsoever but can't stand to be separated from the group for a day, Lyman Orchards offers apple picking, pumpkin picking, farm stands, frisbee golf and more to keep you busy while the rest of us get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is $9 without the coupon or $8 with the coupon.  Lyman Orchards has a heart! One dollar from every admission is donated to the American Cancer Society. Over the past 6 years, they have donated over $128,000 to the fund. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lymanorchards.com/events/lyman_coupon.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for COUPON&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C'mon out for a great day of relaxing, New England fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Amanda O. - (203) 823-5332&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/photos/?photoAlbumId=104030&amp;amp;photoId=728820"&gt;Can we get more 'Mazers' than last year?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191967478000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190652950000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Corn Maze</name><id>6418237</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191771000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6418237/</event_url></item>