<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Razen Kayne is a great rock and roll band, we've seen several times, although I'm not familiar with the venue they're playing at, so if anyone is familiar with the establishment...ie, food? size? parking? cover charges etc.  please fill me in.&lt;br /&gt;But I got this from Kevin Welch a member of the group...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey Gang!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well.....As they say, &amp;quot;all good things must come to an end&amp;quot;. It's been a great ride for 13 years and you great folks have been there every step of the way! You are the reason for us to deal with the difficult club owners (and there's many of them!), pack up all the equipment on snowy nights, and unpack it at 2:00 in the morning (on snowy nights), make rehearsals when we are sick, and a whole slew of other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When we step on that stage and see you up dancing and having a good night...there's not a better feeling in the world! To know that we have a gift that we can give to you and make you happy...well it makes everything we do worthwhile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've seen us at our best AND worst and you still come back. We can't ask more than that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So...if you can come back one more time, we have one final show to give you. On Friday, NOV. 12th - Voices Rock Club (Lowell, MA) .. Our final show, and it's at this really cool venue. Good Food, GREAT Music and a friendly attentive staff will make this place your favorite local spot to let loose...The whole freakin band will be there including some special guests. If you've seen us before, you know you'll have a great time, and if you've never seen us before you might as well come on in and see what you've missed for the past 13 years and say hello/and good bye to the band!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IT&amp;quot;S BEEN A BLAST.......THANK YOU!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd love to see to see YOUR face in the place!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave, Hokey, Kevin, Danni, Mikey, Steve, Terri &amp;amp; George (The whole freakin Band).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the clubs website is www.voicesrockclub.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meetup signs on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289614479000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288966843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raising cane with Razen Kayne for their last performance!</name><id>15349150</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289610000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/15349150/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/7/global_19397975.jpeg</photo_url></item>