<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sanders Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>738747</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114285</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The annual John M. Prather Lectures in Biology will be presented by &lt;a href="http://www.celebatheists.com/wiki/Edward_O._Wilson" target="_blank"&gt;Edward O. Wilson&lt;/a&gt;, Pellegrino Research Professor Emeritus and Honorary Curator in Entomology at Harvard, and one of the world’s leading voices for conservation of global biodiversity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wilson is one of the most influential and accomplished biologists of the last half-century. He is known for his groundbreaking research on the biology and behavior of ants, as well as his celebrated work in such broad fields as island biogeography, sociobiology, and conservation biology. He is the author of two Pulitzer Prize-winning books, On Human Nature (1978) and The Ants (1990, with Bert Hölldobler), as well as the recipient of many fellowships, honors, and awards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wilson’s Prather lectures will encapsulate his remarkable 55-year career in biology at Harvard, and look forward to the critical challenges ahead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Global biodiversity is richer than thought even 20 years ago, but it and the ecosystems supporting it are disappearing at an accelerating rate--to the great and enduring loss to future humanity. Science is not well prepared to handle this issue. We live on a poorly explored planet: only a tiny fraction, probably fewer than ten percent, of species are known to science, when microorganisms are included; and of these, only a minute fraction have been studied at any depth. There are remedies to this ignorance, and when they are applied, a major new front of biology will open, equal and complementary to molecular, cellular, and developmental biology.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reception and book signing to follow at the Harvard Museum of Natural History.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.oeb.harvard.edu/news_events/news_items/prather_2010.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.oeb.harvard.edu/news_events/news_items/prather_2010.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.oeb.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: $10 – general public / Free to Harvard University ID holders. Lecture tickets are required, and can be obtained through the Harvard Box Office in Holyoke Center beginning on March 3. For more ticket info, please call 617-496-2222, or visit the Harvard Box Office web site at &lt;a href="http://ofa.fas.harvard.edu/cal/details.php?ID=40839" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://ofa.fas.harvard.edu/cal/details.php?ID=40839" target="_blank"&gt;http://ofa.fas.harvar...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth</member_name><member_id>8893636</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271372052000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269506236000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Prather Lecture: E. O. Wilson "Biodiversity and the Future of Biology"</name><id>12987882</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270504800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/12987882/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>