<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Attend this Seminar and learn about the functionality of Google Analytics as well as how you can be using this tool to improve your business.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Google Analytics:&lt;br /&gt;Google Analytics is a free website tracking software that measures much more than just how much traffic you get to your site. It provides business owners and marketers the necessary business intelligence for growing revenue and driving action in your website. Our guest speaker, Joe Baz of Above The Fold Design, will provide a one hour demo on this web-based tool and demystify the topic of website metrics. Preceeded and followed by open networking among the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following Topics will be discussed: &lt;br /&gt;1. Metrics defined: Visitors &amp;gt; Visits &amp;gt; Page Views &amp;gt; Hits&lt;br /&gt;2. Dashboard Customization and Report Views&lt;br /&gt;3. Visitor Tracking: Visitor Loyalty, Location Specific Reports&lt;br /&gt;4. Traffic Sources: Referring Sites and Paid / Organic Search Traffic&lt;br /&gt;5. Content Performance: Page Trending and Site Overlay&lt;br /&gt;6. Conversion Goals: Setting up customer sales / lead funnels for tracking performance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;br /&gt;Since 1996, Joe Baz has been involved in every aspect of the Web, including design, development, marketing, content development, analytics and user experience development. He currently owns and operates his own web consulting business, Above the Fold (&lt;a href="http://www.abovethefolddesign.com)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abovethefo...&lt;/a&gt;, which focuses on providing businesses with the strategic and tactical expertise needed to succeed on the Web.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>39</waitlist_count><updated>1235518577000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233768482000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Google Analytics Seminar</name><id>9672210</id><headcount>39</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235084400000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/9672210/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/f/global_1065599.jpeg</photo_url></item>