<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>138 Mathewson Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.820000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Johnson &amp; Wales Academic Center</name><city>Providence</city><id>253116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.410004</lon></venue><fee><label>Optional donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I think we'll change things up a bit this month - rather than the usual open discussion format, this month I'm going to do a presentation on rapid prototyping with Ruby on Rails. This discussion comes with the caveat that I'm still a novice Rails developer, but I've read and done enough to be really excited about how easy Rails makes web development. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're already a seasoned Rails developer I can't promise any secret insights. But, if you are wondering what all the hype surrounding the Rails community is about, or if you just haven't had the time to explore it on your own then I hope to give you an overview of the theories behind Rails and walk you through the creation of a project that's a step above the Hello, World examples you may already have read through.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The presentation will take place at the Academic Center on the Johnson &amp;amp; Wales campus. To get there, walk through the main entrance (directly across from the Hotel Providence) and turn right to enter the main office. Tell the receptionist that you are here for the Meetup event. You'll be able to walk straight past the receptionist's desk and into the presentation space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for lunch, I'll ask all of you to bring yours with you so that we can focus on the discussion. I'll try to keep this under 45 minutes so everyone has time to travel and/or get lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there. Spots may be limited based on the final location, so it's first-come, first-serve (or FILO if you will :))&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Shearer</member_name><member_id>1529786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189872341000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Web Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>webdesign-410</urlname><id>272511</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Providence Web Development Lunch Hour Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186678911000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence Web Development Lunch Hour September Meetup</name><id>6152394</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189699200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/webdesign-410/events/6152394/</event_url></item>