<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Put away the leftover turkey, forget about the holiday shopping trauma and come out to play!  This movie looks like it will be a lot of fun.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be at the theater by 6:30.  The movie is playing upstairs, so I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  We will head in to find seats at 7.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you miss the group, come look for us after the movie. The group will gather outside the room where the movie has just been shown, to discuss the film, allow for restroom breaks and get a head count of all who are interested in heading to the Rockbottom for munchies, beverages and lively conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My picture is on the website, check it out so you can recognize me. I will be wearing a meetup pin and will also have a meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details:&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: November 24, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;Studio: Screen Gems (Sony) &lt;br /&gt;Director: Steven Antin &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Steven Antin &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Cher, Christina Aguilera, Eric Dane, Cam Gigandet, Julianne Hough, Peter Gallagher, Alan Cumming, Kristen Bell, Stanley Tucci &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Drama &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: Not Available &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.burlesquethemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.burlesquet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Ali (Christina Aguilera) is a small-town girl with a big voice who escapes hardship and an uncertain future to follow her dreams to LA. After stumbling upon The Burlesque Lounge, a majestic but ailing theater that is home to an inspired musical revue, Ali lands a job as a cocktail waitress from Tess (Cher), the club's proprietor and headliner. Burlesque's outrageous costumes and bold choreography enrapture the young ingenue, who vows to perform there one day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon enough, Ali builds a friendship with a featured dancer (Julianne Hough), finds an enemy in a troubled, jealous performer (Kristen Bell), and garners the affection of Jack (Cam Gigandet), a bartender and fellow musician. With the help of a sharp-witted stage manager (Stanley Tucci) and gender-bending host (Alan Cumming), Ali makes her way from the bar to the stage. Her spectacular voice restores The Burlesque Lounge to its former glory, though not before a charismatic entrepreneur (Eric Dane) arrives with an enticing proposal... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.burlesquethemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.burlesquet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If movie is upstairs, I will be at a table near the windows at the top of the escalator. If movie is downstairs I will be by the ropes near the concession stand. I will be wearing a meetup pin and have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825735000</updated><rating><average>3.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288795726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Burlesque</name><id>15323979</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290900600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/15323979/</event_url></item>