<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Buckingham Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06001</zip><lat>41.786739</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Huckleberry Hill Recreation </name><city>Avon</city><id>1592136</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.911827</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/c/b/event_11248875.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;I am continuing the easier level hikes as I recover from Achilles tendon surgery.&amp;nbsp; This is a great little park between Collinsville and Avon.&amp;nbsp; We are going to hike the outer loop that goes around the perimeter.&amp;nbsp; This park has a great deal of water to navigate.&amp;nbsp; We will hike about 3 miles approximately 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this hike in in wooded and wet area I recommend boots and no sneakers.&amp;nbsp; The trail is through the woods on an uneven surface.&amp;nbsp; I would carry a small pack with water and a snack.&amp;nbsp; make sure to dress in layers you can take off and put back on as needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always with me, NO DOGS, NO CHILDREN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://mapq.st/edQPOB"&gt;http://mapq.st/edQPOB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the mapquest link to the parking. I would like you to head up Buckingham Rd and at the top of the hill and to the right is a playground with parking.&amp;nbsp; This where we will meet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can discuss after hike lunch.&amp;nbsp; We are close to Collinsville and my favorite, LaSalles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1303684432000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><why>This is a great little wooded park.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301881931000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Huckleberry Hill Recreation Center, Avon CT</name><id>17170994</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302962400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/17170994/</event_url></item>