<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mugford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.505763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Unitarian Universalist Church</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>854935</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.850705</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Me and Thee kicks off the winter season with long-time favorite Chris Smither. The Boston Globe praises Smither as “among the finest acoustic guitarists anywhere in American music.” Since his last visit almost exactly three years ago, Chris has released his 12th album, Leave the Light On.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some artists continually reinvent themselves; others identify their muse early on and spend their careers single-mindedly pursuing it, remaining recognizably themselves through a career-long process of refinement, growth and discovery. Chris Smither belongs to the latter group. Leave the Light On, Smither’s masterful twelfth album — the first he’s released on his own Mighty Albert label — stands as the quintessence of his life’s work while throwing in some new wrinkles that reflect where he’s been and what he’s encountered since the last time around. But Smither’s central theme as he enters his 60s is clearer than ever. “The last three or four records I’ve done are mostly talking about the big questions — life, death, love and . . . not love — and where the whole thing’s going,” he says. What is immediately recognizable to anyone who has encountered Smither on record or in live performance during the course of the last four decades are his been-there, done-that voice and the crystalline, wordlessly eloquent sounds of his fingerpicked acoustic guitar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy your own ticket NOW ($25) at &lt;a href="http://www.meandthee.org/Chris-Smither2009.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meandthee....&lt;/a&gt; as this one  might sell out fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions are here: &lt;a href="http://www.meandthee.org/Directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meandthee....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll try to save a pew - wearing a red scarf, look for me!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235179707000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232198428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chris Smither Folk concert at the Me and Thee Coffeehouse Marblehead</name><id>9542948</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233968400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/9542948/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/6/global_5526982.jpeg</photo_url></item>