<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us at Chaibo at 7pm on Thursday, October 27th as we discuss &lt;em&gt;Before I Go To Sleep&lt;/em&gt; by SJ Watson. It's almost Halloween and the perfect time get cozy with a yummy coffee concoction as we discuss a spine tingling thriller! If you have room, enjoy one of Chaibo's famous pumpkin whoopie pies or a piece of their decadent chocolate cake with your coffee. Mmmm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of the book by Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/feature.html?docId=1000692471"&gt;Amazon Best Books of the Month, June 2011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Every day Christine wakes up not knowing where she is. Her memories disappear every time she falls asleep. Her husband, Ben, is a stranger to her, and he's obligated to explain their life together on a daily basis--all the result of a mysterious accident that made Christine an amnesiac. With the encouragement of her doctor, Christine starts a journal to help jog her memory every day. One morning, she opens it and sees that she's written three unexpected and terrifying words: "Don't trust Ben." Suddenly everything her husband has told her falls under suspicion. What kind of accident caused her condition? Who can she trust? Why is Ben lying to her? And, for the reader: Can Christine&amp;rsquo;s story be trusted? At the heart of S. J. Watson's&lt;/em&gt; Before I Go To Sleep &lt;em&gt;is the petrifying question: How can anyone function when they can't even trust themselves? Suspenseful from start to finish, the strength of Watson's writing allows&lt;/em&gt; Before I Go to Sleep &lt;em&gt;to transcend the basic premise and present profound questions about memory and identity. One of the best debut literary thrillers in recent years,&lt;/em&gt; Before I Go to Sleep &lt;em&gt;deserves to be one of the major blockbusters of the summer. --Miriam Landis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322787282000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317849843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Before I Go to Sleep</name><id>36306822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319756400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/36306822/</event_url></item>