<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a great way for you to find out about our Sierra club events and to meet other members. While you're there, join us for cold beverages, meet new people, find out how you can contribute to the good fight for our environment. This meeting - open to all - will have Sierra Club activists who will explain the projects we're working on, from Alternative Energy, Politics, Legislation, Outings, Parks, plus many other Sierra Club subjects. Limited space - please RSVP as soon as possible! For more info, contact meetup@sierraclubmass.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;La Luna Cafe is a small cafe on the east edge of Central Square a few blocks from the T. There is a parking lot directly behind the cafe. The cafe offers various varieties of coffee, beer and wine, food, and fantastic gelati.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're driving, the mapquest directions do not refelect the new construction that's still underway. Please let us know when you RSVP and we'll send you a map to avoid the construction.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mass Sierra</member_name><member_id>3278292</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200699293000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Environmental Activists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Sierra-Club</urlname><id>229402</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Sierra Club Environmental Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198269027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January Meetup and Introduction to Sierra's Activities</name><id>6951290</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200526200000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Sierra-Club/events/6951290/</event_url></item>