<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>State House</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.225640</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>386899</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.554750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>UPDATE:  Senate will not be meeting until 11 AM tomorrow morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/legislation/2008/SB0337.html" target="_blank"&gt;SB 337&lt;/a&gt; is a bill which will un-do the work of HB406 from the 2006 session. This bill will require parents to submit curriculum's for each of their children to the state. This bill will also criminalize withdrawing your child from the public system without a 30 day notice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking place on Thursday is a Senate floor vote. The full senate will vote on a number of bills, sb337 included. If the bill is passed by the Senate, it will go on to the house for the full committee process over again. Ideally, the hope is to kill the bill in the Senate Chambers tomorrow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SB 337 is a bill which will un-do the work of HB406 from the 2006 session. This bill will require parents to submit curriculum's for each of their children to the state. This bill will also criminalize withdrawing your child from the public system without a 30 day notice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original intent of this bill was to count homeschooled kids as part of the &amp;quot;average daily membership&amp;quot; in order to funnel yet more funding to public schools. This has since been removed from the bill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, there is enough potential damage left in the amended bill to warrant the support of homeschooling parents. As we see homeschooling rights across the nation being jeopardized, standing strong for our parental rights is a necessity. The right of parents to educate their children is a fundamental right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further details please contact Suzanne Hudson at slhudson (at) metrocast (dot) net&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205592675000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Visit the State House and watch our government in action.</why><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205324222000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Homeschooling freedoms under Senate attack...again</name><id>7517045</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205419500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/7517045/</event_url></item>