<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>113 Goodnow Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.456543</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-464-2712</phone><name>Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Princeton</city><id>669307</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.900800</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Description from the website: &lt;br /&gt;

 Twelve miles of trails at Wachusett Meadow traverse vast meadows, woodlands, and wetlands. Brown Hill Summit, South Wachusett Brook, and Glacial Boulder are highlights among many other features. Wildlife is abundant in all seasons, and visitors may take advantage of opportunities to snowshoe, cross-country ski, and canoe in addition to hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Address: &lt;br /&gt;

 113 Goodnow Road &lt;br /&gt;

 Princeton, MA 01541 &lt;br /&gt;

 [masked] &lt;br /&gt;

 [masked]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information and directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Wachusett_Meadow/index.php"&gt;http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Wachusett_Meadow/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll begin our journey at the main parking lot at 11am for a brief introduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll take the North Meadow Trail (behind the Visitor Center), heading up the Glacial Boulder trail to the Brown Hill Loop, leading to the summit (elev. 1312’). After breaking at the summit for viewing and pictures we’ll descend the loop trail, pass Otter Pond, the Giant White Oak, the Farm Pond, and grazing sheep! The hike shouldn't take more than 1.5 hours with breaks for viewing/pics along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail Map&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be prepared for early summer temps, bugs and sun! Note that some sections of the trail is rocky, and there is a climb to the summit (elev. gain of 400 ft.) Also some sections of the trail is over-grown, so long, light-weight pants would be best. Wear sturdy hiking boots, and bring bug repellent, sunscreen, hat, water (and/or gator-aide), snacks, and a camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Visitor Center across from the parking lot has Restrooms, daily logs of wildlife sightings, trail maps and a nature center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a $4 fee to non-members and non-residents of Princeton, payable at the Visitor Center. The day before the hike I'll send out an email with my cell#. Please update your RSVP if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is weather permitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can join us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340043639000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339860373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Wachusett Meadow-Father's Day Hike #2</name><id>69439892</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339954200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/69439892/</event_url></item>