<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Essex Center Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01960</zip><lat>42.536972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lahey Clinic</name><city>Peabody, Ma</city><id>8967712</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.946678</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! Everyone, I just found out there is a bike trail that goes from the North Shore Mall, Peabody up to the Ipswich River in Middleton. It's only 7.4 miles in each direction. Since its a short ride Lets try and squeeze it all in as a week night ride. It will be tight since the sun sets at 7pm so wear reflective clothing &amp;amp; make sure you have lighting of some sort. I use my hiking headlamp if I bike when it's getting dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Independence Greenway runs 7.4 miles one way and runs between the Ipswich River and the North Shore Mall. The trail is mostly continuous except for one on-road segment between Peabody Road and Lt. Ross Park. From the park follow Johnson Street to Lowell Street, under US 1 and I-95, and Peabody Road. This 1.4-mile on-street portion does have heavy traffic and some hills. A sidewalk is available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rail-trail follows the abandoned Salem and Lowell Railroad and offers nice views. It passes by wetlands and ponds that are home to herons, swans and geese.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are going to be cutting it tight with the sunset, so be ready to ride and on you bike by 5:30 or meet us at a different trail head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.peabody-ma.gov/comm_dev/IndependenceGreenwayMap.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.peabody-ma.gov/comm_dev/IndependenceGreenwayMap.pdf&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Parking and Trail Access &lt;br /&gt;

 You can access the Independence Greenway at the North Shore Mall trailhead, near 1 Essex Center Drive next to the parking lot for Lahey Clinic Peabody. Face the mall and follow the hospital signs (H) to the trailhead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've never done this trail before so bare with me this could be an adventure for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards for those who would like to we shall go to one of the local restaurants like Bugaboo Creek for a bite to eat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347413802000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346257355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independence Greenway-Peabody to Middleton, who knew???</name><id>79912912</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347311700000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/79912912/</event_url></item>