<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Ives  Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02818</zip><lat>41.655129</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Goddard  Park</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1346891</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434487</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I plan to start in the Park and then head out to the back roads.  If you only want to stay in the Park, that is fine.  There is an incline or small hill ( depends on your riding level ) in the Park.  It is a good place for newer riders to learn to shift  and how to use your momentum  from going down a hill to make it easier getting up the next hill.  You should be able to get 10 miles or so in the Park. ( you might retrace some )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who want to do some road riding, I have a few options which can get  upwards of 25 miles.  There is one Hill, but  most of the roads are relatively flat, with little traffic. There are some Rolling Hills or Inclines,  which is good practice in using momentum, to get up a hill / incline  with ease.  Because this Ride is a Loop, I will be averaging 13 mph.  If you can go 11-12 mph, you should be fine.  I will wait for you at the intersection.  Casual Riders, can stay in the Park.  On Loop Road Rides, I want to keep everyone together, for safety reasons.  FYI:  There are only 2 Rides that I do, where I ask that you maintain a certain pace.  Again, that is for Safety Reasons !!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring at least one spare tube, for your Bike !!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want, we can do Lunch on the Beach or there is a Fat Belly's Pizza, right after you leave  the Park.   Last time I checked, there was no fee to use the Park.  You do have to take out your own trash and there are restrooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The park is technically within the boundaries of Warwick, in a section that the local residents call Potowomut, at 1095 Ives Road. Potowomat ("Land of Fires" in the local Native American language) is divided from the rest of Warwick by the town of East Greenwich. To get there from Providence, take 95 south, exit #9, a Left Lane Exit,  to Route 4, exiting immedietly at exit 8. Take a right onto Division Street and continue straight to Route 1 (also called Post Road or Main Street) and turn right. At the next light, take a left and follow the signs about a mile to Goddard Memorial Park's enterance on the left. During warm weather, entrances and exits are one-way, with the entrance about a quarter mile farther along Ives Road.  Note: Go in the Main Entrance and that will Lead you straight to the Beach.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are at the Beach.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave N.</member_name><member_id>10478672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338259725000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Grinders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group</urlname><id>1500421</id><group_lat>42.0600013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Foxboro Grind &amp; Grub Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337124971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike Goddard Park &amp; Surrounding Side Streets</name><id>64950182</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338130800000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group/events/64950182/</event_url></item>