<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>355 Prospect Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Leitner Family Observatory at Farnham Memorial Gardens</name><city>New Haven</city><id>181950</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*UPDATE* Rich went and pi$$ed off the weather gods by RSVP'ing, so clouds have once again come along to ruin our good time. let me just say, i think it's great that so many of you come back time and time again to RSVP for an event with such an abysmal cancelation record. stay strong, and come back again next time i event this. we will prevail!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;by the way, for anyone who's interested, i (ben) will be at the lecture at the observatory, which starts at 7pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;seeing as how weather has canceled the past four attempts at this, starting in November, i'm probably crazy for eventing this in April, of all months, but i refuse to give up. even if i'm 100 years old and the last *living* person in the NHC, i'll keep on trying...be it four tries, or ten tries, or a thousand. so without further ado, here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twice a month the grad students at the yale department of astronomy host public nights at the department's observatory on prospect street in new haven. there are two telescopes, each in its own dome, that are powerful enough to get good looks at planets, moons, nebulae, etc. in the past sights have included the rings of saturn, the red storm spot on jupiter, the galilean moons, and various galaxies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the domes are open to the outside air, so dress appropriately. for those driving, there is limited parking in the parking lot, so you may need to park on prospect street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;assuming the weather cooperates and the event is on, i will be there at 7pm for the &lt;a href="http://www.astro.yale.edu/publicnights/LFO-public-current.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;lecture&lt;/a&gt;. the observation begins at 8.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check the following link on the astronomy department's homepage after 5pm the day of to see if the public night is going ahead as planned. or, you can call me, ben, for the update: 203-554-5144&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.astro.yale.edu/publicnights/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.astro.yale...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;pre-party? post-party? definitely possible. thinking maybe drinks at rudy's before and/or after. stars and beers go well together. will update.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175987017000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175099132000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*UPDATE* - No Stargazing Tonight - LECTURE ONLY</name><id>5613408</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175814000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5613408/</event_url></item>