<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>42 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-6789</phone><name>Cambridge Center for Adult Education</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1170238</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121368</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At the Cambridge Center for Adult Education ACAE &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;SPROUTING DEMO&amp;nbsp; and Recipe Demo &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Helen Kobek, Jules Kobek &lt;br /&gt;Urban Homesteaders &lt;br /&gt;Helen Kobek is co-founder and facilitator of DIO (Do-It-Ourselves) Skillshare.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In addition to leading workshops on skils of urban sustainability, she conducts tours of her urban homestead, which incorporates vegetable gardens, composting systems, grey-water recycling, and creative methods of weatherization. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Eating a raw food diet since 2002, she offers support and advice to people making improvements to their diets. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jules Kobek is co-founder of DIO (Do-It-Ourselves) Skillshare, facilitating workshops on skills of urban sustatinability, such as sprouting, growing vegetables, and constructing raised garden beds. She also leads nature walks to identify edible weeds and other wild foods. Preparing all her meals with sprouts grown herself, she has followed a raw food diet since 2002. Devising additional techniques of growing vegetables in small urban spaces is one of her ongoing projects. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sunflower and pea shoots cost a mint at grocery stores, but are cheap to grow at home. Sprouted lentils and buckwheat are healthy, but how do you eat them? In this two-session series, the facilitators, nine-year adherents to a raw-food diet, will show you how to grow sprouts and microgreens using a variety of methods, and then offer hands-on experience preparing tasty dishes with these enzyme-rich, vitamin-packed foods.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Recipes include collard green roll-ups with sprouted mung bean pate, clover sprouts and pea tendrils; sprouted buckwheat tabouli; raw hummus; and spicy sprouted lentils. For more info before you register, call CCAE for the instructors' contact info.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: in order to enroll in section 02 (recipe prep), you must also take section 01 (sprouting demonstration).  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You may, however, take section 01 without taking section 02.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Tuition includes basic sprouting materials.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Section 01 limited to 30; section 02 limited to 16. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;SPROUTING DEMO  &lt;br /&gt;Sec. 01: 1 Wednesday, 5:30-8:00 pm. Mar. 30, 56 Brattle St. Cost $30 &lt;br /&gt;SPTS&amp;ndash;01&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;RECIPE PREP &lt;br /&gt;Sec. 02: 1 Wednesday, 6:30-9:30 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;Apr. 6, 42 Brattle St.  &lt;br /&gt;Cost $76  &lt;br /&gt;Note:&amp;nbsp; To enroll in this class, you must also take Sec. 01.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; SPTS&amp;ndash;02 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;CCAE &lt;br /&gt;42 Brattle Street, Cambridge Ma. 02138 617-547-6789 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ccae.org/raisetheroof/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ccae.org/raisetheroof/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301701806000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299869653000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Attend Sprouting and Raw Recipe Class - Part 2</name><id>16886830</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301697000000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/16886830/</event_url></item>