<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>281 Greenfield Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01373</zip><lat>42.513360</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> (413) 665-2805</phone><name>Magic Wings Butterfly Conservatory &amp; Gardens</name><city>South Deerfield</city><id>669361</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.605700</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please note that we are leaving the RT 20 Rt 146 Park and Ride at 8:30 AM and driving up to Deerfield from there. There are folks looking to car pool from Worcester MA together. Please let me know if you would like to by calling or emailing me through meetup here. My number is 774-239-0214&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, FYI, Historic Deerfield is just a few miles up Rt. 5/10 from Magic Wings. It is free to wander the grounds of Historic Deerfield or you can find out more about admission to the homes &amp;amp; museums at &lt;a href="http://www.historic-deerfield.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.historic-d...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's take a road trip together and check out the Magic Wings Butterfly Place in Deerfield MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Magic Wings Butterfly Conservatory &amp;amp; Gardens consists of an 18,400-square foot facility that includes a 8,000-sq. ft. glass conservatory filled with butterflies, moths and tropical vegetation.The sun shines through the glass walls and heats up the conservatory to an 80-degree tropical-like environment all year round. The heart-shaped pond with Japanese koi graces the center of the conservatory. The sound of the waterfall, peaceful music and hundreds of butterflies fluttering freely through the air creates a tranquil and serene atmosphere. Visits anytime throughout the year are delightful. It's truly amazing inside, for no matter how many people are enjoying the conservatory, it's still a peaceful sanctuary for all. Enter through the main entrance into our plant-filled atrium.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some 3,000 butterflies of all colors, shapes, sizes and varieties go dancing past. Our Flight Attendants are scattered throughout the conservatory, waiting to help you identify the many different butterflies. Brilliantly colored koi rise to the surface of the pond to greet you. Along the sides of the paths, we've tucked park benches for you to sit and relax and watch for as long as you need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can car pool if you like. We will meet at the Mass Pike Park and Ride at 146 and route 20 at 8:30AM. It would be nice if you split costs on gas with whomever you car pool with. We'll ride up together and meet at the entrance of the Magic Wings place at 9:45. WE'll hang out for a few hours and then maybe check out the area for a lunch joint and look around historic Deerfield. PLan on getting back home between 5-6pm that night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the entrance! Look for Scott in his red shirt.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281989312000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277919648000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Butterfly Photo Op at Magic Wings in Deerfield MA</name><id>13961438</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281875400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13961438/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/5/global_16103317.jpeg</photo_url></item>