<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well, we just finished our second meeting and becoming old friends fast. Thanks for all who could attend. We began to look at the first 78 pages of our text, tracing the Jewish and Islamic narratives of the Journey of Abraham and abit of &amp;quot;midrash&amp;quot; or how this journey places light on our own journey as a planet today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget that we can carry on the conversation online at our &lt;a href="http://www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Interfaith Book Club Blog&lt;/a&gt;. Fee free to share your insights and questions on line prior to the meeting. Invite others who may not be able to come to the meeting to join in on line. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next meeting will be November 20, 7:30 at the Shrine. We will be exploring the Christian and Islamic interpretations of the Abrahamic Journey today. As usual, all faiths are invited. I look forward to seeing you all again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Tent of Abraham, Hagar, &amp;amp; Sarah is a gathering of Jews, Christians, and Muslims who have been building a 'Tent' of shared spiritual concern for peace, justice, and healing of the earth. Arising from this effort has been a call to take part in 'The Peace of Abraham, Hagar and Sarah'.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542399000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192581339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club November Meetup</name><id>6562934</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195605000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/6562934/</event_url></item>