<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;Christmas is fast approaching. Lights and decorations are going up everywhere, many people are in a flurry over buying gifts, getting cards in the mail, giving and attending parties and family celebrations, making all kinds of preparations for the holiday. There is a great air of anticipation: we are hoping something wonderful is going to happen. We are getting ready for it. If this is all so wonderful, why are we often wearied with the preparations, and why is there often a sense of let down after it has all passed, even when we have accomplished and attended all that we set out to? The reason is that there is more, much more, to Christmas than the lights, gifts, and events that happen on the outside. That longing in our hearts for something wonderful to happen is really a longing for a rebirth in our connection with God inside of us. This is what Christmas can can be for us, if we use this preparation time to connect to what the season is really about, and to open to the great stillness and receptivity inside of us, for it is into this place that God moves. If we have done this kind of preparation, the coming of Christ at Christmas can be a powerful and fulfilling birth of the love of God inside of us. I invite you to attend this seminar that will delve into the inner meaning of Christmas and teach you how to make your heart ready for the real miracles it can work inside of you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197851669000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196863636000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: The Inner Meaning of Christmas</name><id>6860302</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197678600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/6860302/</event_url></item>