<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Sypnosis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shortkut is a young heart-warming slice-of-life comedy about the trials and tribulations of two con artists, a struggling director and actor and the zany situations they face in the pursuit of their tinsel-town dreams!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shekhar (Akshaye Khanna), an aspiring assistant director, and Chandu (Arshad Warsi), a wannabe junior artiste, meet each other while struggling to make it in the film industry. While Shekhar is supremely talented and confident, Chandu is a buffoon and a non-actor who thinks he is God's gift to Bollywood!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As luck would have it, Chandu manages to steal Shekhar's prized script and is catapulted to super- stardom. Following this incident, Shekhar plunges into a phase of self-pity and dejection, which results in his wife Mansi (Amrita Rao) leaving him! Shattered, Shekhar is now looking for that golden chance to get even with Chandu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What follows is an absolutely hilarious tale of con, deceit, super-stardom and subsequent fall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shot in picturesque Thailand, Shortkut comes with a generous dose of splitting laughter and emotions that tug at your heartstrings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It comes from the production house of veteran actor, Anil Kapoor (Slumdog Millionaire) after the critical success of Gandhi My Father, and from director Neeraj Vora, whose erstwhile venture, Phir Hera Pheri was a smash hit at the box office.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imoviecafe.com/Movies/showtime.aspx?id=Shot&amp;amp;BigImage=shotcutbig.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imoviecafe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My cell is 5083147742. We can meet in the lobby of the cinema 20 minutes before.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247787329000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-27</urlname><id>610218</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Group Closing - Indian Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246630097000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bollywood Movie - Short Kut (The con is on)</name><id>10795794</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247346000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-27/events/10795794/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/4/8/global_9029704.jpeg</photo_url></item>