<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 9788081932&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be our fifth summer that we combine hiking with white water rafting. Last year we introduced the "raft, rinse, repeat" - this year we are adding the "pray we don't plummet" to our itinerary. What does all this mean?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;raft, rinse, repeat&lt;/strong&gt; = The Kennebec River Gorge is one of the most beautiful in the East with steep rock walls with many waves that are four to six feet high. We used to go through the rapids on the top half of the Kennebec River and then float the rest of the way back to camp. Boring! So we convinced the people at Magic Falls Rafting Company that we could skip the float - two trips through the rapids would be better than one. They agreed, so now we get twice the fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wZWyrPA8dg8" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to see the video from last year's rafting trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;pray we don't plummet&lt;/strong&gt; = If you like to hike &lt;em&gt;among&lt;/em&gt; the trees, why not take a zipline canopy tour and travel &lt;em&gt;above&lt;/em&gt; them? Bretton Woods has the longest zipline canopy tour in New England and one of the longest tours in the continental United States. High-flying suspension bridges and hiking trails connect the ziplines, and the tour concludes with the Williwaw Racing Zip, a dual, side-by-side zipline leading right into the Bretton Woods base area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=faFRDaHA0q8" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to see the video from a trip to Bretton Woods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sound like fun? Then join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do not have to do everything - if you only want to hike, that's fine. Just want to zipline, that works too. Only feel like rafting, no problem. Of course you will have more fun if you do them all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Itinerary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will update the hikes in the next month or two (there are plenty of really tall mountains to pick from) but the dates for the rafting and zipline are booked so I want to give you enough time to make the necessary arrangements so you can participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Each day is listed separately on our events calendar - you will need to RSVP separately for each day of this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 6 (Wednesday) Hike in the White Mountains TBD and car camp TBD &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 7 (Thursday) Zipline Canopy Tour with Mount Washington Resort/Bretton Woods and car camp at Magic Falls &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 8 (Friday) White Water Rafting on the Kennebec River with Magic Falls Rafting Company and car camp at Magic Falls &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July 9 (Saturday) Hike in Maine TBD and car camp TBD &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zipline Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be ziplining with the Mount Washington Resort/Bretton Woods. They are located in Bretton Woods, NH, which is about 158 miles north of Boston. This event is limited to just 16 people - the first group of eight will begin at 9:00 AM and the second group of eight will begin at 9:30 AM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=310+Mt+Washington+Hotel+Road,+Bretton+Woods+system,+NH+03575+(The+Mount+Washington+Hotel)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFeJYowIdfJq9-yGKXwIu0nUUUA&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=44.235729,-71.434307&amp;amp;sspn=0.058913,0.153637&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=44.273476,-71.470528&amp;amp;spn=0.11775,0.307274&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=12" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for driving directions via google maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://brettonwoods.com/activities/canopy_tour/overview" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more information about Bretton Woods&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to make the reservations for the group and as soon as the first eight people sign-up and get me their deposit I will make the reservation. Same thing for the next eight people. The price is $101.50 per person but you must pay the $35 deposit in order to register - the balance will be due 14 days prior to the trip. You can either use the Amazon Payments link on this page or you can send me a check (email me for my mailing address).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rafting Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be rafting the Kennebec River with Magic Falls Rafting Company. They are located in The Forks, ME, which is about 248 miles north of Boston. We will be camping there as well (sites right along the river) on Thursday and Friday nights. There is no limit to the number of people that can participate in the rafting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=38+Dead+River+Road,+West+Forks,+ME+04985+(Magic+Falls+Rafting+Company)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFZD4swIdhhnU-yE77M_vUWflhg&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=45.397245,-70.013466&amp;amp;sspn=0.109449,0.307274&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=43.747289,-70.334473&amp;amp;spn=3.801267,9.832764&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=7" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for driving directions via google maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.magicfalls.com" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more information about Magic Falls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make your reservations directly with Magic Falls at (800) 207-7238 . The price before March 1, 2011 is $121.30 - after that the price increases to $141.10 so book your trip early. This includes two nights of camping, two trips down the rapids, and a barbecue dinner after the rafting trip. You will need a 50% deposit at the time of booking - the balance will be due 30 days prior to the trip. When you make your reservations be sure to tell them that you are with the Blair Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please contact me if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310413462000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295401822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>White Water Rafting - 5th Annual Paddle, Plod, &amp; Pray we don't Plummet</name><id>16100568</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310128200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/16100568/</event_url></item>