<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please take a moment to read the ENTIRE update, as I have updated  the new meetup dates/locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEETUPS AT 11:00AM and 1:00PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;SAVE THE DATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boston’s Fourth Annual Divas Unleashed Halloween Pet Parade and &lt;br /&gt;Contest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For the fourth year, ghoulish pups and decked out mutts will &lt;br /&gt;strut their stuff  at the fourth annual Divas Unleashed &lt;br /&gt;Halloween Pet Parade to be held on Sunday, October 26, 2008.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA- - &lt;br /&gt;The event produced by DoggieDay, The Pet Shop Girls and ‘&lt;br /&gt;sPoochies Spa and Boutique for pets has been a knock-out for &lt;br /&gt;the past three years.  This year’s event will top the previous &lt;br /&gt;years with the proceeds going to the American Society for the &lt;br /&gt;Prevention of Cruelty to Animals.  The goal this year is to &lt;br /&gt;raise $10,000 for ASPCA Orange.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Parade check-in is from 10:00am until 11:30am at the DoggieDay &lt;br /&gt;Play Center located at 400 Tremont Street in Boston’s South &lt;br /&gt;End.  The parade officially starts at 12:00noon and ends at the &lt;br /&gt;Band Stand on the Boston Common.  Once all participants have &lt;br /&gt;arrived at the Boston Common, Finalists will be chosen in each &lt;br /&gt;category by a panel of celebrity judges for Most Original, Most &lt;br /&gt;Outrageous and Best Dressed Group.  Prizes will  be given to &lt;br /&gt;the top 8 in each category.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The event is a dead-ringer for fun; Grande Divas, Universal &lt;br /&gt;Motown Recording Group JADA, with lead the parade being driven &lt;br /&gt;down the parade route in Mercedes Bens CLKs on loan from &lt;br /&gt;Chambers Motorcars of Boston, Randy Price will be escorted in a &lt;br /&gt;SMART car offered by the new Colonnade Hotel and a cast of VIPs &lt;br /&gt;will follow as the Salem High School Marching Band and Color &lt;br /&gt;Guard lead playing your favorites including the theme songs to &lt;br /&gt;Star Wars and Harry Potter as well as the Munster mash and &lt;br /&gt;other Halloween Favorites.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Are you ready for your close-up?  LaMuse Photography will be on-&lt;br /&gt;hand as part of our paw-parazzi, snapping candid shots of each &lt;br /&gt;participant.  Keep an eye out and make sure you’re smiling…….&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Can your do sit, stay and give paw the best?  Be there…or be &lt;br /&gt;square!  At the conclusion of the awarding of prizes, all dogs &lt;br /&gt;will get undressed and participant in a very large game of &lt;br /&gt;Simon Says…(with Randy Price as Simon).. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Participants are encouraged to pre-register on-line at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.doggieday.com/halloween" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doggieday....&lt;/a&gt; or purchase tickets at the &lt;br /&gt;DoggieDay Play Center.  Several hundred dogs and owners will &lt;br /&gt;turn out so please help with the efficiency of check-in by &lt;br /&gt;registering prior to the event.  The donations for registration &lt;br /&gt;are $25 per pet or a VIP registration is available for $50 per &lt;br /&gt;pet.  Only registered pets and their owners will be eligible &lt;br /&gt;for contests, prizes and give-aways.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With the success of this parade and having been started here in &lt;br /&gt;Boston, the dog community coms together  to help other dogs in &lt;br /&gt;need.  Here’s hoping Divas goes national next year, to help &lt;br /&gt;even more animals in need.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;ASPCA Mission: Orange is a focused effort to create a country &lt;br /&gt;of humane communities, one community at a time, where animals &lt;br /&gt;receive the compassion and respect they deserve—a nation where &lt;br /&gt;there is no more unnecessary euthanasia of adoptable animals &lt;br /&gt;simply because of a lack of resources and awareness.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For more information, visitwww.doggieday.com/Halloween&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will continue to host TWO meetups! For those of you who have been unable attend due to time conflicts, we will continue to hold our regular Meetups on &lt;b&gt;Sunday&lt;/b&gt; as well as on the 4th &lt;b&gt;Saturday&lt;/b&gt; of every month, 1-3pm (Doggie Day playcenter only).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who would like to be outdoors we will be meeting at BOSTON COMMON,  the green near the Boylston T Stop....(same location as last year)...&lt;b&gt;Meeting time will be 11:00 AM&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; For those who would like to be Indoors ( or head over after the park, this meetup will be held at Doggie day &lt;b&gt;(1-3pm)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should anyone have any questions, feel free to contact me.&lt;br /&gt;Susana&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226248094000</updated><rating><average>3.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221408658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua October Meetup</name><id>8755344</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223823600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/8755344/</event_url></item>