<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the first part of a series of pre-recorded Keylontic Science Workshops which will be shown over the next several Meetups.  Outline for entire series follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Awakening the God-Force Within&amp;quot; and the 12 Vehicles, the 12 Postures and the 12 Responsibilities of Spiritual Mastery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduces the Codes of Passage - the Signs, Seals and Scepters (Vehicles, Postures and Master Keys to Star Gates). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The God-Seed, the &amp;quot;Inner Earth&amp;quot; and Trion-Meajhe Time Matrices, the Ecka Map of the God-World gates, Star gates-Locks-Cruxansataea and the Halls of Amenti Star Gates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduction to Radial-Body Creation - Sculpting Intention, the Scepter Rods &amp;amp; Staff, the God-World Codes:ReushA, Eckasha-A, Eckasha-Aah, Reushayana and Rashayana and ManU &amp;quot;Inner Earth Code&amp;quot; and Immanu &amp;quot;Blood Code&amp;quot; Vecas-Lehaia, Reushia, Shahaia, Ur-immanU, ThUn-immanU &amp;amp; Or-immanU. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Focuses on Veca Code techniques for activation of the Phase 2 ImmanU Eckasha Merkaba, the Lehaia &amp;amp; UrimmanU Codes, the Psonn of Khem A Lo HA Tea, Amenti Meditation Voyage Projection, Seurias Bowing Willow, Swaying Reed, Quaking mountain and Master Se'Ur-1, the Dance of Camelot-Returning to Love: the 6 Upper Body Electrical Seuria Wave Run and Rod-Encoding. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metatronic materials present an expose within the occult teachings of so-called &amp;quot;gods&amp;quot; Osiris, Horus, Thoth, Isis, Enoch, the associated creeds of &amp;quot;YHWH&amp;quot;, the &amp;quot;Tetragrammaton&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Merlin&amp;quot;, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover the hidden realities and truths behind Metatron's Cube, and Metatron's Atom within the forbidden context of the Ancient Eyes of the God-Head and the &amp;quot;Eyes&amp;quot; of Brahman, &amp;quot;YHWH&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Elohim&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Anubis&amp;quot; and the &amp;quot;Dragon&amp;quot;; their relationship to the ancient polytheistic &amp;quot;gods&amp;quot; of Sumeria, Israel, Egypt, Yucatan, Mongolia, India, Rome &amp;amp; Greece and the hidden intimate association with Christian, Islamic, Hebrew and Eastern religious traditions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore the &amp;quot;Mysteries&amp;quot; of Osirus, Urantia, &amp;quot;Archangel&amp;quot; Michael and the 'Un-Godly' Wesedaks races and the ongoing effects on our Life Field. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation reveals PLAN A &amp;amp; PLAN B, and exposes the technologies of the &amp;quot;Turnstiles&amp;quot;, the BeaST, the &amp;quot;Polarization Wave&amp;quot;, the Judgement Day Prophecies of the &amp;quot;Atlantian Script&amp;quot;, Pre-Birth Soul Agreements, the Custodial Land Entrustments shared with Mother Earth Soul and the 3 Paths of Genesis right ahead.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask for Aalia.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254611504000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249153149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Energy Healing by Awakening the God-Force Within - Part 1</name><id>11009550</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253401200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/11009550/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/5/global_5403045.jpeg</photo_url></item>