<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 May Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.257946</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Photo Studios LLC</name><city>Worcester</city><id>5387652</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.825211</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>99.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So... you got that beautiful digital camera unpacked and out of the box. Now, what do you do? In the Introduction to Digital Photography course, students will learn the basic skills needed to "get the most out of their digital cameras" in a friendly and nurturing environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This four week course is perfect for beginning students as well as seasoned amateurs who would like to brush up on some basic skills. No previous Photographic knowledge is necessary. 35mm based single lens reflex (SLR) cameras as well as compact "point &amp;amp; shoot" cameras are welcome. Film based Photographers are welcome as well and may have their film processed and then burned onto a CD by their labs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beginning students will learn basic Photographic principals such as the camera and it's controls, how to use aperture and shutter speed together to get a "proper" exposure, depth of field, white balance, tricky lighting situations and how to get the image right "in the camera" so that lots of time isn't spent correcting the image on the computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the course of four weeks (two hours per week), beginning and more advanced students will gain a better understanding of composition, subject matter and image content. Each student will also get one-on-one instruction on the controls and functions found on their own personal cameras. Students are encouraged to bring in examples of their work for a personal critique by the instructor. Small assignments will be given to gauge the understanding of the lessons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instructor will make his E-mail available during the class as well as afterwards so that students will be able to continue to learn and grow while outside of the classroom. So, grab those instruction manuals that are collecting dust on the shelf or sitting at the bottom of your camera bag and come on down as we demystify the principles of Digital Photography. Courses can be tailor made for individuals as well as groups and can be offered here at the Studio or away at another location. This program is GREAT for Community Centers and Schools as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a limited number of spots and it will be first come first served.To secure your space please pre-pay $99 for your seat by Paypal or stopping down at the studio with check/credit card. Our Paypal address is payment@worcesterphotostudios.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Faculty Bio:&amp;nbsp; Bil Gardiner is a Photographic Artist based in Worcester, MA. The owner of William Gardiner Photography since 2002 and photographing since he was 8 years old, Bil works as a Child and Family Portrait Photographer. An award winning photographer, Bil has exhibited regionally and works in collaboration with the likes of Lou Jones, Stephen Dirado and Patrick O'Connor. A member of the Professional Photographer's Association of New England, Bil is now an educator in Photography and teaches throughout Central Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Classes will be two hours per week, for four weeks.&amp;nbsp; All dates will be from 7-9PM, February 23rd, March 1st, March 8th, and March 15th.&amp;nbsp; In the event of inclement weather, the missed class will be rescheduled.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330046707000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328744447000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CLASS:  Introduction to Digital Photography</name><id>51624232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330041600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/51624232/</event_url></item>