<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>corner of 10th St. &amp; 2nd Ave.</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10003</zip><lat>40.729770</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>347 446 4461</phone><name>St. Marks Church </name><city>New York</city><id>961514</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.986787</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This meetup is in &lt;b&gt;NYC on the eighth anniversary of the events of September 11.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully we can carpool and make the trip together..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To communicate with everyone on this list, send an email to 9-11-270@meetup.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We Demand Transparency&lt;br /&gt;A Conference for Peace, Truth, &amp;amp; New Economics&lt;br /&gt;New York City &amp;lt;&amp;gt; September 11 - 13, 2009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup begins with our attending annual events at ground zero.&lt;br /&gt;A three-day conference, with an opening concert, film premieres, &lt;br /&gt;and a rally for the 9/11 investigation ballot referendum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the formula for building a bigger, post-partisan, mass movement for peace, truth and real economic change. This is the beginning of bridge between the “peace” and “truth” movements. It all starts in NYC, on the anniversary weekend of the 9/11 attacks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;KICK OFF EVENT: 9/11 Anniversary Concert&lt;br /&gt;Friday, September 11th, Walker Stage, 8pm, 56 Walker Street, Manhattan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONFERENCE SCHEDULE at St. Marks-In-The-Bowery:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Sept. 12, 10 AM - 7 PM&lt;br /&gt;Featured Experts on the Real History of 9/11:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Richard Gage, AIA (founder Architects and Engineers for 911 Truth)&lt;br /&gt;    * Erik Lawyer (founder, Firefighters for 911 Truth)&lt;br /&gt;    * Steve Alten (author, &amp;quot;The Shell Game&amp;quot;)&lt;br /&gt;    * Kevin Barrett (author, &amp;quot;Truth Jihad Against the 911 Big Lie&amp;quot;)&lt;br /&gt;    * Barry Zwicker and Ian Woods (Canadian journalists)&lt;br /&gt;    * Barry Kissin (critic of the FBI anthrax investigation)&lt;br /&gt;    * Sander Hicks (author, &amp;quot;The Big Wedding&amp;quot;, investigative journalist)&lt;br /&gt;    * Graham McQueen (Canadian peace and truth activist)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night NYC CAN Rally&lt;br /&gt;9/12, 5-7 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * 911 Family Members, First Responders and Survivors, with an update on NYC CAN’s court battle to get a new investigation for 9/11 on the ballot in November.&lt;br /&gt;    * Bob McIlvaine - Father of 9/11 Victim Bobby McIlvaine, Member of Executive Council, NYC CAN&lt;br /&gt;    * William Pepper, Esq. - Prolific Attorney and Author of &amp;quot;Act of State&amp;quot; Chief Counsel to NYC CAN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also on Saturday, 9/12, 12-6 PM, in the Parish Hall&lt;br /&gt;Film Premieres + Director Q&amp;amp;As:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Jason Bermas (co-director, Loose Change, debuts excerpts Invisible Empire)&lt;br /&gt;    * Daniel Hopsicker (Debuts new film &amp;quot;New American Drug Lords&amp;quot; )&lt;br /&gt;    * Craig Ranke (director, screens National Security Alert)&lt;br /&gt;    * Mike Berger (director, screens Life on the Edge of the Bubble: Blowing the American Dream)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Sept. 13, 2 PM - 10 PM&lt;br /&gt;Featured Activists and Authors on Economics, Intelligence, and Transparency&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Ellen Brown (author, &amp;quot;Web of Debt&amp;quot;, feminist scholar, attorney)&lt;br /&gt;    * William Bergman (former Federal Reserve economist)&lt;br /&gt;    * Russ Baker (author of explosive new book on the Bush family, &amp;quot;Family of Secrets.&amp;quot;)&lt;br /&gt;    * Robert Steele (former CIA agent, expert on Open Source Intelligence)&lt;br /&gt;    * Tony Gronowicz (BMCC Professor, Presenting on the Secret History of the Drug War.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Frank Morales, NYC squatter activist presents on “Squatting in the Shrinking City.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Panel, 8-10 PM:&lt;br /&gt;Can We Build a Mass Movement to End War, and Bring about Real Transparency?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Debra Sweet (National Coordinator, World Can't Wait)&lt;br /&gt;    * Doug Wight (NYC 9/11 Truth Organizer)&lt;br /&gt;    * Graham McQueen (Canadian professor and peace activist.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Matt D’Aloiso (Catholic Worker/Witness Against Torture)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We Are Taking Action&lt;br /&gt;The truth movement in NYC has been on the move for the past two years, gathering over 70,000 signatures to petition the City Council to allow a new 9/11 investigation question to appear on the November, 2009 NYC ballot. In July 2009, the City threw out 24,000 of these carefully validated signatures. However, the NY Supreme Court appointed a &amp;quot;special referee&amp;quot; to arbitrate the conflict, after NYC CAN sued to have the signatures re-certified.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first day of &amp;quot;We Demand Transparency&amp;quot; ends with a two-hour rally for NYC CAN at St. Marks Church. Victims family member Bob McIlvaine, and NYC CAN attorney William Pepper (confidante of Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King), discuss the on-going court battle with the City to allow democracy at the ballot box this November. Part of the proceeds from this conference will benefit NYC CAN. &lt;a href="http://www.nyccan.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nyccan.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opening Night 911 Anniversary Concert:&lt;br /&gt;On the night of 9/11/09 kick off the conference with The NYC stop of the national TRUTH TOUR! An All-Night Concert of New Rock and Hip Hop Artists: Jordan Page, The Madeleine Haze, Sturgeon Scott (from Leftover Crack), and many others, &lt;a href="http://www.polygraphradio.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.polygraphr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Walker Stage, 56 Walker Street in Tribeca $10 at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADVANCE CONFERENCE TICKETS AVAILABLE NOW.&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $40 in advance, $60 at the door. Buy now and save $20. One ticket admits one to both days. (The conference is using a &amp;quot;fair-trade&amp;quot; ticket selling company that does not charge excessive fees. See the blog for special rates for out-of-town groups.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to: &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/76541" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brownpaper...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Advance Price of $40 expires on Aug. 23.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Sander Hicks 347 627 4705 (w.) or sanderhicksdotcom AT gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;4 comments Links to this post&lt;br /&gt;Conference Manifesto&lt;br /&gt;WE DEMAND TRANSPARENCY&lt;br /&gt;the manifesto:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will unite all those who can be united around four demands:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. The USA needs a real investigation into 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. We need a “bottom-up” bailout, economic reforms in banking, and the democratization of capital. We need an economy that works for all, not just the elite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Bush and Cheney must be prosecuted for their crimes against humanity, and their violations of the Bill of Rights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. The USA must figure out what it stands for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We say:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President Obama, you have promised “transparency.” But to the people who have been laboring for eight years under the brutal conditions of Bush/Cheney, real transparency means summoning a greater courage to tackle taboo topics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are four that can no longer go ignored:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investigate 9/11 Now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact:&lt;br /&gt;Sander Hicks, Facilitator, sander@voxpopnet.net, 347 446 4461&lt;br /&gt;Justin Martell, justinmartell@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://changeandtransparency..com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://changeandtrans...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Caputo</member_name><member_id>9333748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267659875000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251120733000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>We Demand Transparency - NYC 9/11/09</name><id>11184958</id><headcount>151</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252674000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/11184958/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/1/global_10624193.jpeg</photo_url></item>