<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>875 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06073</zip><lat>41.665751</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jai Yoga</name><city>South Glastonbury</city><id>1384899</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.603329</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Introduction to Chinese Healing with Erik Harris&lt;br /&gt;4-hour workshop description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. 5 Qi Gong exercises- Wu State, Throwing out the trash, Bouncing, Holding the ball, and Washing Up. Builds up Qi flow, Clears lower vibrational energy and expands “basketball” (Aura).&lt;br /&gt;2. Horse stance and Tai Chi Walk – Builds foundation, Strength, and Grounding. &lt;br /&gt;3. Chanting- 4 Principles of Qi Gong; Zheng, Song, Jing, Kong.  Principles represent Connection with the universe/creator, Relaxation, Tranquility, and Emptiness.  &lt;br /&gt;4. Chants to clear meridians/channels- Allowing for opening of blockages on energy pathways. &lt;br /&gt;Heart- Zhen &lt;br /&gt;Lung/Large Intestine- Shang (Shung&lt;br /&gt;Liver/Gallbladder- Ge (Guh) &amp;amp; Shi (See)&lt;br /&gt;Spleen- Gong &lt;br /&gt;Stomach- Dong&lt;br /&gt;Kidney/ Bladder- Hei- Hei (Hay-Hay) &lt;br /&gt;Brain –Hong &lt;br /&gt;Connection between Heaven and Earth- Ong-A-Hong &lt;br /&gt;5. Qi Gong Healing 10 hand positions- placing the hands on the body at specific position and letting the energy flow to where the healing is needed. &lt;br /&gt;6. 10 Everyday points for healing- Ear point for hearing, ear point for migraines, ear point for gallstones, sky window, GB20 for colds, flu, sinuses, C4 for bursitis/shoulder, T7 for low back pain, Hand point for the neck, foot point for knee pain, Ankle points for hip pain. &lt;br /&gt;7. Family Healing Techniques –Tui Na Techniques of clapping, cupping, pounding, tapping. No knowledge of meridians and points necessary. These techniques open up Qi and clear away past memory. Tapping into the muscle memory we heal the physical restoring the body, mind, spirit connection. &lt;br /&gt;8. Kung Fu Tea Ceremony- Liquid meditation- Smell, Taste, Feel the energy of wild organic tea from old tea trees high up on the mountains in China. Sip, Relax, and Enjoy life. &lt;br /&gt;9. Returning to the Earth- Taoist meditation- while sitting we make 36 circles with our hand around lower Dan Tien clockwise and counterclockwise. Bring hands to prayer position in front of the heart. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tranquility of mind will help me to live long&lt;br /&gt;Smiling will keep me always young&lt;br /&gt;I am the Air&lt;br /&gt;I am the Water&lt;br /&gt;I am the light&lt;br /&gt;With the breeze I blow to and fro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be a basic introduction to ancient forms of Chinese Healing. The exercises and techniques are simple for all to learn and duplicate to spread healing to their family, friends, and strangers. The goal will be to empower people to be of service to themselves and the world. Integrating these practices into daily life will promote optimal well-being, prevention of dis-ease, and fulfill the enjoyment of life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erik  harris</member_name><member_id>10967674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290280759000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285352891000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Chinese Healing</name><id>14884158</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290276000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/14884158/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/4/0/global_12470112.jpeg</photo_url></item>