<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Chestnut Green</address_2><address_1>121 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02035</zip><lat>42.074472</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508.698.9299</phone><name>Waxy O'Connors Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Foxborough</city><id>1018191</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.260729</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Change in the plans - turns out I'll be back from work trip in time to host this on Saturday! So let's steer clear of football games and crazy Gillette Stadium traffic :-) Hope those of you who have RSVP'd will still be able to make it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And the &amp;quot;easy&amp;quot; refers to the attitude you better bring to this ride. As for the pace of the ride - we'll try to get a sweeper - otherwise we'll adhere to the 'keep-guy/gal-behind-you-in-sight' rule which should keep the group together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few of us tried this route one lovely evening this summer, and I ended up taking the group ALL OVER the place except where we needed to be :-) But, it was actually a really nice ride - so let's give it another try!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few &amp;quot;warnings&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;considerations,&amp;quot; if you will:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Patriots are playing at 4:15pm on this day - so take into account the potential for traffic getting to Foxboro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This ride is on well-traveled ROADS so be comfortable riding with traffic and riding with a group (know thyself. If you're not comfy with sharing the road with cars, you will NOT enjoy this ride)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring a relaxed, easy-going spirit and be a good sport...if I got the group lost once, it stands to reason that it'll happen again. But maps will be provided :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because there's ample parking (and beer) here, we'll start near the Walgreens/Waxy O'Connors parking lot (new shopping center on 140 across from Dairy Queen). Look for the bikes - we'll be in the side parking lot closest to the cleaners/Glee gift store/Waxy's/Tanorama stores.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;And get this - &amp;quot;grub&amp;quot; doesn't necessarily need to take place at Waxy's. We might try the Chinese place in the plaza. But I'll take an informal poll when we all meet up that day.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MapMyRide.com is having a technical glitch -- so I'm not sure the map is going to come up correctly but if you're interested in the route, &lt;a href="http://www.mapmyride.com/route/us/ma/foxborough/599127881058073701" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Head south on 140 onto South Street for 2.3 miles to crossroads (West Street and N. Grove Street) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Left for 0.6 mile to end (Rte 106). There's a steep hill at the beginning. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right for 0.1 mile to S. Grove Street on left immediately after the bridge over I-495. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Straight for 2.5 miles to Route 152 at traffic light. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Straight for 0.4 mile to crossroads (George Street) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right for 0.5 mile to Route 1, at stop sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right for 0.4 mile to Shepard Street, which bears right. You'll pass Turnpike Lake on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bear right for 0.4 mile to end (Route 152) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Left for 0.4 mile to Mirimichi Street for right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right for 2.3 miles to end at traffic island. The main road bears right after 0.4 mile and crosses Lake Mirimichi. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Left for 0.3 mile to Mill Street on right (sign says TO STATE FOREST). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right for 1.3 miles to fork (Prospect Street, unmarked, bears left). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bear left for 0.8 mile to end (Granite Street, unmarked). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right for 0.9 mile to end (Route 140). You'll pass Sunset Lake on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turn right on Route 140. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bethany</member_name><member_id>10111481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288304310000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Grinders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group</urlname><id>1500421</id><group_lat>42.0600013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Foxboro Grind &amp; Grub Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286827394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Like SATURDAY AFTERNOON</name><id>15074920</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287855000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group/events/15074920/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/4/global_10374836.jpeg</photo_url></item>