<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>84 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359238</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Campus - Julius Adams Stratton Building </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>438442</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be using various fun activities to facilitate learning including short conversations, games and presentations to review and practice the spanish language.  Future sessions will involve learning about cultures where the Spanish language is spoken. Please RSVP.  If your plans change and you can not make it, please change your RSVP so that others may attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Materials:&lt;/b&gt; Bring a pen, pencils, paper, a Spanish\English Dictionary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to find the organizer(s)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell phone number will be given out to everyone who rsvp's for this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet just inside the building's main entrance that is closest to Massachusetts Ave., in the vicinity of the MIT Federal Credit Union and the restaurant Anna's Taqueria.  I may be standing or sitting down at the tables or chairs closest to the door.  We will then together find a place to sit down in one of the lounges or food court areas. It is fine with me if you can stay for only 1 1/2 of the 2 hours allotted for this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public Transit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MBTA:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kendall Square Red Line - Walk on Main Street in the direction opposite Longfellow Bridge. Take a left onto Vassar Street (no sign for Vassar Street) at the sign that reads Danny Lewin Square. Walk to the other end of Vassar Street and cross over to the other side of Massachusetts Avenue. Take a left and walk a short distance. You will see the concrete Stratton Building on your right. &lt;br /&gt;Hynes\ICA Green Line Boston, transfer to RT 1 Harvard\Holyoke Gate bus or walk toward Cambridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Buses:&lt;/b&gt; RT 1 Harvard\Holyoke Gate; or RT1 Dudley Station via Mass Ave.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My cell phone number will be given out to everyone who rsvp's for this event.  I look just like my photo, except my hair is a darker brown.   Refer to the details section below for more information as to how to find me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>1166817</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210100802000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonspanish</urlname><id>145862</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209856128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spanish Language and Culture Exchange</name><id>7866963</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209927600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonspanish/events/7866963/</event_url></item>