<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (1976) dir Martin Scorsese w/Robert De Niro, Jodie Foster, Cybill Shepherd, Harvey Keitel, Peter Boyle, Albert Brooks [113 min]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I thought it would be interesting to revisit &lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; over the 4th of July weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thirty years old and endlessly imitated, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; still packs a fearsome punch. Of all the psychos, sociopaths, and screw-ups that Robert De Niro has played for director Martin Scorsese, none is more iconic than Travis Bickle, the cuckoo cabbie on a self-appointed mission to wash the scum off the streets of New York. From the lush menace of Bernard Herrmann's score to Jodie Foster's performance as a twelve-year-old prostitute, it's a film that screams to be seen on the big screen. And yes, we are talkin' to you...&amp;nbsp; BBC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; Michael Chapman&amp;rsquo;s lurid cinematography captures the ugly poetics of a sweltering, garbage strewn New York City, and the score by Hollywood legend, Bernard Herrmann casts a further undertone of brooding malevolence. &lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;TAXI DRIVER&lt;/span&gt; is a film that is more than the sum of its parts, even though those parts are amazing on their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An ex-marine Vietnam vet turned New York City cab driver, Travis Bickle works the night shift because he can&amp;rsquo;t sleep anyway; the city is just too out of control. Despite his attempts to find a human connection with a beautiful campaign worker (Shepherd) and an all-too-young prostitute (Foster), the city&amp;rsquo;s malcontents seem to ratchet up their disturbing behavior, Bickle&amp;rsquo;s alienation increases, and his already fragile mind is pushed to the breaking point. This is the film that proved that no one does blood-drenched despair quite like Martin Scorsese. Brattle description&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was while &lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was in post-production that the Daily &lt;em&gt;News&lt;/em&gt; ran the headline &amp;ldquo;FORD TO CITY: DROP DEAD.&amp;rdquo; The movie is Scorsese&amp;rsquo;s hometown farewell (a love letter quite different from &lt;a href="http://www.villagevoice.com/related/to/Woody+Allen"&gt;Woody Allen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s). Like Nero, he torches the joint and picks up his lyre. &lt;em&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/em&gt;is a vision of a world that already knows it is lost. A third of a century later, the Checker cabs are gone, as are the taxi garages at the end of 57th Street and the all-night Belmore cafeteria. Times Square has been sanitized, the pestilent combat zone at Third Avenue and 13th Street where Iris peddles her underage charms has long since been gentrified. New York is no longer the planet&amp;rsquo;s designated Hell on Earth. (Six years after &lt;em&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.villagevoice.com/related/to/Blade+Runner"&gt;Blade Runner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; would dramatize a new urban space.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No nostalgia, though: In other aspects, the world of &lt;em&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/em&gt;is recognizably ours. Libidinal politics, celebrity worship, sexual exploitation, the fetishization of guns and violence, racial stereotyping, the fear of foreigners&amp;mdash;not to mention the promise of apocalyptic religion&amp;mdash;all remain. &lt;em&gt;Taxi Driver&lt;/em&gt; lives. See it again. And try to have a nice day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.villagevoice.com/photoGallery/index/2452927/0"&gt;&lt;img src="http://vvoice.vo.llnwd.net/e14//35-years-later-taxi-driver-still-stuns.6093395.40.jpg" alt="Checkered past: De Niro drives angry." style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jhoberman@villagevoice.com"&gt;jhoberman@villagevoice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
After the film we will go to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion.
Hope to see you there,
Tom</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will hold a red, white, and blue meetup sign near the front row after the film and then we will go to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1309923659000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308967548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scorsese's Taxi Driver</name><id>23442111</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309725000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/23442111/</event_url></item>