<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Off Rte 10</address_2><address_1>Hilton Court</address_1><state>NJ</state><zip>07054</zip><lat>40.840450</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hilton Hotel - New Jersey</name><city>Parsippany</city><id>588841</id><country>us</country><lon>-74.452780</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Halloween 08 Chiller Theater Expo on Saturday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.chillertheatre.com/main.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chillertheatre.com/main.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chillerthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look at the link for the event details; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be contacting those coming with me &lt;br /&gt;Later on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be driving to &lt;br /&gt;Chiller Theatre Toy, Model and Film Extravaganza &lt;br /&gt;Hilton Hotel &lt;br /&gt;Parsippany, New Jersey, 07054&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions can be found on the link.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do go a different way; &lt;br /&gt;From West Haven I 95 to Exit 38 veer left towards &lt;br /&gt;The Merritt Parkway that later becomes the &lt;br /&gt;Hutchinson River Parkway to Exit 26 West on to &lt;br /&gt;I 287 West and I 87. Take exit 15 to get off I 87 &lt;br /&gt;To stay on I 287. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(FYI Exit 55 has a Wendys or Burger King if you need a break. &lt;br /&gt;The Burger King is closer to the High Way Ramp.) &lt;br /&gt;Exit 39B to Rte 10 W towards Dover. &lt;br /&gt;Exit on to Dryden Way. &lt;br /&gt;Left on Campus Drive. &lt;br /&gt;Left on Hilton Ct. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pay attention to turns. &lt;br /&gt;Twice I had missed a turn and had to go back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can Park in the Building Complex on the Left. &lt;br /&gt;Short Walk to the Hilton Hotel beyond the Pond on the &lt;br /&gt;Right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To answer the question of what is Chiller Con? &lt;br /&gt;Chiiller Con has a few things happening; various vendors are selling their products such as DVDs or Model Figurines or Magazines or Autographed Photos, etc. &lt;br /&gt;Newer Genre or B Movie Stars are there to promote their most recent genre movies. &lt;br /&gt;Elder stars come out of their retirement to meet their fans. &lt;br /&gt;Wrestlers, Writers, Artists and other kinds of entertainers also come out to meet their fans. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The October Show has the fans dressed up in all kinds of costumes, esp. &lt;br /&gt;but not limited to Goth outfits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is usually lots of fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to bring your cameras. &lt;br /&gt;A listing of stars / guests will also come in handy. &lt;br /&gt;There might be long lines to get some autographs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chillertheatre.com/gt/gtc4.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chillerthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.chillertheatre.com/gt/gtc4.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They already have out their list of Guests, &lt;br /&gt;There will be more guests later on. &lt;br /&gt;Here are some of the Guests; &lt;br /&gt;Burt Reynolds, Patty Duke, Morgan Fairchild, &lt;br /&gt;Linda Hamilton, David Hedison, Catherine Bach, &lt;br /&gt;Sandra Taylor, Angie Dickenson, Linda Evans, &lt;br /&gt;Fabiana Undenio, Star Trek, Jaws, &lt;br /&gt;Dukes of Hazard, Welcome Back Kotter, &lt;br /&gt;Shock-O-Rama stars &lt;br /&gt;and go to the link to see who else &lt;br /&gt;Is coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Expo is all weekend from Friday, Oct 24 to &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Oct 26. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am going on Saturday, Oct 25. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I plan on going to Hudson Valley to see some&lt;br /&gt;Legend of Sleepy Hollow attractions on the way back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hudsonvalley.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hudsonvall...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.hudsonvalley.org/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If more than one vehicle is going, then the passengers should &lt;br /&gt;Share phone numbers in case the different vehicles have &lt;br /&gt;To contact each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have four tickets for my guests and myself. &lt;br /&gt;There might be a long line if you have to buy tickets at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tickets came with websites and the websites have &lt;br /&gt;Chiller News;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.zacherley.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.zacherley....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.zacherley.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHILLER THEATRE RETURNS TO WPIX &lt;br /&gt;with a Special airing of Tarantula on October 25th! &lt;br /&gt;CHILLLLLLER THEATRE RETURNS FROM THE DEAD! For the first time in over 25 years, Chiller Theatre is back on WPIX with the presentation of the 1955 pulp horror classic Tarantula at 8 pm on Saturday, October 25th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zacherley, The Cool Ghoul (John Zacherle), and former host of Chiller Theatre in New York on WPIX (1963) will resurrect his alter-ego and appear in a cameo spot to open the WPIX October 25 special. Plus, the original chilling Chiller openers: The Six-Fingered Hand and the Monster Montage along with Tarantula trivia will run as interstitials. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the 1955 film, a lab experiment gone awry creates a massive 100-ft. spider that menaces a small Arizona desert town and satiates its bloodlust with cattle -- before moving on to human beings! Tarantula features an un credited cameo by Clint Eastwood in one of his first ever on-screen appearances. Directed by Jack Arnold (It Came From Outer Space, The Incredible Shrinking Man) Tarantula is considered by many to be one of the best of its genre and even inspired composer Richard O'Brien to immortalize it in the Rocky Horror Picture Show. (From Science Fiction Double Feature: &amp;quot;I knew Leo G. Carroll was over a barrel when Tarantula took to the hills!&amp;quot;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After our successful 60th anniversary celebration in June, WPIX received hundreds of requests for the return of Chiller Theatre. We are extremely excited to resurrect Chiller for our viewers with the special airing of Tarantula, said Betty Ellen Berlamino, WPIX/CW11 President and General Manager. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original Chiller Theatre aired in all of its ghoulish glory on WPIX from 1961-1978 and again from 1980 to1982.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.deadelvi.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.deadelvi.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.deadelvi.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B &lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be picking up Maribeth and two of her guests.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225134924000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Coffee Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>coffee-397</urlname><id>570343</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Coffee Talk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210487777000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee Talk &amp; Halloween 08 Chiller Theater Expo on Saturday</name><id>7915916</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224961200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/coffee-397/events/7915916/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/e/global_2654830.jpeg</photo_url></item>