<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Amory</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.316804</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>Center Of Light</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>196692</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102484</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>September Conscious Movie: &lt;b&gt;Sicko&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, September 11th • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Price of Sugar&amp;quot; was scheduled for Sept; but we received a letter from an attorney representing some of the people who are part of this documentary saying that there is a law suit in progress for defamatory statements. This should be resolved this fall. Until we know more about it, the viewing will be postponed.  So, instead of this movie, we’ll be showing Michael Moore’s “Sicko.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movie Description:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;SiCKO is more like a controlled howl of protest than a documentary. Toning down the rhetoric of past efforts--no CEOs, congressmen, or celebrities were accosted in the making of this film--Michael Moore's latest provocation is just as heartfelt, if not more heartbreaking. As he clarifies from the outset, his subject isn't the 45 million Americans without insurance, but those whose coverage has failed to meet their needs. He starts by speaking with patients who've been denied life-saving procedures, like chemotherapy, for the most spurious of reasons. Then he travels to Canada, England, and France to see if socialized medicine is as inefficient as U.S. politicians like to claim--especially those who receive funding from pharmaceutical companies. Moore finds quality care available to all, regardless as to income. He concludes with a stunt that made headlines when he assembles a group of 9/11 rescue workers suffering from a variety of afflictions. When Moore is informed that detainees at Guantánamo Bay--technically American soil--qualify for universal coverage, he and his companions travel to Cuba to get in on that action. It's a typically grandstanding move on Moore's part. And it proves remarkably effective when these altruistic individuals, who've either been denied treatment or forced to pay outrageous costs for their medication, experience a dramatically different system. Nine years in the making, SiCKO makes a persuasive case that it's time for America to catch up with the rest of the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*This meetup is free, but donations are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ring the bell of the big wooden door if you come late; otherwise, it will be open.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254950307000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250002422000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September Conscious Movie:  Film Changed from "The Price of Sugar" to "Sicko"</name><id>11085848</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252711800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/11085848/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/b/b/global_10537211.jpeg</photo_url></item>