<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Bridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.817093</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stripers Inn</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>1631898</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870445</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's try this again!&amp;nbsp; Weather dependent- so will be cancelled due to rain or temperatures below 15 degrees...otherwise- we're on!!&amp;nbsp; This will be a brisk, quick after work walk...perfect to get a little exercise in. I'm told Route 1 provides a little bit of light on this trail, and it's otherwise flat and typically free of any obstacles. I will wear my headlamp, and feel free to bring yours if you have one and want it. It's about 2.5 miles round trip, and I do walk fairly quickly...so I'd like to be able to do the full trail at least once, and perhaps repeat a portion of it if time allows.&amp;nbsp; Since it will only get darker and colder if we wait, we'll kick off right at 5:15, so please be on time (or just hussle and catch up with us...it is an easy trail to find the group!).&amp;nbsp; NOTE THAT WE DON'T MEET AT STRIPERS...Friedenfels St (where the parking lot for the trail is) is directly across Rt 1 from Stripers. It's a little tricky to find at first, but basically the blinking yellow light at Stripers, across Rt 1. Please bring a dollar to contribute to meetup fees. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marilee </member_name><member_id>6596076</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327101461000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326756844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After work walk at Salisbury Rail Trail</name><id>48376102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327011300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/48376102/</event_url></item>