<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Learn How To Legally and Ethically&lt;br /&gt;Hammer the IRS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taxes are probably your #1 expense.  John Hyre would like to help you change that.  As a tax attorney, accountant and real estate investor, he's well equipped to do just that.  On Wednesday, October 13th, he will cover the basics of how to legally and ethically lower your taxes. The speech will be full of substance, not sales hype.  You will learn what the IRS is good at, what it's not good at, and how to take advantage of both situations.  You will learn how to squeeze the most out of depreciation, which entities are best for you (and why Nevada is a waste of your time) and how to get the deductions you deserve.  You will learn about IRS penalties - and how to avoid them.  He'll also teach you how to prepare for an audit and why it's not something to be afraid of.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't miss this one!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;NHREIA Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM, Wednesday, October 13, 2010&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Best Western Executive Court&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;13500 South Willow Street, Manchester&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free for members; $20 for non-members and meetup members&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;It's time for the NHREIA Board elections.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nominations may be made from the membership by or before the October meeting on October 13, 2010. A biography and short statement must be submitted to the Board within five days following the October meeting. Voting, either in person, or by proxy, will be held at the November 10th meeting. Click here for a description of the positions and responsibilities can be found in the NHREIA By-laws.   &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287013417000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-756</urlname><id>633261</id><group_lat>42.9399986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>NH Entrepreneurs Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852335000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The New Hampshire Real Estate Investors Association Monthly Meetup</name><id>tshdnynnbrb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287009000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-756/events/14989670/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/2/global_13142130.jpeg</photo_url></item>