<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Arrow Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.370087</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-910-0822</phone><name>Club Oberon</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1058452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113556</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*** New***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to RSVP so I can send you contact information about meeting up at OM! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at OM Lounge in Cambridge at 9pm for drinks before the show! At 10, we can walk over to Club Oberon (less than 10 minutes) for the show. You are welcome to meet us at the club or just for drinks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This looks like so much fun, it was to tough to pass it up! Let's get a group together for this event. If people are interested, we can meet for a drink before at Red Line or Grendel's Den!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** We have members from a couple MEETUP groups joining us!**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please, please let me know if you are interested ASAP! I want to be able to send updates to those who want to learn more! I'll keep those who RSVP YES or MAYBE in the loop! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;Boston's burlesque home team is coming to Oberon for one performance only: a magical night that re-creates a Golden Age of Burlesque that never really was. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's the ultimate burlesque experience--an elegant evening of rhinestones and feather boas, of spectacle, sailors, and speakeasy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come party on the dance floor like its 1939 as the U.S.O.-inspired show unfolds on all sides of you. It's a wartime, wintertime fable told in swingtime. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The living is easy as Oberon is transformed into a fantasy blend of the best parts of the 1920s, 1930s, 1940s, and 1950s.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dancefloor&amp;quot; tickets are $25...but only$20 using the code POSTCARD. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can read more about it, or buy tickets at &lt;a href="http://bostonbabydolls.net/NEW/Shows/vforvixen.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonbabydoll...&lt;/a&gt;.  You can also buy tickets over the phone at 866-811-4111&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be posted on both Boston Ladies Night AND Boston Nights...please RSVP at either event...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not a plan-ahead type of person? Don't worry...there are other ways to get the discount! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To honor the brave men and women of the United States armed forces, The Boston Babydolls are pleased to offer a 50% discount on advanced tickets to those on active duty. Just enter the code HERO when purchasing your tickets and show your military I.D. at the door when picking up your tickets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also do your part for the Marine Corps' holiday charity, Toys for Tots. Members of the Marine Corps will be on site collecting your donations during the evening. If you bring a donation, you'll get $5 off your ticket. Toys should be:&lt;br /&gt;- Toys should be appropriate for children of any age up to 10 years old&lt;br /&gt;- New (due to health regulations, they are only allowed to collect and distribute new toys)&lt;br /&gt;- Non-violent (no guns or weapons, please)&lt;br /&gt;- Unwrapped&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please RSVP  yes or maybe so I can keep you posted! </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262050092000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Lifers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonnights</urlname><id>860845</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Nights</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259119512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>V for Vixen! Burlesque Show</name><id>11952097</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259978400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonnights/events/11952097/</event_url></item>