<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.842763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Surfside 5 Beach Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>962091</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.816092</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's start the warm weather off with a bang and go see Don't Call Me Shirley on the deck!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SurfSide5 Beach Bar &amp;amp; Grille on Salisbury Beach features a huge 8,000 sq.ft. deck located directly over the ocean, SurfSide5 is the place to catch the surf, sun and fun as well as live music &amp;amp; DJ’s, our popular Reggae Sundays with Hot Like Fire, cool tropical drinks, and LOBSTER IN THE ROUGH! Lobsters, steamers, chowder and more beach fare on the deck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;PLEASE Note: This will be another popular event!  The venue does NOT take reservations BUT I will try to hold seats for everyone that is attending (for both groups). BUT please be patient if we are not able to hold seats for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cover charge:&lt;/strong&gt; NONE!!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; Plenty around the beach, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will be scheduled on my 2 Meetup sites, (Our Circle of Friends and Connection &amp;amp; Friends) there may be more people going to this event then you see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a minute now and put the Meetup phone into your phone, that way if you are are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, you already have it in your phone:  978-304-2811, please note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues?  Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can pay your dues at any event.  Thank you in advance for paying your dues!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a courtesy to everyone in the group come back to the event page and change your RSVP if your plans change or call me/send a message through the site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the deck come in and find us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368290357000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365995149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don't Call Me Shirley @ Surfside 5!!!</name><id>114382962</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368234000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/114382962/</event_url></item>