<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;This is a red hot deal you have to jump on ASAP!&lt;/span&gt; Free admission to an advance screening of the movie '127 Hours' at the Hartford, CT Bowtie Palace theater. Free passes are limited and going fast! This IS a hiking related movie and the trailers look great!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You and a guest are cordially invited to a special advance screening. Please GET YOUR PASS FIRST. Then RSVP here with the hiking group so we know who is trying to go (they overbook as they want a full theater so get there EARLY!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MOVIE SCREENING DETAILS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;===============================&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, November 17, 7:00PM&lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT   &lt;br /&gt;RSVP Code: &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;6C92WW76&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;===============================&lt;br /&gt;TO DOWNLOAD A SCREENING PASS &lt;br /&gt;==============================&lt;br /&gt;1) Go to &lt;a href="http://www.gofobo.com/rsvp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gofobo.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Enter RSVP Code: &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;6C92WW76&lt;/span&gt; (Must enter in all caps to work!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Register with GOFOBO, if you are not already registered&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) Print pass and attend screening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are complimentary, but are expected to go quickly as there is a limited number available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note - &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;arrive early as screenings are always overbooked to ensure a full theater. &lt;u&gt;Seating is first come-first served, and is not guaranteed&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directed by:  Danny Boyle&lt;br /&gt;Screenplay by:  Danny Boyle &amp;amp; Simon Beaufoy&lt;br /&gt;Based on the book &amp;quot;Between a Rock and a Hard Place&amp;quot; by:  Aron Ralston&lt;br /&gt;Produced by:  Christian Colson, Danny Boyle, John Smithson&lt;br /&gt;Executive Produced by:  Bernie Bellew, John J. Kelly, François Ivernel, Cameron McCracken, Lisa Marie Falcone, Tessa Ross&lt;br /&gt;Cast:  James Franco, Amber Tamblyn, Kate Mara, Clémence Poésy, Kate Burton, Lizzy Caplan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;127 HOURS is the new film from Danny Boyle, the Academy Award winning director of 2008's Best Picture, SLUMDOG MILLIONAIRE. 127 HOURS is the true story of mountain climber Aron Ralston's (James Franco) remarkable adventure to save himself after a fallen boulder crashes on his arm and traps him in an isolate canyon in Utah.  Over the next five days Ralston examines his life and survives the elements to finally discover he has the courage and the wherewithal to extricate himself by any means necessary, scale a 65 foot wall and hike over eight miles before he is finally rescued.   Throughout his journey, Ralston recalls friends, lovers (Clémence Poésy), family, and the last two people he ever had the chance to meet?  A visceral thrilling story that will take an audience on a never before experienced journey and prove what we can do when we choose life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;127 HOURS OPENS IN SELECT THEATERS ON &lt;u&gt;NOVEMBER 19&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Disclaimer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Arrive early! Seating is first-come, first-served, except for members of the reviewing press. This ticket does not guarantee you a seat! Theatre is overbooked to ensure a full house. Theatre is not responsible for overbooking. No admittance once screening has begun. This pass is the property of Fox Searchlight, which reserves the right to admit or refuse access to the theatre at the discretion of an authorized studio and/or theatre representative. Duplicate passes will not be accepted. Screening passes are non transferrable. This ticket is NOT for resale. Reselling of tickets is strictly prohibited and punishable by law. All those found in violation will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;MPAA - No Recording&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This screening will be monitored for unauthorized recording. By attending, you agree not to bring any audio and/or visual recording device including laptop computers into the theatre and you consent to physical search of your belongings and person for such device. If you attempt to enter with a recording device, you will be denied admission. If you attempt to use a recording device*, you consent to your immediate removal from the theatre and forfeiture of the device. Nothing contained in this notice shall limit the available remedies Fox Searchlight may have against you. Unauthorized recording will be reported to law enforcement and may subject you to criminal and civil liability (including damages up to $150,000). *This includes cell phones with photo capabilities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To Print (or if you later can't go)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A PDF document will be saved to your computer and will open a window to allow you to save the PDF file to your desktop. You will need adobe reader to view your pass(es). The documents that print with a barcode are your pass(es). Print them out and bring them with you to the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need to reprint your passes or do not have access to a printer now, you may reprint your passes in the MY FOBO area. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;If you are unable to attend the screening, please release your passes in the MY FOBO area (select &amp;quot;Cancel RSVP&amp;quot;) so that others can attend.&lt;/span&gt; Please note that duplicate passes will not be accepted at the screening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;127 Hours&lt;br /&gt;November 17, 2010 - 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Bow Tie Cinemas Hartford Palace 17&lt;br /&gt;330 New Park Ave&lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT 06106 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Hartford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=330+New+Park+Ave+%23+0610&amp;amp;zipcode=06106-2966&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.74712&amp;amp;longitude=-72.713366&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailers and movie information:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxsearchlight.com/127hours" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foxsearchl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290289886000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289437354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advance Screening of Movie: '127 Hours' in Hartford CT</name><id>15410083</id><headcount>43</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290038400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15410083/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/a/4/global_19540260.jpeg</photo_url></item>