<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 Boston Post Rd W</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.338904</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>808693</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.590103</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Comment from Alice&lt;/span&gt; (organizer).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michelle suggested this Meetup. Thanks for activating, Michelle. I've procrastinated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll introduce ourselves and our situations, and see what follows. I'll bring a book I've used called "Organizing from the Inside Out" and say a few words about it as a conversation stimulator if we need one. I always hope for our members, including myself, to find buddies to help them get started and stay on track. I know I always learn something from the conversation. And usually have a few laughs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting will last until we get kicked out or drift off. Usually our meetings last about 1.5 to 2 hours. They work best if we get there on time so everyone is in on the conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've limited the RSVPs to 10 this time because the venue is small. There is a waiting list. You'll be emailed if someone cancels and then get a chance to RSVP. Members can bring a guest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Michelle's original:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think we should meet soon. People need the support of others. Summer is a great time to clean and do those jobs we dont want to do. THere is more time in the summer , the weather is beautiful (open those windows). We could meet at the library, a room in a building (church ect) a park. anywhere . Lets just do it,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I dont know where you met in the past. I am new and just signed up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Panera is in the RK shopping center that houses Hannaford. Panera is toward Office Max. We'll have a sign saying MWPC</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342663774000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Procrastinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers</urlname><id>1357989</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>Metrowest Procrastinators and Clutterers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341584371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lets meet on Wed., July 18th</name><id>72197802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342652400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Metrowest-Procrastinators-and-Clutterers/events/72197802/</event_url></item>