<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In the past several months, our group has had several good discussions touching upon the concept of &amp;quot;emptiness.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Emptiness&amp;quot; is a central concept in Buddhism (some say &amp;quot;the&amp;quot; central concept), and one that for many students of Budhist philosophy seems at times to be simple, at times complex and at times unfathomable. To continue with our exploration of &amp;quot;emptiness,&amp;quot; our book for December will be &amp;quot;Introduction to Emptiness as taught in Tsong-Kha-pa's Great Treatise on The Stages of the Path.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a short book (111 pages with a glossary) that takes the readers through the teachings on emptiness as presented in the Ge-luk sect of Tibetan Buddhism. The author, Guy Newland, has been fascinated by these teachings for over 30 years. He writes in the introduction:  &amp;quot;If you are a person with some background in Buddhism but without specialized expertise in Buddhist philosophy, then -- whether you are a serious practitioner or just curious-- I have written with you in mind.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The book summarizes and explains the key ideas and arguments of the Ge-luk sect's founder Tsong-Kha-pa (1357-1419) that he put forth in the &amp;quot;insight&amp;quot; section of his massive text &amp;quot;The Great Treatise on the Stages of the Path,&amp;quot; which he completed in 1402. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guy Newland is Professor of Religion and Chair of the Department of Philosophy and Religion at Central Michigan University, where he has taught since 1988. He holds a Ph.D. in the history of religions from the University of Virginia, where he studied Tibetan Buddhism with Jeffrey Hopkins. Newland has also studied with many Tibetan scholars in the U.S. and India. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292289655000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263226821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Introduction to Emptiness" by Guy Newland</name><id>12286800</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292284800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/12286800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/5/global_1946069.jpeg</photo_url></item>