<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Paxton</address_2><address_1>Saw Mill Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.309063</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-596-3839</phone><name>Moore State Park</name><city>Paxton</city><id>622697</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.953125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Moore State Park &lt;br /&gt;Sawmill Road, Paxton&lt;br /&gt;508 792-3969 is the number for the Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But this number is for Leah's cell phone 508-596-3839- Leah will be leading this click and shoot. She likes this park and has been wanting to return to take photos for a while. I asked her to lead a click and shoot and this is where she wanted to do it. So let's all join in the fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be a fee to get into the park. It's usually around 5.00 but I am not sure about it. I can not find info on the site to say.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PACK a LUNCH! Please pack a lunch, we'll all meet up around 1pm to have a lovely snack together. Be sure to bring water and sunscreen as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A peaceful 400-acre retreat in the heart of central Massachusetts, Moore was the site of grist and saw mills from 1747 through the early part of this century. It then became a private estate. What remains today is the best of both: stone mill foundations, a restored sawmill, and mountains of glorious rhododendrons, azaleas and mountain laurel. The flowers cascade down hills, line wooded paths and decorate waterfalls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The power of falling water was early New England's primary energy source. Turkey Hill Brook, dropping 90 feet in less than a quarter mile, was a good mill site, and as many as five separate mills may have been built here. The remnants of the mill-village at Moore give a glimpse of the old rural manufacturing economy which was displaced by the industrial developments of the nineteenth century.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/more.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please meet us at the Sawmill in the park. We'll be the ones with the Meetup Sign...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214834637000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>These click and shoots always produce amazing photos. I encourage you all to share them on our Meetup Site's photos area or on or on our Worcester Photo Center Wiki. Check out some of the past click and shoots and you'll see why these are fun days.</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211898789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot - Moore State Park</name><id>8018736</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214661600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8018736/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/1/global_4262481.jpeg</photo_url></item>