<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Financial District Club Quarters Hotel</address_2><address_1>161 Devonshire Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.356221</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 350-9977</phone><name>Elephant &amp; Castle</name><city>Boston</city><id>791944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057235</lon></venue><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover room rental.</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>As part of our monthly discussion series, we're having a conversation about &lt;b&gt;What It Means To Be An Ally on Monday, March 22nd&lt;/b&gt; at Elephant &amp;amp; Castle* by the State Street T stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we're serious about building a cross-issue community, network and movement, then it's crucial that we consider what it means to be an ally. The goal is to move beyond being allies by focusing on the part of the social justice vision we have in common. But first let's sort out what being &amp;quot;an ally&amp;quot; means to each of us and to those we're allied with.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To connect to &amp;quot;the work&amp;quot; and each other in more intentional ways, SoJust is hosting a 3-month discussion series. This is a place for us to explore what we have in common and where we differ on topics that are important to us. This is not a seminar - there will be no presentation -  come with questions you'd like to explore. We'll creatively use the space:  smaller groups to focus on specific topics, pairing up, etc. Join us to learn more about yourself and other SoJusters!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So you know what to expect here's what we have planned:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6pm Socializing - order dinner/drinks (30 min)&lt;br /&gt;6:30 Gather in large circle for introductions (20 min)&lt;br /&gt;6:50 Break into small groups (30 min)&lt;br /&gt;7:20 Report back (10 min)&lt;br /&gt;7:30 Break into small groups (30 min)&lt;br /&gt;8pm Report Back (10 min)&lt;br /&gt;8:10 Closing (20 min)&lt;br /&gt;8:30 Socializing some more&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Elephant &amp;amp; Castle is located at 161 Devonshire Street. T Directions: Take the Orange or Blue Line to the State Street stop. Bear left on State St, Right on Devonshire &amp;amp; head 2 blocks to the pub. Nearest Green Line is the Government Center Stop, and nearest Red Line is Downtown Crossing. This venue IS wheelchair accessible (there's an elevator).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Head downstairs and you'll find us in the conference room. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282061619000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268097278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What It Means To Be An Ally [Discussion]</name><id>12822944</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269295200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/12822944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/6/1/global_13546449.jpeg</photo_url></item>