<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For those with family too far away or those who may not want to travel or go to your boss's house or avoid family or hate turkey, let's all get together for a day of thanks with friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking for at least 4 people who would like to stay close to Providence on T-day. If not, I'll cancel to have time to make alternative plans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been invited to a few things but would rather stay closer to home. I'm suggesting a potluck rather than traditional turkey. Share your favorite recipe, international theme. Beware that some may have food restrictions (vegetarians, wheat/gluten free, dairy) so bring what you can, but don't be offended if some don't eat it. There are some restaurants that have dinner items you can purchase if you don't want to cook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR we can volunteer at the soup kitchen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you rsvp tell us what you'll bring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm willing to host this, but if someone has a little bit bigger place and we need more room happy to move venues. Will email final info closer to the big day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I imagine most people will rsvp NO because it is a holiday, so you don't have to rsvp at all unless you want to join. May come across as the poor sorry people who don't have anywhere to go but I don't want to give that impression if you know what I mean. If no one needs a place to go, I'll cancel the event and follow through on one of the other invites I've had, so all is good, really.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228267032000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226267778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thanksgiving Brunch</name><id>9127399</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227805200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/9127399/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>