<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your Home</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.373188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Your Home</name><city>Boston</city><id>1000833</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120766</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is an introductory workshop for those interested in starting their own business, given by someone who has started several.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PAYMENT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;*Class is $30 in advance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Pre-pay here: &lt;a href="http://buildsmallbiz.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://buildsmallbiz....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This class is designed to answer some basic questions for the budding entrepreneur, such as: Who do I need on my team? What type of planning should I do? What is a mission statement and why do I need one? These questions will not be answered from an academic point of view, but from the experience of a real world business person who has done it before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warning! This will be a very interactive workshop and only those who want to actively participate should attend. This workshop is designed to be informative, fun and practical. Come with your aspirations and questions in hand! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sam Liebowitz is real estate developer and serial entrepreneur. He has been in business for himself since 1993 and has owned several successful businesses, including a software consulting firm, a video publishing business and an Internet business for aerospace engineers and managers. He uses sound business principles to develop new businesses, and provides mentoring to those interested in starting their own business. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides real estate development, his current ventures include Dragon &amp;amp; Tiger Development, a mix-use real estate development company, and World Green Technologies, a company that creates strategic alliances and marketing opportunities in the “green” industry. In the past three years he has held the “How to Start Your Own Business” class for NYC Cashflow, New York Business Network Group, the Chinese Teatime Association, among other groups in New York.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Testimonials:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Thanks for the very valuable information you gave us at Monday evening's workshop.  A mark of success is when that information becomes part of my business plan...and it has.”&lt;br /&gt;-- Susan Ragusa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “Super great event, great experience, better than MBA course with a similar subject, since those teachers have no startup experience at all.” &lt;br /&gt;-- Alan Ding&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CALL IN NUMBER - The bridge number and pass code will be sent to you via e-mail two days before the class.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teleclass Details/Policy: You can be located anywhere in the world to join us. When you register, you will be forwarded a phone number for a conference line where we will all join together.Come to all calls with your notepad/journal and a pen. This call will be recorded and for sale after the class, if you would like to not be on the recording you are free to just listen in. This introductory price is to attend the live call only. No recordings will be sent after the call. Get ready for realizations and you'll want to take notes. In order to receive the number on time you must register in advance. If you have NOT received the call-in number by 3PM EST the day of the class email moxieinthecity@aol.com and you will be sent the contact info and pin number....&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254609929000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>moxiebizsocial</urlname><id>504315</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Social/Singles Networking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249921885000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Start Your Own Small Business Teleclass</name><id>11077429</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252454400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/moxiebizsocial/events/11077429/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/e/global_5337214.jpeg</photo_url></item>