<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 North St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.281070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Medical School</name><city>Worcester</city><id>688100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.805450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Worcester Photography Meetup Member,

Our group has been asked by Ted Settanny, an organizer, to please help photograph the UMass Cancer Walk on Sept 28th. It appears they are expecting over 14,000. people and need our help. You do not have to be a professional photographer, just someone with a camera, some time that day, and a way to burn images to a cd (they'll give us the cd's!) for them. There are some benfits for you too! Please read the note below I got from Ted, I'll be asking you all to lend a hand that day. It will be made an official meeting on our Sept Calendar and I will ask that you RSVP when you volunteer. I'd love for the group to be able to send about 10-15 photographers if possible. The images will be used for their annual slide show and for publicity.

If you have any questions please let me know via email and I'll get back to you!

Cheers,
Donna

Hi Donna,

I am Ted from UMass Medical School- Walk to Cure Cancer.  This 
year is our 10th year and we are expecting a huge turn out, in 
both media coverage and participation.  There will be more than 
14000 people at this event and Michael Damian will be 
performing after the walk. 
  
In addition to our two UMass photographers, we are hoping to include 
photographers from your center to donate their time to our 
event.  The walk has grown considerably over the years and 
requires more photograhers than in previous years.  Time and 
service would be considered gift in kind.  


The scope of photography is comprised of four major areas:

The stage program:  Wehave public speakers (that starts at 11am) and Michael Damian will beperforming.  We would like for a photographer to focus on all stageprograms.  
Water Stops:  The walkroute is five miles (with an option of the shorter one mile route). There is a water stop every mile.  We would like a photographer atevery water stop.  I attached a map of the walk route.  
Group photos:  We need aphotographer to concentrate on team photographs in front of the Lazare Research Building. 
Random shots:  We needphotos of the event as a whole.  Groups of people, individual people,people interacting, etc.   
 
We will provide all photographers with:
A staff Walk to Cure Cancer Teeshirt 
A disc to download photographs 
 
The event date is September 28th and 10am-2pm would be the times we would need photographers.  

Michael Damian performs: 10:45-11am

Public Speakers:  11:00-12:00pm

Walk:  12:00-3:00pm

We have a kick-off breakfast on July 24th where you can learn more about our event and cancer research.  You and anyone else interested is welcome to attend.  I attached the invitation.  

If you have any other questions or concerns, please dont hesitate to contact me.  Thank you for your help!

Sincerely,  
Ted J. Settanny, 

Thank you for supporting the Walk to Cure Cancer. UMass Memorial Foundation
333 South Street 
Shrewsbury, MA 01545
Phone: 508-856-2587
Fax: 508-856-5565 
2008 Walk - Sunday September 28th. 
www.walktocurecancer.com</description><how_to_find_us>We will pick a place to meet along North Road and post it when I can?</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222902154000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213907116000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot - Photographing the UMass Cancer Walk</name><id>8174680</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222610400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/8174680/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/c/global_4509964.jpeg</photo_url></item>