<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The folks at Lincoln Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak have invited us to visit their composite kayak and canoe manufacturing shop located behind their retail shop located just off of Rt. 1 Freeport Maine. We'll get the opportunity to see how the composite canoes and kayaks are made and the various stages of the process. We may also have a chance to see a repair of a kayak and be able to ask questions about the process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marc Bourgoin the new owner of LCK will also be keeping the store open for us after their normal hours for a social gathering of NE Seacoast Paddlers members after our tour of the manufacturing facility. There will be gear on sale and we'll be able to take advantage of a 10% discount on products in the retail store. This is a great opportunity to see how composite kayaks are made as well as do a little Christmas shopping for your kayak family and friends. Feel free to invite your Spouses and SO's along as they can always shop in Freeport while you are touring the LCK facility.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Itinerary:&lt;/b&gt; 4pm arrival, introductions, tour the manufacturing facility and a walk through on how boats are built and a demonstration on repairs. Wrap up around 5/5:30 then gather in the showroom for drinks and snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.paddlelincoln.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lincoln Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We may organize a paddle in the area earlier in the day weather depending.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259615873000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257878187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tour of Kayak Manufacturing Shop at Lincoln Canoe &amp; Kayak Freeport Maine </name><id>11842858</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259442000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/11842858/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/e/global_11752206.jpeg</photo_url></item>