<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Pier Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04046</zip><lat>43.367683</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Cape Porpoise Harbor</name><city>Cape Porpoise</city><id>1017436</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.432060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/5/event_15723301.jpeg" width="333" height="232" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &amp;nbsp;A perennial Seacoast Outdoors favorite, the Cape Porpoise Harbor islands are a paddler's paradise located just north of Kennebunkport, Maine - about 45 minutes north of Portsmouth. This will be our fourth trip and I can't wait to see it again!&amp;nbsp; More complete description below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;RSVPs&lt;/strong&gt;: I'm limiting the size of the group due to the tiny parking area. 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please&amp;nbsp;RSVP only&amp;nbsp;if you're sure you're coming&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Safety/Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;: PFDs required and sea/coastal kayaks with spray skirts are recommended on this trip. We may venture out on the seaward sides of some of the islands if the ocean looks fairly calm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: IT LOOKS LIKE CARPOOLERS ARE MEETING ON THEIR OWN AT DIFFERENT PLACES.&amp;nbsp; DON'T GO TO THE BUS STATION UNLESS YOU'VE MADE ARRANGEMENTS TO MEET SOMEONE THERE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Arrive by&amp;nbsp;9:30 am&lt;/span&gt; @ Portsmouth Bus Station. You&amp;rsquo;ll need time to switch boats from one car to another.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Go to the back of the farthest lot away from the main terminal&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depart promptly at 9:45 am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Please Carpool&lt;/em&gt;. There is very limited parking at the launch.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Launch Site - 10:30am&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt; : Just before the town docks, on the left side of Pier Road, Cape Porpoise, Maine.&amp;nbsp; No kayak parking allowed at the docks but there are restrooms there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Food&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Bring a snack but we'll&amp;nbsp;eat and drink&amp;nbsp;afterwards at Federal Jack&amp;rsquo;s in Kennebunkport.&amp;nbsp; This is a very friendly place that's always welcoming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Fees&lt;/strong&gt;: Help your driver with carpool gas and buy your organizer a drink!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Closest Boat Rentals:&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.coastalmainekayak.com/"&gt;Coastal Maine Kayak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or rent from 
&lt;a&gt;EMS in Portsmouth&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Be sure to specify a SEA kayak.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High tide is @&amp;nbsp;12:50 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy a day of paddling in one of the remaining working harbors along the Maine coast with one of the few remaining manned lighthouses left in Maine. Waterfowl and marine mammals are abundant and the water is generally very calm. This is a fine place for beginners. The Cape Porpoise harbor islands are a paddler's paradise. Immediately you'll notice that the water is crystal clear. It is a deep blue-green but still transparent at 20-foot depths. Seals are everywhere. Beautiful granite rocks line the rugged shore of Trott Island. Seaweed 6 feet long lifts and sways in the mild swell under you. Herding minnows sparkle as they jump out of the water around you. There is little boat traffic here for the simple reason there's no public ramp for amateur fishermen to put in their boats. This is a working commercial lobster-boat harbor. However, we may encounter George HW Bush's speedboat. He flies around&amp;nbsp;with Secret Service boats stuggling to keep up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a description I found: I can't emphasize enough how beautiful this little archipelago is, and how wild. Seals can be found on the east side of Trott Island, and definitely on the rough east side of Cape Island if you want to risk open ocean. Fort and Stage are other islands to explore to the northeast. No island is more than a half mile distant from the next, so you can see how the area fits into most paddlers' idea of a fine half-day exploration. This trip is tide dependent due to extensive mud flats at low tide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://www.getthenack.org/resources/Noyes-CapePorpoiseMaine%20080611.pdf"&gt;More description here.&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&lt;/strong&gt; hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs,&amp;nbsp;and all members&amp;nbsp;and participants&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group&amp;nbsp;from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage&amp;nbsp;including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience&amp;nbsp;and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgement.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;As organizer I make no claims regarding any expertise for this outing as&amp;nbsp;I have no special training.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;As a participant, you agree to stay with the group or inform the organizer directly if you plan to leave early or to go off on your own.&amp;nbsp; -Larry Pilla&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309716584000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309196297000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Porpoise Paddle 4.1</name><id>23691291</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309617000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/23691291/</event_url></item>