<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fottler Avenue and Minuteman Commuter Bikeway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02420</zip><lat>42.427631</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Arlington Great Meadows</name><city>Lexington</city><id>1638346</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.198509</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Rain is predicted for Sunday the 15th.&amp;nbsp; I'll still have the workshop  if it is occasional or light rain (or no rain).&amp;nbsp; If heavy rain, then the  workshop is postponed to the next week- Sunday, May 22, same time and  place.&amp;nbsp; Call 617-492-2340 to check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: $10 - 20 sliding scale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sign up by RSVPing on meetup and please call 617-492-2340&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Japanese knotweed, phragmites, and garlic mustard have parts that are edible this time of year and can be used raw in recipes. In this workshop, you'll learn how to identify these plants, which parts are edible, how to harvest them, and how to use them in meals.&amp;nbsp; Recipes will be provided.&amp;nbsp; We'll also be able to harvest some and take them home, so you can have sensory experiences of how they look, feel, and smell, and direct&amp;nbsp; hands-on experience of harvesting, preparing, and eating them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jules, the instructor, plans to have a series of foraging workshops focusing on one or a  few plants at a time so participants can feel more confident of finding  and using the plants on their own. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please bring- waterproof boots, small knife or cutting instrument, bag or other container for harvest. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you want to taste these plants in the field, bring a gallon of potable water so you can rinse them off.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jules Kobek is the co-founder of DIO (Do-It-Ourselves) Skillshare, facilitating workshops on skills of urban sustainability, such as sprouting, growing vegetables, and constructing raised garden beds. She also leads nature walks to identify edible weeds. After gathering urban wild food for several years, Jules has expanded her foraging to woodlands and marshes. She is studying ethnobotany- the study of the relationship between plants and people in different cultures- and is also learning wilderness survival skills.&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>HJ</member_name><member_id>13327790</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305491081000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Rain is predicted for Sunday the 15th.  Workshop is on if it is occasional or light rain (or no rain).  If heavy rain, then the workshop is postponed to the next week- Sunday, May 22, same time and place.  Call 617-492-2340 to check.

Jules</why><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303318827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harvest Invasive Plants- Food, Antioxidants, Treatment for Lyme's Disease</name><id>17373453</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305486000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/17373453/</event_url></item>