<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us for the &lt;strong&gt;Portland Trading Post&lt;/strong&gt; monthly swap event, inspired by our friends in &lt;a href="http://www.somervilletradingpost.org/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Somerville &lt;/a&gt; - and the success of our recent plant and preserved food swaps!  Trading Post events are&lt;strong&gt; free and open to all&lt;/strong&gt;.  Space may be limited in our first few sessions while we work out the kinks, &lt;em&gt;so please take your RSVP seriously&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plants, seedlings, seeds, preserved or fresh produce, hand-made items, etc. are all welcome at Portland Trading Post.  The main idea is that we are stepping outside of the cash economy and mutually "gifting" things to each other in a way that turns whatever we have in abundance into a diversity of goodness and good will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #c76924"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special for April:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;This month will be a special focus on plants (seedlings, divisions or other propagated friends) and seeds. &amp;nbsp;All other stuff welcome as well but last year's plant swap was so successful that this is the repeat to that event. &amp;nbsp;Please use the comments area below to talk about what you might bring or what you're looking for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The only rules are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No cash changes hands (like anyone has any, anyway.) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't start the swapping until everyone's there and has a chance to look around at what's on offer. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can swap with someone or simply "gift" things to each other without taking a return item. Your choice. The IRS doesn't care about gifts, right? :) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure you've found a home for all your stuff before you leave (or take home what hasn't been gifted). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you bring a food item with multiple ingredients, pls label.
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to talk about what you might be bringing or seeking.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potluck/Food/Snacks/Fiddles/Juggling optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aaron Parker</member_name><member_id>6845673</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302526614000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Trading plants, seedlings and seeds is a fun and affordable way to grow your garden!</why><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289864841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special APRIL Portland Trading Post :: Plant Swap!</name><id>lccwpypgbnb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302460200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/16149428/</event_url></item>