<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305008</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Elm City Market</name><city>New Haven</city><id>4214392</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922737</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Many of us have been Looking forward to the day when this new Grocery Co-Op will open in Downtown New Haven.&amp;nbsp; Wednesday Afternoon, they are finally cutting the ribbon on Elm City Market!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ribbon Cutting ceremony will take place starting at 4:30 pm, and will be followed by a First Night Celebration from 5 pm to 7 pm.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;If you Can't make it for 4:30, don't worry just come check it out after!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone can enter the market following the Ribbon Cutting where there will be local live music and samples around the store.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members of the Co-Op are also invited to start shopping a day early, before the ceremony.&amp;nbsp; The Store will open for sales to the whole public Starting on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A.J. will be running over to catch this event after work and mingle for the first little while (at least) of the party.&amp;nbsp; You can attempt to reach him at 315-345-9348.&amp;nbsp; If it's during the ceremony then texting may be better than calling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there is significant interest we can grab a drink or munchies at a near by location after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Parking you can look for street meetered parking, or the 360 Garage will be open for Credit/Debit Card customers only.&amp;nbsp; If you shop at Elm City Market, you can bring your ticket and get it validated for one hour of parking, and a special rate after that.&amp;nbsp; (When validated $1 for additional 30 minutes, $2 for an additional hour.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that need more location guidance:&amp;nbsp; Elm City Market is located in the bottom floor of the 360 State Street Building, located at the corner of Chapel Street and State Street in Downtown New Haven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're a "Maybe" for this event, just put that in your RSVP comment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>AJ will be there mingling.  If you need to reach him 315-345-9348, Texting might be better considering the event nature but you can call.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320709195000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320025932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Elm City Market Ribbon Cutting / First Night Celebration</name><id>39308772</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320265800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/39308772/</event_url></item>