<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>See site below for details The Massachusetts Pirate Party will be hosting our first conference - Politics: share, remix, reboot. It will be all day on March 10th at the Democracy Center in Cambridge. More details and registration at: &lt;a href="http://www.masspirates.org/blog/conference/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.masspirate...&lt;/a&gt; So far we have the following talks: David House, a researcher at MIT who helped set up the Bradley Manning Support Network, will be giving a talk entitled: Going toe-to-toe with the state: navigating the challenges of a digital activist. Shauna Gordon-McKeon, organizer for the Boston Sunlight Foundation, will talk about some of the programming projects transparency activists are using to open up government data. Writer and publisher Cecilia Tan, and Shane Bugbee will be on the Tales from the Net: Making a living at being creative panel. Michael Anderson will give a talk called Fight Ridiculous With Ridiculous: The Guerrilla Tactics of Fair Use. Also, Conor Sherman will give a talk called Stranger Danger: Don&amp;#146;t Click that Link Even If They Offer Puppies and Candy. Finally, we will have a number of talks by Pirate Party members, including: Exploring Kopimism by Lauren Pespisa Patents Upending by Erik Zoltan Fair Use for Activists by Chris Walsh How to Run for Office by James O&amp;#146;Keefe We will also have time for open discussion of where the Pirate Party should go and what issues we should focus on. We will be showing open or public domain films in the evening. We hope you can join us on March 10th.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331436082000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329514631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3/10 Massachusetts Pirate Partys first conference</name><id>52753042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331431200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/52753042/</event_url></item>