<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Off Totten Pond Rd</address_2><address_1>54 4th Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.393665</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-290-0026</phone><name>Summerfield Suites Hyatt Hotel</name><city>Waltham</city><id>669399</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.259857</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us at Margaritas in Waltham for a night of FREE social and business networking on Tuesday July 27th at 6:00pm. There will be FREE appetizers provided, a raffle for Margaritas gift cards, and much much more! (Not to mention the famous Margaritas!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will have the opportunity to network with business professionals from around the Greater Boston area. Establish relationships to help fuel your business, achieve your goals, and share motivational techniques, all in a casual, laid-back, no-pressure setting! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you been trying to find new ways to meet people? Are you someone who is goal oriented, or looking to surround yourself with like-minded professionals? Perhaps you are in between jobs, or have a passion or hobby that you are trying to develop into a business? Either way, THIS is the event to attend!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your free admission grants you access into a society of self-proclaimed 'Success Addicts' who focus on driving results, pooling resources, and giving/receiving referrals, all to drive action. Our group has helped people start new businesses, establish fruitful relationships with complimentary professionals, and motivate its members to achieve greatness! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Networking, and Success in general, is contagious. SPREAD THE WORD - SHARE YOUR ADDICTION!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*FREE PARKING* is available behind Margarita's - Accesible from PINE ST. around the corner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP and bring your friends! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there! &lt;br /&gt;Wishing you Success, the Best, and Nothing Less! :o) &lt;br /&gt;Dimitry Neyshtadt &lt;br /&gt;617-680-7431 &lt;br /&gt;DNeyshtadt@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dimitry</member_name><member_id>10566344</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284047377000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Success Addicts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>successfulanonymous</urlname><id>1551084</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Successful Anonymous</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278733669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Successful Anonymous Networking at Margaritas</name><id>14057426</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280268000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/successfulanonymous/events/14057426/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/3/global_13312019.jpeg</photo_url></item>