<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Colby Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.405510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Outside the Lines</name><city>Medford</city><id>2549401</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114464</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;FREE open for public fun from 2PM to 10PM. Over 300 people expected and this fills up quickly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many other meetup groups are participating. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside the Lines Artist Web site: &lt;a href="http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theart" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/theart&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participating Non Outside the Lines Artist are donating 20% of their proceeds from any Art sales to Outside the Lines Studios a Non Profit since they are letting us use their space. We are hoping to start a good joint venture with Outside the Lines Studios so we could do this every 3 months or so. We plan on putting out like a donation jar / box too to collect money for Outside the Lines Studios as well. More info on Outside the Lines Studios: &amp;bull; 10,000 Sq Feet Art warehouse at 70 Colby Street Medford MA, with 2 parking lots for 80 cars. &amp;bull; There is a small outside area that we can use too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Their website is &lt;a href="http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.outsidethelinesstudio.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; It is on the edge of the Tuffs Campus in Medford. A 12 -14 minutes walk from Davis SQ, but still close to RT 93.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; A charity that help adults with learning disabilities to experience and create Art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Expect to see 10 to 15 special needs adult to show up to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; If it&amp;rsquo;s a nice day we can open up the large garage door and let fresh air and light in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Next door is an open ball field so we can plan outdoor games here too, like kick ball and volleyball. I am looking for a few Social fun or other Members or fellow Organizers to help fun games both inside and out like Kick ball and volley ball. I have all the sport equipment. I just need people in charge for the outdoor games and for the indoor games. Think of what a fun filled packed day this will be. I wanted to remind all Members to bring coolers full of drinks, ice and snack so all can enjoy too. Thanks and Ciao Biagio ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ Directions: From the MBTA Davis Square T Stop: Turn right out of the station and walk up College Avenue. When you arrive at Powderhouse Square, continue straight across the Square (use the sidewalks to avoid getting struck by traffic!!) onto Warner St., Warner St. becomes Harvard St. at Boston Ave. Continue on Harvard, psassing under the railroad bridge. Colby St. is the next street on your left, just after the Tufts University Science Building. Continue on Colby St, take a quick left and a quick right (this is still Colby St.) and walk to the very end to the big parking lot and you're here. From the North: Take 93 South to Exit 31 (Mystic Valley Parkway/RT.16-E) toward Revere. Turn Right at the Mystic Valley Parkway and continue on this road which becomes Harvard St. Continue on Harvard St. Take a right onto Main St. and take your 2nd left onto Bowdoin St. (just before the little market on your right) Go to the end of Bowdoin and turn righton to Colby St. Got to the end arriving at the big parking lot andyou're here. From the South: Take 93 North to Exit 31 (Mystic Valley Parkway/RT.16-E) Take the exit and keep to the right. You'll come to the intersection of RT. 16 and Main St.(RT.38) Take a left on to Main St. and keep to the right to continue on Main St. Continue on Main St. for about a 1/2 mile and take a right on to Bowdoin St. (just after the little market on the left) Go to the end of Bowdoin and turn right on to Colby St. Got to the end arriving at the big parking lot and you're here.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lelia</member_name><member_id>4161738</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313898103000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312943605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art, Music and Games event at Outside the Lines Studios a Non Profit in Medford</name><id>28929411</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313863200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/28929411/</event_url></item>