<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;Sat, Oct 17 @ midnite!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally I'll be able to make it to this.  Entire description lifted from John's post last month ....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;The Room&lt;/b&gt; is the Citizen Kane of bad movies.'' - Ross Morin, assistant professor of film studies at St. Cloud State University in Minnesota.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the past five years, a Los Angeles billboard has perpetually and ominously promoted a film simply titled: &lt;b&gt;THE ROOM&lt;/b&gt;. Those who could no longer stand the suspense and actually sought out screenings of this film have been exposed to what some people are saying is the greatest midnite movie since THE ROCKY HORROR PICTURE SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Midnite crowds have flocked to attend this show due to it's &amp;quot;so amazingly bad it's 'effing great&amp;quot; charms. In recent years, some of Hollywood's most talented have counted themselves being in the cult of THE ROOM. Paul Rudd, David Cross and Jonah Hill catch the film whenever they can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE ROOM&lt;/b&gt;'s director, producer and leading man is the mysterious Tommy Wiseau. In the film, Tommy portrays &amp;quot;Johnny&amp;quot;, a man who becomes involved in a love triangle when the woman he loves begins sleeping with another man. Johnny is also the mentor of a drug dealing man child, a dog aficionado and possesses an alarmingly unnerving giggle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kept as a L.A. secret for half of a decade, THE ROOM has now found its way to the east coast and we here at the Coolidge are proud to present it in all its baffling glory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But don't just take our word for it, check out what EW and The Onion have to say about the strange new phenomenon of THE ROOM: At a midnight screening in a Los Angeles multiplex, the atmosphere hovers somewhere between rambunctious and mildly terrifying. Whenever a framed photograph of a spoon appears on screen, which it frequently does, audience members throw fistfuls of plastic cutlery. They also perform skits, at one point gathering at the bottom right of the screen and shouting, ''Down here, Tommy!'' anticipating the moment when the face of the lead actor, Tommy Wiseau, looks in their direction. And they comment loudly on blurrily shot scenes (''Focus!'') or inadequately introduced characters (''Who the f--- are you?''). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I strongly suggest you get your tickets ahead of time (&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/?q=showtimes)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;.  This film regularly sells out in advance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dave &amp; John will be sitting outside of the Coolidge at 11:30 PM</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254869455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Room </name><id>11566230</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255837500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11566230/</event_url></item>