<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Boston Harbor Islands&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet onboard the 10:30 ferry to Spectacle Island. The boat will cost $12 and leaves at 10:30 sharp, so get there early to find the ticket office and the wharf. We will arrive at Spectacle Island 10 minutes later, spend an hour there, then catch the 11:45 ferry to Georges Island.  We will catch the 1:30 ferry back to Boston arriving 1:55. Facilities are limited on Georges, so bring water and pack a lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harbor Express and Harbor Islands Express vessels depart from the north side of Long Wharf, adjacent the Marriott hotel and the Christopher Columbus Park. From the New England Aquarium, walk throught the lobby of the Marriott hotel and out the other side where you will see the ticket booth on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonislands.org/isle_profiles.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonisla...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aslo, I just found out that there is a kite festival on Georges Island when you'll be there. If you have a kite, bring it along! You can buy a 2 string kite at the festival called the Be-Bop for $30. I have one and its a blast to fly it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonislands.com/events_search.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonisla...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Georges Island  &lt;br /&gt;Date:&lt;br /&gt;7/28/2007 - 7/29/2007 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day of Week:&lt;br /&gt;Sat, Sun  Time:&lt;br /&gt;  11:00AM  - 3:00PM&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;Expert Kite Fliers will be on-hand to present flying demonstrations and give impromptu instruction. National Park Service &amp;amp; Department of Conservation and Recreation Park Rangers will be on-hand to supply visitors with kite-making materials, and provide kite-making instruction.  &lt;br /&gt;Offered by:&lt;br /&gt;Island Alliance &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With generous support from:&lt;br /&gt;Department of Conservation and Recreation &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Program Fee:&lt;br /&gt;  Free &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Georges Island &lt;br /&gt;At the time of Euro-American colonization, Georges Island was comprised of two drumlins, rising out of the bay like other nearby islands. The island was used for agricultural for two hundred years until 1825 when the U.S. Government acquired the island for coastal defense.&lt;br /&gt;Over the next twenty years the island was dramatically altered and one of the country's finest forts was built. Dedicated in 1847, Fort Warren's defensive design was virtually obsolete upon completion. However the fort served as a training ground, patrol point, and Civil War prison that gained a favorable reputation for the humane treatment of its Confederate prisoners. After one hundred years of military use the fort was decommissioned in 1947 and acquired by the Metropolitan District Commission for historic preservation and recreation in 1958.&lt;br /&gt;To this day, within the fort's dark corridors, the legend lives on of &amp;quot;The Lady in Black,&amp;quot; the ghost of a Confederate prisoner's wife who is said to have been sentenced to death for aiding in an escape and hanged in a black robe made from the Fort's mess hall drapes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spectacle Island&lt;br /&gt;Spectacle Island (105 acres) features a marina, visitor center, cafe, two sandy beaches, and five miles of walking trails that lead to the crest of a 157 foot-high hill, offering panoramic views of the harbor and the city. Supervised swimming is offered daily.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185891545000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183397200000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harbor Islands</name><id>5964709</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185718500000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5964709/</event_url></item>