<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Edgewater drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03106</zip><lat>43.105765</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgewater Canoe &amp; Kayak</name><city>Hooksett</city><id>991054</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467022</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mother's Day Kayak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday May 12th. 11:30 am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edgewater kayak 35 Edgewater Dr. Hooksett, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Cindy 107: 603-315-0275 Co-host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net     Lets get on the water !   RAIN will cancel this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A Dog &amp;amp; Child Friendly Event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like to kayak or always wanted to try ? Then join me , and bring your Moms, friends and yourself, to Edgwater kayak. They rent boats for $5/hr. We will pay for 3 hours and take &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/3/4/event_222795412.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;ourselves up the Merrimack river to memorial field to stop and have lunch. Pack it in a small waterproof bag as it has to fit in the boat with you. Also bring water and sunscreen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are both single and double up kayaks, from 10' to 14'. All come with paddles and life vest. PLEASE WEAR YOUR VEST ON THIS TRIP. I will give a paddle lesson to those that need it. Please ask me before getting in the kayak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When arriving, please park with your car facing onto the grass and to the water to make room for everyone. We will pay Rob the owner. Then get setup in a boats. If you want to bring your own boat there is a small parking fee of $5. Renters are free. There is a small store near the edgwater drive ( Robies, at the lights) if you need water or lunch to bring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be keeping track of &lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : x-large"&gt;YES RSVP"S&lt;/span&gt; and let them know how many are coming. Please plan to arrive on time so we can set you up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions..Cindy 603-315-0275 or Steve Ob1 603-491-1962&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rob owner of Edgewater  Canoe and Kayak 603-540-6520&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;** You will be responsible for yourself at this event. Please wear your vest and come prepared.That way we all have fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liability Release - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the dirt boat ramp</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cindy 107</member_name><member_id>5375585</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368391951000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365415371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mothers Day Paddle</name><id>113252802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368372600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/113252802/</event_url></item>