<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>959 Hope Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.853153</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cook and Brown Public House Ltd</name><city>Providence</city><id>4506872</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.392853</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and event scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Cook and Brown on Hope street, near Lippitt Park on the East Side!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MARK YOU CALENDARS NOW, FOLKS!!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is really exciting!!! &lt;strong&gt;Cook and Brown is usually closed on Monday nights and are opening just for us!&lt;/strong&gt; This is big!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cook and Brown is a nice, relaxed gastrobar with an air of welcoming sophistication and a comfortable bar space. It also has AMAZING food and INCREDIBLE cocktails!!! You may have already heard of them or not, and if you've been, you already know. offering an array of dining options from weekend brunches (yes, they do that, and it's awesome!), fine dinner dining, to Sunday Suppers, THIS is one to know about!!! Once you go, you &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; be back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since they are opening especially for us, there will be special cocktail creations based on P-Collective beverages of choice and an appetizer menu to give you a taste of their regular delectable and tasty menu!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please be sure to RSVP so our numbers are accurate for the event!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm super-excited and I hope you are too! So, let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cookandbrown.com/index.php"&gt;http://cookandbrown.com/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a friend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the brown and pink scarf in my picture, but we're hard to miss and very friendly!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1350522553000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348705121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Cook and Brown!!!! Please RSVP!!!</name><id>84267392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350338400000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/84267392/</event_url></item>