<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>439 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.346640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 338-8884</phone><name>Masa </name><city>Boston</city><id>668968</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069084</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi, everyone!  I've picked &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Masa&lt;/span&gt; at &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;439 Tremont in the South End&lt;/span&gt; for brunch this &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Sunday, at 12:30 pm&lt;/span&gt;, 617-338-8884.  I've had drinks there before and I liked the atmosphere, so I decided to try their Sunday brunch.  It's mainly a Mexican/Spanish menu, but I'm sure they can make simple eggs and bacon for you, too.  Here's the link to the menu, which is quite reasonably priced: &lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.masarestaurant.com/boston/menus/masa_menu_brunch.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.masarestau...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the link to the restaurant: &lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.masarestaurant.com/boston/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.masarestau...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; .  You can find driving directions there and T directions.  It's 439 Tremont, between Arlington and Berkeley Streets.  You can take the Orange line to the Back Bay stop, or the Green line to Arlington.  It's a short walk from either stop.   If you insist on driving, you can look for street parking, but the restaurant does offer valet parking for $16, or the closest garage is the one next to the Back Bay T station.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll email my cell phone number to those who RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;.  See you Sunday at 12:30! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RULES of Engagement for Brunch added by Tonya&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together. Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must contact Annette directly by calling or texting her cell. She will email her cell to all who RSVP Yes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the entrance or at the bar.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225035582000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224035863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Masa - Sunday Brunch - South End</name><id>8964046</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224433800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/8964046/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/2/global_5879858.jpeg</photo_url></item>