<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When: &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 14, 2007, 1:30 PM 20070714T173000Z &lt;br /&gt;Where: &lt;br /&gt;See Description Below&lt;br /&gt;1 &lt;br /&gt;New Hartford , CT 06057&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info/Map &lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;This Event replaces the Kayak even i had planned.. &lt;br /&gt;and is a week earlier than one that was origionally planned.. &lt;br /&gt;So why not make it a combined effort for a few meetup groups...????? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OH CHECK OUT STEVES HIKE FOR HIKE INFO..&lt;br /&gt;I might not do the hike..&lt;br /&gt;but just the water thing...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will still have us meet by my car...Yes i will put an orange cone on the roof /hood or trunk , whichever is facing out... &lt;br /&gt;then we can find the other group or find them on the water..we will figure it out...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;anyway here is the details: &lt;br /&gt;Where: &lt;br /&gt;Satan's Kingdom &lt;br /&gt;Route 44 ( Main Street New Hartford CT) &lt;br /&gt;New Hartford , CT 06057&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info/Map &lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;What's thrilling and relaxing and totally cool? Tubing on the Farmington River. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Satan's Kingdom State Recreation Area, located on Route 44 in New Hartford, CT. Free parking, changing houses, restrooms and shuttle service back to the starting point are available. When you're ready to go, wait in line to sign waiver papers and rent your tube and life jacket. $20 cash.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.5 mile tubing run is more calm than wild, but you will encounter 3 sets of rapids. It isn't for everyone...you must know how to swim. The 2nd set of rapids can toss you off your tube. Depending on the weather conditions, if the water is high, the current can be strong in places. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, go into their website www.farmingtonrivertubing.com. It will give you more info and tips on what to wear. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it rains we will reschedule for the week or some other day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda says: &lt;br /&gt;I would love to be there, but I don't swim. Al will take the reigns (pun). He loves the water!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a group discount rate of $14 pp if more than 10 people sign up. So RSVP early and i will see if i met the rules for the time ?? with firm plans. Al will be in charge of making the reservations for the group. Maybe Al will announce this to his group as well so we will have more people. If this date isn't good, Al will change it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And i see Steve posted it a week earlyier than the one Linda posted so why not make the change ???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;From Hartford... &lt;br /&gt;Head toward Avon/Canton via rte 44... &lt;br /&gt;Right after canton, rte 44 and 202 split, take rte 44 split to the north for about 2.5 miles, look for the Satins Kingdom on the right. &lt;br /&gt;Pull on in and look for the cones on the car..oh its a blue Toyota Avalon..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Map quest, GPS and others, use 112 Main Street (rte 44) new hartford, ct to get you close enough...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I anticipate Steves group will arrive about 1:30 &lt;br /&gt;so thats a good time for us too..maybe eat some snacks there first.. &lt;br /&gt;Ok got to go now... &lt;br /&gt;al-r &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184607126000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183951875000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tubing the Farmington River, Cross posted with Kayak and Steves Hike Group..</name><id>5994296</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184434200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5994296/</event_url></item>