<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce continues to teach us about relationships.   The focus this week will be on those relationships that are unique and complicated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description from Herb: &lt;br /&gt;“Are you or have you ever been in a complicated relationship? Former lover, friends now.&lt;br /&gt;Former friend, now lovers? Lovers every so often? Some kind of 3 or 4 way relationships?&lt;br /&gt;On again, off again. Friends with benefits? Secret or private relationship? Open relationship?&lt;br /&gt;Not sure how to define it? Limited physical connection? Intimate relationship but  no physical relationship? In constant pursuit, but no real relationship? Once a week relationship?  Long distance relationship? Remeeting after 10 or 20 years? This is an evening to explore options, share your experience with confidentiality, and look at creative ways to make your experience more satisfying or at least more defined!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it. Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit has been set.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** About Herb Pearce *****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce is a relationship coach of 30 years for couples, singles and families. His specialty is working with personality differences and ways to bridge differences and enhance relationships.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256870065000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243484076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Examining Unique and Complicated Relationships with Herb Pearce</name><id>10511295</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249081200000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/10511295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/2/4/global_7019412.jpeg</photo_url></item>