<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>409 The Hill</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.078239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.427.2583</phone><name>Blue Mermaid</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>812382</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.759410</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first installment in our Common Sense Tuesdays series. Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come to hear this interactive presentation and be part of the discussion for common sense. The full menu at the Blue Mermaid is available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaker: Todd Puterbaugh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Classical Liberalism, Modern Progressivism and the Occupy Wall Street Movement&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd will contrast classical liberalism with modern progressivism. The former is the philosophy most closely associated with Presidential candidate Ron Paul, while the latter is associated with President Obama. This distinction is important during an era that has seen the rise of the Occupy Wall Street Movement and other rapidly evolving socio-political undercurrents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bio:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd Puterbaugh has undergraduate and graduate degrees in physics, mathematics, and engineering. Todd has been a college instructor, a research scientist, and is currently working as a software engineer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd believes that personal freedom, liberty, and responsibility allow for the happiest and most prosperous society. He also believes that community-based organizations and associations that are free from coercive force are also keys to achieving a prosperous society. Todd has supported or currently works with several organizations whose goals are improving the community through coercion-free peaceful direct action or educational outreach. These organizations include the Church Of The Brethren, the Miami Valley (OH) Adult Literacy Council, YMCA Adventure Guides, Concord Liberty Book Club, NH Seacoast Liberty, the NH Liberty Alliance, and Seacoast Common Sense Community Builders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337737701000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336405757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Common Sense Tuesdays Speaker Series</name><id>63772342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337725800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/63772342/</event_url></item>