<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt Auburn St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10532532</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I received the following information and looking forward to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The show is March 1 at the Democracy Center in Harvard Square. The show starts at 7:30 p.m. It will last about 1 hour and 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the information on the performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The award-winning, musically-driven improv comedy troupe Rebels Without Applauze brings its wacky improv games and on-the-spot singing to the Democracy Center. We'll take your suggestions and make you laugh. We will also play our Apples to Apples Improv Game in which you, the audience, help us create unforgettable characters in ridiculous situations. &lt;br /&gt;

 Tickets are $5 and can be purchased at the door. &lt;br /&gt;

 Giovanni is part of Rebels Without Applauze and is hosting the event and performing in the show. Meet him at the ticket table and then get a seat. After the show, feel free to join the improv troupe for a bite and/or drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also find the announcement on another meet up here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/freethingsinboston/events/104387892/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/freethingsinboston/events/104387892/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giovanni posted directions from Harvard Square on the above site:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right in Harvard Square. It is just a five minute walk. It is right next door to Daedulus, the restaurant. If you walk to corner of JFK and Mt. Auburn (Tasty Burger is right there) from the T station, take a left and follow Mt. Auburn St a few hundred yards to Daedulus and you will see Democracy Center next door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a meetup button/will give out Cell Phone # the night before.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kirk, "Rear Admiral"</member_name><member_id>4863083</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362245348000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361218136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Improv 3/1 in Harvard Square</name><id>105207232</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362183300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/105207232/</event_url></item>