<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wherever you are on New Years Eve, when you go to bed, set an intention to dream a special dream. Ask your dreams for guidance in your life or make a New Years wish for the coming year. Write it down on a piece of paper and put it under your pillow. Write down any dreams or dream fragments you remember in the morning. If you don't get any response the first night, try it again the next night and the next, until you get something. We can talk about the results at our next Meetup and on the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Dreaming in the New Year&amp;quot; event is not a Meetup event in the usual sense. It is actually a time related ritual exercise which anyone can do anywhere. New Years Eve is a traditional time for transition, transformation, and renewal. It is also a great time for setting a dream intention. Here's an exercise you can do at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This exercise takes place at the first sleep of the new year on January 1, when you go to bed, set an intention to dream a special dream. Ask your dreams for guidance or make a New Years manifestational wish or affirmation for the coming year. Create one which is particularly relevant to you personally. Write it down on a piece of paper and put it under your pillow. This will prime the dream pump. Go to sleep.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Examples of guidance questions: &amp;quot;What is my next step in life?&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;What should I make as my primary focus for this new year?&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Should I take that office job in Boston?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Examples of manifestational wishes or affirmations: &amp;quot;I am having health and happiness in this new year.&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I have plenty of money in 2009.&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I am finding and enjoying a perfect mate in 2009.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you wake up, write down any dreams or dream fragments you remember. If you wake up in the night write down any images that occur to you, repeat your dream intention, and go back to sleep. If you don't get any response the first night, try it again the next night and the next, until you get something. We can talk about the results at our next Meetup and on the website.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234727808000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229560341000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dreaming in the New Year</name><id>9355112</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230786000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/9355112/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/f/global_6776143.jpeg</photo_url></item>