<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I will be at the theater by 6:45, we should head in for seats by 7, show time is 7:45.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like the movie will be showing upstairs, so I will snag a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If you get there before me, try to grab a table for the group.  I will be coming from another meetup, but should be there in plenty of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In general, since we see movies opening weekend, it is a very good idea to buy tickets ahead of time...especially if it is a big name movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be wearing a meetup badge and there will be a meetup sign on the table.  Check out my picture on the meetup site, so you will recognize me. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, we gather after the movie just outside the room where it was shown to talk about the movie a bit and get a head count of those who would like to come out for drinks, munchies and lively conversation at the Rockbottom Brewery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: October 8, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;Studio: Warner Bros. Pictures &lt;br /&gt;Director: Greg Berlanti &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Ian Deitchman, Kristin Rusk Robinson &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Katherine Heigl, Josh Duhamel, Josh Lucas, Christina Hendricks, Hayes MacArthur &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Comedy, Romance &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG-13 (for sexual material, language and some drug content) &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lifeasweknowitmovie.warnerbros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://lifeasweknowit...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Holly Berenson (Katherine Heigl) is an up-and-coming caterer and Eric Messer (Josh Duhamel) is a promising network sports director. After a disastrous first date, the only thing they have in common is their dislike for each other and their love for their goddaughter, Sophie. But when they suddenly become all Sophie has in the world, Holly and Messer are forced to put their differences aside. Juggling career ambitions and competing social calendars, they'll have to find some common ground while living under one roof. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Meetup Badge. If movie is upstairs, I will snag a table at the top of the escalator, if it is downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825901000</updated><rating><average>3.79999995232</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285342810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Life As We Know It</name><id>14882402</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286664300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/14882402/</event_url></item>