<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>108 Beal Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.242586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bare Cove Park</name><city>Hingham</city><id>1167668</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.912740</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Let's get out of our winter hibernation &amp;amp; enjoy the first weekend of spring with a 2-3 mile walk in the park...bring the kids &amp;amp; your friendly, four-legged leashed friends. (Note: There will be many dogs in the park; some off leash). The road is paved if you have little ones in strollers, or if the kids want to bring their scooters/bikes. There are also paths through the woods if anyone wants to check out those trails.  There are no bathroom facilities at the park!  I will be at the Beal Street entrance (not the Fort Point entrance) off of Route 3A/Lincoln St., enter by Lynch Field across from Stop &amp;amp; Shop. Afterwards, we can go around the corner to the Hingham Shipyard &amp;amp; grab lunch at Wahlburgers, or frozen yogurt at Red Mango.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bare Cove Park&lt;/strong&gt; consists of 484 acres located along the banks of the Weymouth Back River in the town of Hingham, MA. Set aside as a wildlife sanctuary and a place for public recreation, the park is an exceptional area of river shoreline, wetland, open fields, dense woods, and diverse animal and plant life. The many wild animals that inhabit Bare Cove Park include coyote, fox, and deer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to 1906, the land was privately owned. Due to its convenient access by water to Boston Harbor, the site was acquired by the U.S. Navy and used as an ammunition depot until 1971. In 1972, the Government declared the depot surplus and divided it up for several uses, including Bare Cove Park.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the parking lot by the gate/Beal Street entrance by Lynch Field.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cindy W</member_name><member_id>5146051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364072394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363626880000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bare Cove Park Walk/Hingham</name><id>109838692</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364050800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/109838692/</event_url></item>