<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 bromfield st st 409</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356625</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ubersense Inc</name><city>Boston</city><id>9646862</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060509</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Cocos2d for iPhone is a framework for building 2D games, demos, and other graphical/interactive applications. Cocos2d is powerful way to create compelling 2D graphics using OpenGL and Objective-C. Its powerful enough to create games like Angry Birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am starting to explore Cocos2D for my company's work, and I want to get together with a group of people interested in learning this framework together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My ideal cohort for this meetup are people with working objective C knowledge. You don't need to be an expert but should be comfortable with various iOS frameworks. You are really motivated to learn Cocos2d and plan to be at most sessions to get the most out of the proposed goals. So what are the goals?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is what I would love to do for this meetup (but am totally open to suggestions from the group):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) We'll use "Learn cocos2d 2: Game Development for iOS" (&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Learn-cocos2d-Game-Development-iOS/dp/143024416X"&gt;http://www.amazon.com/Learn-cocos2d-Game-Development-iOS/dp/143024416X&lt;/a&gt;) as our guide book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) We meet every couple of weeks. The catch is that we pre read a certain portion of the above book as homework. We'll try not to make the homework part onerous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) When we meet, we spend an hour or two discussing Cocos2d together and hack up some code. A member of the group could volunteer to summarize the reading material that was homework assignment. This does two things. It reinforces concepts for those who have read the portion being presented. And secondly it helps the presenter crystallize concepts that he/she is presenting to the group. The great thing about this is that we can have discussions around key concepts if something is hard to understand.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krishna r</member_name><member_id>11612869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355274152000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>iPhone Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>iphone</urlname><id>1244625</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>iPhone Developers Roundtable - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353893962000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lets learn Cocos2d together for building 2D games and other graphical apps</name><id>92794042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355263200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/iphone/events/92794042/</event_url></item>