<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kevin Martin&lt;/strong&gt; joins us again to share more specific information about shifting our energy and that of our environment, together with insights gleaned from the field of neurolinguistic programming (NLP)- which a number of us have been finding to be very beneficial in our decluttering efforts this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making a &lt;strong&gt;SHIFT&lt;/strong&gt; in anything we are having a problem with is helpful if it is a &lt;strong&gt;SHIFT&lt;/strong&gt; in the right direction.&amp;nbsp; What we mean by shift can be as simple as a little change in perception of the issue.&amp;nbsp; This change in perception leads to a change in action, and that is what really counts. If you are acting (or re-acting) to your issue the same way over and over again, you get no change.&amp;nbsp; Sometimes a subtle shift is all we need.&amp;nbsp; For some, change is immediate and great; for others, change may be over time and subtle.&amp;nbsp; When it comes to the issue of decluttering or other organizational issues, the problem has been around for a long time without any change in the right direction, so &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ANY&lt;/em&gt; SHIFT&lt;/strong&gt; in the right direction will help.&amp;nbsp; This night will be about making that &lt;strong&gt;SHIFT&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of our members, in fact, after participating in our last two meetings, experienced a watershed experience the night of our last meeting and the following day- a veritable breakthrough that persisted the whole week, apparently, as she plowed through the logjam of inertia and procrastination from which she had been suffering ... even though she honestly had reported during our last meeting that she really didn't&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;feel&lt;/em&gt; any different while we were doing the NLP, EFT, and S.O.R.T. exercises that Kevin suggested. She still sees a lot of work ahead of her, she says - &lt;em&gt;but&lt;/em&gt; is now able to have people over to her home ... and says she is&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;certain&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;now that&amp;nbsp;she can create the peaceful, lovely home that she envisions for herself. Her success is SO exciting to hear, first-hand - offering exhilaration that we hope others in our group will catch, as well! Specifically, she has described experiencing a "subtle shift in energy" that has resulted in more motivation and sustained efforts ... possibly having to do with Kevin's quiet, unassuming manner and focused attention on our individual energies, experiences, and behaviors during the last meeting, she reflected (also opining that Kevin must be a &lt;em&gt;great&lt;/em&gt; hypnotist!!) - along with having a decluttering buddy now, too, perhaps. So- we are scheduling this next meeting to see &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; we can leverage her positive experience in freeing SpaceTime ... &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; we can propagate her life-enhancing energy shift throughout &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; of our group, in a contagious ripple effect! &amp;nbsp;Come be part of our exciting social Experiment!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do come, also, to share &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; SUCCESSES in shifting energy to accomplish decluttering projects, whatever those successes might be ... perhaps by&amp;nbsp;tackling inertia, as our co-member has done. (In fact, I've read that people are &lt;em&gt;particularly&lt;/em&gt; motivated to do whatever we expect to be &lt;em&gt;talking&lt;/em&gt; about in the near future- so, let's build that extra incentive in to our meetings, ok? Ok!) Also feel free to raise any other clutter-related challenges for which you seek solutions, so we can consider scheduling a meeting to focus attention on &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; issue, too. Of course, you are always welcomed to post comments here - or on our group's Message Board, about topics you'd&amp;nbsp;like&amp;nbsp;to see addressed in upcoming meetings, together with information (including contact info, please) about any subject-matter experts you know of and respect who might be willing to come shed some light for all of us on the matter(s) of most concern to &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Come join us - AND&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;INVITE A FRIEND(S!!) who might benefit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, as well ...&amp;nbsp;ideally some Prospective Decluttering Buddy&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;that you know and trust already, perhaps to launch your joint project together &lt;em&gt;right there at our meeting, that night&lt;/em&gt; - and of course to multiply our social Fun element! OR perhaps you will come away from our Meetup with an inspiring, reinvigorating&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Decluttering Buddy(ies) to help you steer into the weeks ahead with a clearer, more peaceful, restorative, and energizing living space! Whenever we attract a large group, we still&amp;nbsp;can do much work via small groups - to derive benefit from&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;the large and small groups. Larger numbers of meeting&amp;nbsp;participants could serve to motivate us even more, validating with "social proof" the importance of our determination to take control of our space and time - in order to achieve better focus on whatever &lt;em&gt;we most want&lt;/em&gt; to do with our lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our new venue, &lt;strong&gt;Andala Coffee House&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;is across Franklin Street just behind First Baptist Church at the intersection with River Street in the heart of Central Square, Cambridge ... photos, transit directions, and more information&amp;nbsp;are&amp;nbsp;here&amp;nbsp;on Yelp:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/andala-coffee-house-cambridge"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/andala-coffee-house-cambridge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Andala, we meet downstairs (if you have any questions about location, just ask Leo there) ... no background music is piped in around us (some can just&amp;nbsp;be heard upstairs) - well suited to NLP demonstrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to order refreshments, ALSO ALLOWING EXTRA TIME TO FIND PARKING, if needed, in or near Central Square. Parking in a lot is available ONLY&amp;nbsp;in City Lots 4, 5 , and 6 ("back of Central Sq.") off Norfolk Street &amp;amp; Bishop Allen Drive -- NOT in the private lot to the left of Harvest Co-op, i.e., off Essex Street, which is carefully monitored and ticketed ... meters in the city lots and on the streets around Central Square operate until 6 pm.&amp;nbsp;While no purchase minimum for refreshments is specified by our host venue, &lt;strong&gt;participants are encouraged to order something substantive to&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;support the business in appreciation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;of Management's permission to meet in their space&lt;/strong&gt;. Please also be advised that &lt;em&gt;commercial eating establishments generally cannot permit on-site consumption of refreshments brought from elsewhere&lt;/em&gt;, due to liability concerns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Approximate)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30 pm- Order dinner&amp;nbsp;or other&amp;nbsp;refreshment: ~$2 for coffee, tea, or soda (and upward) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:00 pm- Celebration together of Decluttering &lt;em&gt;Successes!!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 pm- Shifting Energy &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:30 pm&amp;ndash; NLP and other therapeutic techniques for effecting shifts&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 7:45 pm - Demonstration(s) on volunteers, application to others' volunteered situations&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30 pm- Questions and Answers&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 8:45-9 pm- Wrap-up (feel free to leave, or to linger after this point) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Notepad &amp;amp; pen or other note-taking device, calendar to schedule Action Items (next steps). Dress in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in case the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer) and comfortably, as Kevin sometimes has us do NLP/EFT physical exercises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OUR VENUE WISH LIST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome suggestions for additional possible venues&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;especially quiet, preferably free-of-charge spaces under friendly, fairly flexible management, with ample free parking nearby and public transportation that runs on a frequent schedule until at least 9:30 pm (permitting participants to linger and converse after meetings). ...OR we could meet outside in a public park (with shelter nearby in case of rain) during warm weather, perhaps over a potluck dinner, since group members have said they especially like to be out in Nature- where we need not feel too responsible for how everything looks, and maintenance! (...I also read that a Travel Meetup group might meet in a restaurant at Logan Airport- interesting idea: such&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;relevance!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Might we do something similar?&amp;nbsp; I welcome your ideas!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VIDEO PREVIEWS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Bandler: NLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S. Andreas: Compulsion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: EFT/procrastination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: Tapping&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hung by the Tongue: What You Say is What You Get&lt;/em&gt;, by Francis P. Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Biology of Belief: Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter, &amp;amp; Miracles&lt;/em&gt;, by Bruce H. Lipton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt;, by Richard Bandler&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;EXCERPTS are provided&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in previous Meetup descriptions, e.g., August 1, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLARIFICATION FROM KEVIN--&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Misconceptions&amp;nbsp;about hypnosis&amp;nbsp;abound- formed through TV, movies, and staged entertainment. The most prevalent misconception is that hypnosis is a form of mind control - that a hypnotist can make someone rob a bank or do terrible or absurd things. This is absolutely false! A hypnotist cannot make anyone do anything against their values. No one will do anything they would not normally do or that they have not wanted to do. Onstage, a hypnotist provides a 'safe' atmosphere for people to have fun and act on things they may not normally do socially; however, if they have never wanted to do some particular thing, they will not do so under hypnosis. In a clinical offfice session, people under hypnosis do only what they feel safe doing, and no more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hypnotist is only a guide; the person under hypnosis is actually doing the work by following suggestions. That is why we say that all hypnosis is self-hypnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another general misconception is that someone under hypnosis is sleeping. This is far from true: Most people are totally aware of what is happening around them, and can remember everything. Most&amp;nbsp;hypnosis&amp;nbsp;sessions are experienced as deep relaxation - approximating the state of awakening in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The $10-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal, preferably, or in **CASH ONLY (NO CHECKS)** to Judy Stitt at the event&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;before presentation begins&lt;/em&gt;, please) helps to compensate (1) the presenter for his time, training, and specialized knowledge so generously shared with us, and gasoline for travel into town, and (2) the organizer(s) for time spent planning, administering, and coordinating events, and interfacing with members as needed - and to defray Meetup.com's monthly charge assessed organizers for this Web site and other resources to serve our group.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will set a Meetup tent sign on our table (at least until the formal meeting begins at 7 pm)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>esther</member_name><member_id>3096040</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318922725000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316526844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shifting Energy to Foster Positive Actions/Movement</name><id>34249602</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318892400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/34249602/</event_url></item>