<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will go to an area restaurant following the film for a discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Goethe-Institut Boston and the Coolidge Corner Theatre are pleased to present four new films from Germany highlighting four young directors who, with their first or second features demonstrate that there is more to New German Cinema than The Lives of Others. Four Sunday Matinees showcase a sampling of new and award-winning German films rarely shown outside Europe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films in German with English subtitles and shown in Moviehouse 2. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Price: All $5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Yella&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Christian Petzold?s film is a precisely staged, thickly interwoven metaphysical thriller that confirms him as one of the best German directors of the middle generation.&amp;quot; ? Variety&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nina Hoss won the Siver Baer at the 2007 Berlinale for her portrayal of Yella in this 2007 Christian Petzold drama. Yella leaves her hometown for a promising new job and life, but is ultimately haunted by the truths of her past. Her marriage to her husband, Ben broke down and her professional career had no future in her native town in the Eastern part of Germany, and so Yella decides to search for a job in the West. When she gets to know Philipp, a smart executive at a private equity company in Hanover, she becomes his assistant and gets swept into the world of ruthlessness and big business. Realizing her dreams could come true with Philipp's help, she starts hearing voices and sounds from her past, which menace this seemingly new and better life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dir. Christian Petzold, 1h28m, 35mm&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the exit holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201206259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yella</name><id>7187791</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203269400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7187791/</event_url></item>