<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Time Approximate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The film's depiction of the raw fear lurking below the brothers' braggadocio is the most pronounced emotion in a movie whose focus on the personalities of its criminals suggests an Australian answer to &amp;quot;Goodfellas,&amp;quot; minus the wise-guy humor.&lt;/i&gt; - Stephen Holden, The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to the Melbourne underworld. Following the death of his mother, seventeen year-old Joshua &amp;quot;J&amp;quot; Cody (James Frechville) moves in with his hitherto-estranged family, under the watchful eye of his doting grandmother, Janine &amp;quot;Smurf&amp;quot; Cody (Jacki Weaver), and her three criminal sons - the Cody boys.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eldest son and armed robber, Andrew &amp;quot;Pope&amp;quot; Cody (Ben Mendelsohn)is hiding from a gang of renegade detectives. Middle brother Craig (Sullivan Stapleton) is a successful but volatile drug dealer, whilst the youngest Cody, Darren (Luke Ford), naively follows his eldest brothers' lead. Just as Pope's business partner and best friends decides that he wants out of the game, recognizing that their days of old-school banditry are all but over, tensions between the family and the police explode.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;J&amp;quot; finds himself at the centre of a cold-blooded revenge plot that turns his family upside down and throws him directly into the path of senior homicide detective, Nathan Leckie (Guy Pearce).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;dir. David Michod, w/ James Frechville, Guy Pearse, Ben Medelsohn, 1h52m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/animal_kingdom/" target="_blank"&gt;94% Rating on Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Always a good idea to purchase tickets ahead of time.  This showing probably won't sellout, but there is no better feeling than getting to the theater with ticket in hand and seeing the 'sold out' sign' on the window.  Purchase your tickets when next you visit the Coolidge, and I'll provide a link once this showing is available for purchase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;u&gt;World Cinema Jury Prize at the 2010 Sundance Film Festival,&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Animal Kingdom should provide a fertile opportunity for discussion.  As NPR stated, 'what would you do in this situation'?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we will go to &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Zaftigs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; which has provided a wonderful venue for post-film discussion on Sunday afternoons.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282180437000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Animal Kingdom</name><id>14468765</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283104800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14468765/</event_url></item>