<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Lexington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.412483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 547-5655</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739900</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.233269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/1/4/event_83925332.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Time Traveler's Wife&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;by Audrey Niffenegger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This clever and inventive tale works on three levels: as an intriguing science fiction concept, a realistic character study and a touching love story.&amp;nbsp; Henry De Tamble is a Chicago librarian with "Chrono Displacement" disorder; at random times, he suddenly disappears without warning and finds himself in the past or future, usually at a time or place of importance in his life. This leads to some wonderful paradoxes.&amp;nbsp; From his point of view, he first met his wife, Clare, when he was 28 and she was 20.&amp;nbsp; She ran up to him exclaiming that she'd known him all her life.&amp;nbsp; He, however, had never seen her before.&amp;nbsp; But when he reaches his 40s, already married to Clare, he suddenly finds himself time travelling to Clare's childhood and meeting her as a 6-year-old. The book alternates between Henry and Clare's points of view, and so does the narration.&amp;nbsp; Reed ably expresses the longing of the one always left behind, the frustrations of their unusual lifestyle, and above all, her overriding love for Henry.&amp;nbsp; Likewise, Burns evokes the fear of a man who never knows where or when he'll turn up, and his gratitude at having Clare, whose love is his anchor.&amp;nbsp; The expressive, evocative performances of both actors convey the protagonists' intense relationship, their personal quirks and their reminiscences, making this a fascinating audio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Publisher's Weekly&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328670899000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325885581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Time Traveler's Wife</name><id>46994462</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328572800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/46994462/</event_url></item>