<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Downtown</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04096</zip><lat>43.800635</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yarmouth</name><city>Yarmouth</city><id>1308489</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.186716</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What is &lt;a href="http://www.thelevityproject.com" target="_blank"&gt;The Levity Project&lt;/a&gt;? &lt;br /&gt;It is a social movement with the mission of creating more lightheartedness in our world by engaging in public acts of joy, laughter and levity...(and yes, it is very fun!) in a flash mob style event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is a Flash Mob?&lt;br /&gt;It is when a group of people&amp;quot;spontaneously&amp;quot; gather in a public place to create an event of some sort. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of The Levity Project events focus on creating a sense of play,laughter, and celebration in our world.  You can see some of our videos and events here on &lt;a href="http://www.thelevityproject.com" target="_blank"&gt;our website.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And The Levity Project is coming to Maine for The FIRST big Maine Flash Mob event.   The event will be at the Yarmouth Clam Festival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details about what is happening at the event will only be given out to registrants. &lt;br /&gt;(we promise it is a memorable experience for all!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why do it?&lt;br /&gt;A. It is the first flash mob in Maine and that is kinda fun.&lt;br /&gt;B. By coming together, it is a gift we offer a community of joy and celebration.&lt;br /&gt;C. It is an excellent way to spend part of one's 15 minutes of fame...did we mention there will be 20,000 people there...yup. hahaha!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please join and register using the link&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://thelevityprojectmaine.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://thelevityproje...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is free for all who join in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please forward and invite to anyone you know who might want to join us...we would love to have 200-300 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you and keep laughing,&lt;br /&gt;Katie&lt;br /&gt;PS you can email me at katie (AT) thelevityproject (dot) com and feel free to contact if you have a good source of people who might want to play with us. Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also call 207 239 8667 if you have questions.  I would be happy to speak with you. :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279397478000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Laugh with Maine Laughter Yoga</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Maine-Laughter-Yoga</urlname><id>1336948</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Maine Laughter Yoga Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277645141000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Special Event: The Levity Project is coming to MAINE! </name><id>13924143</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279312200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Maine-Laughter-Yoga/events/13924143/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/c/global_15999500.jpeg</photo_url></item>