<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 491 9400</phone><name>Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>730460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Surely nerds pine fondly for the bygone days of intellectual snobbery. Harvard Square, the heart of intellectual razzmatazz, has already successfully hosted (every other Sunday) four Intellectual Snob Meetups with the unrepentant Nerd Fun Meetup! Some fellow nerds have even showed up with fake moustaches, glasses with fold-up sun flaps, and corduroy jackets with elbow patches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You DON'T have to be a genuine intellectual to attend this Meetup! &amp;quot;Pseudo-intellectuals&amp;quot; are also welcome to fake it! (See: &amp;quot;how to become a pseudo intellectual&amp;quot; on &lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_2000106_become-pseudo-intellectual.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;ehow.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). Just bring your baffling, aloof opinions and a &amp;quot;stiff upper lip&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a test as to whether or not you &amp;quot;qualify&amp;quot; as an intellectual snob, we recommend the audacious Okcupid &lt;a href="http://www.okcupid.com/tests/take?testid=6120266386722915089" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Intellectual Snob Test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for a fun and innocent introduction (you don't need to log in).&lt;br /&gt;Snobs always know, or think they know something deeply meaningful that nobody else knows.  (See: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=2225654801" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;The Society for the Collection of Obscure Facts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on Facebook for examples!) (You will need to log into Meetup to access this link).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar is located in front of the charles Hotel. It's not a full restaurant, nor is it strictly a bar. It's a patio with lots of big tables which includes a bar. There isn't pressure to order food, but if you choose to, a light fare seafood- oriented menu is available. At this time of day, the tables will be in the SHADE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE RAIN LOCATION! IT'S GRENDEL'S DEN, 89 WINTHROP ST., HARVARD SQUARE. &lt;br /&gt;RSVP's will be emailed 24 hr's in advance if rain or excessive wind forecast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although street parking in Harvard Square on Sundays is &amp;quot;unrestricted&amp;quot;, public transportation is recommended (parking space is limited).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a Nerd Fun sign near a row of tables</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>duncan </member_name><member_id>9836304</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280112598000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277688013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intellectual Snob Meetup (Chapter V)</name><id>jcscpynkbhc</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280093400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13930111/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/f/f/global_12156767.jpeg</photo_url></item>