<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.350399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>19 Mile Brook Trailhead</name><city>Gorham</city><id>391517</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194696</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are hiking the Carters this weekend and how would you like to wake up and be there already!  It's off season rates, and If we hurry and make reservations,  we can book many bunks, BUT I need to know you are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will reserve my space (I've always wanted to do this). And will leave it up to you to reserve a bunk and then RSVP. This way no one needs to watch the money and we know who really will be coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals Distance to the hut   3.80 mi Time 2 hr 53 min Elev Gain +1991 ft         1.5 hr hike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/lodging/rates/index.cfm?method=search" target="_blank"&gt;AMC reservations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.outdoors.org/lodging/huts/images/carter_panoramic_2.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price is $30 for AMC members and $33 for non members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrive when it is convenient to hike in, and we will schedule local area hikes on both Saturday and Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Carter's and Wildcats are options. Carter Dome is Scheduled for Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AMC Payments are refundable according to the following guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;Reservations cancelled more than 30 days in advance will receive a full refund.&lt;br /&gt;Reservations cancelled 14-30 days in advance will result in a 70% refund.&lt;br /&gt;Reservations cancelled less than 14 days in advance are non-refundable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BEFORE YOU GO INFORMATION&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Emergency messages relayed to huts via radio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Planning Your Visit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Weather: weather conditions can vary widely during any season in the White Mountains.  You can check weather forecasts, backcountry conditions, and avalanche reports online.  You can also call our Pinkham Notch Visitor Center at 603-466-2721 for questions on trail conditions.&lt;br /&gt;    * Books and Maps: Plan to carry a current map, guidebook, and compass on your trip.  We recommend the AMC White Mountain Guide, available on the AMC Online Store  or by calling 800-262-4455.  You can also get hiking trip ideas and plan routes using White Mountain Guide Online.&lt;br /&gt;    * Carry In/Carry Out: due to our backcountry locations, guests are expected to pack out their own trash and recyclables.  We compost food waste during full-service season; guests should pack out their own food waste in self-service season.&lt;br /&gt;    * Quiet Hours: please be respectful of other guests and observe quiet hours from 9:30 PM to 6:30 AM.&lt;br /&gt;    * Alcohol: Alcoholic beverages are allowed in moderation, and should be consumed in a responsible manner.  Carry in/carry out.&lt;br /&gt;    * Smoking: smoking or open flame are not allowed in or near any structure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to Bring&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * During full-service season (summer and fall)&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;          o Bunk with pillow and three wool blankets provided in our co-ed bunkrooms – bring sheets, sleep sack or lightweight sleeping bag&lt;br /&gt;          o Enclosed gender-specific washrooms have cold running water – you may want to bring a small towel or washcloth&lt;br /&gt;          o Dinner and breakfast are included in your hut rate – you may wish to bring your own snack and lunch items, or buy snack items, soup, or baked goods at the hut (available 11AM – 4PM)&lt;br /&gt;          o Lighting is limited to common areas only.  Bring a headlamp for the bunkrooms at night.&lt;br /&gt;    * During self-service season (late fall, winter, spring)&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;          o Bunk and pillow provided, and bunkrooms or bunkhouses are unheated. Blankets are not provided during self-service season – bring an appropriately rated sleeping bag.&lt;br /&gt;          o Guests pack in own food and have full use of hut’s stove, oven, cookware and serviceware.  Pack out all trash, recyclables, and food waste.&lt;br /&gt;          o Dress for conditions inside and outside the hut. Caretaker available 4:00-10:00PM and 7:00-10:00AM; caretaker may light fire in woodstove on winter evenings&lt;br /&gt;    * Clothing and Gear for Outdoor Activities: having the right equipment during your trip will greatly enhance your outdoor experience in the White Mountains.  It is important to wear proper footwear, and carry warm clothing, foul-weather gear, food and water, and other essentials.  Trail access to our huts can be exposed and can include stretches above treeline.  Be prepared for severe weather regardless of season, dress in layers (including synthetic or wool base and insulating layers, and a windproof/waterproof outer shell), eat high energy foods, and stay hydrated.&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;          o Spring, Summer, Fall Gear List&lt;br /&gt;          o Winter Gear List&lt;br /&gt;          o HikeSafe – Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;br /&gt;          o Leave No Trace Guidelines&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253560131000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249588779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come Stay at Carter Notch Hut:   Its Off Season rates!</name><id>11052496</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253386800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11052496/</event_url></item>