<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Folks, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are having  a music &lt;b&gt;MEETUP&lt;/b&gt; at my house this Saturday 12-5-09 afternoon, from 2PM until 6 PM or a little after.  Come and leave when convenient, the main meetup is 3 to 6PM.  I will give address to attendees &amp;amp; maybes later - it's in East Cambridge near lechmere.  PLEASE RSVP YES SO I CAN EMAIL THE ATTENDEES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope everyone had a good Holiday. Here are the tabulated results of everyones interests, so these will be our general priorities. If your interests change, and new people, let me know what your top 3 interests are.  Thanks for the positive comments! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jam    5 &lt;br /&gt;Record (a CD?)  5 &lt;br /&gt;Open mikes   4 &lt;br /&gt;Collaborative songwriting 4 &lt;br /&gt;support others   3 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So basically, we would: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) &lt;b&gt;Jam,&lt;/b&gt; and I would think this also includes &lt;b&gt;rehearsing&lt;/b&gt; originals and covers, and when they are good enough, start recording. Also working on, developing, arranging  originals.  We could do at least 1 free form improvising jam during each meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Then when it sounds reasonable, &lt;b&gt;record&lt;/b&gt;. When the recordings sound good, then we will make a final recording for mixing down and putting on a CD. We should get originals copywritten, and need a fair plan that I can submit for everyones approval in case of CD distribution, profits, etc. - because your songs are really your property. (One simple way is just everyone gets a copy of the files, and can do what they want.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Meanwhile at any time go to &lt;b&gt;open mikes&lt;/b&gt; for experience &amp;amp; exposure &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opportunities:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) I am going to the &lt;b&gt;Squawk Cafe&lt;/b&gt; open mike tonight Thursday because a friend is having a show. It starts at 9PM, I might be late (around 10PM).  This is a good place to meet and talk after.  This is a no pressure venue, so it’s fine to start playing here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) I was invited to play at a &lt;b&gt;Mini Greenfest&lt;/b&gt;, at the Hynes Auditorium on 12/31 sometime from 1-5 pm. I would think we can get at least aa half hour or more. The theme is environmental songs for Families and children. I have a few environmental songs that I played at the Boston Greenfest 2009 with Paul at the Swedenborg chapel Mystical Event. We can write some more environmental and inpiring uplifting songs a and have a great venue to play, but would have to practice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Greenfest Director&lt;/b&gt;: This is to let you know, if you don't know already, that we have been offered a space for free to have a mini GreenFest for kids and their families during First Night. This is exciting as it gives us an opportunity to get exposure and also educate the public for the new year. We will be at the Hynes Auditorium on 12/31 from 1-5 pm. ] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Anyone interested in singing &lt;b&gt;Christmas Carols/hymns&lt;/b&gt;? - In Harvard Sq, (I have a musician permit), or other events, or old folks homes (you can get paid!. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best Regards - Bill&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260213333000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259882884000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Music Meetup # 2</name><id>12012556</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260039600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/12012556/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>