<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Whiting Farms Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.175727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn at Ingleside</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>906244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641467</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Joy Baldridge&lt;br /&gt;Success with Less Stress&lt;br /&gt;How to Have Fun, Make Money, and Enjoy Your Work and Life&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Thursday, October 21, 2010- 7:45am&lt;br /&gt;Where: Holiday Inn at Ingleside, Holyoke, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $15 in advance, $18 at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joy's programs are fabulously fun, incredibly interactive, insightful, and packed with tons of tangible takeaways you can immediately use to make positive changes that get results.&lt;br /&gt;With her Golden Nuggets, you will learn how to raise the bar on productivity, profitability and performance while increasing your energy and attitude levels.  Joy helps you take your capabilities and success to new heights, and have fun while doing it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joy Baldridge is the founder and president of Baldridge Seminars International, a professional development organization that focuses on management, leadership, sales, communication and priority management skill development, both domestically and globally.  Her first speaking engagement was at the White House, at the age of 19.  She got there by cold calling the president.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joy is the author of The Fast-Forward MBA in Selling, published by John Wiley &amp;amp; Sons, Inc.  This book provides an abundance of what she calls &amp;quot;Golden Nuggets&amp;quot; of information: Useful real-world tips, case studies and strategies designed specifically to help create self-managed business professionals.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288042944000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286332778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Breakfast Meeting- Success with Less Stress</name><id>15017088</id><headcount>54</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287661500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/15017088/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/7/d/global_18527501.jpeg</photo_url></item>