<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello, and Happy Spring to all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May's meet-up will be similar to the conversational format that we've had in the past with one exception:  we're going to talk a little bit about one of Ayn Rand's early works, &amp;quot;Good Copy,&amp;quot; which you can find in &amp;quot;The Early Ayn Rand.&amp;quot;  I believe this can be ordered through Amazon.com or Barnes &amp;amp; Noble without much difficulty.  If you cannot find it, let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Good Copy&amp;quot; is a humorous, short piece of non-fiction from - as the title states - Ayn Rand's early years.  A new member of our group suggested that we read something for the next get-together so that all of us, whether new to Ayn Rand or &amp;quot;veterans,&amp;quot; would have some common ground for discussion.  The thought at this meeting was to begin alternating weeks of fiction with non-fiction.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Secondly, someone suggested that with our group growing like it is (tables of 9 are getting a little crowded at Starbucks) we might want to consider changing the venue.  Apparently, (and I will investigate this) the Beantown Pub would be willing to let us gather there, as long as we &amp;quot;consume&amp;quot; something.  I will find out what the parameters are.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the meantime, please email or post your comments on your suggestions for a venue for May.  We can always do Starbucks again, but in anticipation of the throngs of people that this group is attracting :-)  I would like to have ample space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to come with as little or as much knowledge of Ayn Rand as you have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have to pay meetup.com $19.00 per month to use their site, but for me, this is a small price to pay for the opportunity to meet other people interested in Objectivism, the philosophy of Ayn Rand.  However, if anyone would be willing to donate a dollar or two to help me defray the monthly expenditure, that would be great.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>2499401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540169000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1144015745000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Ayn Rand May Meetup</name><id>4891202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1147035600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/4891202/</event_url></item>