<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Congress Street across from City Hall</address_2><address_1>Faneuil Hall Marketplace</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360058</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Faneuil Hall (in front of the Samuel Adams statue)</name><city>Boston</city><id>710059</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056068</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Crawl In Boston is excited to be throwing our very first World Cup Crawl with proceeds to benefit the Hattie B. Cooper Community Center. 1 - 9PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be traveling Around the World with each bar providing a $3 (or less) specialty drink that represents their country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00 – Red Hat – Mexico - Dos Equis and Margaritas.&lt;br /&gt;2:00 – The Point – Japan – Sake Bombs&lt;br /&gt;3:00 – Red Sky – Italy – Amaretto Sours&lt;br /&gt;4:00 – McFadden’s – England – Gin &amp;amp; Tonics&lt;br /&gt;5:00 - Jose McIntyre's - Spain - TBD&lt;br /&gt;6:00 – Coogan’s – USA – Budweiser and Budlight (only $1)&lt;br /&gt;7:00 – Sanctuary – Poland – Poland Ultimate Punch&lt;br /&gt;8:00 – Market – Brasil - Caipirinha&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That’s right. You’ll be able to sample all these drinks for only $3 each or less. There’s no better deal than that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s some good information to know:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What does this event cost?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are asking for $5.00 to attend. You will receive bracelet which will get you the drink specials at all the bars. Please keep in mind that proceeds of your donation supports the Hattie B. Cooper Community Center Charity. Everyone who donates will be receiving:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Crawl in Boston Nametag&lt;br /&gt;*Crawl in Boston Beverage Koozie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who is Crawl in Boston? &lt;a href="http://crawlinboston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://crawlinboston....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crawl in Boston is a social networking group that gives professionals a chance to meet new people in a casual and fun atmosphere. People of all ages have gathered to join the bar crawls, and we’ve raised money and goods for local charities. We also spread the word about other similar events we’ve heard about, as well as new places and bar/restaurant specials. We’re bringing people together, one drink at a time for local charities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is the Hattie B. Cooper Community Center? &lt;a href="http://cooperctr.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://cooperctr.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hattie B. Cooper Community Center has served Greater Roxbury and surrounding neighborhoods for over 93 years, providing underserved children and their families vital educational services that facilitate growth and development, and creating groundwork for future successes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How Do I Sign Up?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don’t have to. We only ask you RSVP on the Facebook event ASAP. This gives us a better idea on how many people are coming. We can better arrange our schedule so the bars have enough staff to accommodate you all. Also helps let us know how many koozies to order.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to wear?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a favorite team in the World Cup? Represent with their team colors!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276604951000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275588764000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Cup Pub Crawl in Faneuil Hall</name><id>13686762</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276362000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/13686762/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/7/global_15481767.jpeg</photo_url></item>