<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/1/6/event_93886102.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;A Winter's Tale&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;is an intimate evening of storytelling from a talented array of local writers, students, bartenders, and other interesting characters. Each year, creative Seacoast personalities come together in this fundraising benefit for &lt;a href="http://heat-eat.blogspot.com/"&gt;Seacoast (H)EAT&lt;/a&gt;, a small charity that supplies food and heating fuel to local residents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've been to the past three annual &lt;em&gt;Tales&lt;/em&gt; and the evenings are startlingly good with much laughter, pathos, and warmth all around.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TICKETS are $10 each and they WILL SELL OUT. Call River Run bookstore &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;immediately&lt;/span&gt; to reserve: 603-431-2100.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Door is a small space above Dos Amigos Burritos on State Street in Portsmouth (entered from the street through a non-descript red door). They normally have DJs with loud music and a 20-something crowd. That all changes for A Winter's Tale. Seating is very limited. There are always people sitting all over the floor so if you need a chair/couch/stool, arrive early!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True tales told live. No notes. No net.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of theSeacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.&amp;nbsp; Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Arrive by 6pm if you want to sit on a chair.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330315702000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329326836000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Winter's Tale</name><id>52454702</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330300800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/52454702/</event_url></item>