<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Parking Lot is just down the hill from intersection of Main St. &amp; Valerie Court)</address_2><address_1>Lot is near 452 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06514</zip><lat>41.359932</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lake Wintergreen @ West Rock Ridge State Park</name><city>Hamden</city><id>788054</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.965096</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi folks! Hope you can join us for a refreshing Saturday morning walk and talk at one of our favorite spots. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: This Meetup will take place at West Rock, which is a Connecticut State Park located in New Haven and Hamden.  There are various entrances to the park, but we will be parking at Lake Wintergreen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN AND WHERE: Meet at the Lake Wintergreen entrance, which is located on Main Street, between 9:55 and 10:00, and we'll get rolling onto the trail at five after ten. This walk will be 2 hours.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEAR: Hiking or other sturdy shoes with treads;  &lt;b&gt;warm clothing&lt;/b&gt;; warm socks; hat and gloves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST:  &lt;b&gt;Suggested donation&lt;/b&gt; of one dollar, towards the monthly fee that is charged by the Meetup Website.  Please bring any contributions with you on the day of the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Please use Google Maps (or, your GPS) to find the intersection of Main Street and Valerie Court in Hamden -- this is the closest possible intersection that is actually listed on Google Maps, as the lot itself is NOT listed. From Main and Valerie, drive DOWNHILL on Main Street and you will see the parking area at the bottom of the hill, where Main Street bends to the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING NOTE: There is no fee for parking in the lot. Please carpool if possible, as this lot fills up fast on weekend mornings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2716&amp;amp;Q=325276" target="_blank"&gt;Park website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?client=firefox-a&amp;amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google Map -- Intersection of Main Street and Valerie Court&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Organizer (Sarah) will be wearing red</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah </member_name><member_id>7903956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268060800000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hiking-575</urlname><id>1282762</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Walks in the Woods</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266676511000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Haven Walks Saturday Meetup at West Rock</name><id>12655019</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267887600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hiking-575/events/12655019/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/7/global_7013047.jpeg</photo_url></item>