<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>31 College Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.240002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Hampshire Technical Institute, Sweeney Hall Auditorium</name><city>Concord</city><id>413998</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.510002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event being organized by the Concord HQ Meetup and the Official Campaign Staff....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are shooting to get 200-400 people to campaign together for Ron Paul. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have a morning get-together starting at 10am (doors open at 9:30am) with some canvassing training by a long time top political advisor of Dr Paul, Tom Lizardo,  and also a video conference with Dr Paul. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will then go out and do various campaign related activities such as lit drops, sign waves, phone banking, etc. We are inviting all the New England meetups, as well as anyone who wants to drive out! We will have lunch at the cafeteria.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr Paul is planning on video-conferencing with us, since the Concord HQ meetup got a telecon as a prize for donations. He could be subject to last minute schedule changes, but for now, we are expecting the video conference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location will be the New Hampshire Technical Institutes' Sweeney Hall Auditorium in Concord, NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have some activities planned for Sunday for those that can spend an extra night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE SIGN UP FOR THIS EVENT ASAP. We need accurate numbers for planning purposes. Time is getting short, and this is an extremely important event. Please don't wait till the last minute to RSVP. If you are still not 100% sure you can come, just RSVP as a maybe.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194269705000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192880118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Video Conference with Dr Paul, and HUGE Event</name><id>6584165</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1194096600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6584165/</event_url></item>