<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Simons IMAX Theater - Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1245284</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050826</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a joint meetup with the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Parking! - For those of you not working in Boston&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Very challenging - but the following parking garages offer discounted Parking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;- 75 State Street Garage - arrive after 5PM - $12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;- Garage at Post Office Square - arrive after 4PM - $9&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;- 60 State Street arrive after 3:30 PM - $10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's catch the premiere showing of TGR's "One for the Road". Since it is at the Aquarium, we can meet at the Chart House Restaurant's (&lt;a href="http://www.chart-house.com/pdf/happyHour/CH" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.chart-house.com/pdf/happyHour/CH&lt;/a&gt;...) bar for Happy Hour on the Long Wharf from - just past the Marriott and enjoy their BAR specials from 5:30 - 6:30 - Then head over to the IMAX Aquarium line to sit together and watch it on the huge screen... From the TGR web site (&lt;a href="http://www.tetongravity.com/one-for-the-roa" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.tetongravity.com/one-for-the-roa&lt;/a&gt;...) One for the Road is an HD ski film that follows some of the world's most progressive snow sports athletes as it documents their lives on the road and captures some of the most stunning riding to date. Road trips are an integral part of every adventurer's life and a conduit to define one's being. Journeys to new lands shed light on each skier's personal mission. Whether shredding with long time ski partners, or meeting a seasoned character in some far off country, wisdom is gained through these new experiences. The road trip is a metaphor for every skier's existence. Shot on location, prepare for a visually stunning voyage generated with Phantom, Red, Canon DSLR and GoPro HD footage. Join the athletes as they rock a record breaking season in Jackson Hole, immerse themselves into the culture of Japan's powder mecca Hokkaido, discover Iceland's urban side, explore the Balkan wonders of Macedonia and Montenegro, shred deep pillow lines at Baldface Lodge, uncover first descents in Pemberton, BC, and hit full throttle lines in the perfect snow and weather of Juneau, AK. Join the award winning producers at Teton Gravity Research as they embark on the ultimate road trip. Athletes: Sage Cattabriga-Alosa, Ian McIntosh, Griffin Post, Todd Ligare, Chris Benchetler, Dylan Hood, Dash Longe, Daron Rahlves, Sven K&amp;uuml;enle, Rachael Burks, Callum Pettit, Erik Roner, Grete Eliassen, Shroder Baker, Byron Wells, Andreas Hatveit, Rory Bushfield, Nick Martini, Tom Wallisch, Dana Flahr, Mike Riddle, Josh Dirksen Locations: Japan; Iceland; Macedonia; Montenegro; Pemberton, BC; Baldface Lodge, BC; Jackson Hole, WY; Juneau, AK; Tignes, France; Utah; Squaw Valley, CA Caught it last year and it was awesome - so I am sure they have set the bar higher! Regards, Jonathan Here is the link for tickets: To Be Announced!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the Chart House just past the Marriott next to the Aquarium on Long Wharf.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321019235000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Adventurerists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak</urlname><id>1297030</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Ski, Snowboard, and Outdoor Adventurers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316709934000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Teton Gravity Research presents "One for the Road" @ the IMAX Aquarium - Boston</name><id>34562482</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320964200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak/events/34562482/</event_url></item>