<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(edge of Portal Park</address_2><address_1>Causeway St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.365706</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Station T stop</name><city>Boston</city><id>856572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060636</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come along on this tour to discover the things that move in, around, and over the Charles River Basin. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will depart from the Boston Garden, discuss the Bulfinch Triangle, wend our way over the Charles and skirt the Charlestown shore to the U.S.S. Constitution. This route allows you to experience the art, technology and nature of this historic (but often overlooked) area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the tour we will get a close up view of Boston's new cable-stayed landmark, the Leonard P. Zakim Bunker Hill Bridge, go over the locks of the Charles River Dam and observe the ongoing revitalization of the lower basin of the Charles (once called the Lost Half Mile). Not to mention, we get a chance to discuss the alewife herring and its anadromous behaviour, the harbor crossing of a certain Mr. Revere and the exploits of the Boston Ice King.  And there's a story about molasses that is a real winner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This small area of Boston is packed with amazing things to see! Bring along some water and enjoy this journey of discovery. The tour lasts 90 minutes and costs $15 ($5 for card carrying Boston By Foot members -- see web site &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org" target="_blank"&gt;for details on how to join&lt;/a&gt;). We will meet at the corner of Portal Park on Causeway Street - just next to the North Station T entrance kiosk closest to the Boston Garden.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for folks with BBF badges (hats, bags, t-shirts) - blue and white!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278509447000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276892568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boats, Bridges &amp; Locks tour</name><id>13842785</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277989200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/13842785/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/e/global_8513678.jpeg</photo_url></item>