<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Adobe has spent a lot of time making the Flex Framework components as reusable as possible.  But, for normal development you do not need to create components that are as flexible or bullet proof as the ones in the Flex Framework.  In this month's meeting we will learn how to build Flex Components for real world applications.  And if you want to bullet proof your stuff, there will be an introduction for that as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeffry is a technical entrepreneur and the brains behind Flextras, a set of interface components for Flex Developers.&lt;br /&gt;He has a Computer Science degree from the days before business met the Internet and owns DotComIt, an Adobe Solutions Partner specializing in Rich Internet Applications. Jeffry is an Adobe Community Expert and produces The Flex Show, a podcast for Flex Developers.  Jeffry is also co-manager of the Hartford CT Adobe User Group, author of 3 ColdFusion books and over 30 articles, and has spoken at various events all over the US.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his spare time he is a musician, old school adventure game aficionado, and recording engineer. He also owns a Wii. You can check out the components at www.flextras.com/?c=107 , read his blog at www.jeffryhouser.com, check out his podcast at www.theflexshow.com or check out his company at www.dot-com-it.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Mason</member_name><member_id>4527001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241136192000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236129459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Building Flex Components in the Real World </name><id>9874942</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236812400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/9874942/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/f/global_5719263.jpeg</photo_url></item>