<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have been given the suggestion to hike this by a couple of other hiking groups.  It looks really good from their photos and comments.  This part of the Tunxis Trail will take us to the northwestern corner of Southington, into Bristol, and back.  This will be a new trail for me and I am looking forward to the challenge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is considered strenuous due to the fact we will gain over 2000 feet over the duration of the hike.  We will start on the Steep Climb Trail and head up onto the ridge.  The trail is a challenging series of descents and acsents of the western wall of Connecticut's Central Valley.  The distance is about 6 miles round trip.  I cannot put a time on completing so do not plan a tight schedule for the afternoon.  We hike as a group and are only as fast as our slowest hiker.  Those who have been with me before know there is no trail running but we keep a good pace.  I like to look at the surroundings, not just run through the woods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a summer hike so plan on heat.  You will need hiking boots, water, snacks, bug spray, sunscreen, a hat, clothes that wick.  We will take breaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always with me, NO DOGS or CHILDREN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the parking and meeting point.  It is a cul de sac at the end of Panthorn Trail (that's the road name).&lt;br /&gt;GPS USERS, I DO NOT HAVE AN EXACT ADDRESS.  USE THE MAPQUEST LINK TO SEE THE GENERAL AREA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Southington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=199+Panthorn+Trl&amp;amp;zipcode=06489-1070&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.6324&amp;amp;longitude=-72.924709&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have no plans to go to the amusement park.  I hear the Pig Out BBQ, 16 Eden Ave in Southington is good.  Its 3 miles from the site. &lt;a href="http://www.thepigoutbbq.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thepigoutb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other post hike options can be discussed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1279759289000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277164057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Tunxis Trail and Compounce Ridge, Southington CT</name><id>13869377</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279461600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13869377/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>