<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well obviously it's going to be raining a bunch, so bring your umbrellas!! The pre meetup Jazz festival event meetup is off.   In a way, rain might work towards our favor, as I'm going to look into an after movie meetup dinner  at Brown Sugar, a nice Thai restaurant across the Fens from the MFA.  We will be walking a bit in the rain where ever we go (Umbrellas!!) If your not going to come, please change your RSVP.  Brown Sugar is a small place.  We might be able to get 3 tables of 4-6 at 7:30 -7:45.  We'll see!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the MFA website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston film lovers join audiences from four continents to judge the next generation of international filmmakers at the 11th Annual Manhattan Short Film Festival. The festival receives over 700 entries from more than forty-five countries. Of these, twelve finalists are selected for screening at over 200 cinemas across Europe, North, and South and Central America in which audience members are asked to vote for the winner. With past finalists going on to win Oscars and moving into the Hollywood feature film industry, the Manhattan Short Film Festival has become a testing ground for raw, new talent. Program about 2 hours long. For more information and to read interviews with the Finalists of 2008, visit the festival Web site at www.MSfilmfest.com. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Members, Seniors, Students $8; Adults $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll head up Huntington towards Mass Ave to discuss.  Pho and I, a Vietnamese restaurant a block or two past Shwarma,  is my choice, but I could be talked into Qdoba or Shwarma via responses or an uprising after the movie.  There's also a Thai place nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, before this Movie event is the Berklee Beantown Jazz festival.  This event is sponsored by Berklee School of Music and runs from 1-6 on Columbus Ave.  Lots of food, and 3-4 sound stages of live Jazz music.  I will be there from about 2:15 to 4:15 if anyone want's to meetup before the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details of the Jazz fest are at this link  &lt;a href="http://www.beantownjazz.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beantownja...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And a map of the six blocks that the Beantown jazz fest is located (on Columbus Ave between Mass Ave and Burke) can be seen at the URL that follows.  You'll notice it's in relatively close proximity to the MFA (about 4-5 blocks diagonally throught the Northeastern campus from the Burke/Columbus intersection to the MFA).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;saddr=Burke+St,+Boston,+MA+02120&amp;amp;daddr=42.340545,-71.081736&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=CThr1BSSDmAZFW4FhgIdyFHD-w%3B&amp;amp;mra=mi&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=16&amp;amp;sll=42.33899,-71.0815&amp;amp;sspn=0.007137,0.013819&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.341132,-71.093903&amp;amp;spn=0.014274,0.027637&amp;amp;z=15" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Front of the screen, right side, at the end of the film, with meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222899169000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219089045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Manhattan Short Film Festival 2008</name><id>8570771</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222550100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8570771/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/0/global_5207152.jpeg</photo_url></item>