<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 134 South Dennis</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>41.714291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cape Cod Rail Trail</name><city>Dennis</city><id>3311352</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.154289</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Debra Hodgkins @ (508) 237-4454&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;When: Saturday, May 18, 2013 at 10:30 AM&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them. &lt;br /&gt;

 Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate. &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Cycling the Cape Cod Rail Trail&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The trail one way is 22 miles (44 round trip). The ride starts at 10:30 am at the Trailhead on Route 134 in Dennis. &lt;br /&gt;

 Guests are not permitted - all participants must be members of the South Shore Hike and Bike Group. &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The objective is to ride at about a 12 - 15 MPH pace. &lt;br /&gt;

 While I have been on this trail many times before I did all of my current research for this trip using the Internet. You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 • Click for a map of the trail &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/ccrt.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/ccrt.pdf&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Unlike hiking, biking is no fun in the rain. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel. I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the ride and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 • Click for the current weather forecast (&lt;a href="http://noaa.gov"&gt;noaa.gov&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Below is a list describing the minimum items required to participate in this event. &lt;br /&gt;

 • &lt;strong&gt;Helmet:&lt;/strong&gt; You must wear a properly sized and adjusted bicycle helmet that has been tested and meets the uniform safety standard issued by the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC). &lt;br /&gt;

 • &lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear:&lt;/strong&gt; Liquids to stay hydrated and food to stay nourished. White headlight and red taillight if we will be riding before sunrise or after sunset. A multi-purpose tool or small repair kit. A spare tube.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 =====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The Address for your gps is &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps/place?q=416+East-West+Dennis+Road,+Dennis,+MA&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ftid=0x89fb392e0d231c7b:0x4edcbcc9773aa6ac"&gt;https://maps.google.com/maps/place?q=416+East-West+Dennis+Road,+Dennis,+MA&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ftid=0x89fb392e0d231c7b:0x4edcbcc9773aa6ac&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 416 East-West Dennis Road, Dennis, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 ===== &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the bicycle safety tips described at &lt;a href="http://www.massbike.org"&gt;www.massbike.org&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra </member_name><member_id>12483780</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368898336000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368637065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cycle the Cape Cod Rail Trail</name><id>119531932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368887400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/119531932/</event_url></item>