<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>873 Whalley Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06515</zip><lat>41.326642</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.389.9555    </phone><name>Kehler Liddell Gallery</name><city>New Haven</city><id>800189</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.959489</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>So sorry for all the confusion here, I have found that Kehler Liddells web site has the wrong information, conflicting with another source, this is the revised date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all enjoyed these two amazing Artists when we were fortunate enough to view their work during Open Studios weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frank Bruckmann &amp;amp; Susan Clinard&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3-6pm&lt;br /&gt;Artist Talk at 3pm; Live music by Oud player Qusai Al Bakri&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Susan Clinard:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether I am sculpting from life in clay, bending wire, or carving wood, I strive to reveal nature’s truths – the duality of chaos against perfect symmetry. My inspiration is often in life cycles. The ongoing tearing down and rebuilding as seen in both the physical world as well as in the human psyche. Over the past decade, I have moved from sculpting figures for the figure’s sake to experimentation with a wider range of materials; primarily found natural objects. This integration has simplified my forms and figurative elements. The resulting sculpture is open to the intuitive and interpretive response of an audience, rather than the single narrative intention of the artist. The work draws on and layers nature’s puzzles with personal and political themes of inherently deep emotion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My work is an exploration of nature’s forms, distorted and perfect, found and inspired. It is simply art reflective of life which contains the ugly and the beautiful without interruption. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://clinard.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://clinard.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frank Bruckmann:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frank began his studies at the DuCret school of Art in New Jersey, and then took classes at the Art Students League in NYC. In Paris he studied at the Ecole des Beaux Arts, and spent nearly a decade in France and Spain, copying the masters in the great museums, and painting landscapes in the cities and countryside. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now a resident of New Haven, CT, Frank has found endless subject matter for landscapes in New England, but periodically packs his easel and travels farther and wider in his VW camper. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fbruckmann.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://fbruckmann.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will wear the bw scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292296126000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288488265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frank Bruckmann &amp; Susan Clinard</name><id>15282841</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292184000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/15282841/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/6/global_19200534.jpeg</photo_url></item>