<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>about .5 west of the Cog parking lot</address_2><address_1>Base Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.263730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ammonoosuc Ravine parking lot</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>292562</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.425359</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be meeting at the Ammonoosuc Ravine parking lot at 7:45 and leaving some cars there while carpooling to the Edmands Path Trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please put your name on the waiting list if you would like to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this is an advanced level hike.  All attendees must have prior hiking experience hiking above treeline and hiking 4000 foot mountains.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must be prepared for severe weather conditions.  Hats, gloves/mittens and no cotton clothing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must be able to hike at a two mile an hour pace for a minimum of four hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability policy as outlined on this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; starting at Edmands Path Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 2.90 mi/2 hr 42 min/+2405 ft on the Edmands Path &lt;br /&gt; From its trailhead, the path runs nearly level across two small brooks, then it crosses Abenaki Brook and turns sharp right onto an old logging road on the far bank. The trail diverges left off the old road and crosses a wet area. Soon it begins to climb steadily, undulating up the west ridge of Mt. Eisenhower, carefully searching out the most comfortable grades. The trail swings left and angles up the mountainside on a footway supported by extensive rock cribbing, then passes through a tiny stone gateway. It crosses a small brook running over a ledge, and soon the grade becomes almost level as the trail contours around the north slope of Mt. Eisenhower, affording excellent views out through a fringe of trees. It breaks into the open, crosses the nose of a ridge on a footway paved with carefully placed stones, and reaches the Mt. Eisenhower Loop a few yards from the Crawford Path. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Eisenhower Loop &lt;br /&gt; entering alpine zone &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.38 mi/11 min/+330 ft on the Mt Eisenhower Loop &lt;br /&gt; It passes through a grassy sag just to the right of Red Pond and then ascends moderately from a ledge overlooking Red Pond. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Eisenhower &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 3.28 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 2 hr 53 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2826 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -91 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2735 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.38 mi/11 min/-330 ft on the Mt Eisenhower Loop &lt;br /&gt; From there, it descends moderately to a ledge overlooking Red Pond, then drops steeply over ledges, passes through a grassy sag just to the left of Red Pond. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Edmands Path &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+5 ft on the Mt Eisenhower Loop &lt;br /&gt; It finally climbs briefly to a junction on the left with the Edmands Path to rejoin the Crawford Path on a small, rocky knob. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+24 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Edmands Path can be reached from this junction by following the Mt. Eisenhower Loop for a short distance. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Eisenhower Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.20 mi/56 min/+595 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Mt. Eisenhower Trail from the Dry River valley enters right. The Crawford Path then begins the ascent of the shoulder called Mt. Franklin, first moderately, then steeply for a short distance near the top. The trail reaches the relatively level shoulder and continues past an unmarked path on the right that leads in 130 yd. to the barely noticeable summit of Mt. Franklin, from which there are excellent views, particularly into Oakes Gulf. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Monroe Loop &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.70 mi/26 min/+14 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Mt. Monroe Loop diverges left to cross both summits of Monroe, affording excellent views. It is about the same length as the parallel section of the Crawford Path but requires about 350 ft. more climbing. The Crawford Path is safer in inclement conditions because it is much less exposed to the weather. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Monroe Loop &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.10 mi/3 min/-45 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Mt. Monroe Loop rejoins on the left, and the Crawford Path continues along the edge of the precipice that forms the northwest wall of Oakes Gulf, then follows a relocated section.  It then descends easily to Lakes of the Clouds Hut. &lt;br /&gt; to AMC Lakes of the Clouds Hut &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+1 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Ammonoosuc Ravine Trail enters on the left at the corner of the hut, and in another 30 yd., the Dry River Trail enters on the right. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Dry River Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.15 mi/7 min/+89 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Crawford Path crosses the outlet of the larger lake and passes between it and the second lake, and in a short distance the Camel Trail to Boott Spur and the Tuckerman Crossover to Tuckerman Ravine diverge right at the same point. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Camel Trail and Tuckerman Crossover &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.71 mi/36 min/+489 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Crawford Path then ascends moderately on the northwest side of the ridge, always some distance below the crest. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Davis Path &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.02 mi/1 min/+21 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; The Davis Path, which has been following the original, less sheltered location of the Crawford Path, enters on the right, at the foot of the cone of Mt. Washington. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Westside Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/28 min/+524 ft on the Crawford Path &lt;br /&gt; In another 50 yd., the Westside Trail, a shortcut to the Northern Peaks, diverges left. The Crawford Path runs generally north, switching back and forth as it climbs the steep cone through a trench in the rocks. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.10 mi/5 min/-52 ft on the Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; Descending from the summit of Mt. Washington, the Gulfside Trail diverges right from the Crawford Path. The trail is on the right (west) side of the railroad track. After passing between the buildings, it leads generally northwest; avoid random side paths toward the south. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Trinity Heights Connector &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/6 min/+182 ft on the Trinity Heights Connector &lt;br /&gt; From the Gulfside Trail, just north of that trail's junction with the Crawford Path, the path runs approximately southeast over the rocks to the true summit (marked by a large sign). &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Washington &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 7.48 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 6 hr 2 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +5078 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -825 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +4253 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.20 mi/6 min/-182 ft on the Trinity Heights Connector &lt;br /&gt; From the true summit (marked by a large sign), the path runs approximately northwest over the rocks to the Gulfside Trail, north of its junction with the Crawford Path. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/11 min/-176 ft on the Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; Th trail crosses the railroad and turns sharp left. It passes a junction with the Trinity Heights Connector, a link in the AT, which branches right and climbs for to the true summit of Mt. Washington. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Great Gulf Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.50 mi/28 min/-420 ft on the Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; As the Gulfside Trail turns sharp left at the extreme south corner of the Great Gulf, the Great Gulf Trail departs on the right. The trail heads northwest, between the Cog Railway on the left and the edge  of the gulf on the right. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Westside Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.10 mi/6 min/-112 ft on the Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Gulfside descends gradually to a point near the Clay-Washington col (5,391 ft.), where the Mt. Clay Loop diverges right to traverse the summits of Mt. Clay. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Clay Loop &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.30 mi/11 min/+12 ft on the Gulfside Trail &lt;br /&gt; After a slight ascent, the Gulfside begins to angle down the west side of Mt. Clay, and the Jewell Trail from the Cog Railway Base Rd. enters from the left. From this junction, the ridge crest of Mt. Clay can be reached by a short scramble up the rocks without a trail. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Jewell Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 2.70 mi/2 hr 38 min/-2511 ft on the Jewell Trail &lt;br /&gt; From the Gulfside Trail, the Jewell Trail angles down the slope at an easy grade to what remains of the ridge. It continues down the slope of Mt. Clay at a moderate grade with rough, rocky footing before it connects with and zigzags down the ridge crest. It reaches the trees and descends west, staying well below the ridge crest. Then it passes through a blowdown patch at the edge of the steep wall of Burt Ravine, where there are interesting though limited views. It then descends southwest by long switchbacks. It crosses Clay Brook on a footbridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 11.48 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 9 hr 42 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +5238 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -4374 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +864 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here leaving alpine zone &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.60 mi/29 min/-356 ft on the Jewell Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Jewell Trail descends the crest of the low ridge between the Ammonoosuc River and Clay Brook, joining the old route of the trail. The old path (sign) can be followed left, to the Base Station. The Boundary Line Trail diverges right. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Boundary Line Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/15 min/-60 ft on the Jewell Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Jewell Trail descends at an easy grade, crosses the Ammonoosuc River, then leaves the woods directly across the road from the parking area. &lt;br /&gt; to Jewell Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 12.48 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 10 hr 26 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +5283 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -4834 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +449 ft &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280168494000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277746618000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EDMANDS PATH TO MT WASHINGTON &amp; EVERYTHING IN BETWEEN</name><id>13937023</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279971900000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13937023/</event_url></item>