<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for the late update, I should have done this a few days ago...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I now know the movie time. The movie is at 7:00. I'll be at the movie theater at 6:30. We'll be watching Kung Fu Pand in the digital projection room, that will be interesting. I recommend buying your tickets ahead of time on fandango.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be waiting by the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where the tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand. I'll be at the theater by 6:30 and we'll head into the theater 10 minutes before showtime, a.k.a. 6:50.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Woohoo! I love animated films; I love kung fu films; and here we have a combination! Genius! I do, however, hate the &amp;quot;chosen one&amp;quot; plot device, sigh, it's so stale and boring, but I'll deal with it for cartoon animals who are masters of a martial art!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also gather outside the theater where the movie showed so we can go together to a local resteraunt. Be sure to let someone know if you want to come out with the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Synopsis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Kung Fu Panda&amp;quot; features Jack Black as Po the Panda, a lowly waiter in a noodle restaurant, who is a kung fu fanatic but whose shape doesn't exactly lend itself to kung fu fighting. In fact, Po's defining characteristic appears to be that he is the laziest of all the animals in ancient China. That's a problem because powerful enemies are at the gates, and all hopes have been pinned on a prophesy naming Po as the &amp;quot;Chosen One&amp;quot; to save the day. A group of martial arts masters are going to need a black belt in patience if they are going to turn this slacker panda into a kung fu fighter before it's too late!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Website&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kungfupanda.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kungfupanda.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kungfupand...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;object width=&amp;quot;425&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;355&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;embed src=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/v/RR4TIYEAmIk&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;quot;" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; type=&amp;quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;425&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;355&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/embed&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/object&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie is upstairs, I'll be waiting by the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where the tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214356081000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207613373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kung Fu Panda</name><id>7695146</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212791400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7695146/</event_url></item>