<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Roger's Campground Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03584</zip><lat>44.468475</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>roger's campground</name><city>Lancaster</city><id>7193192</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.544678</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Note: This is a week long Liberty festival held by the Free State Project in New Hampshire. It starts the 18th of June, but the last weekend is when many arrive. We are planning a caravan / road trip for those interested in going that will leave Friday. Please stay tuned, this meetup will be updated as details are solidified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who • What • When • Where • Why • How&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHO:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone that wants to come, but particularly those that love freedom and indiviudal liberty, and more specifically those that have signed the Free State Project statement of intent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHAT:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Porcupine Freedom Festival (aka PorcFest) sponsored by the Free State Project will occur in Lancaster, NH for the entire week of Monday, June 18, 2012 through Sunday, June 24, 2012. Come to learn about the FSP, efforts for liberty, and the future of freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest is a week full of fun and excitement for freedom lovers of all ages. As previous PorcFest attendees have said, there’s simply not enough time to do every fun activity… you’ll just have to come back next year! This year, every day will have a theme. Tuesday will be dedicated to Learning About NH and the FSP. Wednesday will feature events about the arts. Thursday and Friday will be dedicated to music and comedy. Saturday will be about Family Fun. Don't worry if you can't be there every day. All week there will be educational seminars, forums, speakers and a wide array of events to suit all tastes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest will feature an entire section of the campground dedicated to kids and family fun! All kids are invited to participate in daily crafts and activities like games and mixers. The fun filled week will culminate in a Family Day, which will be full of activities for all ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest has a full array of firearms events for seasoned gun enthusiasts and newbie shooters alike: there will be an Appleseed marksman’s training, basic firearms etiquette and safety classes, seminars about firearms and the law, and even ammunition reloading for more experienced shooters!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PorcFest features the famous Soapbox Idol, a contest where participants can perform their own unique rants on whatever topic they deem worth ranting about! You, the audience, can help judge whose rant rocks the hardest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and shake your groove thing on the dance floor at Buzz’s Big Gay Dance Party! There will be other mixers and parties throughout the week as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best speakers in the liberty movement will be lending their ideas to PorcFest attendees all day. Big names so far include economist Bob Murphy, secesionist Bill Buppert, Freedom's Phoenix, and New Hampshire's own Free Talk Live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the highlights of PorcFest will be Agora Valley, where vendors will serve the needs of PorcFest attendees in a radically free-market way! Buy, sell, trade, and learn about agorism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While you're being catered to by all of the great Agora Valley vendors, be sure not to eat too much. You'll want to sample the dozens of dishes at the Liberty Ladies’ 6th Annual One Pot Cook-off! Maybe you’d like to enter – there will be prizes for the best dish – but equally rewarding is being a One Pot Cook-off judge! Sign up for this when you register.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional activities include a pig roast featuring hogs from a Free Stater homestead, an ice cream social, pool and pizza party, live broadcasts of liberty-centric media, and lots more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHEN:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;June 18-24th, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHERE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roger's Campground in Lancaster, NH. Go to www.rogerscampground.com to book your campsite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHY:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Free State has been chosen and each year the Porcupines of the Free State Project meet there to show our spines. ALL who support the FSP and our goals should come to meet, mingle, befriend, and plan&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340047682000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337875683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Porcfest 2012, the Porcupine Freedom Festival </name><id>66168942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340035200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/66168942/</event_url></item>