<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 U.S. 4</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03748</zip><lat>43.644657</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mickey Roadside Cafe</name><city>Enfield</city><id>8068772</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.142227</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This weekend has good weather and we are blessed with many trails to hike and to repair. I am leaving the choice of activity to those who sign up. Each day begins with meeting for breakfast at 8:30. &lt;br /&gt;

 If trailwork, we work on the west side of Mt Cardigan with less than a mile hike to the jobsite. We reset old woodwork on the West Ridge Trail then descend and add more drains and rock steps on South Ridge Trail. Not huge rocks, and anyone who can hike can learn to set them correctly using simple tools to gain mechanical advantage. The result is a dryer and more stable trail, plus the satisfaction of knowing you made the improvement. BYO work gloves, tools and dark chocolate supplied. &lt;br /&gt;

 Hiking would be a section hike on the Appalachian Trail in NH, leaving a car at each end. The best candidates are Moose Mtn, Smarts Mtn, and Mt Cube. Each has a slightly different height and length, but all have some kind of view. Did I forget to mention the dark chocolate? &lt;br /&gt;

 These days we'll arrange via the comments allowed on this page. I am doing these days alone if that is how it turns out, but company makes them much better.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341829518000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341493506000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>hike or trailwork, your choice</name><id>72036842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341664200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/72036842/</event_url></item>