<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;MICHAEL SHELLENBERGER&lt;br /&gt;and &lt;br /&gt;TED NORDHAUS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;discuss&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Break Through: Why We Can't Leave &lt;br /&gt;Saving the Planet to Environmentalists&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge Forum is pleased to welcome MICHAEL SHELLENBERGER and TED NORDHAUS for a discussion of their newly co-authored book, Break Through: Why We Can't Leave Saving the Planet to Environmentalists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nordhaus and Shellenberger triggered a firestorm with the publication of Break Through, contending that the politics that dealt with acid rain and smog can’t deal with global warming. The nations that ratified the Kyoto protocol have seen their greenhouse gas emissions go up, not down. And the destruction of tropical rain forests, a key driver of global warming, has accelerated. What today’s ecological crises demand, say the authors, is not that we constrain human power but rather unleash it. We must go beyond interest group environmentalism and liberalism to create a politics focused as much on uncommon greatness as on the common good. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“To win, Nordhaus and Shellenberger persuasively argue, environmentalists must stop congratulating themselves for their own willingness to confront inconvenient truths and must focus on building a politics of shared hope rather than relying on a politics of fear.” —The New York Times Book Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Smart...not least because it would allow greens to frame climate change as an inspiring challenge, not just a pending catastrophe. And that's a contrarian position that just might help win the climate wars.&amp;quot; —Time  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Green groups may carp, but the truth is the book could turn out to be the best thing to happen to environmentalism since Rachel Carson's Silent Spring.&amp;quot; —Wired &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Their overall message - the enviros 'must choose between a resentful narrative of tragedy and a grateful narrative of overcoming'--will resonate with even dedicated tree huggers.&amp;quot; —Outside Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[Break Through] is unremittingly interesting, sharp, and wide-ranging, and it provides a great deal fo thoughtful comment for anyone trying to figure out how to rally public support behind action on climate change, or indeed behind any progressive change.&amp;quot; —Bill McKibben, The New York Review of Books&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242347304000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240253223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Environmentalism</name><id>10227241</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241652600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/10227241/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/7/global_6176535.jpeg</photo_url></item>