<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A famous comedian has a near-death experience&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George is a very successful stand up comedian who learns that he has an untreatable blood disorder and is given less than a year to live. Ira is a struggling up-and-coming stand up comedian who works at a deli and has yet to figure out his onstage persona. One night, these two perform at the same club and George takes notice of Ira. George hires Ira to be his semi-personal assistant as well as his friend&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the past few years, writer/director Judd Apatow (The 40-Year-Old Virgin, Knocked Up) has shown that nothingnot even losing your virginity or the miracle of childbirthis sacred. About his third film behind the camera, he says, Im trying to make a very serious movie that is twice as funny as my other movies. Wish me luck! Apatow directs Adam Sandler, Seth Rogen and Leslie Mann in Funny People, the story of a famous comedian who has a near-death experience. Adam Sandler, Eric Bana, Jason Schwartzman, RZA and newcomer Aubrey Plaza join a cast that reunites Judd Apatow with Seth Rogen, Leslie Mann and Jonah Hill in their third comedy together. [Official Universal / Columbia Synopsis] [D-Man2010]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y-oGqZBWQ9Y" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253874647000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248459404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Funny People</name><id>10950219</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249171200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/10950219/</event_url></item>