<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>DATE CHANGE due to the fact that the first Sunday of the month will be over Labor Day weekend, and many of you will more than likely be drinking Mud Slides and throwing down Clam Rolls in some sandy town on Cape Cod. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last month, we continued talking about Chapter 1 in &amp;quot;Objectivism, the Philosophy of Ayn Rand.&amp;quot;  I printed out copies of the O.P.A.R. study guide so that people could look at the questions being discussed.  If you have a book or a study guide, feel free to bring it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My goal for this meet-up group is to provide a venue through which we can better understand Objectivism and meet others who share the same interest.  As our group has evolved from a semi-Objectivism-focused gathering of interesting people engaging in directionless coffee-talk, we've gained a real focus and are having some very interesting dialog (or is it &amp;quot;dialogue&amp;quot;?)  My main goal nowadays is to keep the group focused on the topic at hand and not allow a tangential discussion to take on a life of its own.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you've never been to our meet-up (or even if you came last fall when we were still finding our way), come (back) and give our group a try.  I think you'll find it to be a productive and enjoyable use of your time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll hope to see you the SECOND Sunday of September, Sept. 10th, from 5PM to no later than 7PM in the basement of Starbucks on Boylston at Berkeley!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have to pay meetup.com $19.00 per month to use their site, but for me, this is a small price to pay for the opportunity to meet other people interested in Objectivism, the philosophy of Ayn Rand.  However, if anyone would be willing to donate a dollar or two to help me defray the monthly expenditure, that would be great.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>2499401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540431000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1154902073000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Ayn Rand September Meetup</name><id>5064333</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1157922000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/5064333/</event_url></item>