<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Red Sox Natives Mindy&amp;nbsp;and Craig&amp;nbsp;will be running this years Run To Home Base race. Please consider donating to help&amp;nbsp;them reach their $1,000.00 fund raising goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All Natives are invited to come out and cheer Mindy and Craig before, durring and after the race. At the conclusion of the race supporters who are inside Fenway Park will be allowed on to the field to walk the Warning Track and take photographs. It was a blast last year! THIS WILL TAKE PLACE SUBJECT TO THE DISCRETION OF THE RED SOX MANAGEMENT AND WEATHER AND PLAYING FIELD CONDITIONS!&amp;nbsp;Please RSVP if you would like to attend. Time is approximate but all should plan on being inside Fenway Park at 10 am. Race begins at 8 am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year our own Native Pinch Runner Lindsay ran the Run to Home Base road race in support of local servicemen and women returning from combat in Iraq and Afghanistan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Run to Home Base is a 9K race organized by the Red Sox Foundation  &lt;br /&gt;and Massachusetts General Hospital. The funds raised will go toward the  &lt;br /&gt;Home Base Program, a philanthropic partnership that is dedicated to  &lt;br /&gt;improving the lives of New England servicemen and women returning home  &lt;br /&gt;with combat stress disorders through clinical care, innovative research,  &lt;br /&gt;education, family support, and community outreach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This cause means a lot to many of us who know family and friends with men and and women that have willingly signed up to fight overseas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the race on the website:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;OFFICIAL WEBSITE HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To donate, go to the home page, &lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.runtohomebase.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.runtohomeb...&lt;/a&gt; and click on Support a Runner. Type in the first and last name&amp;nbsp;in lower case letters and hit the search button; that will bring you to another page where you can click on the name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the next page, click on Make A Donation and follow the prompts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The deadline to donate is Friday, May 14.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fenway Frank&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post Script: Last year Lindsay did the math; 9 kilometers around home base equals  &lt;br /&gt;80.7 home runs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Event takes place at discretion of Red Sox and weather. We will not know until day of event. Meet in Section 18 Box Seats while the race is on-going. Meet at the Pesky Pole after the race to enter the field weather and Red Sox permitting.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>3178870</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig </member_name><member_id>14417422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306210143000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><why>It is your chance to support a good cause and be on the Fenway Park field.</why><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303733944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk Fenway Park Warning Track With Mindy &amp; Craig after The Run to Home BaseRace</name><id>17422246</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306076400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/17422246/</event_url></item>