<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;a striking micromasterpiece... utterly, wonderfully unique&amp;quot;  Austin Chronicle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're looking for a B-movie monster mayhem adventure, I'm afraid you've come to the wrong place. There's no city-stomping here. In fact. &lt;b&gt;Beetle Queen Conquers Tokyo&lt;/b&gt; is a film notable for its stillness, its gentleness, its contemplative mood. Yet its title is entirely apt, as its subject is an integral part of Japanese culture with its origins in the same place as those much-loved monster movies. This evocative documentary explores the island nation's fascination with insects and, through this, the Japanese character itself.Japan's love of insects, we are told, is partly rooted in the artistic notion of mono no aware, the appreciation of, or oneness with, nature that needs no intermediary, not even words. The film itself relates to this tradition and is often wordless, presenting us with moments of visual splendour, long passages of stillness in which we watch the way raindrops fall into a lake. We skip between places, styles, even types of film with little explanation, but it doesn't matter. There is no simple linear narrative. Beetle Queen is more like a poem, combining fragments of experience to show us something much more than the sum of its parts.Extraordinarily beautiful and certainly very different from other films you're likely to see this year, Beetle Queen Conquers Tokyo captures a whole world in the buzz of crickets, in the beating of delicate wings.  Eye For Film&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to the trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.beetlequeen.com/video.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beetlequee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Beetle Queen Conquers Tokyo&lt;/b&gt; is as much about the people who see the bugs, as the bugs themselves. I’m a huge fan of Japanese film, and Oreck, an American, has created a picture that is intriguingly Japanese in its sensibilities. There are images of sublime and staggering beauty as the camera captures the air, the earth and the mountains of Japan. Each person who wanders in and out of the frame posesses a unique voice and without too much posturing on the part of the filmmakers these characters get the films’ main themes across; that a life lived close to nature offers more than one without it. Whether or not you agree with the sentiment, Beetle Queen makes a compelling argument for it. Cinematropolis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After this  early Saturday screening we'll stroll down Huntington Ave to the outdoor dining area near Northeastern Univ for our group discussion. First person who mentions Godzilla or Mothra picks up the tab.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Red Meetup sign near the front of the theater after the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273108569000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beetle Queen Conquers Tokyo</name><id>13399275</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276354800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13399275/</event_url></item>