<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Coolidge is proud to be one of 12 independent theaters from around the nation to participate in its &amp;quot;Art House Project.&amp;quot; In honor of the Sundance Film Festival's return this month (Jan 17-27 in Park City, Utah), the Coolidge presents a specially curated program of shorts from the 2007 festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. DEATH TO THE TIN MAN&lt;br /&gt;How the Oz tin woodsman lost his limbs and his lover, and how he tried to get his life back. Winner of an Honorable Mention in Short Filmmaking. dir. Ray Tintori. USA, 2006, 12 min, b/w&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. PEACE TALK&lt;br /&gt;Little Jonna and her friend Emilie play at being soldiers, but Jonna?s mother doesn?t approve of the course their game takes. dir. Jenifer Malmqvist, in Swedish with English subtitles. Sweden, 2006, 14 min, color&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. KING&lt;br /&gt;The older woman in apartment 3B has unusual plans. dir. Caran Hartsfield. USA, 2006, 16 min, color&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. SALT KISS&lt;br /&gt;On a secluded island off Rio, the carefree 45?year?old Rogério struggles to bring his recently engaged best friend back to the good life. dir. Fellipe Gamarano Barbosa, in Portuguese with English subtitles. Brazil, 2006, 18 min, color&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. GOD PROVIDES&lt;br /&gt;A look at the varied and unexpected responses to natural disaster. dirs. Brian Cassidy, Melanie Shatzky. USA/Canada, 2006, 9 min, color&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. EVERYTHING WILL BE OK&lt;br /&gt;A series of dark and troubling events force Bill to reckon with the meaning of life?or lack thereof. Winner of the Jury Prize in Short Filmmaking. dir. Don Hertzfeldt. USA, 2006, 17 min, color &amp;amp; b/w&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. HAPPINESS&lt;br /&gt;One evening after work, a female factory worker buys a box of happiness in a strange discount store and has to decide what to do with it. dir. Sophie Barthes. USA, 2006, 11 min, color&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total runtime: 1h37m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;purchase tickets in advance as this is likely to be shown in the short theater with the DVD player behind the door: &lt;a href="https://www.readyticket.net/webticket/webticket2.asp?WCI=BuyTicket&amp;amp;WCE=2007+SUNDANCE+SHORTS,012420081900,4,130" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.readytick...&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be the short guy at the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Our humor and fun never run short.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200661845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2007 SUNDANCE SHORTS PROGRAM</name><id>7143594</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201219200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7143594/</event_url></item>