<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>488 Farmington Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.766624</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BRAZAS</name><city>Hartford</city><id>664310</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.707690</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Churrascaria (choo-rah-scah-REE-ah) is the name used to describe a restaurant that serves meat, mostly grilled, and Rodizio is a method of serving the different cuts of meat that originated in the south of Brazil in the early 1800's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concept is to serve a wide variety of different cuts of beef, pork, lamb, chicken, etc., in succession, to each diner individually right at their table, thus there is not a traditional menu. The restaurant features a fixed-price continuous tableside service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Churrascria Braza is a dining experience like no other. Sit back, relax and enjoy the truly unique steakhouse atmosphere from Rio Grande do Sul in Southern Brazil.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The featured meats are seasoned to perfection and slow-roasted over an open flame to capture their individual flavor. The savory cuts are presented on skewers and carved tableside by our authentic Gaucho chefs, at the guests' request.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant is under new ownership and our gracious host, Julio (new owner), promises a most sensational dining experience...so let's give it a try!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julio has also told me he is bringing in Latin musicians on Friday and Saturday evenings. So let's enjoy the experience...Latin style!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can join us!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the table with the hungry people and the meetup sign! Or ask for reservation "Meetup/Terri"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250899088000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248141310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Anyone for Brazilian Tonght?     Churrascaria  Braza in Hartford!!!</name><id>10920529</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250290800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/10920529/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/d/7/global_9784823.jpeg</photo_url></item>