<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>276 Edmands Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.330697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-405-1686</phone><name>Ann and Mark's home</name><city>Framingham</city><id>972696</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our gift to you, your family and friends, and the community:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A FREE Class on Meditation Can Be Easy!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Wednesday evening, July 14th, 7:15 – 8:45 pm&lt;br /&gt;276 Edmands Rd., Framingham, MA 01701 (our home)&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Are you aware of the benefits of meditating, but can’t get yourself to do it, or it seems too difficult?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• &lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Research proves that meditation can reduce your stress, inflammations and pain, blood pressure and risk of heart disease; and it reverses aging.  &lt;br /&gt;• It can increase your creativity and mental abilities, focus and concentration, ability to heal, and your general health and longevity.  &lt;br /&gt;• It can also relieve anxiety and emotional problems, help you make better decisions, and give you improved mood stability.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;And, it's a great way to set or shift into the perfect &amp;quot;allowing&amp;quot; mood for your day, feeling perfectly aligned with all that you desire.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The list goes on, but would any one of these be reason enough to give it a try?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;In sum, meditation can be one of the easiest and most effective means to living with greater harmony, happiness and well-being.   It’s an opportunity to &lt;b&gt;peacefully transform your problems, your fears, and any pain and stress in your life into something more positive.  And, you don’t have to sit in silence for long periods of time to gain the multitude of emotional and physical benefits!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come to experience how simple and delightful meditation can be.  You’ll learn:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Some simple techniques you can do for yourself for any length of time that is comfortable for you.&lt;br /&gt;• How to easily get into and maintain a meditative state and create pleasurable feelings.&lt;br /&gt;• Tips and techniques to help you succeed at meditating, as well as how to use mental rehearsal for improving performance and to influence how you will behave and respond in future situations.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will not be doing traditional silent meditations.  The class will consist of 2-3 guided meditations.  All you have to do is let go and listen to the facilitator’s voice as she leads you through the process, like listening to a good story.       &lt;/b&gt;                                &lt;/span&gt;                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;The meditations will leave you totally relaxed with &lt;b&gt;magnificent feelings of peace, love, happiness and hope- essentially feeling really, really good!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;All are welcome! &lt;/b&gt; Please share this with your e-mail lists and groups, your friends, and your family!  It's a wonderful evening - like going on a mini retreat!  &lt;b&gt;Registration is required by either rsvp'ing on our meetup site or e-mailing your name, e-mail and phone # to AnnIde@NewPossibilitiesCoaching.com.   You’ll receive confirmation, instructions and a reminder.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;“I have never meditated before. It has always been hard for me to get difficult thoughts out of my head.  Tonight I really relaxed and seemed to go into another world.  It was great.  Thanks!”  Susy C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Your meditation showed how easy it can be to focus – something I usually think of as an effort.  Thanks, it was very nice!”  John H.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I generally struggle with being in a quiet space and being present; but tonight’s class helped me channel positive energy and feel good about who I am.”  Michele G.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Class leader:  Ann Ide is a certified Master level NLP Practitioner, Trainer, and NLP Life Coach with over 15 years experience. She has trained and consulted people nationally.  Her passion is helping people move beyond suffering and mere survival, and creating “New Possibilities” in their lives for greater harmony, happiness and success. She provides personal and group coaching, guided meditations, and business workshops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For important parking instructions, go to our files page, under the &amp;quot;More&amp;quot; link at top of meetup page.  Thank you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're down a very long driveway, with white mailbox at street end.  Please check files for further important instructions.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279206237000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276799157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Meditation Can Be Easy Class</name><id>13831961</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279149300000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/13831961/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>