<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SATURDAY IS LOOKING LIKE A PRETTY GOOD DAY SO FAR !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Sunny, with a high near 65. &amp;lt;~~~~BRING A LIGHT PADDLING JACKET&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and some warm comfortable clothes for Barbie-Q..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, Most Events are planned for Saturday but Sunday is the back up day in the event of bad weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of you know this is a very unique location. For those of you that have not been here, well i am not telling you anything about it !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WEATHER for this location:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Close up view:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/northeast_loop.php"&gt;http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/northeast_loop.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prediction:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KCEF&amp;amp;state=MA"&gt;http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KCEF&amp;amp;state=MA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;National View:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/index_loop.php"&gt;http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/index_loop.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are worried about how many miles any trip is, (Then its too many for you), if you are worried about how much time the event will take away from your precious day, (Then its too Long for you) , but if you are interested and find the events to be a&amp;nbsp;Meaningful&amp;nbsp;Challenge or a Physical and Mental REWARD, Then it may be a too short of an event making you want more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(No events are recommended for Complainers or Wimps ! That includes the ones where we just go to eat and relax.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do not like to give the miles or time because i do not know, its not like a hiking trail at a set speed,&amp;nbsp;We set our own courses, stop in places, vary our speed, and deal with the tide, current, wind, or even the waves. When its time to eat, then its "Head em Up, Movem Out", and Wishbone will be readying up the Chuck Wagon for us with some sizzeling meat cooked nice and tasty with a few drops of&amp;nbsp;Whiskey !..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SOURCE of this river must be a very special one, maybe it has a Mysterious COLD &amp;nbsp; Spring ????&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/d/d/event_32508861.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very popular spot for many reasons - one that you will see yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;YOU MAY HAVE TO BE CREATIVE IN&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;PARKING HERE..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IF THE PARKING LOT IS FULL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;YOU MAY HAVE TO DROP OFF AT THE RAMP AND PARK AT AN ADJACENT STREET, ie River rd or East st..etc.....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;i have faith in your ability to be creative and find a solution if its actually needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The River is a low current FLAT water river,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;the only fast part is upstream spot where we have to turn around and maybe have to cross a tree or 2..etc...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This upstream spot is our stop destination, then its head to the Dam via a diversion into a hidden cove.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(wimps and complainers can get out at the starting spot as we pass by).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a perfect river for a "Recreational Yak" &amp;nbsp;and your "ocean&amp;nbsp;cruisers"&amp;nbsp;(you will learn some turning techniques here which you will need on the ocean anyway).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its more of a sight seeing river and a place to enjoy slowly and&amp;nbsp;deliberately, no need to&amp;nbsp;paddle&amp;nbsp;fast here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~&amp;gt; Yes i know what the real name of the river is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, so i call it "Cold Spring River" &amp;nbsp;(The name of the street of the put in spot).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet and start to paddle around 11:15 am or so, If you are late, paddle upstream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind the drive time to the site..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group pot luck after party will be "On Site" or at the RES, we will decide as we finish up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember No Barbie-Q flames at the RES..&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;BUT we can get away with it "On Site".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The grill will be loaded anyway. I plan to bring some special meat this time that we have not had for some time, (no fish guts or chicken parts)... its either Porkupine or Lion of some kind, maybe even Wild Turk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I going "Safari Hunting" Friday on the way home from work so its what ever i Bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The River Exploration starts (Left) "Upstream" from the boat ramp till we can't go any more in the WILD Jungle Environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the way up take some pics, you will SEE why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then on the downstream return trip, go past &amp;nbsp;the boat ramp and head down stream to the opening for the coves and, islands, from there its exit to the Dam..etc..&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a shore area for snacks near the dam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barbie-Q or Picnic after we return and after&amp;nbsp;loading&amp;nbsp;up till its time to go home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Please join us for our SUNDAY relaxing event at Hurt Park if you can.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_____________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GETTING THERE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use your GPS: 525 Cold Spring Rd Belchertown, MA 01007&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or cross check some of your mapquest directions and look at your maps to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Hartford, CT: Please use the directions that follow only for a guide to your own specific directions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be aware there may be bridge work in certain areas or damage from the recent storm.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Merge onto I-91 N toward Springfield- 25.9 mi Just North of Springfield city&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take exit x???? for I-291 E/US-20 EAST toward I-90/Mass.Pike EAST&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;go 0.2 mi follow signs for I-291 East and merge onto I-291 EAST/US-20 East&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continue to follow I-291 EAST for 5.0 mi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the I-90 EAST/I-90 W exit toward Masspike/Boston/Albany 0.3 mi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Merge onto I-90 EAST toward Boston Direction and go apx 11.5 mi Take exit 8 toward MA-32/US-20/Palmer/Ware 0.3 mi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Merge onto Palmer Ware Partial toll road Once under the Mass Pike bridge,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;take a left onto HIGH st for 0.4 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep Right onto CHURCH st then take RIVER st for 1.4 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a left onto STATE st go apx 0.7 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bear Right onto JIM ASS st for 1.1 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep strait on and Continue onto Bondsville Rd for 1.5 mi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn left at Cold Spring Rd and go apx 0.1 miles or over bridge and turn left into the parking lot,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park so we can all fit... This is a small lot with apx 30 spaces max and its a popular spot so park where you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(The other alt route is I-84 to Stafford Springs and up 32..etc..)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OR Just follow your GPS: and maps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayaks available: PLEASE CHOOSE THE ONE YOU FIT IN OR CAN HANDLE and indicate that in your RSVP area, i find keeping track via the comments on the bottom of the event or e mail to be very difficult since i get so many of them bout all kind of requests and it does not reflect changes in RSVP'ees..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please understand i can only carry 7 total and prefer to have enough for those that reserved and also not to have any sitting un supervised in the parking lot or left on the boat ramp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;ANY of MY KAYAKS need to be reserved prior to me leaving for the PADDLE SITE preferably by the night prior to or the event: (i may not get a chance to check MEETUP.COM in the morning of the event and there is the pre-travel time..etc for me to get busy with).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yes its a STRAPPING &amp;amp; WAPPING&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;**&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;$20.00**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;PER FULL DAY for kayak types, brands and special equipment you simply can not get from any other source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(This is really a donation i do need to maintain, repair, and add new equipment over time. it also covers the costs of the "Decent Quality" boats with&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;all the Special Accessories&amp;nbsp;including the transportation to and from the site, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Or you can rent the DURABLE Plastic ones they have at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.cckstore.com/rentals/rentals.htm"&gt;http://www.cckstore.com/rentals/rentals.htm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(or where ever else you get them) for a $50+ price range and you get to clean and load-unload them yourself on your own car if my yaks are not OK for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you have a lot of money, a junky car that ya don't care if the roof caves in a bit, and think that dragging some Hunk of plastic on the rough tar all the way down the boat ramp to the water is how you portage to the water, oh i forgot..if you &amp;nbsp;stand on the floor to get in and moving your fat azz back and forth on the plastic seat like you are scraping off your hemmeroids till you finally get to and in the water is how experts do it, then ya better rent from Collinsville or someone else.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 I have some cheap life jackets and some GOOD ones, (Remember a decent life jacket should be a top quality one, its really a form of cheap life insurance so you can enjoy your life in the long run).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Everyone's&amp;nbsp;favourite is the Medium Kokatat* Ladies MsFit Tour: (this is also purchased by guys since it has a great fit and versatility) Its really too small for me, but i like the way it works and feels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many ladies in the group have tried this one and now own the exact model also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/product/751058" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.rei.com/product/751058&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;amp; &amp;nbsp;another TWO i chose for me and you is : &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.watersports.co/womens-kayak-life-vests/c1000001793/stohlquist-towmotion-womens-kayak-life-jacket-2010-p219446.html"&gt;http://www.watersports.co/womens-kayak-life-vests/c1000001793/stohlquist-towmotion-womens-kayak-life-jacket-2010-p219446.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.backcountry.com/kokatat-outfit-tour-personal-flotation-device?CMP_SKU=KOK0096&amp;amp;MER=0406&amp;amp;CMP_ID=SH_FRO001&amp;amp;mv_pc=r126&amp;amp;mr:trackingCode=78A4AEC8-8E50-E011-9324-0019B9C043EB&amp;amp;mr:referralID=NA"&gt;http://www.backcountry.com/kokatat-outfit-tour-personal-flotation-device?CMP_SKU=KOK0096&amp;amp;MER=0406&amp;amp;CMP_ID=SH_FRO001&amp;amp;mv_pc=r126&amp;amp;mr:trackingCode=78A4AEC8-8E50-E011-9324-0019B9C043EB&amp;amp;mr:referralID=NA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When using my boats you have to wear the life jacket, i can not be responsible for your stupidity if you don't since its common knowledge to practice safety in this and&amp;nbsp;ALL OTHER paddling groups since the unexpected happens too often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Besides, i spent over $100 on some of these jackets for your safety, don't stuff the life jacket in the back somewhere by your azz.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;I want to see your head above the water and that other part of your body can stay hidden down in the water.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;I don't think you want me to take a picture of only your azz bobbing up and down with a life jacket floating by it for your funeral, the picture may say something in a unflattering way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;####&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 All my yaks come with the TOP RATED Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles because they are Hollow and light (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths (220-230) and types (strait, or ergonomic bent, small and normal shaft dia's.)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 You choose your preference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; ####&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also for comfort is my favourite "Yak Pad's" optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; ####&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed for quick and easy access:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;PLEASE read some of the information on the hyperlinks below for the kayak specs and then INDICATE WHICH KAYAK YOU FIT IN AND OR CAN HANDLE in your RSVP if you need one of the following Yaks:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;( I will do what i can to SUGGEST WHICH ONE IF NEEDED based on your physical size and skills if you are not sure).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #1&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Eddyline Wind Dancer Fiberglass/Kevlar, Red, Rudder Equipped 18' @ 24" wide. This is an older&amp;nbsp;expedition&amp;nbsp;style sea kayak designed for rough sea conditions and heavy loads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) &amp;nbsp;Sea kayak of moderate weight (52 LB).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with beginner and up skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;------- &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RESERVED FOR FELICIA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #2&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped 15'-3.5'' @ 22"wide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (49 LB) ladies kayak&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is the heavier model and largest cockpit of the Eliza series. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.frontenac-outfitters.com/kayaks/one_boat.cfm?ID=706"&gt;http://www.frontenac-outfitters.com/kayaks/one_boat.cfm?ID=706&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;---&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;--- &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #00ff00"&gt;AVAILABLE&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; ****&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;THIS KAYAK IS &amp;nbsp;FOR SALE&lt;/span&gt;****&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #3&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Necky Eliza Advanced Composite (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version 15'-3'' @ 21" wide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (45 LB) Ladies Kayak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is the medium size cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.frontenac-outfitters.com/kayaks/one_boat.cfm?ID=702"&gt;http://www.frontenac-outfitters.com/kayaks/one_boat.cfm?ID=702&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;--- --- &amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RESERVED FOR KAREN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #4&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Necky Eliza Composite Special Ultra Light Version (Very Thin&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Fiberglass&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;and now with reinforced floor), Yellow, Skeg Version 15'-3'' @ 21" wide.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is the lightest of the Eliza Series and also with the smallest cocpit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://playak.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;catid=5010:boats&amp;amp;id=2150:Eliza-Ultralite" target="_blank"&gt;http://playak.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;catid=5010:boats&amp;amp;id=2150:Eliza-Ultralite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/press_room/press_releases/eliza_paddlerspick/"&gt;http://www.neckykayaks.com/press_room/press_releases/eliza_paddlerspick/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;--- ---&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RESERVED FOR SHERRI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #5&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Wood Cedar Strip Night Heron by Guillemot Kayaks, Fixed Skeg 18' @ 20" wide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea Kayak with a hard chine, low rocker Greenland style hull (50 lbs).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Greenland style Paddle available also if&amp;nbsp;specifically&amp;nbsp;REQUESTED.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cricketdesigns.com/greenland.htm"&gt;http://www.cricketdesigns.com/greenland.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs) with NOVICE/INTERMEDIATE and up skills.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/30/detail" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/30/detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;---&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #00ff00"&gt;RESERVED ?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;--- &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #6&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;NDK Greenlander Pro Fiberglass, Red, Skeg Equipped. Greenland style, fast kayak for ocean crusing. 18' @ 21" wide&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Low&amp;nbsp;initial&amp;nbsp;but moderated secondary&amp;nbsp;stability when on full edge.&amp;nbsp;Medium sized paddler (150-180 lbs) with &amp;nbsp;a MINIMUM of Intermediate to Advanced sea paddling skills needed for this boat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.maineislandkayak.com/ndk_greenlander.html#greenlanderpro"&gt;http://www.maineislandkayak.com/ndk_greenlander.html#greenlanderpro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;---??---&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;reserved for Joe Six Pack Abs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KAYAK #7: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;*OR* &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;SPACE TAKEN ON THE TRAILER is: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;AVAILABLE&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ok I wish you all a good day..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;al-r&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing an ORANGE HUNTING hat at the parking lot, and striped Cones on car roof.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316388933000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313924512000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SEP 17 FALL SEASON KAYAKING @ COLD SPRINGS RIVER in MA Potluck BBQ on site.</name><id>30289361</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316271600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/30289361/</event_url></item>