<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This moderate hike on a portion of the Housatonic Range Trail will be a total of about 3.4 miles in an out-and-back style. It will be an upward grade on the blue blazed trail for about 1.6 miles with a little climbing of rock but not bad. We'll make our way to a &amp;quot;tube&amp;quot; in the rocks we'll have to climb for 10 feet. Then on to Kelly's Slide (you need good shoe tread to not slip on this) via blue/red blazed side trail for the best views. We'll look for the blue/orange trail from there to see if we can find the Candlewood Cave, a rockfall cave mentioned in some literature. If we find it we will explore this small cave. Then on to the summit of Candlewood Mtn. with elevation of 991 ft. We then head back via the main trail to the starting point.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the trail see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.berkshirehiking.com/hikes/housatonic_range.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.berkshireh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet up at the parking area (10 - 12 cars) for Tory's Cave off of Rte. 7 at 9:30 AM then shuttle down to the parking area (6 cars) off of Rte. 37 on Concord Way  for the trail. Parking is limited there. We will spend about 2 hours on the trail so we should be done by 11:30 PM.  We'll shuttle back to the Tory's Cave parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: There is caving at Noon that our group is doing after this event very nearby (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/calendar/6428837/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ). You may wish to consider doing too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment:&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart water.&lt;br /&gt;* Hiking boots or sneakers with very good tread for traction.&lt;br /&gt;* Lunch to eat after the hike especially if you will do the cave event next.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to Tory's Cave parking (a *bit north* of New Milford on Rte. 7):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=&amp;amp;address=480+Kent+Rd&amp;amp;city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode="&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Textual directions:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 7 north out of New Milford center for about 3 miles at which point you'll pass the intersection of Rt. 37 west and Rt. 7. &lt;br /&gt;* A short distance later a gas station will be on your left. Drive 1.3 miles (passing the first street sign for the semi-circular Squash Hollow Road) and turnleft into a large dirt parking area (in two parts: a semi-circle and then a huge open field).&lt;br /&gt;* Look for Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan!&lt;br /&gt;* The blue trail markers can be seen at the apex of the semi-circular parking lot.   The parking lot is at an old quarry construction site.&lt;br /&gt;* The trail heads uphill into the woods. Tory's Cave is about 100 yards into the woods.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Note:  If you see the second street sign for SquashHollow Road, you've gone too far. Drive back  about 0.4 of a mile.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to Concord Way trail parking:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;latitude=&amp;amp;longitude=&amp;amp;name=&amp;amp;phone=&amp;amp;level=&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;cat=&amp;amp;address=10+Concord+Way&amp;amp;city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode="&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leader on this one is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is available from Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan from the Hartford area and potentially available for pick-ups along the I-84 corridor heading west of Hartford, CT. Please arrange with Kevin S as soon as possible and indicate in RSVP if you want in on the carpool. The van will leave the northcentral CT area starting at 7 AM and should arrive at the meetup location at about 9:15 AM (given a couple stops for carpool pick-ups). Return to northcentral CT will be at about 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191246002000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190778567000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on Housatonic Range Trail near New Milford CT</name><id>6429190</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191072600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6429190/</event_url></item>