<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>318 Broadway</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02909</zip><lat>41.820057</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-861-1770</phone><name>Julian's Restaurant</name><city>Providence</city><id>871301</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.428297</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anyone up for a re-visit to Julian's in Providence?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julian’s is the kind of restaurant that transcends time and place. It could be tucked away in Berkeley, California, or hidden behind an unmarked door in Greenwich Village, or coveted by a small city like Providence. Luckily, it’s the latter. Julian’s has loads of charm of the bistro-on-a-budget sort. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The exposed brick walls serve as a gallery of local artists' work for sale; the dining room tables are likewise individually handcrafted and decorated (although, alas, not for sale). But the real character is in the kitchen---chef Julian Forgue himself. He changes the menu often, listing ten or so selections that are guaranteed to be cooked with fresh products and passion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrées typically include an exotically trimmed burger and favorites like chived tempura cod and vegetarian choices like the nightly &amp;quot;tofu scramble.&amp;quot; Flavors are bright, and inspiration is drawn from regional cuisines the world over. The menu is small enough that the misses are rare---and even they still exhibit culinary exuberance. Hit or miss, we always look forward to our next meal here. We’re guessing that’s what Julian wants, too.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the LARGE table!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kerrie Amatelli</member_name><member_id>2732003</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247008518000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244088152000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet Up @ Julians!</name><id>10572817</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245191400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/10572817/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/8/global_6156808.jpeg</photo_url></item>