<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It had to happen eventually! AMC Framingham has taken Frost/Nixon off its general admission list for this weekend. HOWEVER, all is not lost! It is playing at the Premium theater. Since there's another snow storm coming, I've moved the movie time to 4:30 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our discount tickets work a little bit for the Premium, but the original price for the movie is $18.75. We get a few bucks off. Expect to pay &lt;u&gt;about&lt;/u&gt; $16.50 for the movie, though. I'll figure out the price when I get my own voucher exchanged tomorrow. This price INCLUDES all the free popcorn, soda, tea and coffee you can eat and drink (so it probably comes out about the same price as a regular movie with snacks).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, if you still would like to go, &lt;b&gt;please call the theater (508/628-4422) to reserve your seat&lt;/b&gt;. I cannot do it for you, or I'd get charged for no-shows. Paul and I will be sitting in seats 608 and 609. If you'd like to sit near us, please request nearby seats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the bar inside the Premium theater at 4:15. Since our seats are already chosen for us when we make reservations, we don't need to be there extra early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I understand that the change of venue to the Premium and the additional cost and the change of time from 7 to 4:30 will result in a few of your RSVPs to slant from yes to no. I apologize for that. But I do ask that you keep your RSVP current. If you're still planning on attending, you don't need to do anything except call the theater to reserve your seats.&lt;u&gt; If this changes your plans, please change your RSVP.&lt;/u&gt; I still need to know how many people to expect. Also, if the weather changes your plans, please update your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ALTERNATE PLAN:&lt;/b&gt; If you'd like to see another movie at that time at the regular theater, please start a discussion on our board to let other people know and email me (dana@framesbydana.com). Bride Wars, Gran Torino, Marley and Me, Seven Pounds, and Twilight all start about the same time as Frost/Nixon. Then we could all meet at Friday's after. If you'd like to form a group for the regular theater, I'm sure we can arrange something so that I can deliver the discount tickets for the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; The Premium theater is right next to the general admission theater. They share a parking lot, but the entrance is just to the left of the main doors. I will be waiting by the bar for you. Yes, there's a full bar at the Premium, which is why it's an over-21 crib.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REMEMBER TO BRING ID W/  YOU TO THE MOVIE, AS THE PREMIUM IS AN OVER-21 ESTABLISHMENT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email me with questions! dana@framesbydana.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809928835/info" target="_blank"&gt;Frost/Nixon&lt;/a&gt; looks like a must-see for all journalists, history buffs, politicos, or, well, people who want to understand better what happened with Watergate and Richard Nixon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;For three years after being forced from office, Nixon remained silent. But in summer 1977, the steely, cunning former commander-in-chief agreed to sit for one all-inclusive interview to confront the questions of his time in office and the Watergate scandal that ended his presidency. Nixon surprised everyone in selecting Frost as his televised confessor, intending to easily outfox the breezy British showman and secure a place in the hearts and minds of Americans. Likewise, Frost's team harbored doubts about their boss' ability to hold his own. But as cameras rolled, a charged battle of wits resulted. Would Nixon evade questions of his role in one of the nation's greatest disgraces? Or would Frost confound critics and bravely demand accountability from the man who'd built a career out of stonewalling? Over the course of their encounter, each man would reveal his own insecurities, ego and reserves of dignity -- ultimately setting aside posturing in a stunning display of unvarnished truth. Frost/Nixon not only re-creates the on-air interview, but the weeks of around-the-world, behind-the-scenes maneuvering between the two men and their camps as negotiations were struck, deals were made and secrets revealed... all leading to the moment when they would sit facing one another in the court of public opinion.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the meetup with exact time a few days before, but let's go see the Saturday evening/night movie. Think of it as a group date!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted tickets for FMM members and their guests is $8.50. Small popcorn and small soda vouchers are available for $3.00 each. Please be sure to include guests in your RSVP, so I know how many to expect. Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at this historical film on 1/10!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231891605000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230927854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frost/Nixon</name><id>9427828</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231621200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/9427828/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>