<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;Organizer: Joe Ciarcia 415.480.4335 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ - ALL POTENTIAL PARTICIPANTS WILL BE WAIT LISTED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Because of the advanced nature of this hike (steep climb, above treeline travel, lots of miles, and lots of elevation gain) all potential participants will be wait listed. The limit for this trip will be 10 people. Only sign-up if you have similar experiences &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;this&lt;/span&gt; winter and have been actively in the past 2 months. I will let people know if they will be added to the trip within 24-48 hours of them joining the wait list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;==&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is to traverse the whole Franconia Ridge and we will hit four of the 4,000 footers in NH along the way - Flume (#25 @ 4,328'), Liberty (#18 @ 4,459'), Little Haystack (4,760'), Lincoln (#7 @ 5,089'), Truman (5,020'), and Lafayette (#6 @ 5,260') along the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Lafayette is the highest peak in the Franconia Ridge - there are stunning views of the Bonds and the Pemigewasset Wilderness Area from its summit and the open ridge between Little Haystack and Lafayette. While this route would be packed with people in the summer, you can expect to see a lot fewer people during the winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be climbing up the Liberty Spring trail to the Franconia Ridge Trail. We will head south on the Franconia Ridge Trail and grab our first peak of the day, Liberty. From there we will continue southwest along the Franconia Ridge Trail to Flume.  At Flume, we will retrace our steps over Liberty and continue north along the Franconia Rdige Trail. We will hit Little Haystack which will provide us a wonderful view of Lincoln. Continuing north along the ridge we will hit our final peak, Lafayette. From Lafayette we will use the Old Bridle Path (stopping by the Green Leaf Hut for a quick visit) to return to our cars. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs -&lt;/strong&gt; Dogs are permitted provided they are experienced hikers. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need things like warm layers, wind protection, goggles, snow shoes, and traction &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Microspikes/Hillsounds, MOUNTAINEERING CRAMPONS, AND MOUNTAINEERING SNOWSHOES ARE REQUIRED&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. If you do not have all 3 of these items, you will be turned away at the trailhead. While warmer days are upon us in Boston, there's still TONS of snow up north. The dramatic temperature swings this time of year can take a trail from hard packed to ice to mush in a matter of hours. I will update everyone if weather conditions dictate that we bring more than what is described here. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you don't have the required items you put yourself and everyone else at risk.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~1.5 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 14.0 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 6000 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. It should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 10 hours to complete this trip (this does not include time for rest breaks)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.162996757670605&amp;amp;lon=-71.64459228515625"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(weather.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will meet in the parking lot for the Old Bridle Path trailhead. Since this is where we will finish we will leave a few cars here and then drive to where we will start the hike.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;According to Google Maps this spot is about 138 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 11 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(google.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Mazda 3 Wagon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ciarcia</member_name><member_id>40840452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367775017000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366602342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Full Franconia Ridge Traverse (ADVANCED)</name><id>115522432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367665200000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/115522432/</event_url></item>