<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For those of you that have lunchtime free, or work odd-hours, we're going to New Haven's &lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org/" target="_blank"&gt;International Festival of Arts &amp;amp; Ideas&lt;/a&gt; to see &lt;a href="http://www.taikoza.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taikoza&lt;/a&gt;, a professional taiko group from NYC, at &lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org/event.php?id=39" target="_blank"&gt;1:15pm&lt;/a&gt;.  We may also be hanging-out at the Festival afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of you liked the Wesleyan taiko group, these guys should be a big step above (&amp;amp; less loud since outdoors).  Thunderous taiko drums, and traditional reed, stringed, &amp;amp; percussion instruments too.  Free show, at the Family Stage on the upper Green.  You may wish to bring a blanket, folding chair, picnic, snacks, etc. Bring my cell number so you can find me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TAIKO:&lt;/b&gt; Taiko performances are like a cross between drumming, primal music, martial arts, multiple instruments, and dance. They include unique choreography, and various instruments. It definitely includes powerful rhythms that will get into you physically (there's a LOT of bass in taiko drumming).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've never seen a taiko ensemble, here's a &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2GnkubmHaXE" target="_blank"&gt;clip&lt;/a&gt; of a pretty good college student group in rehearsal, and here's a &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jPdOmY1BjAU" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt; for the world-famous Kodo monks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WEATHER:&lt;/b&gt; At this point, forecast says there's a 20% chance of showers, so you may wish to bring an umbrella just in case.  Since weather can impact Festival events (forcing them to change location, cancel, etc), you may wish to check the Festival website before coming, or you can try calling me to see if I know anything.  If I do learn anything I will attempt to send out an email.  To check the website, go to the homepage &lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artidea.or...&lt;/a&gt; and look on the left underneath the calendar to see if there's weather news.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOST:&lt;/b&gt; Jason, cell 203-901-4957 (feel free to call or text)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to arrange car-pools, chat about the event, etc, click &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/messages/boards/thread/4893272#18625026"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to visit the thread on the message board&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213982594000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213473827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wed. 6/18 - Professional taiko in New Haven</name><id>8143146</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213809300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8143146/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/0/global_4452832.jpeg</photo_url></item>