<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to everyone who came yesterday to our Green/St. Patrick's Day party!  Once again, we brtoke a record with the highest attendance on record so far.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all enjoyed seeing our friends that are new owners attending for the first time -- Jeanne Lee &amp;amp; her family with Lulu,  Karen and Kevin Beck with Bailey, Crystal and Sabrina Haupt with Lexi,  Barbara Smith with her two girls, Tess and Minky in the matching Norwegian knit blue sweaters!, Jen Samson and her new baby, Kristen Samuelson with Toby, Beth Hickey with her two babies, including her adorable, shy little Yorkie.  Hermel also returned with his adorable little black Pom, Onyx.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Maltese Meet for the coming month will take place on Sunday, April 2.  It will be a Welcome Spring/Easter party, with pastels in order!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We will meet again from 1pm to 4pm at Especially for Pets in Sudbury. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several members reported success with Angels Glow curing their dogs' tear stains, which was very welcome news!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite your friends that have Maltese to any of our Meets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On another note, we were very sorry to hear of the death of Marcy Frankel's dad, who has attended the Meets a few times, in Florida.&lt;br /&gt;Those of you who want to express sympathy can reach her at Marcy 0101@aol.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in April!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maltese best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1144170126000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1141585720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Maltese April Meetup</name><id>4868465</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1143997200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/4868465/</event_url></item>