<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/b/a/2/event_68659362.jpeg" width="147" height="221" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of you who have been around long enough know that this group started just over 4 years ago, and what better way to celebrate this happy occurrence than with great food and excellent conversation with friends both new and old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have a great recipe that will feed 10-20? Please make a batch and bring it on over. And in return, you can experience the food brouhgt and shared by others. The RSVP limit will be increased to 24 for this event over the usual 12, as we're not planning on playing any games that night (although who knows if Catch Phrase will make an appearance). It would be appreciated if we do have a higher than 12 RSVP count that some people bring chairs (I think I max out at seating for 14). Also, if it does reach 24 people, I might still raise the RSVP limit again, it will just be a slightly spread out night. When you RSVP, &lt;strong&gt;please try to indicate what you might bring or make in your RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;, or email me as soon as you think of it so that we don't have multiples of the same things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, please note that although the event starts at 7:00 and could last until about 10:00 or so, do not feel that you have to show up at precisely 7:00 and that you have to stay the whole night, we expect people to float in and out as their schedule permits and stay as long as time allows.  This is a great way to meet some of our other members outside of a usual game night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you made some new friends by being part of this group, or would like to make some more new friends, please come join us in celebrating those new friendships and connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS  Store bought food is fine, we do not judge here at RIGaEG.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email my house number the day of or before the event. Park on the same side as my apartment (north/downhill side)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368995258000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364062614000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RI Games &amp; Events Anniversary Potluck</name><id>110688722</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366239600000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/110688722/</event_url></item>