<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On Saturday, June 26, 2010, thousands of people across the nation will gather in their backyards, neighborhoods, communities and parks to take part in a one-night event that will provide an experience for all generations to connect with nature.

Remember summer evenings catching fireflies, star-gazing and sharing campfire stories? Roasting marshmallows around a campfire is a simple way to create new memories for your friends, family and children. Plus the health benefits and family memories will stay with you for years to come.


[b]National Wildlife Federation’s Great American Backyard Campout[/b] is the ideal solution for today’s indoor kids who only spend a fraction of their day outdoors. Plus it is time to recapture an essential part of childhood—outdoor play.
&lt;xobject width="470" height="264"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/IZXhuJkxxEg&amp;color1=0xb1b1b1&amp;color2=0xd0d0d0&amp;hl=en_US&amp;feature=player_embedded&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;
Join in the fun with families, friends, and communities for the sixth annual Great American Backyard Campout on Saturday, June 26. National Wildlife Federation encourages parents and kids alike to trade their website for a campsite and screen time for green time to experience a night under the stars with Mother Nature.

In the last two decades, childhood has literally moved indoors with kids spending almost eight hours per day in front of electronic media. Simply put, the nature of childhood has changed, and there isn’t much nature in it. Doesn’t leave much time to catch a firefly, does it?

Studies show that outdoor time helps children grow lean and strong, enhances creativity and attention spans, decreases aggression, and boosts classroom performance. Bottom line—healthier, happier kids.
A signature fund-raising event for the National Wildlife Federation's Be Out There movement, the Great American Backyard Campout will let kids explore a whole other world right in their own backyard, at a neighborhood-hosted campout, or at large community campouts.

When camper’s register on National Wildlife Federation’s website, they’ll get helpful information to make their camping experience a memorable one. There are also easy-to-use campout recipes, nocturnal wildlife guides, campfire songs and games, nature activities and more.

www.backyardcampout.org


[divider]


How can we use this as a Meetup?   RSVP and let us know what your campout plans are.  If your inviting others to join you, invite  in your comments and how to contact you and if you have extra camping supplies. ( For example: invitation for 2 families, my place, please email.  or campground location, site#  room for 3 tents must contact me if interested) 

Just your family in the back yard? that's good too, Share your plans.  you are showing your support.

Turn off the electronics and get out of the house!   

No RSVP limit for this event, the more the merrier! 

Rain or shine, how else will you find out if the tent leaks. It will be interesting to find out at 2 AM how the kids act or REact.</description><how_to_find_us>contact each other by email and phone. set up plans for meals/potlucks by the fire</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277597394000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276799409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great American Backyard Campout June 26</name><id>13832009</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277593200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13832009/</event_url></item>