<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Sansho the Baileff&amp;quot; , a Japenese epic was one of many Janus films that had their all too short run at the Brattle last Fall. While I apologize for the unseemly hour of its screening, here is the description from the MFA:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of Mizoguchi's crowning achievements, Sansho is a jidai-geki (period film) set in feudal Japan. A disgraced aristocrat is sent into exile, leaving his wife and children to fend for themselves. After an attack by raiders, his wife is sold into prostitution and his children are enslaved?one submitting to his fate and captors, the other continuing to yearn for escape. This story of intertwined quests, shot by Mizoguchi's frequent cinematographer Kazuo Miyagawa, is a poetic adaptation of a Japanese legend. Winner of a Silver Lion at the Venice Film Festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And from the All-Movie Guide: On its French release in 1960, Sansho the Bailiff was ranked by Cahiers du cinéma as the best film of the year, topping such classics as Breathless, L'avventura, and Psycho. Critics were struck by the film's gorgeous photography, elegant camerawork, and exotic settings and by Kenji Mizoguchi's signature use of imagery that quietly evokes a spiritual transcendence above the suffering of the material world. Unlike Akira Kurosawa's frequent use of close-ups and fast-paced editing, Mizoguchi, here as elsewhere, keeps his camera distant and his takes long, resulting in a contemplative style in which the characters' suffering and pain seem vivid, yet small compared with the immutability of the landscape. The result is a film that is thoroughly engaging up to its devastating finale. Though it was initially more popular in the West than in Japan, this masterpiece has since been widely recognized as one of Mizoguchi's most beautiful works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be holding a Meet-Up sign near the front row after the film and then on to a local Mid-Eastern cafe for lunch and our discussion. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1168270209000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1167670032000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sansho the Baliff</name><id>5356497</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168097400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5356497/</event_url></item>