<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Frederic G. Corneel Memorial Lecture&lt;br /&gt;Blessed Unrest: How the Largest Movement in the World Came into Being, and Why No One Saw it Coming. - Monday, May 21 - 6:30 p.m. to 8:00 p.m. - Old South Meeting House&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Hawken, environmentalist, author, founder of Erewhon Trading Company, Smith &amp;amp; Hawken, and the Pax Group, and executive director of the Natural Capital Institute. Moderated by Steve Curwood, host of Living on Earth. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From billion dollar nonprofits to single person causes, there is a growing worldwide movement of organizations dedicated to restoring the environment and fostering social justice. This is a movement with no name, leader, or headquarters, but it can be seen in every city, town, and culture. It is organizing from the bottom up and is emerging as an extraordinary and creative expression of shared values worldwide. What are the driving forces behind these developments? Can the interests of these organizations translate into effective government policies and profitable businesses? Join us tonight as Paul Hawken?environmentalist, businessman, and founder of the first natural foods company?addresses the creation of a worldwide grassroots movement based on hope and humanity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This program is part of the Ford Hall Forum?s continuing series on environmental issues. It is presented in collaboration with the Old South Meeting House as part of the Partners in Public Dialogue Series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion afterwards: Location TBD&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541298000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176849312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Environmentalism; Lecture &amp; Discussion</name><id>5680849</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179786600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/5680849/</event_url></item>