<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I will go on this hike, and gee since im a few hundred feet from the water for a few hours, all hot, sweaty and in desire for a good paddle afterward..might as well bring the yaks...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the hike info:&lt;br /&gt;Your Assistant Organizer, Kevin S, sent the following message &lt;br /&gt;to the members of The Hartford Area Hiking Meetup Group:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Announcing a new event for The Hartford Area Hiking Meetup &lt;br /&gt;Group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: Hike at Mansfield Hollow SP in Mansfield CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Saturday, July 8, 10:00 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Click the link below to find out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Description: This is a roughly 5 mile hike with water &lt;br /&gt;views in Mansfield Hollow State Park around the northern end of &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Lake. We will follow the blue blazed trail &lt;br /&gt;that circles the lake. There are two spots of only about .1 &lt;br /&gt;mile each where we will have to walk on the shoulder of a road &lt;br /&gt;but this should not be an issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the park at 10 AM at the northwestern parking &lt;br /&gt;area off of Rte. 89. Then we will hike in a clockwise direction &lt;br /&gt;around the lake. The hike should last about 2.75 hrs. at a &lt;br /&gt;leasurly pace and be over by about 12:45 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group has the option of stopping someplace in Mansfield &lt;br /&gt;Center or Storrs for lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one is Kevin S (&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;) so please direct &lt;br /&gt;questions on this event to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more and RSVP here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/events/5006441/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you dont want to do the hike or timing cant let you..why not join in for the lunch after the hike..&lt;br /&gt;Meet some of the hikers, maybe some hikers will kayak or yak in the water later also..I dont know when lunch will be done so i guessed at the start time..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The water area has 3 rivers feeding in, all of which have explorative properties. There are interesting islands and coves to also checkout. The lake is divided by Bassetts Bridge into a small area and a larger area.&lt;br /&gt;Clean water too...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Boat Launch:&lt;br /&gt;I see the hike is at a slightly different parking location, but we will hike past it from the description.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-84, south on rte 195 through Storrs to Mansfield ctr &lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. &lt;br /&gt;Will see a picknick area on left go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-384, follow rte 6 to toward Willimantic. &lt;br /&gt;6 and 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6. &lt;br /&gt;Follow ths highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte633 or s. frontage rd.) it is acually a parallel to rte6 connector to rte 195, &lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too, &lt;br /&gt;Go north on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, same info from here as above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue Toyota Avalon with the 2 kayaks on a old sailboat trailer. Yeh one kayak with a 55 horsepower motor on it and a torpedo prop...&lt;br /&gt;The RedNeck Jet....runs on pure moonshine...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1152112388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CrossList and Yaking in the Mansfield Hollow</name><id>5008924</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1152381600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5008924/</event_url></item>