<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 New Hampshire Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.087349</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Two International Place</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>12748542</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.812958</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NOTE: We are unable to meet at our regular location this month due to the recent fire. We will be meeting in my offices' conference room on Pease Tradeport. See "Location" below for details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly Challenge:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Our challenge for this month's meeting is &lt;strong&gt;Trashy&lt;/strong&gt;. Between now and the meeting, take up to three photographs which somehow speak to your interpretation of the subject - please feel free to take great liberty with your interpretation of the subject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't be shy, we have a very encouraging group of critics and we'll all learn something from the experience. Most of all, &lt;strong&gt;have fun shooting&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions for Uploading Photos:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Upload photos at www.PhotoMeets.com - an upload site for Seacoast Photographers' challenges. If you already have an account, login and add your photos. If you haven't created an account there yet, click the "Request Invite" button, add your name and email, choose a password, and you can then upload your photos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Due to the recent fire in the building, we've been asked to meet elsewhere as crews update the electricity and repair walls and ceilings. If you're entering Pease from the Spaulding Turnpike or the malls, continue on Pease Blvd. straight though the first light at International Drive. You'll see two white buildings with blue/green trim, our building is the second one. Turn left into the parking lot just before the intersection with New Hampshire Avenue. If you miss the driveway, make a left onto NH Avenue and enter the first driveway on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter the building from the Pease Blvd. side, take the elevators on your left to the third floor, and go straight across the hall on exiting the elevators to the NH Room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Other: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Bring other photos if you'd like feedback or critique, and be prepared to [helpfully] critique others'.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything photography- or photographer-related is fair game.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in the front, and take the elevator on your left to the third floor. The NH Conference room is directly across from the elevator.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366403859000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349123191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seacoast Photographers Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>qxvnndyrgbxb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366324200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/110246122/</event_url></item>