<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>173 Water Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.962673</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>East Bay Grille</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>7491832</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.669182</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Well there is a 40% chance of Rain and 19 mph winds and the moon isn't rising until after 930. Tomorrow isn't much better and the moon doesn't rise until 1030 pm. So we're just going to have to go out and have some fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EAST BAY GRILLE has a band that looks pretty lively.  CHEAP VOOVA - I have it on good authority that they are a great party band.  They usually start around 9-930 so we should get there by 830 to get a good seat. I will have a BIRTHDAY BALLOON with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry about the change in plans but we can't win all the time so lets's roll with it and make it a fun night anyway. I hope to see most of you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you get there early for dinner or need directions my cell is &lt;strong&gt;508-479-7690&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.................................................................................................................&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather is still pretty iffy. But it seems pretty certain that Friday will not be a good day - either because of Rain or Clouds. So we'll shoot for Saturday with Sunday as the backup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I am posting this but need an organizer. I probably won't be able to go. So one of you will need to step us as my assistant organizer on this event. I don't want to skip it because it's becoming so popular and since it only comes around once per month.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The date will be somewhere between Friday and Sunday - we'll pick the exact day the week before. Whichever is the best weather day. Saturday is supposed to be a SUPER moon - whatever that means. But my guess is SUPER bright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/a/event_229082842.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This will be the&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 LONG BEACH HIKE.  It's about a 7 mile loop. In case you don't want to do the entire distance please bring a friend so you can turn around whenever you like.  Yes the first part will be on the road unless its a very low tide. It can be rocky but manageable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a flashlight for your safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a great time. I hope many of you can join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please dress I layers for the weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Apres-hike festivities will be TBD. The New World Tavern is always on my list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE DON'T BRING YOUR DOGS.&lt;/strong&gt; Unfortunately, as much as we love them, they are not allowed past the parking area because of the nesting birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;FYI - the moonrise calender&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/astronomy.html?n=2406&amp;amp;month=4&amp;amp;year=2013&amp;amp;obj=moon&amp;amp;afl=-11&amp;amp;day=1"&gt;http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/astronomy.html?n=2406&amp;amp;month=4&amp;amp;year=2013&amp;amp;obj=moon&amp;amp;afl=-11&amp;amp;day=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/astronomy.html?n=2406&amp;amp;month=1&amp;amp;year=2013&amp;amp;obj=moon&amp;amp;afl=-11&amp;amp;day=1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Birthday Balloon. No it's not my Bday but we can pretend. Maybe I'll get a free beer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369741267000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367005723000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Night Out to EAST BAY GRILLE to see a band Since the Weather SUCKS</name><id>116358952</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>97200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369528200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/116358952/</event_url></item>