<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Heublin Tower is a beautiful landmark in the Hartford area.  For this hike, we will meet at the back parking.  That means pull into the parking area near the road, drive thru the green gate and past Reservoir 6.  The parking is at the back of the reservoir with a Port-o-Potty! We will complete an 6.5 mile loop that will take us to the tower and back by the reservoir.  The tower will be a great place to break for lunch and enjoy the views from the top.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start at the back parking area.  From there we will hike to the far end of the Reservoir.  We will take a right onto the blue/red alternate trail.  We will pass the Tower shortcut and keep heading north.  (Scott assures me the blazes have been restored, thanks power company).  We will join the blue Metacomet Trail above the wussy recreational trail that starts in Simsbury.  We will end up at the tower for a lunch-ish break.  We will then stay on the blue Metacomet down to the Reservoir and back to the parking area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like us to be on the trail no later than 10:00, so please be on time.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is considered a moderate hike with a 700ft gain.  It should be do-able for many.  The trail is well traveled and marked.  Please understand though, we are NOT hiking the wide, groomed recreational trail.  We will be on the Metacomet Trail in the woods doing real hiking.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Please wear appropriate footwear (boots) and bring snacks or lunch and water.  It is now time for sunscreen and bug spray, the ticks are out.  I expect this hike to last not more than 4 hours depending on trail conditions and the group that attends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, NO DOGS, NO CHILDREN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Reservoir 6 is on Rt. 44 in West Hartford.  From Bishops Corner, travel north on Rt. 44.  You will see the sign reading Reservoir 6, Metropolitan District on your right. &lt;br /&gt;From Avon, at the junction of 44 and 10, take 44 south for 2.3 miles.  The lot will be on you left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the road closest to Reservoir 6.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=West+Hartford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Old+Stone+Xing&amp;amp;zipcode=06117-1854&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.79117&amp;amp;longitude=-72.781959&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272981056000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>21</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>53</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270809387000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Heublin Tower/Reservoir 6, West hartford</name><id>13133080</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272807900000</time><rsvp_limit>68</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13133080/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>