<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>577 Crawford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.557716</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>FCA Flight Center</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>10212102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.754265</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/f/e/event_176934782.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Last week was a huge success and we have been asked once again to help these people that are in desperate need of supplies. We are flying back to Rebublic (KFRG) 132 miles located on Long Island and delivering supplies to Atlantic Aviation located on the south side of the airport. We will be under the call sign Compassion then your aircraft tail number.  Please stop into FCA in the morning to recieve a briefing. Supplies will then be delivered to everyones aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talking with the lineguys that helped unload our aircraft, they were all very touched by what we were doing.  Some have lost their entire life and then to be hit again by a Northeaster that brought them snow...very hard to imagine.  The items being requested are easily packed and flown down.  If we meet at 7:30 Sunday morning, then we all should be off the ground and back at FIT before noon. The people of NY area were hit harder than we could ever think of.  Imagine getting a couple dozen planes with supplies heading down there once again?  If you helped in ANY way last week, you know how you felt all week!  I'm in!  Please RSVP and answer pilot or co pilot or other and specify. Thanks!!! Charley&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Stop into FCA for a pre flight Briefing</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352647953000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352332480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hurricane Sandy Relief Flights Trip #2</name><id>90428082</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352637000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/90428082/</event_url></item>