<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 N Lake Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.275074</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>9788556100</phone><name>Quinsigamond State Park</name><city>Worcester</city><id>308800</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.758410</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Click &amp;amp; Shoot  -- May 16&lt;br /&gt;Eastern Sprints Rowing Championships&lt;br /&gt;Lake Quinsigamond, Worcester, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Eastern Sprints is one of the oldest and most prestigious rowing events of the year for college teams. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many schools represented including the big names in rowing like Harvard, Penn and Yale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sprints run for two days each year on Lake Quinsigamond. The viewing stands and launch ramps are inside Quinsigamond Lake State Park. This year the race date is May 16. Saturday, May 15 is a pracitce day only. There is continuous rowing starting at 8 am and running until 5 pm.. The main event – the championship eights -  are on Sunday afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entrance fee is $10. You can leave and re-enter at will, so you can shoot on the Rt. 9 Bridge or along both sides of the lake. There is lots of color and action from all the teams and their boats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is food at the park and also many places to eat at the nearby White City Shopping Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is along the streets and at the UMASS Medical Center Parking Lots ($).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many schools set up tents on the park grounds for their fans. If anyone has a tent, we can set up one for our group also. Tent space is first-come-first-served so you will have to get there early to get a space. Anyone?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entrance is on N. Lake Ave., Worcester, about a hundred yards north of Rt. 9 (across from UMASS Medical).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s meet at 11 am on Sunday, May 16, at the entrance on N. Lake Ave. Bring water and lots of sun screen, wear comfy shoes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/quin.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meeting at the gate 11AM - Lou's cell number is 774-275-1882</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lou Swinand</member_name><member_id>2604245</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274052959000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273163256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click &amp; Shoot: Eastern Sprints Rowing Championships</name><id>13404431</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274022000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13404431/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/1/global_14867249.jpeg</photo_url></item>