<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Southbridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.261272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>877-571-7469</phone><name>Hanover Theatre</name><city>Worcester</city><id>840605</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.803322</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Upcoming Exhibit &lt;img src="http://www.worcestermass.org/media/windows/terri-preist.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; Coming April - July, 2012 - Taking It to the Street! 
&lt;p&gt;Worcester Windows Curatorial Committee is delighted to announce its&amp;nbsp;upcoming exhibition,&amp;nbsp;titled &lt;em&gt;Taking&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;It&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Street!.&lt;/em&gt; Curated by Worcester State University&amp;nbsp;alums Howard McGinn and Anne Seuthe,&amp;nbsp;the newest cycle of Worcester&amp;rsquo;s Community Gallery will include works by 36 artists working in painting, sculpture, drawing and photography.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To launch the exhibition, an &lt;strong&gt;opening&amp;nbsp;reception will be held at The Hanover Theater on April 12 from 5 p.m. to 7 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt; Worcester artist, Terri Priest, whose paintings will be on view at the theatre, will open the event with a brief talk. The curators chose Priest for the high caliber of her paintings, for her lifetime achievements as an artist, and for her long standing commitment to the artists of Worcester. Shown here: &lt;em&gt;Vermeer The Guitar Player, c. 1670, oil on canvas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Light refreshments will be served at the reception and there will be a cash bar. Following Priest&amp;rsquo;s talk, guests will be invited to take the walking tour that starts at The Hanover Theatre&amp;nbsp;on Southbridge Street, proceeds on to Franklin, Portland and Front Streets and ends up at the City Hall Gallery, 455 Main Street,&amp;nbsp;where the Worcester Alliance of Photographers will be showcasing works by 25 photographers in an exhibition titled The People of Worcester County.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Taking&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;It&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;To&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Streets&lt;/em&gt; will give a nod to the days of window shopping when a stroll through city streets was an enjoyable past time in itself. &amp;nbsp;The Worcester Windows program also underscores the contemporary practice of artists showing their work in alternative venues. What better way to find new audiences for their work than to go public! In &lt;em&gt;Taking It To The&lt;/em&gt; Streets, both the artists and the community are enriched.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;A sampling of some of the works available for view offered below. The&amp;nbsp;Spring 2012&amp;nbsp;Worcester Windows exhibit features the following artists and organizations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.worcestermass.org/media/windows/april-2012/wap-mikenyman.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worcester City Hall, 455 Main Street&lt;/strong&gt;: featuring People of Worcester County, works of photography by the &lt;strong&gt;Worcester Alliance of Photographers&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;People are what make Worcester County a better place to live, work and visit. This collection of images shows the many different and diverse people that can be found here in Worcester County. The people represented here have very different backgrounds, jobs, and some may be history makers. Photographers were tasked with seeking out and capturing images of people that can be seen throughout the county. This cross section of imagery from around the City really does showcase - through the photographers eyes - just who can be found here. We hope you'll enjoy the images and perhaps you'll see someone you know.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participating photographers include: Bayda Asbridge, &lt;em&gt;Tina 1&lt;/em&gt;; Dagmar Dankova, &lt;em&gt;Teammates 3&lt;/em&gt;; Frank Jansen, &lt;em&gt;Shared&lt;/em&gt;; John Preves, &lt;em&gt;Dr. Gonzo&lt;/em&gt;; Luke Whalen, &lt;em&gt;Love 2&lt;/em&gt;; Don Ricklin, &lt;em&gt;Major Taylor and His Bike 3&lt;/em&gt;; Marla Zenesk, &lt;em&gt;Preacher&lt;/em&gt;; Melissa Borgesen, &lt;em&gt;White Green Hill&lt;/em&gt;; Michelle French, &lt;em&gt;The Owl Shop&lt;/em&gt;; Mike McCool, &lt;em&gt;Jodi&lt;/em&gt;; Mike Nyman, &lt;em&gt;Kelly 3&lt;/em&gt;; Molly Harrington, &lt;em&gt;The Spice of Life&lt;/em&gt;; Scott Erb, &lt;em&gt;Chefs of the People's Kitchen&lt;/em&gt;; Norm Eggert, &lt;em&gt;Linda Dagnello&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Worcester Art Museum&lt;/em&gt;; Andy Davis, &lt;em&gt;Looking Back&lt;/em&gt;; Russ Garre, &lt;em&gt;Billy 1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Bianca 3&lt;/em&gt;; Sharon Freed, &lt;em&gt;Downtown 1&lt;/em&gt;; Sonja Johnson, &lt;em&gt;Ice Storm 1&lt;/em&gt;; Susan Rollins Daige, &lt;em&gt;B24-2&lt;/em&gt;;&amp;nbsp;Trisha Barry, &lt;em&gt;Rodeo 2&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Veteran's Day&lt;/em&gt;; Troy Thompson, &lt;em&gt;EcoTarium&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and &lt;em&gt;Tower Hill&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Worcester Alliance of Photographers is a place where both amateur and professional photographers meet to talk about technical aspects of photography, be create and share ideas. The WAP meets the last Thursday of every month. Additional details available&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/photo-22" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;online&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Telegram &amp;amp; Gazette, 20 Franklin Street&lt;/strong&gt;: featuring soft sculpture sewn dolls by Terry Jenoure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.worcestermass.org/media/windows/april-2012/jennifer-tibbetts.jpg" width="315" height="220" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baystate Savings Bank, 32-36 Franklin Street&lt;/strong&gt;: featuring oil paintings on canvas by Jennifer Tibbetts and Allan Small&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;60 Franklin Street&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; featuring paintings on panel by Sarah Bliss&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.worcestermass.org/media/windows/april-2012/joyce_conlon_portland.jpg" width="349" height="263" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;60 Franklin Street - corner of Portland Street:&lt;/strong&gt; featuring paintings by Joyce Conlon, Catherine Carter, Alicia Hunsicker, Matt Armen, Janine Schmitt, and Lisa Maillett, and drawings by Jeff Stauder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanover Theatre for the Performing Arts, 2 Southbridge Street:&lt;/strong&gt; featuring paintings on canvas by Terri Priest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;24 Southbridge Street&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; featuring photographic works on paper by Kristin Nason&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;44 Front Street&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; featuring sculptural installation by Kait Brink&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nu Cafe, 335 Chandler Street:&lt;/strong&gt; featuring &amp;nbsp;paintings on canvas by Deborah Garner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;455 Main Street, 4th Floor, Worcester, MA 01608 &lt;br /&gt;

 Phone: 508-799-1400 ext. 3 &amp;middot; Fax: 508-799-1406 &amp;middot; &lt;a href="mailto:info@worcestermass.org"&gt;info@worcestermass.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will start at the Hanover Theater and work our way through the show to the city hall gallery where there will be sweet treats.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334359454000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331834495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>People of Worcester Gallery Show at City Hall - Reception</name><id>56486122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334264400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/56486122/</event_url></item>