<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>bpl.org</phone><name>Rabb Auditorium at Boston Public Library in Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>883985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I had the pleasure of seeing this 'little' documentary at the Boston Film Festival last year and have been looking forward to seeing this once again. &lt;b&gt;King Corn&lt;/b&gt; begins with two young  Massachusett's post-grads having an isotope analysis of their hair, discovering that they, like most Americans are pretty much a corn derived product. From the ubiquitous corn-syrup found in mostly everything to the corn-bred livestock we eat-yes, we are all children of the corn. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;King Corn&lt;/b&gt; USA 2007 90 min. &lt;br /&gt;Our heroes, Ian Cheney and Curt Ellis, decide to rent an acre of corn farmland for one season  in Iowa to become familiar with the practices  of modern American farming and then follow the trail of their corn harvest till it reaches our local supermarkets in its myriad forms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those keeping score at home, this documentary got a 95% rating on Rotten Tomatoes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A breezy diary from a pair of first-time farmers, as well as a wry rebuke to a nation devoted to eating cheaply but not necessarily well, King Corn makes its points without much finger-wagging. Chicago Tribune&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Corn: It?s everywhere, though most of us probably don't realize it. During the past 30 years, the New World plant has become absolutely pervasive in the United States, turning up in everything from soda to meat to jokes (just joking), and contributing to cheap foods that have negative effects on our health. Hence, the documentary King Corn. Without calls to action or divisive language, this artistic little piece of investigative journalism explores the hand-in-hand transformation of corn and the American food supply. Alibi.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A link to the obligatory full review:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.filmthreat.com/index.php?section=reviews&amp;amp;Id=9851" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.filmthreat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, the films at the Public Library are free and thanks Nicole for pointing this screening out. The  screen and set-up at the Boston Pulblic Library is pretty good and a lot better than many we pay the customary $10 for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there - anyone know of a good place to eat near Copley? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Darn, I knew I should have bought the King Corn T-Shirt last summer when I had the chance, but alas, I'll be near the front row after the film's conclusion with only a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206987011000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205195688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>King Corn at Boston Public Library</name><id>7506787</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206813600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7506787/</event_url></item>