<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Exit 19 off Rte. 495. Turn at BKing</address_2><address_1>11 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.149307</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-478-7010</phone><name>DOUBLETREE HOTEL</name><city>Milford</city><id>871306</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.486671</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Project Smile is a non profit organization dedicated to helping children involved in traumatic events. Since October 2003, Project Smile has donated over 26,000 stuffed animals, coloring books, small toys and reading books to 154 police and fire departments in New England as well as the Mass. Department of Children and Families to help comfort children entering foster care. Many of the children who receive these items were involved in car accidents, witnessed domestic violence, are victims of abuse or other crimes, coping with the loss of a loved one or sick/injured. www.projectsmile.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Project Smile was founded by Catherine, your group organizer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a very special event as we celebrate Project Smile's 6th Anniversary. Event features a tremendous silent auction with over 98 items, live music, debut of the 2010 calendar, raffle, appetizers, complimentary Beija Rum cocktail and cash bar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tix are only $10 and include a calendar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karen Swensen, Emmy award winning NECN anchor and reporter will be the special guest speaker. Miss Massachusetts will also be attending. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Auction items include:&lt;br /&gt;Southwest Airline Tickets&lt;br /&gt;TV Diner with Billy Costa, &amp;quot;Diner for a Day&amp;quot; certificate- be featured on the show!&lt;br /&gt;Sam Adams Patriot Brewer certificate- a case of Sam Adams beer per month for a year!&lt;br /&gt;The Colbert Report Tickets&lt;br /&gt;F1 Racing tickets&lt;br /&gt;LimoLiner tickets&lt;br /&gt;Boston Celtics tickets&lt;br /&gt;Autographed Red Sox, Patriots, Bruins and Celtics items&lt;br /&gt;Autographed Jay Leno photo and book&lt;br /&gt;WEEI Sports Radio, &amp;quot;producer for a day&amp;quot; certificate&lt;br /&gt;Worcester Sharks tickets and autographed hockey stick&lt;br /&gt;Beatles RockBand game&lt;br /&gt;white rafting trips, restaurant gift certificates, golf outings, limo rides, museum visits, jewelry, gift baskets and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your help is needed more than ever, so please join us for a fun evening and help bring a smile to a traumatized child.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254870919000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252986309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wonderful Charity Event Project Smile 6th Anniversary Celebration</name><id>11375092</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254522600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/11375092/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/9/global_10723817.jpeg</photo_url></item>