<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Boston's own social media samurai Farhana Cannon the founder of iMedia Exposure giving some powerful tips on how to skyrocket your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this call, she will be discussing why every business needs to utilize social media to market to their customer base, and how to use Facebook to promote your business&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you'll learn during this free session:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How the Timeline format of pages on Facebook can represent your brand image.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how you can create photo albums to show the different aspects of your business and create a website within a website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The importance of back-linking is also very important and doing this properly can be easy and we will show you how.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The importance of ads to generate buzz about your business and we will break down how to do this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to coordinate all of your marketing efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to schedule posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Farhana will be also give VIP access to a selected few people for her upcoming Boston Business Symposium where Founder of CEO Space Berny Dohrmann mentor to top business execs will be speaking. She has invited a few of her "inner-circle" business colleagues to create a most incredible speaking line-up on October 20th. Each speaker has promised to share their most desired success secrets and many of the intricacies of their business building system that is keeping them on the 'cutting edge' of whats working now. It is important to stay ahead of the rest so make sure to not miss this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Featured Speaker:  Farhana Cannon, Founder of iMedia Exposure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event Host: Mark Reinert, Founder of Authentic Business Growth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webinar Access Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The webinar  will take place at 7:00 pm Eastern Time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time of the webinar, or for the replay, go to the URL below to see slides and for access to the audio by phone, webcast or Skype.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skyrocket Your Business With Social Media&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://attendthisevent.com/?eventid=33951234" class="linkified"&gt;http://attendthisevent.com/?eventid=33951234&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I look forward to “seeing” you then.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Reinert</member_name><member_id>7305695</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349320667000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348846012000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skyrocket Your Business With Social Media</name><id>84525472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349305200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/84525472/</event_url></item>