<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;The tiny Scots Island of Todday suffers from a wartime (WWII) whisky shortage. Luck of luck, a ship full of the precious liquid is wrecked on a reef. The islanders conspire to smuggle the whisky off the ship right under the noses of the pesky British revenue officials. Numerous clever comic complications occur before the happy ending,which, we are told by the narrator, was not so happy once all the whisky was consumed. Regarded by devotees of British comedy as the best and most representative offering from the short-lived Ealing Studios. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ealing studios produced some truly hysterical films directly after WWII  including The Ladykillers, The Lavendar Hill Mob, and Kind Hearts and Coronets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dvdbeaver.com/film/DVDReviews18/whisky_galore_dvd_review.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dvdbeaver....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And while this movie might be accused of stereotyping the Scottish ( hey, I'm part Scottish!) it was chosen as the 3rd best film about Scotland by the National Museum of  Scotland-right after Braveheart and Trainspotting and before The 39 Steps. See this link:&lt;a href="http://www.iofilm.co.uk/scots/top20a.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.iofilm.co....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sounds like a fun movie. And as is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meetup Sign near the front row after the movie and then its off to who knows where to discuss- probably just a local restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187397483000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185236281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whiskey Galore! At the HFA!!!</name><id>6066971</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186614000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6066971/</event_url></item>