<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;In her follow-up to&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;Me and You and Everyone We Know&lt;/em&gt;, internationally acclaimed artist, author and filmmaker Miranda July returns with her moving and fearless drama&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;The Future&lt;/em&gt;. When thirty-something couple Sophie (writer/director July) and Jason (Hamish Linklater) decide to adopt a stray cat, their perspective on life changes radically, literally altering the course of time and space and testing their faith in each other and themselves.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;From The Boston Phoenix:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Ultimately the film becomes downright mystical, culminating in a more existentially disturbing variation on the time stoppage stunt in&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;The Adjustment Bureau&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;mdash; by way of 
  &lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Goodnight, Moon&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Somewhere along the way Sophie and Jason shed their annoying inconsequentiality and self-absorption and achieve genuine pathos. They confront the void of the future, in which they must shake off infantilism and face the responsibility of growing up, their only clarity coming from a tiny spark of awareness waiting in a cage&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;From the AVClub:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;The Future&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is full of amusing, lovely little moments that are just a degree removed from being too cute, whether July is being stalked by her favorite comfy shirt, or following a little girl&amp;rsquo;s plan to sleep in a hole to its logical endpoint.&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;The Future&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is elliptical, but never shaggy. July is focused throughout, mediating on movement&amp;mdash;the seduction and fear of it&amp;mdash;while encouraging the audience to care about a pair of do-nothings who like to preserve the broken. There&amp;rsquo;s even a creeping level of tension in the movie, as July and Linklater decide what to do when it&amp;rsquo;s their&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;relationship&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;that&amp;rsquo;s busted. Do they toss it out? Or just tape up the frayed wires and get a few more not entirely satisfying years out of it? In July&amp;rsquo;s constrained world, the resolution to that question qualifies as a nail-biter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #1b2615"&gt;Have to admit to being surprised at the good reviews and buzz surrounding this film. &amp;nbsp;So, thought we'd have an enjoyable (but genuinely pathosotic?) time watching this summer film, and enjoying a brew outside at the CBC afterward.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #339966"&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;
     &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Well gather as a group after the film in the lobby area around the ticket-taker booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314106564000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312665058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Future</name><id>28512801</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313959500000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/28512801/</event_url></item>