<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 North Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.794758</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-643-6892</phone><name>Whiton Memorial Branch Library </name><city>Manchester</city><id>898915</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.523716</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At our last meetup, we all sang HU an ancient love song to God, which is the chanting of the word HU.  I thought it might be nice to have a meetup in which we sing HU for about 15 to 20 minutes and then enjoy some fellowship afterward when we can share what we experienced during the HU song, or just enjoy the company of spiritually minded individuals like ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the ages, followers of many spiritual traditions have used prayer, the singing of holy words, and meditation to bring themselves closer to God. In the same way, those who have discovered HU, an ancient name for God, sing it for their spiritual upliftment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of your beliefs or religion, you can sing HU to become happier and more secure in God's love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Singing HU draws us closer in our state of consciousness to the Divine Being. This is its purpose. It is for those who desire spiritual love, freedom, wisdom, and truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you sing HU and sit in quiet contemplation, you might also perceive the inner Light and Sound. The Light may appear as brightness or colors on your inner visual screen. The Sound may be musical or the sounds of nature, such as the wind or the ocean. However you experience the presence of God, it is bringing you a broader understanding of the life you lead.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be upstairs in the King's Daughter's Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabelle Morton</member_name><member_id>10332926</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340928978000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Central-Connecticut-Spiritual-Experiences-Group</urlname><id>1551111</id><group_lat>41.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5199966431</group_lon><name>The Central Connecticut Spiritual Experiences Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340671183000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HU Chant</name><id>70732422</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>3600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340924400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Central-Connecticut-Spiritual-Experiences-Group/events/70732422/</event_url></item>