<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Avenue de Lafayette</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353809</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 912-1234</phone><name>Hyatt Regency</name><city>Boston</city><id>722096</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061920</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>183.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Usher in 2009 in sumptuous style at The Back Bay Gala (hosted by BEG - Boston Event Guide), at the Hyatt Regency Boston Hotel in downtown Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several of our members have attended prior BEG events (such as The Resolution Ball) and their events ROCK! So a bunch of us have already bought tickets, booked our hotel rooms and are keen for as many people as possible to join us for this awesome party:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your night to remember starts with a cocktail reception and a scrumptious all-inclusive dinner. &lt;br /&gt;Then, slide over to the dance floor as the live band, The Love Dogs, and a DJ help you dance the night away with swing, Motown, Soul, R &amp;amp; B, 70s, 80s, 90s and current top-40 dance hits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;All-Inclusive Dinner Package (7:30pm - 2am) includes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An exclusive hors d'oeuvres reception starting at 7:30pm, complimentary cocktail reception and delicious dinner stations served from 7:30pm - 9:30pm (menu below), premium bar, dancing, midnight toast, entry into the grand ballroom, cash bar, gift bags and party favors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRICE: Only $179 + $4 service fee = &lt;b&gt;$183&lt;/b&gt; (The October &amp;amp; November discounts have expired).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: After the current discounted block of tickets sells out, price will rise to $205. After 12/20, price rises to $220. After 12/29, price will be even higher !!! Price the week of the event will be $250&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**** The longer you wait to buy your ticket, the higher the price will be ****&lt;br /&gt;**** Full price for this event will be as high as $250 this year ****&lt;br /&gt;**** So if you want a good deal, do not delay buying your ticket!! ****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would rather skip the dinner and attend the reception and dance, or dance only, these options are available, and are cheaper than the full dinner package:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostoneventguide.com/events/bbg.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Reception &amp;amp; Dance and Dance Only Ticket Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You need to buy your own ticket &lt;u&gt;directly from Boston Event Guide&lt;/u&gt; at&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostoneventguide.com/events/bbg.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostoneven...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted hotel rooms are available at The Hyatt Regency Boston until 12/23/2008 for $199 (normally $390) by calling 888-233-1234 and mentioning the Back Bay Gala for the discount.&lt;br /&gt;(NOTE: Parking of $12 for the evening or $30 for valet parking is not included.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info on the hotel, see: &lt;a href="http://regencyboston.hyatt.com/hyatt/hotels/" target="_blank"&gt;http://regencyboston....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;***** &lt;u&gt;DINNER MENU IN DETAIL&lt;/u&gt; *****&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Enjoy a welcoming reception with delicious passed hors d'oeuvres:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Risotto Arancini with Spicy Tomato Coulis&lt;br /&gt;Peking Duck Roll with Hoisin Sauce&lt;br /&gt;Miniature Chicken Wellington with Cabernet Reduction&lt;br /&gt;Tandoori Chicken Satay with Cucumber Raita&lt;br /&gt;Mushroom Phyllo Triangle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salad Station:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Bibb Lettuce with Great Hill Bleu Cheese&lt;br /&gt;Locally Grown Tomatoes, Dried Cranberries and Cider Vinaigrette&lt;br /&gt;French Served Apple, Endive and Feta Salad with Lemon-Thyme Vinaigrette&lt;br /&gt;Arugula, Pear and Reggiano Salad with Chives and Pine Nut Pesto&lt;br /&gt;French Served Spicy Greens with Preserved Lemon, Chick Peas, Parmesan and Peppercorn Vinaigrette&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pasta Station:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wild and Domestic Mushrooms with Truffled Lunette Pasta in Porcini Mushroom Jus&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Cavatappi with Roasted Fennel Sausage, Garlic Slivers and Julienne Tomatoes&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;Farfalle with Smoked Chicken and Broccoli in Roasted Tomato Vodka Cream&lt;br /&gt;Served with&lt;br /&gt;Freshly Grated Parmesan Cheese And Warm Garlic Bread&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carving Stations:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bacon Wrapped Turkey Breast&lt;br /&gt;Sweet Potato and Raisin Salad&lt;br /&gt;Cranberry-Pecan Chutney and Bourbon Gravy&lt;br /&gt;Yankee Corn Bread&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Salmon En Croute&lt;br /&gt;Shaved Fennel and Caper Salad&lt;br /&gt;Garden Carrots Roasted with Fresh Thyme&lt;br /&gt;Caper-Herb Tartar Sauce&lt;br /&gt;Grilled Flatbreads&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pastrami Crusted Sirloin&lt;br /&gt;Marbled Baby Maine Potatoes with Rosemary and Thyme Butter&lt;br /&gt;Caraway Jus and Red Cabbage Slaw&lt;br /&gt;Multigrain Loaf&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Served with:&lt;br /&gt;Roasted Garlic Mashed Potatoes&lt;br /&gt;Chef’s choice of seasonal vegetables&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Desserts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lemon Mousse Tart wit Blueberry Compote&lt;br /&gt;Individual Apple Pie with Caramel Sauce&lt;br /&gt;Fig, Mascarpone and Biscotti Parfait&lt;br /&gt;Chocolate Yule Log&lt;br /&gt;Double Chocolate Tart with Cranberry Coulis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Served with Freshly Brewed Starbucks Coffee, Decaffeinated Coffee, and Assorted Tazo Teas&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will advise location for meeting up/some pre-dinner cocktails by e-mail on 12/31</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn L</member_name><member_id>3649230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231114199000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tall Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostontallsingles</urlname><id>1235066</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Tall Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223766389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Year's Eve Party: Back Bay Gala</name><id>8944493</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230768000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostontallsingles/events/8944493/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/5/global_5827173.jpeg</photo_url></item>