<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Congress Street, 2nd floor, Boston MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.352741</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Society of Architects</name><city>Boston</city><id>7356022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052582</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Common Boston Common Build (CBCB) is a design and construction competition that challenges participants to design and build a project in response to real community needs in just less than three days. The CBCB is open to teams and individuals from all disciplines and experience levels. Anyone interested in actively addressing social, economic and environmental issues is invited to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The competition embraces client-designer relationships and emphasizes quality construction, creative reuse, innovation, design legibility and overall responsive impact on the community’s needs and context. Conceptual issues related to the place, security, materiality, ecology, connectivity and adjacency will be explored. Project scope may vary as determined by individual teams, but programmatic, budgetary parameters and the build site will be announced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Common Boston and Boston Building Resources have partnered to host this year’s competition, which will raise awareness of the built environment and inspire connections across the urban fabric while enhancing the cause of one of Boston’s “Off the Grid” communities. The CBCB aims to prove that even when created in less than 72 hours, an innovative and influential response to a real problem can alter the way we interact with and understand the built environment while seeking tangible benefits for the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kickoff: Thursday, June 21, 6:30 pm at Boston Society of Architects, 290 Congress Street, 2nd floor &lt;br /&gt;

Tour with Judges: Sunday, June 24, 1:00 pm (at the build site, which will be announced at the kickoff and then posted to the CBCB Web page) &lt;br /&gt;

Awards Ceremony: Wednesday June 27, 7:00 pm at Boston Society of Architects, 290 Congress Street, 2nd floor &lt;br /&gt;

Registration forms are available at CBCB.CommonBoston.org &lt;br /&gt;

Contact CBCB@CommonBoston.org to confirm your registration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://commonbuild2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Registration is highly recommended for this event&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://commonbuild2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://commonbuild2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://commonboston.org/cb12-cbcb/</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jen Sutherby</member_name><member_id>47375052</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340330197000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337818982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>COMMON BOSTON - Common Build 2012 Kickoff</name><id>66081732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340317800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/66081732/</event_url></item>