<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This Meetup has  to do with Energy Healing, Consciousness Expansion,  Psychic Development and the disclosure of previously cloistered records.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now EVERYONE can develop capabilities once believed to be reserved only for certain &amp;quot;gifted&amp;quot; individuals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the reason why technical details about Indigoes, and the role they came to play in personal and planetary healing is VERY relevant for members of this group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-ancient history is discussed, introducing the reason why Indigoes are incarnating at this time. The history discusses 3 different seedings of specific race lines here, as well as role played by various ET groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Technicals about the differences in Indigoes' multi-dimensional DNA energetic template are introduced, using  &amp;quot;High Science&amp;quot; KS terminology (discussed at a previous Meetup).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to group discussion, an informative video will be shown.  A book of diagrams containing differences in the energetic template of their DNA strands will also be passed around for members to view.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2 hour video ends with a meditation technique. Members are welcome to bring along personal recorders, so they can repeat that technique at home later on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have ANY interest in our hidden history,  where we came from, and what are our evolutionary options... you can't afford to miss this Meetup!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although these details may be new to you, the implications are PROFOUND!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is also a WAKE-UP CALL to all who are interested in deep level energy healing...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;which is MULTI-DIMENSIONAL!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's TIME to become aware of certain VITAL truths... as necessary to partake of the immense gift the Indigoes came to bring!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the lady with the long black hair and BIG smile!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249163680000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244650262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indigo Children &amp; Adults: The REASON for their Multi-Dimensional DNA Differences</name><id>10621486</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247353200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/10621486/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/5/global_5403045.jpeg</photo_url></item>