<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>My first experience with this meetup group was in the fall of 2008, when the original Organizer arranged a wine tasting at the home of a group member who lived in Lowell. The tasting featured little-known Italian wines, was hosted by Lowell restaurant owner Dick Rourke, and followed by a magnificent Italian dinner at his restaurant, Ricardo's Cafe Trattoria.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fast forward a year and a half. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am now the group's Organizer. John, the group member who hosted that wine tasting, recently rejoined the group. Dick Rourke. a/k/a Ricardo, has opened a gourmet wine and cheese cellar called &amp;quot;Tutto Bene&amp;quot; in Lowell. And they have once again been persuaded to pool their talents and resources to create several unique pairings of Italian wine and cheese just for our group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The $10 cost for this special tasting includes Ricardo's selection of Italian wines and cheeses. While Ricardo will be occupied at the wine shop and restaurant that day, he will pass his recommendations along to John and I to present at the meetup. That being said, if you have a favorite wine and/or cheese, please bring it along. After all, we are here not just to expand our culinary horizons, but to share our taste experiences!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This tasting will take place in a private home, so address info and directions will be sent to you after you R.S.V.P. If you are interested in staying on for dinner at the Cafe Trattoria, please let us know that when you R.S.V.P. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278161717000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273548505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine and cheese tour of Italy -- by way of Lowell!</name><id>13445849</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276376400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/13445849/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/f/global_14970431.jpeg</photo_url></item>