<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2378 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.396828</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Good Food Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>833542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129688</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Christmas Concert: Tuesday, Decmeber 23 - 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join in the Spirit of the season with Father Peter Bowes as he performs live on acoustic guitar for your holiday inspiration and enjoyment. Father Peter plays original devotional music in the folk rock style. He has produced nine CDs of inspirational spiritual music which can be found on CDBaby and www.SophiaRecords.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has devoted his life in service to God; for over 20 years, he has served as a Priest and Master Teacher. Currently, he serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ/Sophia, teaching and ministering to his spiritual students, and guiding fifteen Centers of Light and their ministers around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father Peter’s music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within. Listen to his music on Sophia Radio. When not traveling, Father Peter lives at the Center of Light in Chicago, IL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is free, but donations are welcome. All proceeds benefit The Peace Center, a non-profit initiative to support peaceworkers.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Visit www.JimsGoodFood.com for directions - accessible by the T on the Red Line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230769662000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229368703000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Christmas Concert with Father Peter Bowes</name><id>9342382</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230076800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/9342382/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/d/global_4477485.jpeg</photo_url></item>