<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Walk-In Registration</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Turning the Key:  &amp;quot;Finance Your Deals Like a Pro&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the biggest stumbling blocks stopping investors dead in their tracks time and time is again is financing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So often we hear &amp;quot;I've got the deal, now how the heck do I finance it?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For new investors, that's enough to bring their entire business to a screeching halt and send them back to their J.O.B. never to touch real estate again. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even experienced investors who know how to get the deal sometimes secure a property with their own hard earned money only to scramble to find the rest of the money to close. Many sleepless nights later, some do find the money... but many don't and lose their deposits, their pride, and sometimes their shirts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So this begs the question: &amp;quot;what's the best way to finance your deal?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well that all depends on the particular deal, and instead of sharing ONE way strategy to finance your deal, we're bringing you FOUR different experts for ONE busy night! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instead of keeping it strictly to four presentations, we're going to let each presenter share their ONE strategy with you, and at the end, open it up for questions. Bring your deals, bring your questions, and bring your notepad, as you'll get to ask your question and potentially get 4 different perspectives! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/6/" target="_blank"&gt;Pre-Register for Turning the Key&lt;/a&gt; and save $5.00!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3372062</member_name><member_id>3372062</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205019076000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202432692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turning the Key: "Finance Your Deals Like a Pro"</name><id>7287052</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204846200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/7287052/</event_url></item>