<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Financial District Club Quarters Hotel</address_2><address_1>161 Devonshire Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.356221</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 350-9977</phone><name>Elephant &amp; Castle</name><city>Boston</city><id>791944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057235</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event looks like it is going to be a lot of fun.  Done by the same group that did the Mob Father dinner, this should be just as much fun.   It is a very interactive type of dinner theater that has everyone laughing.  They are offering our group a discount price of $38.  There will be envelopes on the table to tip the actors who are also the wait staff during the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All rsvps for this event are waiting list.  You have to call the box office (781-780-3858) to reserve a seat and select an entree.   The web site will not work for reservations.  You need to use the code:   NERD FUN GHOSTBASHERS to get the discount and be seated at one of the nerd fun tables.  Once you have paid to reserve a seat, let me know and I will change your rsvp to yes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more details, including the menu, check out the link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mysterycafe.com/ghostbashers/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysterycaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be outside the restaurant at 5, we will probably want to head inside around 5:15, dinner starts at 5:30.  Show will run till about 8PM. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I thought it might be nice to go out for drinks after the show, if you have suggestions for a good place for the nerds to descend upon after, please let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They are holding 25 seats for us.  They have to release the seats to the general public by October 16th, so please call them before then to reserve a seat.  Please rsvp to waiting list that you have reserved your seat, and I will move you to the yes list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be outside the restaurant with a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1287944645000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284140639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ghost Bashers</name><id>14725125</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287867600000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14725125/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/4/4/global_17842676.jpeg</photo_url></item>