<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 52 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380165</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name> Harvard University, Northwest Labs</name><city> Cambridge</city><id>1598503</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.115501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mimouna Boston Festival&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, April 30, 2011&lt;br /&gt;9:00 PM – 1:30 AM &lt;br /&gt;Northwest Labs, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;52 Oxford Street, Cambridge (Harvard Square)&lt;br /&gt;$20 Young Adult/Student (under 39) or $30 Adult (over 40) at www.NewCenterBoston.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$40 Door - Cash Only, All Ages&lt;br /&gt;*Food and bar additional cost – cash only*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrate Boston’s second annual Mimouna festival!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mi-moo-whaa?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moroccan Jews have historically marked the end of Passover by inviting their Muslim neighbors to celebrate in their homes with food and music. That’s Mimouna.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The American Islamic Congress and Prism update this cross-cultural tradition with a late night, all-cultures-invited party, spiced with the flavors of the Middle East and North Africa. Just as Moroccan Jews and their neighbors stroll from home to home to share in the festivities, partygoers will experience room after room of filled with food, drink, film, photography, spoken word, comedy, music, henna and art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring music from Amoud, Ilan Bar-Lavi, Atlas Soul, Club d’Elf, Michael Mammon and Boujemaa Riguzi, and the Spirit of Sepharad; spoken word from the Hebrew Mamita herself, Vanessa Hidary; comedy from Iranian Tissa Hami; an interactive art exhibition that you help build; henna tattoos; and, an interactive, panoramic picture experience of Jewish settlements in Morocco. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets and event schedule at www.NewCenterBoston.org. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304215866000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's a huge arts and cultural festival this Satuday in Cambridge! It's 5 bands, dancing, henna, comedy, story telling, slam poetry and more! Details on exactly who is perfomring at www.NewCenterBoston.org. </why><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304021868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mimouna Boston </name><id>17470275</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304211600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/17470275/</event_url></item>