<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Introduction to Search Engine Marketing: Search Engine Optimization, Pay-Per-Click, Banner Ads, and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So you've designed and built the world's greatest website and your client is ecstatic.  The site is beautiful to look at, easy to navigate, and gives visitors lots of incentive to part with some of their hard-earned money.  Now what?  Is your job done?  Do you move on to other projects and let the quality of the work speak for itself?  Is this enough?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The answer, of course, is no.  When it seems like everybody and their brother has their own website, how do you stand out from the crowd?  There's no simple answer, but a solid understanding of Search Engine Optimization techniques, Pay-Per-Click Advertising Services, and Banner Ads goes a long way towards making your website more than just a pretty curiosity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Fischer (...me, in other words...) of New Haven-based web design and marketing firm DFFCO will be speaking about these fundamental techniques for gaining visibility in a crowded field.  Using real world examples and a solid dose of common sense, I will help take the mystery out of building a successful Internet marketing campaign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start with mingling, food, &amp;amp; drinks from 6-6:45, presentation from 6:45-7:30, post-mingling from 7:30-8:00.  Pizza will be served and drinks (soda and wine/beer) provided. A $10 donation ($5 for students) is suggested for helping offset the costs of having the group ($20/month) plus the food. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;December's meeting will once again be held at the offices of Elements LLC (www.elementsdesign.com).  Thanks, Amy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elements LLC&lt;br /&gt;King's Block&lt;br /&gt;20 Grand Avenue&lt;br /&gt;New Haven, CT 06513&lt;br /&gt;(Corner of Grand and Front along Quinnipiac River)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is parking on-site accessible from Front Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will (obviously) be there and I hope that you can all make it too! Please RSVP so we can know how much food/drink to have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--David&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ps - Please use the message board to post resources you have found helpful - organizations to join, books, journals, etc.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165619291000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162230421000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Search Engine Marketing</name><id>5232477</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165446000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/5232477/</event_url></item>