<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 David Mugar Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115 </zip><lat>42.357266</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 366-9066</phone><name>DCR Hatch Shell</name><city>Boston</city><id>865554</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072758</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come one, come all, for a day of fun, food and games on the Esplanade! Now that the weather is getting better, we wanted to mix it up by playing some outdoor games. Our first outdoor games event this year was a blast, so we're going to do it again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following groups have been invited to our first Meetup Game Day:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Beantown Gamers&lt;br /&gt;    * Boston Cards and Conversation&lt;br /&gt;    * Girls Just Want To Have FUN&lt;br /&gt;    * Inquisitive Minds&lt;br /&gt;    * Mass Fun and Games&lt;br /&gt;    * Social Fun&lt;br /&gt;    * Peanut Butter &amp;amp; Jelly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT DO I NEED TO BRING?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a chair or blanket to sit on if you can, some drinks and snacks, along with any games that you want to play. Here are some ideas: bocce balls, horseshoes, dodgeballs and kickballs, frisbees, croquet sets, volleyball net, badminton sets... if the wind is calm, maybe even some board games!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT'S THE PLAN?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although we'll send out contact information with our final plans, the goal is to meet by the footbridge near the front of the Hatch Shell, at around noon. After about 15 minutes or so, we'll cross over the bridge and make a &amp;quot;camp&amp;quot; with our blankets. We'll sit down, eat and mingle, then break up into groups to play whatever games we have available. Like MGN, you'll be able to move around the games as you please! This is a great way to mix and mingle with old and new friends, and perhaps learn something about other Meetup groups in the area!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT IF IT'S RAINING?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather is bad, then we may need to cancel Meetup Game Day. We'll send an announcement to all RSVPs by 9:00am the morning of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET THERE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meters are free in Boston on Sundays, and there are a number of parking garages around the area. However, the Esplanade is most easily accessible via the T. Get off at the Charles/MGH Stop on the Red Line and follow signs to the Esplanade, or you can get off at Arlington on the Green Line and walk down Arlington Street. Cross over Storrow Drive on the footbridge, pass Community Boating and head towards the Hatch Shell.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"We'll be giving out contact information to all members who RSVP."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Becki</member_name><member_id>4147212</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>8840173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274635121000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274294228000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun in the Sun - Games at the Esplanade with Boston Cards &amp; Conversation &amp;others</name><id>13533460</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274630400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/13533460/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>