<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Axe in the Attic&lt;br /&gt;2 pm&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 19, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;Remis Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Axe in the Attic by Lucia Small and Edward Pincus (2007, 110 min., video). In the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina, two New England filmmakers drawn together by outrage, take a sixty-day road trip from New England to New Orleans. Along the way they meet evacuees and witness the loss, dignity, perseverance, and humor of people who have become exiles in their own country. The breakdown of trust between a government and its citizens, the influence of race, class, and gender-as well as the ethics of documentary filmmaking itself-form the backdrop for this universal story of the search for home. &lt;u&gt;Opening night for Human Rights Watch International Film Festival.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MFA members, seniors, and students $8; general admission $9.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suffering and Smiling&lt;br /&gt;4:30 pm&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 19, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;Remis Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suffering and Smiling by Dan Ollman (Nigeria/US, 2007, 65 min., video). &lt;u&gt;Focusing on the legendary African singer and activist Fela Anikulapo Kuti and his son, Femi,&lt;/u&gt; Suffering and Smiling depicts the impact of their politically charged music. Following Nigeria's independence in 1960, Fela used his songs to speak out against the country's corrupt leaders and gave a voice to Nigeria's disenfranchised underclass, singing of a free and united Africa. Upon his death in 1997, Femi has continued his father's legacy. Equally passionate and charismatic, he sings about the dire situation in his country, asks why the world's most resource-rich continent has the poorest people, and struggles to maintain a vision of better days ahead for the common people of Nigeria. In English and Yoruba with English subtitles. Description adapted from the Human Rights Watch International Film Festival. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MFA members, seniors, and students $8; general admission $9.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion will follow at a local, quiet, restaurant!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will stand at the front of the theater on the aisle with a handmade Meetup Sign and a booming voice following the 4:30 pm showing of Suffering and Smiling.  Attendance at both films not required, but discussion will follow Suffering and Smiling.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Your New Year's Resolution was to be introduced to new ideas, new films, and new sounds.  What better way than to join a group of film/music afficionados who will expand your experience into action and exposure to what's going on in this great city?</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200241797000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Human Rights Watch at the MFA</name><id>7104270</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200769200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7104270/</event_url></item>