<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Front Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.981155</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Town Hall Gallery</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1625121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.947128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffcc00"&gt;SPECIAL this Month - Equipment Swap:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Got a lens you don't use and want to sell or swap? Don't know what to do with those studio lights you bought with good intentions but never used? Bring it to the meeting a half hour early (at 6PM) so everyone can gander on their way in. At the end of the meeting, we'll hold a sale-or-swap so those underloved items can go to a good, caring home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Brown Bag Bingo&lt;/strong&gt; continues this month, and we have a submission for a photo critique.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #ffcc00"&gt;Monthly Challenge:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Our challenge for this month's meeting is &lt;strong&gt;Rhythm&lt;/strong&gt;. Between now and the meeting, take up to three photographs which somehow speak to your interpretation of the subject - please feel free to take great liberty with your interpretation of the subject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't be shy, we have a very encouraging group of critics and we'll all learn something from the experience. Most of all, &lt;strong&gt;have fun shooting&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions for Uploading Photos:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Upload photos at www.PhotoMeets.com - an upload site for Seacoast Photographers' challenges. If you already have an account, login and add your photos. If you haven't created an account there yet, click the "Request Invite" button, add your name and email, choose a password, and you can then upload your photos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An account allows you to upload faster and will keep track of all your previous uploads. If you'd rather upload anonymously, simply &lt;a href="http://www.photomeets.com/mymeetups.cfm"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;, click the "Upload Photos for this Event" button, complete the required information, upload your photos, and you're done!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; We meet at the beautiful Town Hall Gallery building, directly across from the bandstand and Town Hall Offices. Park on the street or in the nearby municipal lot and walk on over - you may enter at the front or left side of the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Other: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Bring other photos if you'd like feedback or critique, and be prepared to [helpfully] critique others'.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything photography- or photographer-related is fair game.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The gallery is in historic downtown Exeter. The door will be open, come on in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364175190000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>60</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356113421000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seacoast Photographers Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>qxvnndyrfbcc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363905000000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/96162872/</event_url></item>