<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Gorham Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders</name><city>South Portland</city><id>863730</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.332540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Sundays at Tiffany's by James Patterson&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://writemeg.files.wordpress.com/2009/01/sundays_tiffanys.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a brief synopsis of the book!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AN IMAGINARY FRIEND.... Jane Margaux is a lonely little girl. Her mother, the powerful head of a New York theater company, makes time for her only once a week, for their Sunday trip to admire jewelry at Tiffany's. Jane has only one friend: a handsome, comforting, funny man named Michael. He's perfect. But only she can see him. Michael can't stay forever, though. On Jane's eighth birthday he leaves, promising that she'll forget him soon. He was there to help her until she was old enough to manage on her own, and now there are other children who need his help. AN UNEXPECTED LOVE... Years later, in her thirties, Jane is just as alone as she was as a child. And despite her own success as a playwright, she is even more trapped by her overbearing mother. Then she meets Michael again--as handsome, smart and perfect as she remembers him to be. But not even Michael knows the reason they've really been reunited. AND AN UNFORGETTABLE TWIST... Sundays at Tiffany's is a heart-wrenching love story that surpasses all expectations of why these people have been brought together. With the breathtaking momentum and gripping emotional twists that have made James Patterson a bestseller all over the world, Sundays at Tiffany's takes an altogether fresh look at the timeless and transforming power of love.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be sitting at the table by the cafe door. I'll leave the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248477271000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240957973000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Book Club - Sundays at Tiffany's</name><id>10288982</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248303600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/10288982/</event_url></item>