<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hall A</address_2><address_1>1 Oxford St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.376324</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Science Center, Hall A, Harvard University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>537656</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.115746</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a meetup at a Lecture at Harvard University, organized by the Massachusetts Humanists.  Several people from Boston Atheists are likely to attend, but this isn't an official BA event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bill O?Reilly rails against ?secular progressives? nightly, and it has become fashionable among the far-right intelligentsia to bash secularism as morally bankrupt. In this speech, Rob Boston will explain why the secular state is the only vehicle that can ensure religious and philosophical freedom for all. Boston will discuss how an official policy of government secularism, far from being hostile to religion, is in many ways the best friend faith ever had.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert Boston is assistant director of communications for Americans United for Separation of Church and State and the assistant editor of AU's monthly magazine Church &amp;amp; State.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston, who joined the Americans United staff in 1987, is recognized as a leading writer and researcher on church-state topics and an articulate advocate for the separation of church and state He covers the U.S. Supreme Court for Church &amp;amp; State and has attended oral arguments in every church-state case at the high court since 1988.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://masshumanists.org/index.php?name=News&amp;amp;file=article&amp;amp;sid=39" target="_blank"&gt;Full Details and Direction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a Lecture organized by the Mass. Humanists association, but a number of folks from Boston Atheists are planning to attend.  Look for Zach or Nora at the event, Winfield may or may not be able to make it.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Winfield</member_name><member_id>4964612</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235658856000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Like all events, enjoy an afternoon discussing an interesting topic with a professional speaker and socialize with other like minded Atheists/Agnostics/Humanists who have a stake in the preservation of our Secular Democracy.</why><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205014513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lecture@Harvard: In Defense of a Secular State (Rob Boston)</name><id>7493207</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205083800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/7493207/</event_url></item>