<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;A slide show presentation from a permaculturist's 3-month Asian adventure.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Food. Art and Architecture. Ritual. Culture. Transportation. Sustainability. Ecology. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join member Lara Schneider for a virtual journey through the heart and soul of the lands in which she and her partner recently traveled.  Lara didn't travel with the aim of studying permaculture, but she has lots of colorful and interesting photos to share which help open up our perspective to other lands/culture.  This is especially relevant for us as we seek to &amp;quot;write the new story&amp;quot; of our own culture, re/discovering time-honored patterns and combining them with new learning and strategies for a resilient future. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited for this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;You may know Lara from her yoga practice, Radiant Nature.  Besides her work in yoga, Lara has been an organic gardener/farmer, environmental educator, and community organizer for thirteen years. She believes in yoga as a means of strengthening oneself for a richer and more committed life off the mat, and as a trained permaculture designer one of her interests is exploring the relationship between ecological awareness and the inner landscape.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Portland Location (being confirmed) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potluck Supper at 6:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Presentation (followed by discussion/questions) to start around 7:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;Close around 8:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potluck Breakdown &lt;br /&gt;Last Name A-G: Bring a salad or side dish &lt;br /&gt;Last Name H-M: Bring a snack or appetizer-type item &lt;br /&gt;Last Name N-S: Bring bread or a beverage &lt;br /&gt;Last Name T-Z: [Also] Bring a salad or side dish &lt;br /&gt;No legal last name?  Bring chocolate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)! Please consider bringing your digital camera and posting up a few photos after the event!  Potluck food safety ideas here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fycs.ifas.ufl.edu/news/2007/potluck.htm"&gt;http://fycs.ifas.ufl....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248818289000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245765557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Colorful Journey: A Permaculturist's Impressions from India and Thailand</name><id>10715445</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248388200000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/10715445/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/f/global_9323951.jpeg</photo_url></item>