<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Day Pond Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06415</zip><lat>41.556446</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(203) 226-698</phone><name>Day Pond State Park </name><city>Colchester </city><id>714313</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.421074</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Explore a pond created by pioneers to power their sawmill, then wander through the Salmon River State Forest past cascading waterfalls. Be adventuresome and continue to explore the Forest along the Salmon River and down to a newly-renovated covered bridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail Map: &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/deep/lib/deep/stateparks/maps/daypond.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/deep/lib/deep/stateparks/maps/daypond.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given that the Comstock Bridge Connector trail is not a loop, but contains several scenic opportunities, I have described three possible routes of varying difficulty:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- shortest (let's call this one "Baby Bear"): a one-way hike starting at 1:15pm at the Comstock Bridge just off Route 16. Hike the Connector trail to the South Loop trail and end at Day Pond. Convince a fellow adventurer to drive you back to your car. Approx. distance = 2.5mi, approx. time = 1.25hr, elev. gain approx 600ft (according to GPS).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- slightly longer ("Mama Bear"): a loop hike starting at 10:30am at Day Pond. proceed counterclockwise around the Salmon River Trail North &amp;amp; South loop, with a side-trip to the waterfalls via the red/blue Spur Trail. end at Day Pond. Approx. distance = 2.9mi, approx. time = 1.5hr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- most difficult/scenic ("Papa Bear"): a loop/backtrack hike starting at 10:30am at Day Pond. proceed along Salmon River Trail North Loop, side-trip to the waterfalls, continue counterclockwise around to Connector trail, hike down to Comstock Bridge. After a short lunch break, backtrack along the Connector trail to the South Loop trail and end at Day Pond. Total distance = 6.8mi, approx. time = 4hr, elev. gain &amp;gt; 1000ft (according to GPS).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be leading all parts of this hike except the South loop portion of "Mama Bear". When we reach the Comstock Connector trail, someone will be nominated to lead those continuing on the South loop back to Day Pond (approx 0.6mi, approx 15min).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you respond "Yes" to this hike, please indicate which route interests you by responding to the questionnaire.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail Map: &lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/deep/lib/deep/stateparks/maps/daypond.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/deep/lib/deep/stateparks/maps/daypond.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HIKE TIMES: Papa/Mama Bear paws will hit the trail promptly at 10:30am, so please aim to be parked along Day Pond Road no later than 10:15am. Baby Bears should aim to be at the Comstock Bridge parking lot (intersection of CT-16 and Comstock Bridge Road) by 1pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS for Papa/Mama Bear hikers: There's an error in Google Maps for this location, use Mapquest instead and search for Day Pond, Colchester, CT. From the intersection of CT-16 and CT-149, head north on CT-149 (Westchester Road) four tenths of a mile to Peck Lane on your left. Make the slight left onto Peck Lane and proceed 350ft to Day Pond Road, turn left onto Day Pond Road and continue for 0.4mi or until the road is gated. The state park is also gated for the winter so we will be parking along the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LATITUDE/LONGITUDE OF PARKING AREA, Papa/Mama Bears: not useful - both Google Maps and Mapquest are unable to find the location using coords.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HIKE LOGISTICS, Papa/Mama Bears: Look for me holding a HARTFORD AREA HIKING Meetup sign somewhere along Day Pond Road near the pond. We will proceed from there to the blue-blazed trail head which is just past the bridge over the Day Pond Brook (near the dam).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS for Baby Bear hikers: From the intersection of CT-2 and Ct-16 near Colchester, proceed west on CT-16 for 6.4mi to arrive at Comstock Bridge Road. Turn right onto Comstock Bridge Road and immediately look for the parking area on your right for the covered bridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LATITUDE/LONGITUDE OF PARKING AREA, Baby Bears: 41.553147, -72.449290&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HIKE LOGISTICS, Baby Bears: The Papa Bear hikers should be arriving at the covered bridge around 1pm. I'll have one of the HARTFORD AREA HIKING signs on my backpack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Problems finding the parking lot? Call Kevin H at 860-451-9804&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who wish to go should have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* A daypack or lumbar pack - To carry trail food, water, and any extra items&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* At least 1-2 quarts (1-2 liter) drinking water, depending on route&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Hiking boots advised&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Bug spray advised (to repel ticks, which are found in leaf litter even in winter; see &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.health.ny.gov/publications/2737/"&gt;this publication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for discussion of tick and insect repellents)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2716&amp;amp;Q=325184"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for more information on Day Pond State Park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Count Me In" or "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking Meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==================&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin H</member_name><member_id>10192861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367178061000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366766599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Day Pond &amp; Salmon River forest hike</name><id>115874222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367072100000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/115874222/</event_url></item>