<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Chuck Hagenbuch will introduce the concepts of ORM and then put them to work.  Horde's RDO system is a light-weight, PHP 5, PDO-based version of ORM that also draws heavy influence from the Data Mapper pattern(&lt;a href="http://www.martinfowler.com/eaaCatalog/dataMapper.html)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.martinfowl...&lt;/a&gt;. Entity and Mapper objects are simple and very flexible, while providing plenty of ways to extend and add functionality and domain logic. Associated patterns such as Horde_RDO_Lens allow for powerful decoration of result sets with efficient memory and object use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio:  Chuck Hagenbuch founded the Horde Project in 1998 and has been working with PHP and the world of web development ever since. He is currentlya consultant doing work focused around Horde and PHP web development. He has provided professional PHP services to many prominent PHP-using organizations, including Google, PayPal, and Portugal Telecom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Horde Framework:The Horde Application Framework is a mature, evolving application framework (featured in BostonPHP's Framework back-off) that has been used to build complex applications for years.  It forms the core of the widely used IMP webmail application and the Horde Groupware suite. In addition, it provides a large number oftested, feature-rich components that can be used to build additional Horde applications, to integrate Horde functionality into other applications, or to build completely standalone sites. &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181341853000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178148960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BostonPHP June User Group:: Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) in action</name><id>5735157</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181169000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/5735157/</event_url></item>