<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Mountain Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06032</zip><lat>41.721367</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hill-Stead Museum</name><city>Farmington</city><id>7406402</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.827522</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/2/b/2/event_123349842.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;SUNKEN GARDEN POETRY FESTIVAL &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Poetry Prelude 5 pm; Music by Eight to the Bar begins 6:15; poet Dana &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/f/b/event_38459131.jpeg" width="67" height="43" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Gioia reads 7:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$5.00 per person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;parking free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;All performances will be at Hill-Stead Museum, &lt;strong&gt;rain or shine&lt;/strong&gt;, under tents during inclement weather. HILL-STEAD NOW HAS A POETRY TENT THAT WILL BE UP ALL SEASON!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Dana Gioia&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;"Through his poignant verse, insightful criticism, and inspired leadership of the NEA, Professor Gioia has helped millions of Americans experience the positive and transformative power of literature and the arts."&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Former Chairman of the National Endowment for the Arts, &lt;strong&gt;Dana Gioia&lt;/strong&gt;, is an internationally acclaimed and award-winning poet. A native Californian of Italian and Mexican descent, Gioia has published three full-length collections of poetry, as well as eight chapbooks. His poetry collection &lt;em&gt;Interrogations at Noon&lt;/em&gt; won the 2002 American Book Award. An influential critic as well, Gioia's 1991 volume &lt;em&gt;Can Poetry Matter?&lt;/em&gt;, a finalist for the National Book Critics Circle award, is credited with helping to revive the role of poetry in American public culture. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Gioia has authored many literary anthologies, and his poems, translations, essays, and reviews have appeared in numerous magazines including &lt;em&gt;The New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Washington Post Book World&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The New York Times Book Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Slate&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;The Hudson Review&lt;/em&gt;. Gioia has written two opera libretti and is an active translator of poetry from Latin, Italian, and German. Gioia has been the recipient of ten honorary degrees. He and his wife, Mary, have two sons. Read more at &lt;a href="http://sunkengardenpoetry.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Sunken Garden Poetry&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span&gt;Photo by Lynda Koolish.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.hillstead.org/images/activities/music_eightbar.jpg" alt="Eight to the Bar" width="250" height="200" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Eight to the Bar&lt;/strong&gt;'s material, like their outlandish wardrobes and onstage choreo, is a colorful mix of forties jazz and swing, fifties jump blues, and their own swing-influenced tunes. With their female vocals, saxophone, guitar, bass, keyboards and drums, this unique sextet, named "Best Live Band 2010" by &lt;em&gt;Hartford Magazine&lt;/em&gt;, pack a musical and visual wallop not seen in New England since the group's inception in 1975. Since that time they have released eleven CDs, seven videos, and have excited audiences from Europe to the Caribbean. The band has released its 11th CD, &lt;em&gt;The Romper Room&lt;/em&gt;, and has just returned from a weeklong tour of the Republic of Georgia where they performed in August at the invitation of the U.S. Embassy there. Find out more at &lt;a href="http://www.eighttothebar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.eighttothebar.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span&gt;Photo by Jim Coon.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The &lt;strong&gt;gates open&lt;/strong&gt; at 4:30 pm. Pre-performance &lt;strong&gt;Preludes lecture series&lt;/strong&gt; takes place 5–5:45 in the Makeshift Theater. &lt;strong&gt;Music begins&lt;/strong&gt; at 6:15 pm; &lt;strong&gt;poetry begins&lt;/strong&gt; at 7:30 pm. Attendees may bring their own &lt;strong&gt;food&lt;/strong&gt; or purchase on site (sandwiches, wraps, salads and beverages), from &lt;strong&gt;The Epicurean Caterers&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.theepicureancaterers.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.theepicureancaterers.com&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;strong&gt;Attendance&lt;/strong&gt; to the Festival is $5 per person, free ages 12 and under. On-site &lt;strong&gt;parking&lt;/strong&gt; is FREE. Bring a blanket or lawn chair for &lt;strong&gt;seating&lt;/strong&gt; in and around the garden. In case of &lt;strong&gt;rain&lt;/strong&gt;, performances will be held indoors or under a tent.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will fly balloons, look for the black and white scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339890505000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338133016000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SUNKEN GARDEN POETRY FESTIVAL</name><id>66536962</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339623000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/66536962/</event_url></item>