<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We were unable to hold an actual Pow Wow, this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its place, I'll post reviews of films that we would have discussed at the Pow Wow in order to help everyone make choices.  Those with high rating in bold.  Please feel free to add comments so that it will feel like we held a Virtual Pow Wow, and use this space to hook up with other members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;5:15 - The Pleasure of Being Out of Step - No Reviews - Profiles legendary jazz writer and civil libertarian Nat Hentoff, whose career tracked the greatest cultural and political movements of the last 65 years. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;5:30 - Lonely Boy - IMDB: 5.6 - The romantic misadventures of a schizophrenic bachelor. "Overall Lonely Boy succeeds in painting a man with mental illness. The performances are solid and the film is shot with some clever movements. However, the lack of any relief from the mental illness makes the too long running time a chore. That combined with a late flashback that reveals obvious plot details make Lonely Boy a film with too many highs and lows to fully recommend."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;5:45 - The Act of Killing - IMDB: 7.8/&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RT: 100% &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;- A documentary that challenges former Indonesian death squad leaders to reenact their real-life mass-killings in whichever cinematic genres they wish, including classic Hollywood crime scenarios and lavish musical numbers. JANICE PAGE "You’ve never seen a movie like this documentary from director Joshua Oppenheimer. It’s about Indonesian death squads who tortured and executed communists in the 1960s. Their story would be dramatic enough told straightforwardly, but Oppenheimer has the kooky-brilliant-outrageous idea to let former squad members also craft their own revealing narratives, complete with reenactments, done up in cinematic genres from noir to musical. The controversial result can be as absurd as it is horrific to watch. Can these unremorseful killers, as casual about dispatching a human life as they are about dressing in drag, be for real? Should you feel bad for even giving them your time? Just when it all seems a bit too staged and slimy to stomach, you see the bile erupt onscreen, too, and the volume of it haunts. Executive produced by Werner Herzog and Errol Morris; in Indonesian, with subtitles."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;6:00 - The Last Day of August - IMDB: 4.6 - A paraplegic's friends pay him an unannounced visit to challenge his secluded life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;6:00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong style="color : #800080"&gt;(BRATTLE)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Muscle Shoals - IMDB: 6.4 - Located alongside the Tennessee River, Muscle Shoals, Alabama is the unlikely breeding ground for some of America's most creative and defiant music. Under the spiritual influence of the 'Singing River' as Native Americans called it, the music of Muscle Shoals changed the world and sold millions upon millions of copies. At its heart is Rick Hall who founded FAME Studios. Overcoming crushing poverty and staggering tragedies, he brought black and white together in Alabama's cauldron of racial hostility to create music for the generations while giving birth to the 'Muscle Shoals Sound' and 'The Swampers'. Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, Percy Sledge, Gregg Allman, Clarence Carter, Etta James, Alicia Keys, Bono, and others bear witness to Muscle Shoals' magnetism, mystery, and why it remains influential today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;8:00 - The East - IMDB: 7.6/&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RT: 88% - &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;An operative for an elite private intelligence firm finds her priorities irrevocably changed after she is tasked with infiltrating an anarchist group known for executing covert attacks upon major corporations. "A refreshing concept, persuasive acting, and effective pacing make Brit Marling's latest, The East, one of the most captivating films of Sundance 2013...A stunningly inventive thriller."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span&gt;8:15 - Stories We Tell- IMDB: 7.8/&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RT:88% &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;- Stories We Tell is an inspired, genre-twisting film by Oscar (R)-nominated director Sarah Polley, and produced by Anita Lee for the NFB. Her playful investigation into the elusive truth buried within the contradictions of a family of storytellers paints a profound portrait of a complicated and deeply loving family. "Tthe probing, emotionally devastating documentary that was, for this critic and many others, the revelation of the first week of the Venice Film Festival."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;8:30 - Narco Cultura - IMDB: 7.9 -&lt;/span&gt; To a growing number of Mexicans and Latinos in the Americas, narco traffickers have become iconic outlaws and the new models of fame and success. They represent a pathway out of the ghetto - a new form of the American Dream, fueled by the war on drugs. NARCO CULTURA looks at this explosive phenomenon from within; cycles of addiction to money, drugs and violence that are rapidly gaining strength on both sides of the US/Mexican border.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;8:45 - Berberian Sound Studio - IMDB: 6.4/&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RT: 75% &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;A sound engineer's work for an Italian horror studio becomes a terrifying case of life imitating art. PETER KEOUGH "&lt;/span&gt;Director/writer Peter Strickland emulates existential horror films like Roman Polanski’s “The Tenant” and David Lynch’s “Mulholland Drive” as the term “looping” takes on a diabolical new meaning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;8:45 - (BRATTLE) - The Final Member - IMDB: 7.4 - Thirty miles from the Arctic Circle, in the northern Icelandic town of Husavik, stands the Icelandic Phallological Museum - the world's only Penis museum. Over 40 years, the founder and curator has collected every specimen from every mammal except for one elusive penis needed to complete his collection: The Human Specimen. The film follows the curator's incredible, sublimely comic, often shocking quest to complete his eccentric collection, and the two intrepid men who have raised their hands to be the first human donor. "This project isn't intended to mock or titillate anybody, but to depict with sincerity and good humor the story of one man's quest."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;9:00 - Tiny: A Story About Living Small - No Reviews - What is home? And how do we find it? TINY follows one couple's attempt to build a Tiny House from scratch with no building experience, and profiles other families who have downsized their lives into houses smaller than the average parking space. Through homes stripped down to their essentials, the film raises questions about sustainability, good design, and the changing American Dream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please feel free to add a comment to meetup with other members, or to add information for any film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367195190000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366577295000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Evening Films at the BFF</name><id>115467662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367183700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/115467662/</event_url></item>