<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Quality St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06611</zip><lat>41.256035</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>203 452 5197</phone><name>Trumbull Library</name><city>Trumbull</city><id>379788</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.217674</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Lorraine Warren Ghost Hunter Speaks at Fundraiser for the&lt;br /&gt;Trumbull Library from 7 to 9 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Psychic investigator, author, and lecturer Lorraine Warren will speak at the Trumbull Library on her most famous cases with her late husband Ed, (including the Amityville haunting) as well as describe her recent paranormal investigations.  Please join us for this special event! Tickets are $20 and are available at the Main Librarys Information Desk.    Capacity is limited. Proceeds will go to help create a Teen Space at the Library.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; www.warrens.net/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; www.trumbullct-library.org/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from I 95 South&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 38 towards Ct-15 Merritt and Wilbur Cross Pkwys&lt;br /&gt;Merge onto Milford Pkwy&lt;br /&gt;Take the exit onto CT - 15 S/Merritt Pkwy towards NYC&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 50 for CT-127 White Plains Rd towards Trumbull&lt;br /&gt;Slight right at CT-127 / White Plains Rd.&lt;br /&gt;Continue to follow CT-127&lt;br /&gt;Turn left at Quality St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a fountain on your right.&lt;br /&gt;The Entrance to the Trumbull Library is past the fountain &lt;br /&gt;On your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walk into the Main Entrance facing Quality St.&lt;br /&gt;There is also a side entrance on the side of the fountain&lt;br /&gt;but for these directions you are&lt;br /&gt;Encouraged to use the front main entrance.&lt;br /&gt;Do not go through the Sliding Doors going further into the Library.&lt;br /&gt;Turn left going the direction towards the phone on the wall.&lt;br /&gt;There are rest rooms on the left just before you walk into the &lt;br /&gt;Community Room where the lecture will be held.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are seriously going to this presentation, &lt;br /&gt;Instead of RSVPing as a typical wishy washy Meet Upper,&lt;br /&gt;Then I encourage you to make your own arraignments with them&lt;br /&gt;Before next Monday, October 1.&lt;br /&gt;You can either call them at (203) 452-5197 or e-mail using the link &lt;br /&gt;www.trumbullct-library.org/&lt;br /&gt;I am guessing that you can use the Ask A Librarian link to give them a reservation.&lt;br /&gt;They will not accept credit cards.   They are asking for checks or &lt;br /&gt;cash in person for the $20 presentation fee.  The Librarian said that the Brookfield &lt;br /&gt;Presentation was sold out, so there is a concern that this presentation&lt;br /&gt;Might also become sold out.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I am not getting involved in the reservation process for those&lt;br /&gt;Who are going to this event and paying $20 to the Trumbull Library.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To give even more of an idea where the Trumbull Library is, there is a Stop and &lt;br /&gt;Shop Shopping Complex across the street up on a hill.  &lt;br /&gt;It is on the same side of the street as the Trumbull Town Hall.&lt;br /&gt;If you go further down the Quality Street and take a left, that will put you on&lt;br /&gt;Rt 111 Newtown Tnpk / Main Street.    Rt 111 will take you to the Trumbull Mall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have other appointments that night, so I am not sure if I can attend.&lt;br /&gt;I did not buy a ticket for the event when I was there on Monday, 9/24.&lt;br /&gt;If I do attend, then I wear glasses, short beard and often carry a purple&lt;br /&gt;Back pack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not a SGRA event, because they will be having a presentation on&lt;br /&gt;More Than a Bump in the Night at the Wilton Library at the same time.&lt;br /&gt;I am not making the Wilton event into a Meet Up for this group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybes for the Warren Presentation will be allowed up to October 4.&lt;br /&gt;All Maybes will become No on October 5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191810851000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190435524000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lorraine Warren in Trumbull Lib on October 5</name><id>6406516</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191625200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6406516/</event_url></item>