<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone that wants to get in the Christmas mood from the get go in Boston, and have a look at Nova Scotia's annual gift, join me with your camera on the Common Thursday night from 6-8 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The City of Boston's Official Tree Lighting hosted by Mayor Thomas M. Menino, the Boston Parks and Recreation Department, title sponsor the Province of Nova Scotia, and media sponsors WCVB-TV Channel 5 and MAGIC 106.7 FM comes to Boston Common on Thursday, December 2, from 6 p.m. to 8 p.m.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The holiday decorations throughout Boston Common and the Public Garden, including the city's official Christmas tree, 50-foot, 50-year-old white spruce, donated by Gary and Roseann Meisner of North Alton, Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia, and selected by Ross Pentz of the Nova Scotia Department of Natural Resources,, will light up in sequence when Mayor Menino throws the switch with Santa Claus.  Joining Mayor Menino will be Deputy Premier of Nova Scotia the Honourable Frank Corbett and members of the Royal Canadian Mounted Police.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chronicle's Anthony Everett and NewsCenter Five's JC Monahan will host Channel 5's live broadcast of the event beginning at 7 p.m.   The celebration will feature the Radio City Rockettes, 2006 American Idol runner-up Katherine McPhee, Grammy-winning R&amp;amp;B singer Patti Austin, the Boston Pops Gospel Choir with a cameo appearance by Pops conductor Keith Lockhart, a capella group Five O'Clock Shadow, the Boston Arts Academy, MAGIC 106.7's Nancy Quill and Mike Addams, and Police Officer Stephen McNulty who will lead the end-of-show sing-along.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show-closing pyrotechnic display is underwritten by the Boston Pops.  Refreshments and fun giveaways will be provided by in-kind sponsors Dunkin' Donuts, Cabot Creamery, H.P. Hood LLC, Nantucket Nectars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This marks the ninth year that Nova Scotia joins with the City of Boston to present the Christmas tree on Boston Common.  It is also the 39th year that Nova Scotia has given a tree to the people of Boston as thanks for relief efforts following the December 6, 1917, explosion of a munitions ship in Halifax Harbor.  Within 24 hours of the disaster a train loaded with supplies and emergency personnel was making its way from Boston to Nova Scotia.  2010 marks the 93rd Anniversary of the Halifax Explosion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be outside the Park Street T between 5:45 and 6:10, and then I can be reached at 857-221-2041. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potential pint afterward at local tavern for those that want to keep the festive atmosphere going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Holding small Canadian flag outside Park St T station</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce Turnbull</member_name><member_id>4018534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291335365000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290824131000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>69th Boston Common Tree Lighting </name><id>15563746</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291330800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/15563746/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/4/global_19880836.jpeg</photo_url></item>