<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For this month's Book Club Meetup we will be discussing the popular book &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Memory of Running&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, by Ron McLarty.  I just picked it up two days ago, and I'm really enjoying it so far.   The pleasure of reading this book comes from going along for the ride as Smithy Ide transforms himself and takes back his life.  Can't wait to discuss it with you on October 7th at Panera! &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Come as you are - if you couldn't &amp;quot;finish&amp;quot; (or start!) the book, join us anyway for a lively discussion with like-minded and likable people!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Review from Publisher's Weekly:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smithy Ide is a really nice guy. But he's also an overweight, friendless, womanless, hard-drinking, 43-year-old self-professed loser with a breast fetish and a dead-end job, given to stammering &amp;quot;I just don't know&amp;quot; in life's confusing moments. When Smithy's entire family dies, he embarks on a transcontinental bicycle trip to recover his sister's body and rediscover what it means to live. Along the way, he flashes back to his past and the hardships of his beloved sister's schizophrenia, while his dejection encourages strangers to share their life stories. The road redeems the innocent Smithy: he loses weight; rescues a child from a blizzard; rebuffs the advances of a nubile, &amp;quot;apple-breasted&amp;quot; co-cyclist after seeing a vision of his dead sister; and nurtures a telephone romance with a paraplegic family friend as he processes his rocky past. McLarty, a playwright and television actor, propels the plot with glib mayhem—including three tragic car accidents in 31 pages and a death by lightning bolt—and a lot of bighearted and warm but faintly mournful humor. It's a funny, poignant, slightly gawky debut that aims, like its protagonist, to please—and usually does.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be near the front with my book!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meagan</member_name><member_id>6521348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226446038000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222205567000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Meetup - The Memory of Running</name><id>8818279</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223420400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/8818279/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/4/global_5626532.jpeg</photo_url></item>