<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>The address will be sent a few days prior to the event to all the "yes" RSVPs</address_1><state>CT</state><lat>41.512222</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ralph's house in Cheshire</name><city>Cheshire</city><id>4316452</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.903610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's time to wind down the year and get into the Christmas spirit with great friends, new people that will be great friends and chase away the blues. Whatever holidays you celebrate bring it with you to share with whoever is here. Wherever did 2011 go? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Let's celebrate the season and reflect on good things that have come our way in 2011 and get ready for (gulp) 2012. I am inviting all to share this holiday at my house. The situation is the same as past wine tasting events... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Wine night at my house... on a Sat December 3, 2011! in Cheshire CT 6pm - 10 pm + &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine (no boxed wine please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food, hors d'oeuvres or dessert. Please indicate what food item you want to bring when you sign up. This invitation will go out to 5 groups of 15 people ea. Please bring your own glass. I have some, but not enough for all even though I now have some extra Benmarl wine glasses now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVPs close 3 days before the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is $15 or more. Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $30 or more depending on the quantity of people in the group, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste testing... &lt;br /&gt;

Reds Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir, &lt;br /&gt;

whites - sav blanc, chards, reisling, pinot grigio, etc &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a person&amp;rsquo;s spot if you do not show up. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event if you don't have it already to all the "yes" RSVPs, due to this being a private residence. It should go without saying to Drink Responsibly. I will have water and coffee too. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Enjoy, responsibly!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph</member_name><member_id>8774347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323369041000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320609971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sat 12/3 - Christmas Wine tasting at Ralph's house</name><id>40178812</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322953200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/40178812/</event_url></item>