<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Girls in Trouble centers around Sara, a 16-year old girl with a promising future. Like many girls her age, Sara gives in to passion with her boyfriend and becomes pregnant. Deciding against an abortion, she chooses open adoption with George and Eva, a couple starved for a baby. After the baby is born, George and Eva become weary of Sara's neediness and intrusion into their lives, and decide to keep Sara away from them and the baby. Sara, in desperation, then compounds her mistakes in a attempt to find a role in her daughter's life. Caroline Leavitt's novel illuminates the choices and mistakes we all make in life, and the repercussions that has in the many lives those choices affect. The Washington Post says of Girls in Trouble, &amp;quot;The pleasure of this novel, our 'enjoyment' of it, comes from Leavitt's wisdom about the deep chasm of misfortune, her exploration of misfortune's steep slope and her recognition that climbing out of misfortune's pit, step by arduous step, requires a heroism that literature, with its capacity for rendering the elevated quality of ordinary experience, can portray so beautifully.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245868545000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223655366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Novembers Book - Girls in Trouble by Caroline Leavitt</name><id>8937243</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226446200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/8937243/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/f/6/global_5813110.jpeg</photo_url></item>