<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Long Hill Rd. Exd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.230709</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Hellenic Center</name><city>Dover</city><id>1536383</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.910072</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There are various ticket options, but two options are $60 per ticket or $150 for a VIP reception with Rep. Paul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Dover GOP site:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 13px"&gt;The newly formed Dover Republican Committee has arranged for Congressman Ron Paul to be their guest speaker at their inaugural Lincoln-Reagan dinner on March 25th. This will be Congressman Paul&amp;rsquo;s first visit to New Hampshire of the 2011-2012 election cycle. The Texas Congressman is widely assumed to be contemplating another run for President, and has a considerable base of support in New Hampshire from four years ago. Paul was the second place finisher of the WMUR straw poll at the Republican Annual Meeting, and enjoys support among both TEA Party Republicans and Independents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 13px"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled the Congressman chose to attend as our special guest,&amp;rdquo; said Chris Buck, Chairman of the Dover Republican Committee. &amp;ldquo;Congressman Paul has a history of advancing innovative ideas about the role of government, and we are looking forward to hearing what he has to say. This is a big deal for Dover Republicans.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NH GOP Chairman Jack Kimball (himself a Dover resident) will also speak, and will take the opportunity to welcome the potential presidential candidate to New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event is expected to draw attendees from across New Hampshire, and likely Maine and Massachusetts as well. To accommodate all the guests, the Dover GOP decided to hold the event at The Hellenic Center on Long Hill Road in Dover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : 13px"&gt;&amp;ldquo;We looked at what the Dover Chamber did for their meeting as a template,&amp;rdquo; says Buck. &amp;ldquo;The feedback on that event was universally positive.&amp;rdquo; Bon Ami Catering will cater the dinner, and tickets cost $60.&lt;/span&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To purchase tickets:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://dovergopdinner.eventbrite.com/"&gt;http://dovergopdinner.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd Puterbaugh</member_name><member_id>4083337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301096673000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298750266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Paul @ Dover GOP Dinner - March 25th</name><id>16715445</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301092200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/16715445/</event_url></item>