<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Temple Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304665</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-498-2500</phone><name>Criterion Cinema</name><city>New Haven</city><id>827452</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928467</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>[OPTIONAL DINNER BEFOREHAND AT KATZ'S DELI ON TEMPLE STREET (ACROSS THE STREET FROM THE THEATER) AT 5:30]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...not just another mindless monster movie about a killer Korean mutant tadpole!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seriously, the reviews are in at 93% at &lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/host/" target="_blank"&gt;Rotten Tomatoes&lt;/a&gt;, and even Anthony Lane of The New Yorker is raving about a movie  critics say &amp;quot;combines scares, laughs, satire, and social dynamics into a riveting, poignant piece of film making.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SYNOPSIS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IN THEATERS MARCH 9, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bong Joon-ho?s THE HOST is a giddy revelation--an inspired and unexpectedly moving contribution to the monster movie genre. Several years ago, a crooked government official from the United States ordered the dumping of toxic substances into Seoul?s Han River. Years later, the hapless Gang-du (Song Kang-ho) is working at his father?s food stand along the river, caring for his bright daughter Hyun-seo (Ko A-sung). But one day, a monstrous creature emerges from the water and embarks on a murderous rampage throughout the community, swallowing Hyun-seo whole. Gang-du?s bullish younger brother Park Nam-il (Park Hae-il) and sister Nam-joo (Bae Doo-na) condemn him for being such a failure, while their father angrily chastises them for being so cruel. But when Gang-du receives a cell phone call from Hyun-seo, the family must band together to reclaim her. Unfortunately, at this stage, the government has announced that the monster is the host of a dangerous virus, and anyone who has come into contact with it--namely Gang-du--must be isolated. As the monster continues to wreak havoc on Seoul, Gang-du, his father, and his siblings must learn to work together to bring Hyun-seo home. Bong Joon-ho?s third film, after BARKING DOGS NEVER BITE and MEMORIES OF MURDER, firmly establishes his status as one of the world?s most gifted storytellers. Not simply a monster movie spectacle--though it is certainly that and then some--THE HOST also works as a poignant family drama and a biting critique of America?s invasion of Iraq.&lt;br /&gt;______________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showtime is 7:10 at the Criterion, your contact is Michelle (815-6200).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175037038000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174592810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Host" at the Criterion....</name><id>5595225</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174863600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5595225/</event_url></item>