<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Chestnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02331</zip><lat>42.023537</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>781-934-7814</phone><name>The Wildflower Cafe</name><city>Duxbury</city><id>210769</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.683560</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Well, actually, we haven't done dessert yet, either; but this will be a first for the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group. This will also be Mike's first time coordinating an event, so please join us on Saturday, January 20th at 10:30 a.m. at The Wildflower Cafe in Duxbury.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Tucked into a row of businesses in Duxbury's commercial district, The Wildflower Cafe is unassuming from the outside, but upon entering, one finds a homey atmosphere and food that might be described as upscale (but affordable) comfort food. In other words, a good place for people who think that the FOOD, which often gets short shift when people decide to go out for breakfast, deserves as much consideration as the OUTING.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is a smaller venue than some, so we are limiting attendence to ten members. Please come and help make Mike's first event a fun one!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer: Mike S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Max/Min: At least 4 people by Noon on January 16th, max of 10 attendees.  &lt;br /&gt;*If the event sells out and you can and want to attend please RSVP No and in your comments section state &amp;quot;Please put me on the waitlist.  Date/Time&amp;quot;  (Of course, you want to include the date and time you RSVP'd.  RSVP's are listed in order but we don't know what day or time unless you tell us.)  One of the Organizers will then email you if a space opens up, or close registrations until you are able to update your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Note: If you RSVP Yes but are no longer able to attend please update your RSVP no later than 6pm the day before the event.  If the event is sold out and others are waiting to attend please update your RSVP by 10am the day before the event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: This is a Member's Only event.  RSVP Required to Attend unless otherwise stated by Group Organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: Maybe RSVP's are not allowed.  If you are a Maybe then RSVP No and put in your comments that you might be able (or would like) to attend and will update your RSVP if you are able to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: $2 per person.  Please pay the Event Organizer or one of the Group Organizers (if they are in attendance).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Rt 3, take Exit 10 and head north on Rt 3A (i.e., take a right off the ramp from Rt 3 North, a left off the ramp from Rt 3 South). You should almost immediately pass through a small cluster of businesses including Bennet Gas on your right.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Travel distance on Rt 3A is just about 1.5 miles. Shortly before you turn off Rt. 3A you'll see (on your right) a playground behind a chainlink fence. Also on your right at this point you'll note a yellow, diamond-shaped sign reading &amp;quot;School Bus Stop Ahead&amp;quot; and another with a symbol denoting a pedestrian crossing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Watch carefully on your right because you will quickly come to Chestnut St. The Milepost Restaurant is on the near right corner and signs indicate that Rt 3A bears left, while a right turn goes to S. Duxbury.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Go right onto Chestnut and follow it until it ends in the Business District. You will clearly see Duxbury Wine &amp;amp; Spirits straight ahead, as well as a tall flagpole. The building on your right, just before you enter the intersection, houses four businesses, including Halls Corner Store, Empire Cleaners, Duxbury Village Realtors and (farthest to the right) The Wildflower Cafe. You're there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1169480045000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1167853332000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast: The Final Frontier!</name><id>5362325</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1169307000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5362325/</event_url></item>