<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Somerville</address_2><address_1>45 Day Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395584</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-776-0552</phone><name>Sacco's Bowl Haven</name><city>Somerville</city><id>172732</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123570</lon></venue><fee><label>Bowling &amp; group expenses</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>To begin the countdown to &lt;i&gt;Socializing for Justice's 3rd birthday&lt;/i&gt; later this summer - we're heading back to where we held our 3rd event back in October 2006.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bowling for Justice&lt;/b&gt; at Sacco's Bowl Haven* in Davis Square!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Sacco's features candlepin bowling.  Whether it's your first time or you're a candlepin pro, just come to enjoy yourself.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us if you want to &lt;i&gt;cross-promote your events and campaigns&lt;/i&gt;, are &lt;i&gt;new to the area&lt;/i&gt; and looking for groups to get involved in, or you've been looking for &lt;i&gt;like-minded progressives&lt;/i&gt; to hang with in Boston.  &lt;b&gt;Newcomers always welcomed!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At SoJust events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;No Program. No Speaker. Just us.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hey organizers!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word &lt;b&gt;bring flyers for the free lit table&lt;/b&gt; - and there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*This is an all ages event - Sacco's doesn't serve or allow alcohol but you can bring in your dinner and we'll provide some snacks. The price is $10 to bowl + $2 to cover group expenses. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We are reserving 4 lanes at a group rate for 2 hours so RSVP to reserve a space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the website - just click '&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/"&gt;Messages&lt;/a&gt;'.  The &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/calendar"&gt;SoJust Calendar&lt;/a&gt; is packed with social justice-related events held throughout Greater Boston.  Help us keep it filled - tell us about events you hear about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From our FAQs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;It's not very easy for me to meet new people and I'm not really one for small talk at bars.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hear you. That's why at SoJust events, in addition to traditional name tags, we have &amp;quot;Ask Me About&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Looking For&amp;quot; tags. That way you can slap whatever you're into lately up on your shirt and wait for fellow SoJusters to approach you. These seem to do the trick of moving past the basic &amp;quot;what do you do for work? where do you live?&amp;quot; questions to conversations that lead to more substantial connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;What actually happens at events?&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll always be greeted by friendly folks who can help get you socializing, introduce you to people, and chat with you about questions or wishes. It's likely a few people will be there promoting their campaigns and issues (&lt;i&gt;yes, SoJust welcomes that sort of behavior&lt;/i&gt;). At our bigger events, there's always a literature table to toss down flyers, postcards, and other paraphenalia about events around town. Most importantly, we can pretty much guarantee there will be someone there you've never met before. As one of our members said, &amp;quot;You are bringing together people who might never get together otherwise - if that ain't a step towards justice I don't know what is.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt;  and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245883186000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243133211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bowling for Justice</name><id>10480303</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244583000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/10480303/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/6/2/global_8767634.jpeg</photo_url></item>