<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.419998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Capitol Theater</name><city>Arlington</city><id>385816</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.160004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>EXPLORING FRIENDSHIP  Join us for a unique improvisational theater experience to explore the meaning of Friendship in our lives and enjoy an optional dinner afterwards. This is how it works: The theatre company uses spontaneous acting to develop the content of the performance and through song, dance and movement it creates a show from interaction with the audience.  The theme for February 25th is FRIENDSHIP and how it is relevant in your life (and perhaps particularly as members of Mosaic). This will be a fun and powerful evening. Check out truestorytheater.org to learn more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trip's Cooridantor:&lt;/b&gt; Susan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Optional dinner:&lt;/b&gt; After the Show at PASHA located at 669A Massachusetts Ave– Turkish and Mediterranean Cuisine (many vegetarian choices)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP&lt;/b&gt; by February 20 so the Trip’s Coordinator can reserve seats and include an email addr for Susan to connect with you for further arrangements&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEET:&lt;/b&gt; At 7:15 PM in the lobby of The Arlington Center, &lt;b&gt;369 Massachusetts Ave*&lt;/b&gt; in Arlington so we can acquire seats together for the 7:30 PM performance.  Street parking is readily available. &lt;br /&gt;COST: True Story Theater - $15 at the door, and $5 if you are not a full paid member of Mosaic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Please Note that the Meetup's system selected 204 Mass ave (the movie theatre) but the actual address should be 369 Mass ave which is in the Arlington Center.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Susan will follow up with you when you rsvp.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298683502000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295734839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TRUE STORY THEATER at the Arlington Center</name><id>16147258</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298679300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/16147258/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/f/global_20779279.jpeg</photo_url></item>