<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Coolidge Corner is running the best series:  Raising the Barre - film versions of famous dance performances.  Five of us saw the first in the series, The BOLT, which was astounding - the perfect antidote to Black Swan.  Now, the Coolidge is showing a film that features three performances of Stravinsky works danced by the Mariinsky Ballet (the former Kirov).  The last, Rite of Spring, uses the original Nijinsky choreography - and is sure to be fascinating, explosive, and inspiring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be outside the theater at 10:45 and we will go someplace after for food and conversation.  Where depends on how many people show up.  Please join me.  I can't tell you how much I am looking forward to this event and would love to share it with my favorite movie people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last performance wasn't sold out, but it's probably prudent to get your tickets ahead of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is the text from the Coolidge web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE FIREBIRD&lt;br /&gt;With the Mariinsky Ballet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In February 1909, Sergey Pavlovich Diaghilev (1872 - 1929) had the opportunity to hear two short, but brilliant, orchestral works by the young composer Igor Stravinsky (1882 - 1971), at a concert in Saint Petersburg, Russia. Impressed by the promising composer, Diaghilev, the incomparable impresario of the Ballets Russes, commissioned some arrangements for his summer 1909 season in Paris. The Firebird was premiered on 25 June 1910 at the Paris Opera House, directed by Gabriel Pierné. The ballet was an immediate success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ballets Russes enabled Fokine to fully realize his ideas since he shared the same vision of ballet with Diaghilev, perceiving it as a total work of art where every element must be in harmony with the artistic project. As for Diaghilev, he found in Fokine the choreographer who could bring his enterprise the right amount of novelty needed to captivate but not clash with the audience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE WEDDING (LES NOCES)&lt;br /&gt;With the Mariinsky Ballet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This ballet in four scenes recounts the entire story of a Russian peasant wedding.&lt;br /&gt;Igor Stravinsky started to compose The Wedding using folk texts that he adapted, relating the details of a traditional Russian peasant wedding. The score for the first two scenes was finished in the spring of 1915 but the complete work was only finished two years later on April 4th, 1917 in Morges. Diaghilev decided to put these choreographic scenes on the program of his Ballets Russes in June 1923. The choreography was entrusted to Bronislava Nijinska, sister of the famous dancer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Le Sacre Du Printemps (The Rite of Spring)&lt;br /&gt;With the Mariinsky Ballet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The premier of Le Sacre du Printemps at the Théâtre des Champs-Élysées, Paris, on 29 May 1913 caused a veritable scandal. The audience was shocked by the primitive violence of the ballet. It was so radically rejected that the ballet was taken off after eight performances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although long forgotten, thanks to the relentless work of Millicent Hodson, Nijinsky's original choreography was recreated. After fifteen years' research, notably helped by Marie Rambert who had been Nijinsky's assistant, she managed to recreate the original Rite of Spring, which was performed by the Joffrey Ballet on 30 September 1987 in Los Angeles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this work, Igor Stravinsky further developed the rhythm and harmony, elements he had already experimented with in his first two ballets, the Firebird and Petrouchka.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Choreography by Michel Fokine, Bronislava Nijinska and Vaslav Nijinsky&lt;br /&gt;Starring Alexandra Iosifidi and Yekaterina Kondaurova&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mariinsky Theatre, St. Petersburg, 1h50m&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298290534000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295191844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raising the Barre:  Stravinsky and The Ballet Russes</name><id>16066790</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298217600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16066790/</event_url></item>