<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1180 Turnpike Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03071</zip><lat>42.776161</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Windblown Cross Country Skiing and Snowshoeing</name><city>New Ipswich</city><id>12931702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.900269</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/e/4/event_226516612.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beginners, novices, and pros!!! &lt;br /&gt;

 Pack up your overnight gear/essentials for an approx' 8 mile trek of NH's Wapack Trail, celebrating it's 90th year.  The hike begins at the trailhead for Temple Mtn, then South across Burton and Holt Peaks, a visit to Kidder Mtn, then on to Windblown Ski Area's Mountain Top Shelter atop Barrett Mountain in New Ipswich, NH to learn from each other about the gear and skills needed for an overnight backpack trip. &lt;br /&gt;

 After a restful evening in the shelter/tent/hammock we'll spend Sunday exploring Barrett and New Ipswich Mountains. &lt;br /&gt;

 Spot cars can be parked at the Windblown Ski Area for transport back to Temple Mtn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This trip is meant be a great opportunity for first time overnite trekkers to do a thorough try out of their gear and skills. It's hoped we're joined by more experienced backpackers who are willing to help out us beginners and novices. I'm asking a couple experienced trail adventurers to join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A maximum of 10 backpackers can be accommodated at the shelter site at a cost of $8 per person, with a maximum charge of $90 for the site. It's suggested to have 6 in the shelter itself, and 4 in tents. . We can mix it up as long as there's just 10 of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain Top Shelter has great distant views to the north and west. It is an Adirondack style shelter. There is an outhouse but no water, bring your own TP. Fires are permitted except in dry periods. For most of the year, water is available from a stream by hiking east down Barrett Mountain half way down to where a wide ski trail crosses and there is a small bridge. If you need water and the stream is dry, hike to the "Barn" on the trail map, just above the "Swimming Pond". There is a hydrant located on the far left corner with well water. Caution: The hydrant is not a pump. To operate it, lift the handle up as far as it goes and be sure to leave it in the down position when you are done. You may need to disconnect a garden hose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there are more than 10 people interested in this adventure, there's an additional shelter/tent site available at a cost of $8 per person,  $25 minimum, $90 max for the site. &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************** &lt;br /&gt;

 Friends of the Wapack &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.wapack.org/"&gt;http://www.wapack.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Windblown Ski Area Accomodations &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://windblownxc.com/accomodations/shelters-camping.html"&gt;http://windblownxc.com/accomodations/shelters-camping.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ******************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John &amp; Lise</member_name><member_id>42966142</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367787049000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364405580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wapack Trail 1 Night Beginner Backpack Trek</name><id>111331932</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>115200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367668800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/111331932/</event_url></item>