<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The waxing moon will&amp;nbsp;guide us on our journey&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;up the slow and meandering Exeter River.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Its forested banks will dance with shadowy shapes and night time sounds.&amp;nbsp; We might be startled by great blue herons taking flight or fish splashing ahead of us.&amp;nbsp; With bats circling overhead and maybe the sounds of owls or nighthawks, we'll wend our way along this dead-calm river in the waning light.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/7/8/event_55641112.jpeg" width="337" height="263" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Burritos&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lasolastaqueria.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3987cb"&gt;Las Olas Taqueria&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is right around the corner if you'd like to get a bite &amp;amp; a beer afterward. (The burritos are sized for two!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;: Arrive at&amp;nbsp;6pm, launch by 6:30pm, stay out until 8 or 8:30pm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;nbsp;is no motorboat traffic on this freshwater river.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: The air and water will be cooler by mid October but hopefully not too cold.&amp;nbsp; If you have questions about what to wear, please contact me.&amp;nbsp; If you don't have a wet or dry suit, then fleece and polyester garments (or undergarments) should be sufficient. You might also want to get a pair of wetsuit booties or waterproof boots if your feet get cold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;RENTAL KAYAK AVAILABLE - ask Larry for details&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Both kayaks have been rented.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lights&lt;/strong&gt;: Coast Guard regulations require that after sunset all paddle boats show a white light that can be seen from all sides.&amp;nbsp; This can be a light that attaches to your boat with a suction cup, or a light fastened to your body - preferably your head.&amp;nbsp; But, you don't want anything too bright because it will blind other paddlers and impede your ability to see and enjoy the moonlight.*&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;A couple of glow sticks attached to your bow &amp;amp; stern work very well.&amp;nbsp; Also bring a brighter flashlight or headlamp&amp;nbsp;so you can see the shore when we return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: Flashing or strobe lights should only be used in emergency situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;* Moonlight not guaranteed! And neither are the owls...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather,&amp;nbsp;water temperature, and other factors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&lt;/span&gt; hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fee is for meetup site expenses and planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the back of the park on the other side of the ball field.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318199863000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315926352000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Evening MOONLIGHT Paddle</name><id>33367322</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318024800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/33367322/</event_url></item>