<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Germania St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.314191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-368-5080</phone><name>Sam Adams Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>719460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>RSVPs were up to 119 and I just found out their maximum capacity is 75.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/sad.gif' border='0' alt='sad' /&gt;  Since I posted this awhile ago, please double check your calendar and make sure you can attend.  If so, please RSVP again.  I'm so sorry for this inconvenience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am asking that folks &lt;u&gt;NOT&lt;/u&gt; RSVP for more than one guest, and only then if you know for sure they'll attend.  I really want to minimize no-shows on this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE NOTE&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Due to everyone's youthful appearance, a valid picture ID will be required for admission. Identification issued outside of North America will not be accepted, but a passport is OK.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I am asking that people be willing to donate at least $5. It's not required, but they are doing this after hours &lt;u&gt;and&lt;/u&gt; they are making a special exception for us because they don't do group tours on Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is the private brewery where new beer is developed, some of which never makes it to production. They are happy to answer any general questions about brewing, etc., but they will not tell us how to make their beer. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;I'd like to go out afterward to eat and buy T.J. a beer to celebrate his birthday. We'll even sing Happy Birthday... (Be afwaid. Be vewwy, vewwy afwaid)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby wearing a big smile. You'll find me. ; )</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269349931000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>64</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268224309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sam Adams Brewery Tour</name><id>12837462</id><headcount>65</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269037800000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12837462/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/global_13572155.jpeg</photo_url></item>