<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 Concord Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.395687</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>National Association for Armenian Studies &amp; Research</name><city>Belmont</city><id>9705102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.173843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Frances Moore Lappé, famed author of the influential and seminal Diet for a Small Planet, will speak and receive the Humanist of the Year 2013 award from the Ethical Society of Boston on May 12. The award will be presented at 10:30 a.m. in the Lecture Hall at 395 Concord Ave., Belmont. All are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She will speak on "Reframing Environmentalism with an EcoMind” -- how ending global poverty and meeting the climate challenge are all of one piece. Her message will be carried through stories of possibility, from women in rural India reclaiming power over their food security to villagers in Africa effectively turning back the dessert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lappé is the co-founder of three national organizations that explore hunger and environmental crises, and solutions to those problems. Her most recent book is Ecomind: Changing the Way We Think To Create the World We Want, which will be available for purchase and signing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She appears frequently as a public speaker and on radio, and is a regular contributor to the Huffington Post and Alternet. She is also a contributing editor at Yes! Magazine and Solutions Journal. Articles featuring or written by Lappéhave also appeared in O: The Oprah Magazine, Harper's, The New York Times, The Los Angeles Times, The Nation, People and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368379844000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368130119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ESB Humanist of the Year Award</name><id>118608072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368369000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/118608072/</event_url></item>