<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Chestnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02331</zip><lat>42.023441</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-934-7814</phone><name>The Wildflower Cafe</name><city>Duxbury</city><id>210769</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.683228</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In case the title didn't give it away, this is our second attempt this year to go to The Wildflower Cafe. The first, back in June, resulted in a great Meetup... Just not at Wildflower, due to the restaurant making an unexpected and unprecedented change in their summer schedule.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This was your choice in our &amp;quot;W&amp;quot; poll, though, and we're happy to take this second chance to bring the group back to the place where we had our seventh event, back in 2007, because Wildflower still serves tasty comfort food in a fun, cottagey atmosphere in a space tucked into a row of businesses in Duxbury's commercial district. Unassuming from the outside, it turns out to be a place worth knowing about.  The Wildflower Cafe serves breakfast all day so you will have your choice of breakfast, lunch or both!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our annual Columbus Day lunch has become an SSDOMG tradition. This year, we look forward to sharing with you both an event and a place that have established themselves as perennials.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Wildflower Cafe&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Monday, October 11th @ 1:00pm &lt;br /&gt;8 Chestnut Street &lt;br /&gt;Duxbury, MA 02331 &lt;br /&gt;781-934-7814 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Location:&lt;/b&gt; Outside the front door if it's nice out. We will then go in together as a group. Otherwise, inside the Lobby. If you arrive after we are seated ask for the Meetup Group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: This restaurant does not accept reservations but we are able to call-ahead.  We may have to wait a couple minutes to be seated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Mike and Angela &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; Min of 6 people by 7pm on Thursday, October 7th. Max of 14 people.  (Increased max to 14 people @ 4:30pm on Sun 10/10/10.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; One per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fees:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members &amp;amp; Guest - FREE, Group Members - $2, Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; 10pm on Sunday, October 10th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page.  (Deadline extended to 10pm on Sun 10/10/10 @ 4:30pm on Sun 10/10/10.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the wait staff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/b&gt; We will be dining come rain, snow, sleet, hail, storm, or sun.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on &amp;quot;Weather&amp;quot;). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;From Rt 3, take Exit 10 and head north on Rt 3A; i.e., take a right off the ramp from Rt 3 North (coming from Cape Cod), a left off the ramp from Rt 3 South(coming from Braintree/Boston). You should almost immediately pass through a small cluster of businesses including Bennet Gas on your right. Note that if you come to a traffic light and see a mall with a Hannaford supermarket and an Ocean State Job Lot straight across from you, you've gone the wrong way off the ramp and need to turn around!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Travel distance on Rt 3A is just about 1.5 miles. Shortly before you turn off Rt. 3A you'll see (on your right) a playground behind a chain link fence. Also on your right at this point you'll note a yellow, diamond-shaped sign reading &amp;quot;School Bus Stop Ahead&amp;quot; and another with a symbol denoting a pedestrian crossing. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Watch carefully on your right because you will quickly come to Chestnut St. The Milepost Restaurant is on the near right corner and signs indicate that Rt 3A bears left, while a right turn goes to S. Duxbury. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Go right onto Chestnut and follow it until it ends in the Business District. You will clearly see Duxbury Wine &amp;amp; Spirits straight ahead, as well as a tall flagpole. The building on your right, just before you enter the intersection, houses four businesses, including Halls Corner Store, Empire Cleaners, Duxbury Village Realtors and (farthest to the right) The Wildflower Cafe. You're there! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287099842000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284768580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Perennial Blooms for Columbus Day!</name><id>14808787</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286816400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/14808787/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/b/global_14765243.jpeg</photo_url></item>