<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7416 Mountain Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05672</zip><lat>44.530888</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Spruce Camp Base Lodge</name><city>Stowe</city><id>10309462</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.781349</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/2/event_183660802.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;How about a weekend at Stowe? As you may already know, Stowe is a premier resort in the Northeast with the best terrain and consistent snow. &lt;br /&gt;

 From the legendary "Front Four" for advanced skiers to the gentle Toll Road the resort will please all levels and the effective ski terrain is big enough and lifts are well-thought and speedy enough that it never feels too crowded even on holiday weekends. &lt;br /&gt;

 Here is the deal you may consider to purchase for $175 Per Person Dble: &lt;a href="http://skicbsports.com/stowe-dec.htm"&gt;http://skicbsports.com/stowe-dec.htm&lt;/a&gt; and it includes: &lt;br /&gt;

  2 nights lodging, " Mountaineer Inn At Stowe " &lt;br /&gt;

  2 day all lift ticket at Stowe (regular price is $92 per day!) &lt;br /&gt;

  2 Continental Breakfasts &lt;br /&gt;

  discounted rentals and lesson &lt;br /&gt;

  Free shuttle service throughout the area &lt;br /&gt;

 The Hotel features include indoor pool, hot tub, restaurant and tavern. &lt;br /&gt;

 Live Entertainment at several location nightly nearby. &lt;br /&gt;

 PLAN: (All Ideas are welcome!) &lt;br /&gt;

 Friday &lt;br /&gt;

  Arrival &lt;br /&gt;

  TDB &lt;br /&gt;

 Saturday &lt;br /&gt;

  Have breakfast at the hotel and meet around 8am at the mount &lt;br /&gt;

  4:15 meet at Matterhorn for Apre Ski/bite and a drink &lt;br /&gt;

  Chill at the Inn (relax in room, go swimming, or chill at hot tub or sauna) &lt;br /&gt;

  7:00pm Grab dinner at the restaurant the Inn or TBA &lt;br /&gt;

  TBD-TBD-TBD &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunday &lt;br /&gt;

  12:30pm meet at lodge at the top of Four runner quad at Mt. Mansfield for lunch &lt;br /&gt;

 OTHER ACTIVITIES &lt;br /&gt;

 There is an excellent groomed x-country ski area in town. Ice climbing in Smuggler's Notch. Hiking (snowshoes can be rented). Mt. Mansfield is the tallest peak of Vermont and has magnificent views of neighboring high peaks of NY and NH. &lt;br /&gt;

 Dog sledding: &lt;a href="http://www.stowe.com/activities/dog_sled/"&gt;http://www.stowe.com/activities/dog_sled/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Snowshoe tour: &lt;a href="http://www.stowe.com/activities/nordic/page"&gt;http://www.stowe.com/activities/nordic/page&lt;/a&gt;... &lt;br /&gt;

 cross country skiing: &lt;a href="http://www.stowe.com/activities/nordic/cros"&gt;http://www.stowe.com/activities/nordic/cros&lt;/a&gt;... &lt;br /&gt;

 __________________________________________________________________________________-As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. I can not be held responsible for injuries or consequences of accidents while participating in any activities or during vehicular transport. Users assume all responsibility of liability and shall hold the organizer or assistant organizers blameless for any injuries or expenses sustained while on this event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Natalia </member_name><member_id>9105996</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355674455000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Russian Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>expatrussian-64</urlname><id>1112191</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Families with Russian Kids, Moms Club, Playgroups</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354201396000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ski/Snowboard at Stowe VT (Dec 14 - Dec 16)</name><id>93327162</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>158400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355515200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/expatrussian-64/events/93327162/</event_url></item>