<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Notes: This is not a meetup event. Roots and Wings Healing Arts Center and Ann are co-sponsoring this event for all who wish to participate. We're sharing this opportunity and experience with you, as it is always an easy way to align and to feel gooooood; and this is how you allow all that you desire to come to you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;We invite you to come and immerse yourself in the space of spirit with peace, love and feeling good. Come to relax and align with who you really are and to open yourself to the joy in all that you are. This is always a most wonderful evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evening will consist of 2-3 guided meditations. All you'll have to do is listen to Ann’s voice as she guides you through the meditations, each one usually about 15 - 20 minutes long, with discussions in between.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The selection this evening will be focused on connecting to Spirit and your ability to dream and create.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;***If you like, you can bring a mat, blanket, and pillow to fully relax lying down. Or you can use what's available there, too, of course. &lt;u&gt;Please arrive around 7:05 to get settled, so we can start on time.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All are welcome. The class is appropriate whether you are a beginner to meditating, or experienced. Please invite others to sign up and join you! Forward this to your friends, family and groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been registered to capacity lately, so either RSVP'ing thru this site, or registration is required. Non- meetup guests should register by sending name, e-mail, and phone number to: annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com. They’ll receive confirmation of their registration and a reminder.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;If your plans change, please change your RSVP so we will not be turning away people unnecessarily, as we have done in the past.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;i&gt;“I really did enjoy your guided meditations tonight. I arrived here feeling so exhausted and found during the experiences tonight an opening and energy re awakening inside. It was very healing for me to have this experience, and there were many tools I will leave here with.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295398560000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293399002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Evening of Guided Meditations for the Community </name><id>15823503</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295136900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/15823503/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>