<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>536 Danbury Road (Route 7)</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06776</zip><lat>41.541579</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 350-CORN</phone><name>Larson's Family Farm Haunted Corn Maze</name><city>New Milford</city><id>1390818</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.421128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Gang, &lt;br /&gt;   I've been wanting to do a haunted corn maze anyway, and the bucket list is doing one Sunday, so I'm cross-posting this from their site. Hope you can join us!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil 203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut's best Haunted Corn Maze and Zombie Graveyard at Larson's Farm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to Connecticut's best Haunted Corn Maze and Zombie Graveyard at Larson's Farm in New Milford, CT, during the scariest time of the year. Adventure seekers are invited to discover for themselves if the terrifying tales of Larson’s corn field are true. Enter if you dare, but as you wander the more than three-and-a-half acres of frightening paths, watch out for the lost souls and undead lurking amid the stalks. And, beware of ghostly beings and predators searching for their next victims.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bigger than a Haunted House or Haunted Mansion and much more frightening than any Haunted Woods! If you make it out alive, you'll know why Corn will never be the same.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;# This haunt is not recommended for very small children, those who are easily frightened,&lt;br /&gt;and people with heart conditions.&lt;br /&gt;# The ground is uneven, so please wear good walking shoes&lt;br /&gt;# There are no refunds.&lt;br /&gt;# Be sure you're brave enough to face the maze before purchasing a ticket.&lt;br /&gt;# There is no smoking and no alcohol permitted on premises.&lt;br /&gt;# Cameras &amp;amp; flashlights are not permitted in the haunt.&lt;br /&gt;# No running.&lt;br /&gt;# Please keep your hands to yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What? Haunted Corn Maze&lt;br /&gt;Where? Larson's Farm 536 Danbury Rd (Route 7) in New Milford, CT Directions below.&lt;br /&gt;When? Sunday, October 17th at 7pm&lt;br /&gt;How? Tickets are $15.00. Over 20 attendees and we'll get a $1 off each. They accept cash, MC and Visa.&lt;br /&gt;Why? Why the heck not? You did see children of the corn right?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Haunted Corn at Larson's Farm has relocated for 2010 to a larger, more evil, haunted field at 536 Danbury Road (Route 7) in New Milford, CT. Just over the Brookfield border and only minutes from Danbury and Bethel. Traveling North on Route 7 the haunt is 1 mile North from the end of the new Route 7 expressway on the left hand side. Traveling South on Route 7 the haunt is 0.8 miles South of New Milford High School on the right hand side. Click here for door to door directions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287360646000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287005728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Haunted Corn Maze and Zombie Graveyard</name><id>15100714</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287356400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15100714/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>