<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 JFK St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Le's Vietamese Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120180</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;La Danse&lt;/b&gt; (2009) dir Frederick Wiseman [159 min] &lt;br /&gt;Playing at The Brattle Theater at 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; If you RSVP YES after 7:30 pm Tuesday 12/8 you are also promising to be at the restaurant around 5:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Paris Opera Ballet is one of the world’s great ballet companies. In his new film &lt;b&gt;LA DANSE&lt;/b&gt;, acclaimed documentarian Frederick Wiseman(Titicult Follies and Belfast Maine) follows the rehearsals and performances of seven ballets and provides an intimate look at this legendary company. The film shows the work involved in administering the company and the coordinated and collaborative efforts of choreographers, ballet masters, dancers, musicians, and designers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frederick Wiseman is one of the world’s great documentary filmmakers. Eschewing voice-over narration, talking head interviews and onscreen bluster, Wiseman stands back and lets his subjects speak for themselves for as long as it takes to tell their stories. This technique has resulted in some of the most powerful documentaries of the past 50 years. Brattle Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;PLEASE NOTE: The film starts at 7:00 PM  is over 2 1/2 hours long-and its a Friday night. When you RSVP please indicate if you can attend our pre-movie meetup at Le's at 5:30. Since Fred Wiseman is a Boston native, I suggest pre-ordering tickets at The Brattle's online site: &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the finest dance films ever made, but there’s more to it than that. If you did not already know the names of the stars of the Paris Opera Ballet — Aurélie Dupont and Laetitia Pujol stand out particularly — you will nonetheless have acquired an almost tactile sense of who they are. “How can we know the dancer from the dance?” wondered William Butler Yeats in his poem “Among School Children.” It’s a simple and also endlessly mysterious question, one that Mr. Wiseman, in his patient, meticulous, magical way, both restates and answers.   NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wiseman’s films are as much living organisms as they are subjective portraits.  Time Out New York&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;La Danse will screen at The Brattle througout the weekend  but this will be the only time Fred Wiseman will be present as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meetup sign at the restuarant and then again at The Brattle before the film starts. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258426346000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Paris Ballet - Director Fred Wiseman Present</name><id>11891585</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260570600000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11891585/</event_url></item>