<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From website:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://ct.org/Growth_Network.asp" class="linkified"&gt;http://ct.org/Growth_Network.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Our mission is to stimulate collaboration, innovation and entrepreneurial activity between leaders and executives of the business and education communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to participate and share thoughts and ideas on howwe can best work together to stimulate growth, create innovation and spur economic activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

We feel it&amp;rsquo;s important to challenge the status quo, and construct a solid foundation for future growth by utilizing and developing talent that exists today in our region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Name: &amp;nbsp;Xcellr8 Innovation Cell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Location: Tolland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cell Leader: Kevin Bouley, President of Nerac, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meeting time and location: 8:00 to 9:00 am, the second Thursday of each month at Nerac, Inc offices in Tolland, One Technology Drive, Tolland, 06084&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact: Paige Rasid, (860) 289-0878, x335 prasid@ct.org&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the Connecticut Growth Network?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The Connecticut Growth Network is a discussion and action forum of statewide leaders, consisting of small peer-led, local networking groups or cells.Each local cell is comprised of technology executives, entrepreneurs, investors and professional service providers with an interest in discussing the issues affecting Connecticut&amp;rsquo;s technology future. Local cells also introduce groups of tech leaders for the purpose of possible business collaboration, development and assistance. The Connecticut Growth Network was established by the Connecticut Technology Council in 2004.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Growth Network connects companies, entrepreneurs, investors or dealmakers and creates an involved community of concerned leaders in the technology industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Once a month, over breakfast, lunch, or dinner, Local Cell Leaders convene five to fifteen friends or colleagues to discuss a specific issue -- an important issue facing their companies, communities, or the State. Occasionally, a guest speaker is invited. And sometimes, there is no planned program, but just a desire to revisit with peers and help solve a pressing issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Local cells may be organized by vertical industry, profession, target market, special interest, or simply geography. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

There are four key goals for the Connecticut Growth Network:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to stimulate direct collaboration and innovation between participants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to knit together the diverse geography of the State's industries and intellectual centers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3. to advance a competitive economic agenda for the State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4. to secure major investments in the culture of innovation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The Connecticut Technology Council currently has four established networking discussion groups or cells who meet monthly. The groups meet in Stamford, New Haven, University of Hartford and Tolland. Look for these events on the www.ct.org calendar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Information only. Please RSVP through event details below.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368117604000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>startupcafe</urlname><id>1540019</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Startup Cafe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326252096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Xcellr8 Innovation Cell</name><id>dsvhlcyrhbmb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368100800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/startupcafe/events/113543122/</event_url></item>