<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to invite you to a seminar given by Mother Clare Watts, who is a very special Teacher. She wrote a book about her life and personal spiritual journey. It is called Giving Birth to God: a woman's path to enlightenment. She was a home birth midwife for 17 years and a mother of 4 children.  Currently, she lives in Colorado and travels throughout the country giving lectures and classes about peace and having a one on one connection to your inner Self.  She only comes to Boston 3 times a year so you don't want to miss it. The fee is to cover her airfare.  Please join me at this special event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gratitude&lt;br /&gt;Gratitude seems like such a basic and small thing. After all, we say &amp;quot;thank you&amp;quot; many times each day. So isn't this gratitude? Yes, it is, in a small way. But gratitude can be a much larger element of your life, and actually can generate the power to move mountains. Why is this so? What if you are too mad about what has occurred in your life to feel gratitude? This seminar will help you understand not only what large scale gratitude is, but also how to move from resentment and anger into the healing power of feeling grateful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This seminar will be held from 10am - 2pm and a light lunch is included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings,&lt;br /&gt;Rev Gabrielle&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542141000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189567623000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Gratitude</name><id>6341672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189864800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/6341672/</event_url></item>