<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please read the entire Write Up and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver before signing up for this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Event Rating: Moderate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Distance: 5.5 Miles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Time Duration: 3 Hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Blaze Orange: REQUIRED&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/9/e/event_135745502.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great Swamp covers a total land area of 3349 acres. Acreage is divided among the following cover types: wetlands (2262 acres), forest cover (897 acres), agricultural land (eighty-eight acres) and other lands (102 acres; brush, utilities etc.). The area contains extensive forested freshwater wetlands, dominated by red maple swamps with some cedar swamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The paths are wide and the terrain is relatively flat. This time of year, everything should be blooming. Also the Osprey should be around. (Large Prehistoric Birds that live in the Swamp). Bring binoculars if you have them and/or your camera with a telephoto lens.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hiking distance is 5 1/2 miles which should take about 3 hours. Bring Snacks, Sunscreen and Bug Spray.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Minimum of 1 Liter of drinking water per person is Required.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hunting season continues in the DEM Management areas and all hikers are required to wear at minimum of 200 square inches of florescent orange on their person above the waist.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Address of DEM Office at Great Swamp:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;277 Great Neck Road, West Kingston, RI 02891&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions: From Providence, take Rt 95 South to RI 4 South to US 1 South to RI 138 West. Follow RI 138 West to Liberty Lane in West Kingston (Look for the sign in the above photo). Follow Liberty Lane to the end at the Railroad Tracks and turn Left onto a gravel road (Great Neck Road). Stay straight on Great Neck Road for about 1 Mile past the DEM office and maintenance building and continue straight on this gravel road to the parking lot at a barred gateway.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Note: Do NOT take Liberty Lane off RI 2; it does NOT connect to Liberty Lane off RI 138.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Also, after the DEM office on Great Neck Road there are 2 left turns, Do NOT take either one, stay straight on Great Neck Road to the parking lot at the end.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Safety First!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John N</member_name><member_id>11460346</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368405568000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368132878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Swamp, Weber Hike # 1</name><id>118615212</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368370800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/118615212/</event_url></item>