<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of the few indie films of the summer that everyone agrees is a must see.  And there's no better way to escape the summer heat than a good movie.  Note that the Kendall is showing the film on two screens. We are going to the *5:05* show.  Early purchase of tickets is strongly advised.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In The Kids Are All Right, comedic surprise is combined with poignant emotional truth in a funny, vibrant, and richly drawn portrait of a modern family. Nic and Jules (Annette Bening and Julianne Moore) are married and share a cozy suburban Southern California home with their teenage children, Joni and Laser (Mia Wasikowska and Josh Hutcherson). Nic and Jules—or, when referred to jointly by Joni, &amp;quot;Moms&amp;quot;—gave birth to and raised their children, and built a family life for the four of them. As Joni prepares to leave for college, 15-year-old Laser presses her for a big favor. He wants Joni, now 18, to help him find their biological father; the two teenagers were conceived by artificial insemination. Against her better judgment, Joni honors her brother's request and manages to make contact with &amp;quot;bio-dad&amp;quot; Paul (Mark Ruffalo), an easygoing restaurateur. The kids find themselves drawn to the confirmed bachelor's footloose style—especially in contrast to Nic, a principled doctor who has long established their house rules. Jules, who has been looking to start a new career in landscaping, also strikes up a rapport with Paul. As Paul comes into the lives of the forthright four, an unexpected new chapter begins for them as family ties are defined, re-defined, and then re-re-defined. Directed by Lisa Cholodenko (High Art, Laurel Canyon). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(I'd list all the good reviews but it would seem too much bragging.  Seriously -- not a mediocre one in the bunch!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film, I'll be near the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279656846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Kids Are All Right</name><id>14160980</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280005200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/14160980/</event_url></item>