<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>505 Amherst St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.793477</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-882-6923</phone><name>Nashua Community College</name><city>Nashua</city><id>1083067</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.523828</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Topic: A Full Day of Safety Seminars, Safety Events, and Vendor / Manufacturer Displays. If people are interested in going to this annual event, sign up online with FAA and here. Maybe if there's enough interest we can drive or fly up for the day. Stay as long as you want and attend the events you're interested in. I'll post a line up as soon as I find one. Select Number: EA6549411 Description: This year marks the Expo's 14th anniversary and will feature Doug Stewart, a Designated Pilot Examiner, Master CFI, and flight school owner as the keynote speaker. Enjoy a full day of safety education, tour numerous vendor and manufacturer displays, and meet and speak with FAA personnel from Air Traffic Control, Flight Standards, the FAA Safety Team, Runway Safety, Airports Division, and the Aviation &amp;amp; Space Education Program. Click on the link below to see all of the details and register for this exciting annual event! To view further details and registration information for this seminar, click here. The sponsor for this seminar is: The FAA Safety Team The FAA Safety Team (FAASTeam) is committed to providing equal access to this meeting/event for all participants. If you need alternative formats or services because of a disability, please communicate your request as soon as possible with the person in the 'Contact Information' area of the meeting/event notice. Note that two weeks is usually required to arrange services. The following credit(s) are available for the WINGS/AMT Programs: Basic Knowledge 3 - 1 Credit&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367171496000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365251301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"New England Aviation Safety Expo"</name><id>112979772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367064000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/112979772/</event_url></item>