<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cambridge</address_2><address_1>11 Springfield Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)492-4495</phone><name>Ole Mexican Grill</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>145665</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello, all -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The date is 9th December for this brunch! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully, it will provide us all with a much-needed reprieve from the hectic days of the Holiday season. And also add some piquante to the chill that will most likely be in the air from the Boston winter! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Olé has gotten some wonderful reviews, and is known for both its traditional and non-traditional Mexican menu items, as well as its famous guacamole which is made by hand right at your table. It should be a fun time with good food and the usual interesting conversation at the tables. Hoping to see many of you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Antonina&lt;br /&gt;cell : 917.531.4928&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;It is a short bus ride from Lechmere or Harvard Square, and a short walk from Central Square for those taking public transportation. There is a public parking lot directly behind Ole´and there is usually street parking available, as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving:&lt;br /&gt;Springfield Street is a small side street on the northeast side of the Cambridge and Beacon/Hampshire Street intersection (1369 Coffee Shop is on that corner). Olé is the first building on the right as you turn onto Springfield from that intersection. It has a large sign in front and is a brightly painted building that is hard to miss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to call me if you need further directions on the 9th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link for Olé's website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.olegrill.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.olegrill.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And here is a bit of a review from the Phoenix:&lt;br /&gt;Erwin Ramos isn?t Mexican, but he cooks like he is. The executive chef at Olé Mexican Grill, Ramos and his brother Ranan opened the restaurant in 1996 to bring authentic Mexican cuisine to Cambridge. The kicker is that the Ramoses were born in the Philippines. But because Mexico?s culinary roots commingle with those of his native islands, Erwin has used knowledge of both to benefit us all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And it has. The brothers bring decidedly non-Mexican fare to Olé?s menu. Not a burrito or hard-shell taco is in sight ? and that?s a good thing, because those Americanized versions of Mexican dishes might accidentally sway you from Ramos?s pozole Olé, a pork-and-hominy stew that will make you forget you?ve ever had it with beef and potatoes. A steaming, vat-like bowl of cubed pork, hominy, and broth comes with a side plate of lime wedges, diced red onion, shredded lettuce, julienne radishes, chilies, cilantro, and corn-tortilla crisps. Think Vietnamese pho, Mexican-style: you can add any accoutrements your palate can handle, and decide whether to eat it with a fork or a spoon. Pozole originated in Mexico?s Pacific coastal region and is normally served at Christmastime. Luckily for you, Olé serves it year-round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197390100000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195695045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Olé Mexican Brunch - 9 December!</name><id>6785508</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197214200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6785508/</event_url></item>