<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>670 W Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.314977</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-853-23--</phone><name>Quinsigamond Community College</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1049099</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.796795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The 13th Annual Pet Rock Festival will be held on Sunday, Sept. 11, 2011 at Quinsigamond Community College in Worcester from noon to 5 p.m. Tickets are $13 for adults and $5 for kids under 12. Note, this is a $1 increase for adults; Pet Rock Fest has not raised its ticket prices in more than six years. Brought to us by &amp;#147;Top Dog&amp;#148; sponsor, TD Bank, and &amp;#147;Fat Cat&amp;#148; sponsor New England Hospice, as well as Especially for Pets, VCA and more, Pet Rock will once again feature all your favorites: live music, the Adoptable Pet Parade, a Cat Photo Contest, vegetarian food, kids rides, speakers and 100s of animal related vendors and organizations. This year, Mass Vest-a-Dog is hosting a &amp;#147;Tribute to 9-11,&amp;#148; which will include demonstrations and representatives from local police departments, rescue organizations, therapy dogs and more. Visit here for our updated list of nonprofit animal organizations who are signed up to particpate. Visit here for our sponsors and vendors. Are you interested? Email petrockfest@gmail.com. Pet Rock Fest on Facebook. Pet Rock on MySpace. The Pet Rock Fest and the Worcester Animal Rescue League are proud to announce that responsible pit bull owners can attended Pet Rock 2011 with their canines, muzzle free! An exemption from the Responsible Pit Bull Ownership Ordinance has been made to allow responsible dog owners to enjoy a fun day at Pet Rock with their canine best friend! Dogs of all breeds attending must be well behaved with dogs and people, leashed (no retractable leashed), and have a valid dog license.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315864591000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315590692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Visit the NEBBC Booth at PetRock in Worcester! Scavenger Hunt &amp; Prizes!</name><id>32907772</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315756800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/32907772/</event_url></item>