<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us at the Coolidge for an evening of burlesque education and entertainment to benefit The Great Boston Burlesque Exposition (www.Burlesque-Expo.com).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, Burlesque historian David Kruh (author of Always Something Doing: Boston's Infamous Scully Square) takes us on a tour of The Old Howard, Boston's most famous burlesque hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next, we get to watch Barbara Stanwyk in the in a forgotten film noir gem Lady of Burlesque (1943). This movie is based on a novel by Gypsy Rose Lee, a real-life burlesquer and the inspiration for the musical Gypsy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, after the movie, the Boston Babydolls Burlesque Troupe take the stage for an eye-popping, bumping, grinding, show! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost is $12. All proceeds benefit The Professional Burlesque Society, a non-profit educational organization that helps burlesque, sideshow, and vaudeville performers educate themselves not only about their performance skills, but also about the realities of doing business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, we will be meeting after the film. Nicole, your friendly meetup assistant organizer, will be holding a Meetup sign at the front of the theater after the program ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. If anyone has any suggestions for where to meet afterwards, please message Nicole. It needs to be near the Coolidge and open after 9 pm. Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170893399000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169090858000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Babydolls/Lady of Burlesque</name><id>5403718</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170720000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5403718/</event_url></item>