<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Groton St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01432</zip><lat>42.563055</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nashua River Rail Trail</name><city>Ayer</city><id>1482820</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.587999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Organizer: chris Link 617-877-9385. ===== Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them. Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate. ===== What we're doing We did these rides last year as a way to keep the legs active on the weekends that we have to schlep the kids to and fro so I thought we would repeat them again this year. The plan is to ride every other weekend throughout the spring, summer, and fall. While we won't be racing, and there will opportunities to stop along the way, I want to keep a steady pace of 12 - 15 MPH once we get moving. We will use the Nashua River Rail Trail, which is a former railroad right of way that travels about 12 miles from end-to-end through the towns of Ayer, Groton, Pepperell and Dunstable and part of Nashua. It offers a 10-foot wide paved surface for the entire length and travels along a varied landscape offering numerous scenic overlooks and opportunities to see wildlife. Guests are not permitted - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. ===== Trip Summary The objective is to ride at about a 12 - 15 MPH pace. We will ride from Ayer to the northen end of the trail and return. This should be about 24 miles round trip. While I have been on this trail many times before I did all of my current research for this trip using the Internet. You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety. Click for information about the Nashua River Rail Trail (MA Department of Conservation &amp;amp; Recreation) ===== Weather Unlike hiking, biking is no fun in the rain. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel. I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the ride and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. Click for the current weather forecast (noaa.gov) ===== Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies Below is a list describing the minimum items required to participate in this event. Helmet: You must wear a properly sized and adjusted bicycle helmet that has been tested and meets the uniform safety standard issued by the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC). Other Essential Gear: Liquids to stay hydrated and food to stay nourished. White headlight and red taillight if we will be riding before sunrise or after sunset. A multi-purpose tool or small repair kit. A spare tube. Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip. If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone. ===== Directions we will meet at the parking lot in Ayer. Look up the rail trail on the internet if you don't know where that is. Click for customizable driving directions (google.com) ===== Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the bicycle safety tips described at www.massbike.org; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be setting up my bike behind a blue subaru outback.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris L</member_name><member_id>6602385</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346717999000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346601696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last minute Nashua River Trail bike meetup.</name><id>80501072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346675400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/80501072/</event_url></item>