<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.253.5927</phone><name>MIT's Rockwell Cage Gymnasium </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>817808</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096264</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a small-group event, so please sign up only if you're sure you can go and if you are willng to buy your ticket in advance.  Please sign up before Wednesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why don't a few of us join the Greater Boston Divorced and Separated Meetup Group for an annual event that has to be seen to be believed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are available, in advance, online, please buy them that way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is the Friday After Thanksgiving? A grand event that could only happen at MIT! Participants link their mini chain reactions together forming one mega chain reaction – set off at the end as the event's thrilling culmination.Boysheadgear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1,500 people from all over watch and participate in this fun-for-all-ages "extreme" event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it's the reaction induced between one creative contraption and another equally crafty contrivance, or the joyful reactions sparked on the faces of the spectators, the MIT Museum's Friday After Thanksgiving (F.A.T.) Chain Reaction is a one-of-a-kind, must-be-seen-to-be-believed engineering feat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artist/inventor Arthur Ganson masterminds the choreography of this Rube Goldberg machine, assisted by MIT teams and participants who range from Girl Scout troops to artists and engineers. Spectators talk to the teams, engage in spontaneous contraption making and fill the seats waiting for the magic moment when all the machines are linked up to set off a chain reaction with a surprise ending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making a chain reaction allows people to explore their own creativity, and see how their unique contraptions relate to a larger whole. No matter how different the chain reactions, inevitably, with a little string and duct tape, they all work together beautifully. &lt;br /&gt;

 How does it work?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The MIT Museum's F.A.T. Chain Reaction event allows people to join the fun as spectators or as participants. Participants can register to bring their own contraptions. Artist and inventor Arthur Ganson, renowned chain reaction creator, is on hand to help with connections and play master of ceremonies for the action. &lt;br /&gt;

 Can anybody do it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course! Participants range from Girl Scout troops to artists and engineers, from MIT clubs to high schools and family teams. Teams have come from as far away as Michigan and California!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;F.A.T. Chain Reaction &lt;br /&gt;

 November 23, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 1:00 - 4:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;

 Rockwell Cage Gym &lt;br /&gt;

 Spectators: $15 for adults or $12.50 in advance, &lt;br /&gt;

 $5 for children ages 5-17, students, seniors and MIT ID-holders. &lt;br /&gt;

 Free for children under 5. &lt;br /&gt;

 Spectator fee includes free same-day admission to the MIT Museum, open until 6:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron R.</member_name><member_id>4515948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353705126000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353263689000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>witness the Friday After Thanksgiving Chain Reaction at MIT</name><id>91914892</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353693600000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/91914892/</event_url></item>