<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Storrow Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.869.8786</phone><name>Esplanade at the Hatch Shell</name><city>Boston</city><id>931749</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085946</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Warren J. is hosting this event&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Summer means outdoor concerts at the Hatch Shell on the Charles. While everyone wants to be there on July 4, the more enjoyable concerts are the less crowded events during the summer. Join us for a picnic and concert by the Boston Landmarks Orchestra led by Christopher Wilkins, conductor. The theme is “Landmark Virtuosos” and features &lt;em&gt;Concertstruck for Four Horns&lt;/em&gt; by Schumann&lt;em&gt;, Sinfonia Concertante&lt;/em&gt; by Haydn and &lt;em&gt;Symphony No. 4 (“Italian”)&lt;/em&gt; by Mendelssohn.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We’ll gather starting at 5:30PM for socializing and a pot-luck picnic. Look for our big blue tarp near the front center of the oval. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bring a picnic item to share and your own beverage&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Use your imagination as to what people might like; appetizers, main dishes, salads, desserts are all welcome. We’ll provide the plates, cups, utensils, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Important: Bring a (low preferable) lawn chair (beach chair) or blanket.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; The Hatch Shell is on the Charles River Esplanade next to Storrow Drive in Back Bay at Arlington Street. Detailed directions are at the Hatch Shell website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking&lt;/strong&gt; is very limited. The right lane of Storrow Drive westbound between Berkeley and Gloucester is available for parking starting about 30 minutes before the concert (6:30). These spaces fill rapidly. Most Back Bay and Beacon Hill streets are resident-only parking. There are metered spaces on Beacon between Arlington and Clarendon as well as on Berkeley, Clarendon and Charles Streets that are open for visitor parking, although some are no parking until 6:00 for the rush hour. &lt;strong&gt;Those on Beacon tend to empty out of daytime parkers around 5:00. Check the signs to be safe. Meters are in operation until 6:00; make sure you feed enough quarters to get you to that hour.&lt;/strong&gt; The most convenient and reasonably priced garage is the Boston Common Underground Garage. Entrance is on Charles Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By MBTA (recommended):&lt;/strong&gt; Take the Red Line to Charles/MGH or the Green Line to Arlington; each is about a ten minute walk away. Back Bay Station (Orange Line/commuter rail) is a 15 minute walk away.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;RAIN CANCELS THE EVENT!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ww.landmarksorchestra.com, &lt;a href="http://www.hatchshell.com/"&gt;www.hatchshell.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345869773000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340923963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concert and Picnic at the Hatch Shell</name><id>71188602</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345676400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/71188602/</event_url></item>