<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>900 East Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.527122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comfort Inn</name><city>Meriden</city><id>1046895</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.772480</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wednesday, March 10, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Comfort Inn. 900 East Main St. Meriden, CT&lt;br /&gt;7:00 to 9:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MARCH MADNESS: FREE To All Attendees&lt;br /&gt;Register Now at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=242" target="_blank"&gt;www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=242&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guest Speakers:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ted Lanzaro (CPA)&lt;br /&gt;Tom Ackman (Cardinal Home Inspection LLC)&lt;br /&gt;George Chiodo (Surface Creation)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOPICS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ted Lanzaro&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to accelerate and maximize depreciation on the properties you buy&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; The difference between a repair and an improvement and how to maximize your deductions with repairs&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to make sure you are taking all of the deductions allowed to you by the IRS tax code&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; How to get tax credits for making your properties more energy efficient&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8594; Why you want to be considered a real estate professional&lt;br /&gt;Ted Lanzaro is a certified public accountant with over 20 years experience specializing in the real estate and construction industries. His current client base includes real estate investors ranging from individual landlords to commercial property owners, real estate brokerage firms, and real estate developers. Ted is a frequent contributor to newspaper and magazine articles and has published numerous articles on real estate and taxation in the Commercial Record and New England Real Estate Journal. Ted is also an experienced real estate investor and runs Eagle Homebuyers in Shelton, CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tom Ackman&lt;/i&gt; - Inspection of 100 year old buildings. Expectations and concerns.&lt;br /&gt;Tom Ackman owns Cardinal Home Inspection, LLC and is licensed Connecticut and Massachusetts for home inspection. In addition to residential inspections, he does commercial, multi family, new construction, and mold sampling. He is a certified Housing and Urban Development inspector, and a state accredited Radon tester. He has an MBA from the University of Hartford and worked in property and casualty insurance for 30 years. He is an affiliate of CTREIA, MASSREIA, and the Greater Hartford Association of Realtors. He is past treasurer of the American Society of Home Inspectors and served on its national educational council.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;George Chiodo&lt;/i&gt; - Resurfacing Countertops, WalkWays, Steps, Tile Walls, and pool Patios.&lt;br /&gt;George Chiodo will demonstrate his products for Resurfacing Countertops, WalkWays, Steps, Tile Walls, and pool Patios. Want to rent or sell your units fast? Want to demand top rent for your units? Turn your everyday units into luxury units at less expense.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Information Exchange:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Bring your question - and our members will discuss their solutions.&lt;br /&gt;-Bring your deal and bring your business cards.&lt;br /&gt;-Network with new and experienced landlords and property managers alike!&lt;br /&gt;-Find out who's buying and who's selling&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When there are people, property, and payments involved, it's essential to understand what you're doing, both legally and financially.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268438988000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267465889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Apartment Owners Association of Connecticut Meeting</name><id>12744884</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268265600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12744884/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/7/global_5005143.jpeg</photo_url></item>