<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>Mass. Ave. &amp; Church St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374420</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Church Meetinghouse</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>274946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118858</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;CHRIS HEDGES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;explores the&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Empire of Illusion:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge Forum is pleased to welcome journalist CHRIS HEDGES as he discusses his new book Empire of Illusion: The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Empire of Illusion, Chris Hedges argues that we now live in two societies: One, the minority, functions in a print-based, literate world, that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other, a growing majority, is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. In this “other society,” serious film and theatre, as well as newspapers and books, are being pushed to the margins. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the tradition of Christopher Lasch’s The Culture of Narcissism and Neil Postman’s Amusing Ourselves to Death, Hedges navigates this culture—attending WWF contests as well as Ivy League graduation ceremonies—exposing an age of terrifying decline and heightened self-delusion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is free; no tickets are required&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Info: 617.661.1515 - Email: rbcass@harvard.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris Hedges, who graduated from the seminary at Harvard Divinity School, was a foreign correspondent for nearly two decades for The New York Times, The Dallas Morning News, The Christian Science Monitor, and National Public Radio. He was a member of the team that won the 2002 Pulitzer Prize for Explanatory Reporting for The New York Times coverage of global terrorism, and he received the 2002 Amnesty International Global Award for Human Rights Journalism. Hedges is the author of the bestseller American Fascists and a National Book Critics Circle finalist for War Is a Force That Gives Us Meaning. Mr. Hedges is a Senior Fellow at The Nation Institute and a Lannan Literary Fellow, and has taught at Columbia University, New York University, and Princeton University.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present. See message board below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267832218000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265554889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Empire of Illusion</name><id>12542469</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267659000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12542469/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/7/global_6176535.jpeg</photo_url></item>