<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Learn More and Register at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=453"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=453&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Will Learn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 * How to buy real estate below market value. &lt;br /&gt;

 * Why the bank's loss is your gain. &lt;br /&gt;

 * How to locate distressed properties. &lt;br /&gt;

 * How to research and evaluate foreclosure properties. &lt;br /&gt;

 * How to calculate your profits. &lt;br /&gt;

 * And much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 5:45 - Networking &lt;br /&gt;

 Network with other investors and real estate professionals in Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00 - Early Bird Workshop &lt;br /&gt;

 Deal or No Deal. Have your property deal analyzed by CT REIA experts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 - Speed Networking &amp;amp; Member Deals &lt;br /&gt;

 Organized so that you get to meet the people you need to meet! Hand out a lot of Businesss cards, so bring a lot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 - Member Deals &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring Your Deals for Our Deals segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 - Al Lowry &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn Dr. Lowry's secrets of making money with shadow inventory in Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Al Lowry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Epitomizing the saga of "rags to riches," Dr. Albert Lowry has risen to become America's premier authority on real estate investing. He started out with no money, but he did have a burning desire to succeed, plus plenty of common sense. He began fulfilling his dream by getting his real estate license and learning how to sell property. He rapidly began acquiring duplexes and triplexes, and did the routine maintenance himself. He continued building his portfolio and began expanding his method to include leveraging, rehabilitating, and exchanging his investments. Within a very short time, he mastered the real estate market and began creating the concepts and techniques that are the backbone of the Lowry Formula.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340068587000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338385141000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA June 2012 Real Estate Meeting: Making Money With Shadow Inventory</name><id>66926972</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340055000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/66926972/</event_url></item>