<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>219 Bear Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.385627</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-951-1499</phone><name>EP Levine</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1252367</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.264727</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thriving, not just surviving with Nick Vedros&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February 8th 2011, 7:00–9:30 pm registration and networking at 6:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members who have heard Nick talk previously will know that his infectious enthusiasm and energy for photography and business are just what we need to thrive rather than just survive in these challenging times!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Thriving Not Just Surviving&amp;quot; with Nick Vedros&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more than three decades, Nick Vedros has been producing award winning work for his many clients, which include Apple, Coca-Cola, IBM, Microsoft, and Sony.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the deceptively simple phrase “I put four sides around an idea,” Nick sums up the approach that keeps clients coming back.  Whether shooting at his state-of-the-art digital studio in Kansas City or on location anywhere in the world he is needed, he will tell you that technology alone can’t bring an idea to life. It is imagination that transforms a concept into a memorable visual experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ask Nick how he sees client relationships, and his answer is immediate.  “My role is to understand our clients’ objectives, manifest their ideas, and achieve their vision.” Nick comes to the creative table to listen, to collaborate, to interpret, and to create--in that order.  If, along the way, his clients are pampered, charmed, inspired and entertained, chalk it up to the ineffable charisma and hospitable ambience that are part and parcel of the Vedros Shoot Experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s no mystery that Nick has an astounding client retention rate. On a Vedros shoot, every detail is obsessively controlled.  There is no shortage of creative inspiration or top shelf resources. Challenges are anticipated and addressed proactively.  Nick creates an atmosphere of confidence that frees clients to concentrate on creative direction.  The music is great, the panoramic views spectacular, the hospitality genuine, and the humor constant.  With Nick, you’re not just going to a photo shoot. You’re having an entire creative experience.  The Vedros Experience. Is it any wonder that one shoot with Nick Vedros is never enough?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cost   Online  At Door&lt;br /&gt;Members  FREE  $15&lt;br /&gt;Students  $5          $15&lt;br /&gt;Non-Members $20  $35&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: EP Levine’s new Waltham location at 219 Bear Hill Road, Waltham, MA 02451&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$35.00 for guests &lt;br /&gt;Free to CIPNE members and ASMP Members&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Baker</member_name><member_id>5043048</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alan J. Kidawski</member_name><member_id>5162177</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Iadarola</member_name><member_id>5198329</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297267235000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294343209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thriving, not just surviving with Nick Vedros</name><id>15946786</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297207800000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/15946786/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/e/global_20639374.jpeg</photo_url></item>