<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 Hesperus Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.585976</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-283-2080</phone><name>Hammond Castle Museum</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>770013</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.692583</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SATURDAY JULY 3 ... In celebration of Hammond Castle's 80th Fourth of July Anniversary come join &amp;quot;John Hays Hammond, Jr.,&amp;quot; as he shows you his castle home, and learn from him exactly why he built this fortress for himself and his wife Irene Fenton Hammond.  Special Hammond tours commencing on the front drawbridge in fair weather, and the museum lobby if it is raining.  Museum admission is charged for these tours: $10.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tour starts at 12 noon, let's gather between 11:30 a.m. and 11:45 a.m. I will wear my Meetup button. &lt;b&gt;Please note the following: It is suggested that you NOT use a GPS device as it will send you the wrong way on any of these roads and highways which will delay your arrival at the Museum. See directions below. The parking lot only holds 40 cars and they are well-attended in the summer, so I recommend getting there early. If I get a lot of yes RSVPs right away, I can let them know to expect a group. Hammond Castle Museum is not handicapped accessible. Groups that arrive over 15 minutes late cannot be guaranteed a full tour if there is another tour following theirs.  Groups over 30 minutes late will have to conduct their own non-guided tour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Hays Hammond, Jr., built his medieval-style castle between the years 1926 and 1929 to serve both as his home and as a backdrop for his collection of Roman, medieval, and Renaissance artifacts.  In addition, the building housed the Hammond Research Corporation, from which Dr. Hammond produced over 400 patents and the ideas for over 800 inventions.  Second only to Thomas Alva Edison in number of patents, John Hammond was one of America's premier inventors.  His most important work was the development of remote control via radio waves, which earned him the title, &amp;quot;The Father of Remote Control.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tour many rooms including the great hall, indoor courtyard, Renaissance dining room, two guest bedrooms, the inventions exhibit room, the library, the War room, the kitchens, the Natalie Hays Hammond exhibit room, the tower galleries, as well as several smaller rooms and passage ways including a secret passageway.  Visitors may also enjoy the beauty of the castle grounds and a view of the Atlantic shore line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Drive North on Route 128 until you reach exit 14. At the end of the exit ramp turn right onto Route 133 toward Gloucester. Stay on route 133 until the end of that highway. With the harbor in front of you take another right onto Route 127 South (Western Avenue). About a mile and a half down Route 127 south look for a left hand turn marked Hesperus Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can see the green street sign about a third of the way up a telephone pole on your left, but more importantly there is a small blue sign on a that pole which says &amp;quot;Hammond Castle&amp;quot;. Turn left at these signs and the Castle Parking Lot is three quarters of a mile down Hesperus also on the left. Drive to the very end of the parking lot where you will see the entrance. Turn left very carefully as it is a blind turn for traffic coming toward you. Park and walk to the East end of the parking lot and walk down the stairs. The castle itself is straight ahead of you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is suggested that you NOT use a GPS device as it will send you the wrong way on any of these roads and highways which will delay your arrival at the Museum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the front drawbridge in fair weather, and the museum lobby if it is raining, wearing a Meetup button.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>404606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1278337156000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276648748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Tour of Hammond Castle in Gloucester</name><id>13813908</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278171000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13813908/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/0/global_15793840.jpeg</photo_url></item>