<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Newbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352589</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emmanuel Church</name><city>Boston</city><id>4761672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://static.wix.com/media/ebf6cb_a79246e70ef6297bc558c763a7856f29.jpg_srz_361_551_75_22_0.50_1.20_0.00_jpg_srz" width="274" height="418" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Queridos Portuguese Language Speakers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can join me in enjoying another Boston Portuguese Festival 2013 event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The festival consists of a series of Portuguese cultural events co-hosted by the Boston Consulate General of Portugal. (&lt;a href="http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org"&gt;http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is a concert and reception for contemporary music composer &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Andreia Pinto Correia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a public and free event, however donations will be gladly accepted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Concert seats are limited to 150 and given to those on a first come, first serve basis. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event starts at 6:15pm with a reception and then followed by the concert starting at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet 15 before at 6:00pm at the entrance lobby, so we can meet and greet before the event starts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are late, I can not guarantee that you will be able to recognize members of the group for this will be a roaming, mix and mingle event. So please do your best to be on-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will also be a co-Meetup event with the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/"&gt;Boston Culture Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am looking forward to enjoying this event with the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;****************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;****************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org/#!portuguese-contemporary-music-/cp5h" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org/#!portuguese-contemporary-music-/cp5h&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The music of composer Andreia Pinto-Correia is distinguished by influences of Iberian literary traditions.&lt;/span&gt; Her music, described by The New York Times as an “aural fabric”, and “ mysterious, elegant, magical” by the New Music Box, was profiled in the prestigious literary magazine Jornal de Letras, who proclaimed that “the music of Andreia Pinto-Correia has been a major contribution to the dissemination of Portugal’s culture and language, perhaps a contribution larger than could ever be imagined”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;​Ms. Pinto-Correia upcoming season includes a commissioned work by the Fromm Music Foundation at Harvard University to be premiered by the Berkeley Symphony Orchestra under the direction of conductor Joana Carneiro. The work will have its European premiere later in the season at the Gulbenkian Foundation Grande Auditório also under conductor Joana Carneiro along with European premieres of Pinto-Correia’s Elegia a Al-Mu’tamid and Xántara. Other highlights include a New Music USA Music Alive Composer Residency, a new work commissioned by the Boston Symphony Orchestra Brass Quintet, as well as the world premiere of Territories, an operatic work with libretto by Betty Shamieh featuring soprano Haleh Abghari and the Mivos Quartet to be performed at the Institute for Advanced Study in Princeton. In addition, Olhos, espelho e luz, an extended work for tenor soloist and woodwind ensemble with text by seventeenth-century priest Padre António Vieira, and commissioned by the University of Minnesota, will have its world premiere during the Fall of 2013. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Her past season included a commission from the American Composers Orchestra premiered at Carnegie Hall, a premiere by the Minnesota Symphony Orchestra as part of the 2012 Composer Institute, a European premiere by the Orquestra Metropolitana de Lisboa, as well as a composer-residency with the leading Portuguese chamber orchestra OrchestrUtópica.  She is currently composing the opera O Búfalo Mágico (Souba et le Yak), a Companhia Ópera do Castelo/Drumming GP co-commission with original story with libretto by acclaimed West African writer Ondjaki, to be premiered by a consortium of theaters during the 2014 season. Ms. Pinto-Correia has received commissions from such notable institutions and performers as the European Union Presidency, Tanglewood Music Center, Dinosaur Annex Ensemble, Winsor Music, Culturgest (Portugal’s National Bank), OrchestrUtópica, Drumming GP, Avian Music Ensemble, and Antena 2/RTP (Portugal's National Broadcast) to name a few.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Awards and honors include a Tanglewood Music Center Fellowship; European Network of Opera Academies;Susan and Ford Schumann Center for Composition Studies-Aspen Music Festival; MacDowell Colony residency; Toru Takemitsu Award by the Japan Society; National Orchestral Network/Ear Shot Fellowship; UC Davis Fellowship; Valparaiso Foundation residency (Spain); Berta and Edward C. Rose Scholarship, Composers Conference Fellowship, Orquestra do Algarve Fellowship, Sacatar Foundation Fellowship (Brazil), Luso-American Foundation Scholarship, several ASCAPLUS awards, and various NEC Composition and Merit Awards, among others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Born in Lisbon, Portugal, Andreia Pinto-Correia began her musical studies in her native country at the Academia de Amadores de Música and at the Escola Luís Villas Boas, and is currently a teaching fellow in composition at the New England Conservatory in Boston, where she studied with Michael Gandolfi. She received her Master of Music degree from NEC, with Academic Honors in Jazz Composition as a student of legendary jazz composer Bob Brookmeyer.  She has also collaborated with her father at the Centro de Tradições Populares Portuguesas at the University of Lisbon, developing a catalogue of ethnomusicology field work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;﻿&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;﻿The event is open to the public and admission is free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368288479000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366495431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portuguese Contemporary Music Composition "Azulejos" - Concert and Reception</name><id>115341702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368136800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/115341702/</event_url></item>