<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;Looking for an inexpensive way to get a reading with a psychic or medium?  The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies hosts a Psychic Sampler the first and third Sunday of every month from 4:00 PM to 5:30 PM.  A warm and open environment where you can meet readers of varying techniques and skill levels, this is a great event to attend if you have never had a reading and are curious to see what it’s all about, or if you are seeking intuitive input regarding your life path.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;****************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Please be aware that our format is changing. Starting Sunday, September 2nd, we will be changing to a ticketing and schedule system. Upon arriving at the Sampler, you will be required to purchase ticket(s) – one per reading at $5.00 per ticket. You will then sign up for a time-slot with whichever reader(s) you choose of those available that day. The readings will be limited to strict 15 minute slots and limit one reading per reader.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Any questions, please email vroy@kripara.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;****************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #999999"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;Also, if you are a reader and would like the opportunity to participate as a practitioner in a psychic clinic, please contact vroy@kripara.com for further information on how to become a clinic reader&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;Drop-ins welcome!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;***********  Disclaimer (the legal stuff)  ***********&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;All readings are offered for entertainment purposes only.  What you choose to do with the information, including any action you take following receipt of any information, is your own personal responsibility and choice.  Information received at the Psychic Sampler is not a substitute for professional services, and should not be construed as guidance of any form on financial, psychological or health related issues. For such matters you should seek advice from an appropriate and qualified expert in said field.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;By attending any Psychic Sampler you also agree that you are over the age of eighteen (18) and that you are responsible for your own well-being during and following any psychic reading.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;By attending and/or receiving a reading at any Psychic Sampler you agree to the terms as set forth above, and hereby release (for yourself, heirs, executors and assign) KRI, The Center for Consciousness Studies, and each individual reader from any liability arising from any information given at any Psychic Sampler.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #666666"&gt;***************************************************&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #10474c"&gt;DIRECTIONS!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #10474c"&gt;KRI Center for Consciousness Studies is located at 1 Bayside Road, Unit 5, Greenland, NH 03840 ** The building is directly on the corner of 33 and Bayside. From the I-95, take exit 3 (95 northbound) or exit 3B (southbound) to Route 33 W. The Center will be 2.6 miles on the right, directly on the corner of 33 and Bayside, in the Gowen's Corner Plaza. The entrance is just to the left of Bayside Custom Frame &amp;amp; Mirror.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Valerie Roy</member_name><member_id>4599203</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346706487000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344809798000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic Sampler</name><id>dlssjcyqmbdb</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346616000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/77461572/</event_url></item>