<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>between Devens St &amp; Harvard St</address_2><address_1>83 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.373922</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 242-6009</phone><name>Tangierino</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>761029</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062762</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Who wants to Rock the Casbah? Well join us on our return to Tangierino for a great Moroccan &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/55580212/?action=copy#mce_temp_url#"&gt;food&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.tangierino.com/tangierino-restaurant-in-charlestown/entertainment.html"&gt;entertainment&lt;/a&gt; experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE NOTE OUR SEATING IS 8:00 PM HOWEVER YOU MUST ARRIVE BY 7:45 PM SO WE CAN BE SEATED ON TIME.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Please check out the &lt;a href="http://www.tangierino.com/tangierino-restaurant-in-charlestown/menus/dinner-menu.html"&gt;Tangierino Menu&lt;/a&gt; so you're prepared to place your order and we are able to enjoy our meal soon after we're seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Five (5) minute walk from Bunker Hill Community College station (orange line).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRIVING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your driving route. Advise you double check that you've entered addresses correctly and included zip codes, so you arrive at the correct location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Valet is an option and the cost is $15.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A garage near the USS Constitution ship is NAUTICA GARAGE at 88 Constitution Plaza Charlestown, MA 02129 (617) 337-0068. The parking fee is a flat rate of $5 after 5pm (exactly) until 3am and is a ten minute walk from Tangierino's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Legal street parking is extremely scarce and nearly impossible to find, especially at this time of day. If you're able to find parking on the street, I suggest you read the street signs to ensure it is a legal space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I list the Reservation Rules, please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I had to provide my credit card for this reservation and&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;will be charged for each cancellation within 24 hours of the reservation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You MUST be certain you can attend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;Rules for this Meetup:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If it is less than 24 hours from the meal and you are not able to attend because of an emergency (and NOT because you have a better offer) or you are running late on the day of the dinner, you MUST call or text me at &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(617) 445-7549.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All RSVPs are on a first reply, first seated basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the meal is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP and if you answered the RSVP question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the meal and you have not attended nor contacted me, you will be REMOVED and BANNED from BBLD.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within 24 hours of the reservation and you do not contact me, you will be REMOVED and BANNED from BBLD.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/members/3389565/"&gt;Tonya&lt;/a&gt; about rejoining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will arrive at 7:45 PM to welcome you from the restaurant bar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359430295000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358356499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at Tangierino on Friday January 25th at 8 PM</name><id>99897802</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359162000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/99897802/</event_url></item>