<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-380-9254</phone><name>Watertown Center</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1195181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183898</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per session</description><amount>49.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;pre&gt;
Hi Beautiful!


Thank you again for expressing your interest in 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
embarking on a deeper journey through Tantra with other love-minded folks.  
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;



&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
I want to offer YOU, one who expressed interest directly, 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
to receive first dibs on a spot in this more exclusive training.  


I'm excited to share what's in store for you! 

*  6 exclusive, private, 2-hour, experiential Tantra practice (and study)sessions
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
*  Selected readings for self-study and group sharing/practice
*  A private discussion group just for us! 
*  Discounted private Tantra sessions with me during the course of the program
*  Participation in Ignite Your Heart, Transform Your Relationship (Oct 2012) - first telesummit of its kind! 
*  BONUSES including a free 15-min Astrological birth chart reading with my colleague Peter Panjoyah (he's amazing!)
*  Unlimited mentorship from me via email, as needed during the course of the program 


And the above doesn't address what you will TRULY receive during this program -- and that is -- 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
depth of connection with the other participants.  Have you been taking Tantra workshops here and there?  
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Dropping in to one and then another a few months later?  Showing up occasionally, feeling incredible when you leave, 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
only to return home and have it disappear?  This program is FOR YOU!  
 &lt;br /&gt;



&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
My students and clients have been asking and I am finally ready and able to respond.  
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
I, myself, am truly looking forward to exploring deeper connection 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
in community; and to sharing my deeper passion and experience with you.  
 &lt;br /&gt;



&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
There's also one more VERY EXCITING thing and that is that because YOU inspired me to develop this program, I am giving you a HUGE DISCOUNT.  
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
The Sacred Tantric Fire Advanced Practice Group will run for $497.  But YOU my friend, will register for only $297!!!  
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
That's $200 off the regular price.  They'll only be approximately 10-15 participants, so if you know for sure that you are interested, 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
I invite you to register before Friday, September 7th at midnight to receive the discount.    
 &lt;br /&gt;



&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
The first step to participate is a brief application found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/MN25VGQ"&gt;
http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/MN25VGQ&lt;/a&gt; 
 &lt;br /&gt;



&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Once you've completed the application, I will contact you - you MUST put your name and email address on your application, thanks!
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Feel free to email me with questions:  Robyn@SacredTantricFire.com 

 &lt;br /&gt;





&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
The following are the days/times chosen for this course:


Friday, Sept 21st from 7-9 pm
Friday, Sept 28th from 7-9 pm
Friday, Oct 12th from 7-9 pm
Friday, Nov 9th from 7-9 pm
Wednesday, Nov 28th from 7-9 pm
Friday, Dec 7th from 7-9 pm 


Ready to discover deep intimacy and divine connection with a lovely group of people just like you?  

NOTE - there are 7 spots remaining in this exclusive program.  I'm soo excited!!!  
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Please share your interest with me ASAP so we can discuss whether this program is a good match for you. 
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Couples, singles, any gender preference, relationship style....ALL ARE WELCOME HERE!
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;



&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
With love,

Pushana


P.S.  To avoid this message and others getting stuck in your spam folder, please add Robyn@SacredTantricFire.com to your address book.  Thanks!  

P.S.S.  Payment plans available.
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348321410000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>new-england-tantric-meetup</urlname><id>804252</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>New England Tantric Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346811993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sacred Tantric Fire Advanced Tantra Practice Group</name><id>80891182</id><headcount>14</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348268400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/new-england-tantric-meetup/events/80891182/</event_url></item>