<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of State and Pleasant Streets</address_2><address_1>26 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Richdale Food Store</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1126642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;The 8th Annual American Red Cross Chocolate Tour!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let's go to Newburyport and check out the stores that will be serving a selection of chocolate goodies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We  have done this in the past and we had a lot of fun, we will be walking  around Newburyport, checking out all the merchandise in the stores, and  of course eating chocolate (Yummmy).&amp;nbsp; Last year there were over 15+  stores/restaurants that give out different versions of chocolate  treats.&amp;nbsp; It is a good cause cause the money raised helps the Red Cross,  so it's a win win for all!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: $15.00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Let's meetup at Richdale and walk over to the place that we can get the tickets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE PARKING&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;There are 3 municipal lots downtown &amp;ndash; as of &lt;strong&gt;May 9th&lt;/strong&gt; Newburyport will be implementing meters in these parking lots.&amp;nbsp; The  plan is that if there is a meter then you will have to pay to park in  that spot, not sure if all 3 lots will have the parking meters in them  but be aware of them.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The 3 lots are located at Green &amp;amp;  Merrimac Streets, State and Harris Streets  (next to the Library) and on  Prince Place. There are 2 lots run by the  Newburyport Redevelopment  Authority They are located at either side of  Waterfront Park along  Merrimac Street Between The Black Cow and Not Your  Average Joe&amp;rsquo;s (West  Lot) and Water Street (East Lot). You may also park  in legal spots on  the street. If you park in a nearby neighborhood,  please be respectful  of residents and all parking laws - do not block  fire hydrants or  driveways. Police will ticket or tow all cars which are  parked in  illegal spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;lease  remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel  at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;If  you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at  this event.&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at  your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your  Organizer&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp; We thank you for paying your dues. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Remember  to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t  forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you  had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be outside of Richdale.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306069414000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We LOVE chocolate and Newburyport is beautiful in the spring time!</why><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301097528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chocolate Tour in Newburyport</name><id>17059092</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305999000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/17059092/</event_url></item>