<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Spy&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is the long-awaited feature film version of John le Carr&amp;eacute;'s classic bestselling thriller. The time is 1973. The Cold War of the mid-20th century continues to threaten international relations. Britain's Secret Intelligence Service (SIS), code-named the Circus, is striving to keep pace with other countries' espionage efforts and to keep the U.K. secure. The head of the Circus, known as Control (John Hurt), personally sends dedicated operative Jim Prideaux (Mark Strong) into Hungary. But Jim's mission goes bloodily awry, and Control is forced out of the Circus&amp;mdash;as is his top lieutenant, George Smiley (Gary Oldman), a career spy with razor-sharp senses. Estranged from his absent wife, Smiley is soon called in to see Undersecretary Oliver Lacon (Simon McBurney), who tells him that he is to be rehired in secret. There is a gnawing fear that the Circus has long been compromised by a double agent working for the Soviets, jeopardizing England. Supported by younger agent Peter Guillam (Benedict Cumberbatch), Smiley pores over Circus activities past and present, trying to find the mole. Also starring Colin Firth, Tom Hardy, Toby Jones, Kathy Burke and Ciar&amp;aacute;n Hinds. Directed by Tomas Alfredson&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;(Let the Right One In)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.filminfocus.com/tinker_tailor_soldier_spy"&gt;Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Spy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomas Alfredson&amp;rsquo;s adaptation of John le Carr&amp;eacute;&amp;rsquo;s novel channels the author&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere of unceasing suspicion, overlapping alliances, and moral decay with such admirable precision, theaters would need only to pipe in cigarette smoke and the rattle of a failing Eastern Bloc HVAC system to make the experience immersive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After, we plan to make reservations at Think Tank, whose Bento Box was named as one of Boston's 10 Best for 2010, and which we need to check out for 2011!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet us in the lobby after the credits near the ticket takers.  John will send an email on the day of the event to make sure everyone finds the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324250295000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323403018000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Spy</name><id>43896442</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324157400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/43896442/</event_url></item>