<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone, &lt;br /&gt;It's time for our monthly Conscious Movie Night once again! If you like to see movies that mean something and then talk about them with other people, then Conscious Movie Night at the Center of Light is for you. This time we will be viewing Joyeux Noel. I have heard only glowingly positive reviews from every person I have talked to who has seen it. Every one. So I'm completely looking forward to seeing it and I invite you all to join us! &lt;br /&gt;Here is a short description of the film (from Amazon):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Academy Award, Golden Globe and BAFTA nominee for Best Foreign Film, Joyeux Noel (Merry Christmas) tells the true-life story of the spontaneous Christmas Eve truce declared by Scottish, French and German troops in the trenches of World War I. Enemies leave their weapons behind for one night as they band together in brotherhood and forget about the brutalities of war. Diane Krüger (Troy), Daniel Brühl (Good Bye Lenin!) and Benno Fürmann (The Princess and the Warrior) head a first-rate international cast in a truly powerful, must-see film. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you Friday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347511000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230090827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night: Joyeux Noel</name><id>9382958</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230337800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9382958/</event_url></item>