<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>111 Ocean Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02601</zip><lat>41.650615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-775-7990</phone><name>The New Hyannis, Mass Hostel</name><city>Hyannis</city><id>1319766</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.280802</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;This trip is the best of both worlds&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be staying at the Brand New Hyannis Hostel on the Cape!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can come down early Saturday morning or stay overnight Friday and Saturday at the hostel with me :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll taken the Island Queen Ferry in Falmouth (&lt;a href="http://www.islandqueen.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.islandquee...&lt;/a&gt;) One option is for you to drive Saturday to the Ferry straight from home or drive from the Hyannis Hostel and park at the lot which is situated quite close to the Ferry.   &lt;b&gt;We will take the 9:00am Ferry to Oak Bluffs.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afte we take the ferry over, we'll then bike from Oak Bluffs to Edgartown.....go to the lighthouse beach and grab lunch at this really good sandwich shop I know.   We may do some more biking, ice cream eating etc....(I'd say no more than 18-23 miles total that day on the Vineyard -perhaps much more if the group is into it).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll then take the Ferry from Oak Bluffs back to Falmouth and depending on how you got there, go back to the Hyannis Hostel.  We can all go out to eat at a local/fun place that evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, we'll bike the Cape Cod Rail Trail (it's 22 miles long each way- there's also a shorter version) ; we can get a group consensus on how many want to do the whole loop or whether we're pooped and want to do less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a bike in good working order, a spare tire that fits your size wheel, plenty of water, a helmet, and energy snack food.   Oh yeah, bring a sense of  humor because Rob Fox has been known at times to get lost and I need a group of people with a sense of adventure!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Fox&lt;br /&gt;Founder/Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Cell on the day of the trip is 617-894-8454</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rob Fox</member_name><member_id>4368625</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280935897000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278865911000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brand New Hyannis Hostel - 1 Day on Martha's Vineyard, 1 Day Cape Cod Rail Trail</name><id>14067713</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280532600000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/14067713/</event_url></item>