<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Where: Umbagog Lake State Park &lt;br /&gt;Route 26 &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, NH 03579&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Sept 3rd-6th (Labor Day Weekend).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is cross-posted to the New England Hiking Meetup, the New England Camping &amp;amp; Outdoor Group and the Dance &amp;amp; Activities Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We have decided to DELAY our trip by one night, due to the weather which will be the worst on Friday evening.  We will be at Umbagog beginning TOMORROW, SATURDAY SEPT 4th.  If anyone is interested in joining us, we have some extra spaces, so please let Kate K know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each site accommodates 4 adults.  We have booked a primitive site on the island. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt; Unreserved sites on the base camp are available!&lt;/span&gt; We could coordinate with those that are staying at the base camp! I'd like to see a group stay at the base camp - it is such a great location!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is my favorite place to camp and is also dog friendly!  There are RV sites, tent sites and some cabins on the lake shore, but also remote sites where you can rent a canoe, paddle out and set up on the island or along the lake shore.  It is highly ranked for kayaking and I believe there is a roped-off swimming area on the main beach.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This lake is just about pristine.  Yes, it's a LONG drive north, but so worth it!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So what is there to do around here?  Check out this link for information about the Umbagog Wildlife Refuge and things to do:  &lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/northeast/lakeumbagog/opportunities.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/no...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am planning a hike to ascend the&lt;b&gt; .7 mile fire tower trail&lt;/b&gt; on Mt. Magalloway in Pittsburgh on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have never been to the 1/3 mile Magalloway River Trail (which is handicapped accessible) and would up for checking it out.  It is described as &amp;quot;a good place to view moose, boreal birds and waterfowl. It features an easy walk through a forested river's edge to an observation platform overlooking the backwaters of the Magalloway River. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fishing, kayaking, swimming and yes, &lt;b&gt;MOOSE WATCHING&lt;/b&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.umbagogchambercommerce.com/moose.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.umbagogcha...&lt;/a&gt;)  are all popular activities up here.  It might be possible to organize canoeing or wildlife pontoon boat trip ($35 per person)  &lt;br /&gt;Or there is the Northern Forest Heritage Park (a re-creation of the logging camps which for years were integral to the economics of the Umbagog Area... the park provides guided pontoon boats rides on the Androscoggin River.)  See &lt;a href="http://www.northernforestheritage.org/main.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me know what you want to do and I will try to organize something.  Or just do NOTHING, which can be kind of refreshing too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camp's check-in is at 1pm Friday.  Check out is at 11am Monday.  We will be checking in on Saturday morning!&lt;/b&gt; The campsite is requiring 3 day reservations for this weekend.  Up to 4 adults per site - 6 people per site if children are included. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You MUST reserve your site directly with the State Park yourself.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283538160000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278940539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Labor Day Weekend Dog-Friendly Camping at Lake Umbagog</name><id>14075485</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283533200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14075485/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/f/global_16375599.jpeg</photo_url></item>