<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me at the Brattle to enjoy Bette Davis? two Oscar-winning performances: &lt;i&gt;Dangerous&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Jezebel&lt;/i&gt;.  We'll meet and discuss after &lt;i&gt;Jezebel&lt;/i&gt;.  If you?d only be able to see one of the films, please indicate your intention when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dangerous&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; (screens at 5:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bette?s first Oscar-winning role finds her as a ruined, alcoholic actress named Joyce who has caught the eye of wealthy architect Don (Tone). Don falls for Joyce while he is trying to rehabilitate her and Despite Joyce?s warnings that she is a jinx and will only lead to his ruin, Don breaks his engagement and risks his fortune to revive her career on Broadway. But, of course, complications ensue as Joyce?s bad luck begins to impede upon their relationship ? including petty husbands, car accidents, and bankruptcy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jezebel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; (screens at 7:15)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bette won her second Oscar for her lead role in this drama set in the high society of 19th century New Orleans. She stars as Julie, a headstrong Southern belle who can?t help but act out, alienating her loving fiancé (Ford) and labeling herself a Jezebel. Despite her desire for independence, Julie comes into her own when a deadly outbreak of Yellow Fever occurs and she has the opportunity to redeem herself. Bette proves herself as well, bringing depth to a role that could have been a scene-chewing disaster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it?s off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217540184000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214695650000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bette Davis Double Feature</name><id>8236417</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217367000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8236417/</event_url></item>