<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(A few hundred feet East of Mt. Clinton Rd)</address_2><address_1>Rte 302</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.234306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Highland Center at Crawford Notch</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>1839181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.421936</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This Sunday we'll be hiking Mt. Avalon, Mt. Field, Mt. Willey and Mt. Tom. The total trip length is &lt;strong&gt;10 miles&lt;/strong&gt; with an &lt;strong&gt;8 hour&lt;/strong&gt; book time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike requires that you have &lt;strong&gt;recent experience&lt;/strong&gt; hiking this distance in these conditions. Winter is almost here. It's already snowing in the mountains. Temperatures could be near freezing so proper gear is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please meet at the Highland Center &lt;strong&gt;before 8:00 am&lt;/strong&gt;. We'll wait until 8:15 if anyone is late. I don't usually get cell phone reception in the mountains so I probably won't get any messages. It's about a &lt;strong&gt;3 hour drive from Boston&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Planned Route:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start at the Avalon Trailhead near the Highland Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike the Avalon Trail to Mt. Avalon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt. Avalon to the Willey Range Trail to Mt. Field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt. Field to Mt. Willey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back across Willey Range Trail to Mt. Tom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt. Tom to A-Z Trail and back to the trail head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Gear:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Headlamp (the flashlight app on your iphone doesn't count)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warm insulating layers (fleece for example)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waterproof/Windproof Rain coat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hat, gloves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map and compass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your own food and water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike is dog friendly. I'll have my dog with me. If you bring your dog, it is your responsibility to determine if it's capable of doing this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Boone the yellow Lab dog with a blue pack.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Garrett</member_name><member_id>6580546</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319478446000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318969615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tom, Field, Wiley and Avalon</name><id>37862632</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319371200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/37862632/</event_url></item>