<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sneak Previews of New Cinema Followed by Lively Conversation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now in its 16th year, Talk Cinema, created by Harlan Jacobson, exists to give film lovers a chance to be part of a community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that individual tickets are $20&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;The Talk Cinema feature on Sunday, January 10 at 10:00 am, stars Maria Bello, William Hurt, and Kristen Stewart as three strangers on a road trip through the Louisiana back country, by the director of My Son the Fanatic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each screening showcases innovative independent and foreign films that have not yet been theatrically released, followed by discussions led by distinguished critics and filmmakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don't know what you will see until you arrive at the theatre! And while what you see is a complete surprise until the lights go down, we can tell you that last year's series included sneaks of such Oscar-winning fare as Slumdog Millionaire, and Man on Wire. The Sneak Preview on September 12 was Bright Star, a film by Jan Champion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some selections are meant to stretch the viewer’s perspective, some are meant to expand the viewer’s geopolitical horizons, and always to inform... New cinema is viewed as a peephole into new territory, whether it is cinematic, thematic, political or geographic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is a critic: One of the program’s distinctive features is the opportunity for members to review films and to refer films to each other. This is a great way to deepen your film experience and connect with other cinephiles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seen so far:&lt;br /&gt;Sept 13 - BRIGHT STAR&lt;br /&gt;Oct 4 - AN EDUCATION&lt;br /&gt;Oct 25 - MEN WHO STARE AT GOATS&lt;br /&gt;November 15 - THE MESSENGER&lt;br /&gt;December 6 - YOUNG VICTORIA&lt;br /&gt;January 10 -?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John will be sipping coffee across the street at the Panera Bread starting at 9:15 to meetup with folks so that we can sit together. Look for the cool sleepy dude with a cup of Peet's coffee and the Movie section from the Globe so we can talk about what we've heard, what we'll see, and what we think.. Due to the discussion after the film, there will be no formal meetup following Talk Cinema.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a film talking group at Panera Bread before the show, or a film chattering group sitting in the first couple of rows in the balcony.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262363231000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Talk Cinema with Harlan Jacobson</name><id>12189892</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263135600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12189892/</event_url></item>