<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>South River Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01339</zip><lat>42.625216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-800-866-6943 </phone><name>Moxie Outdoor Adventures</name><city>Charlemont</city><id>1062928</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.855350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Come White Water Rafting!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the fall and a day on the river.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You need to call the rafting company and make your own reservation (tell them you're with Rebecca's group).  Moxie Outdoor Adventures - 1-800-866-6943&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;You have to RSVP as Maybe, and then e-mail me after you buy your ticket, and I'll change you to Yes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please book ASAP!  Rafting company can't hold tickets for us any longer--so there may be X spaces left in this Meetup event, but no actual tickets available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rafting starts at 10, so we will meet 9:45 in Charlemont (2 - 2 1/2 hours from Boston).&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;a href="http://www.moxierafting.com/deerfield_directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.moxierafting.com/deerfield_directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.moxierafti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Car drivers:  please indicate if you can carpool and drive people; say town you live in.&lt;br /&gt;People needing rides:  say your town and that you need a ride.  (remember, I need a ride from Boston!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should bring the following: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bathing suit, shoes you can get wet, sweater, hat, windbreaker &lt;br /&gt;Sun screen, water bottle, any medication &lt;br /&gt;Change of clothes, including dry footwear and towel &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moxie Provides: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Licensed whitewater guides, fun professional staff &lt;br /&gt;All equipment, PFD, paddles, helmets, wetsuit rentals &lt;br /&gt;State of the art self bailing rafts &lt;br /&gt;Lunch, Shuttles, and Photo Show &lt;br /&gt;Store: T- Shirts, Photos, Wetsuit rentals &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lake Moxie Camps - South River Rd, Chalemont Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.moxierafting.com/deerfield_zoar_gap.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.moxierafting.com/deerfield_zoar_gap.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.moxierafti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is co-listed with Boston Volunteer Meetup, so only sign up in one place!&lt;/b&gt;  Size limit of group can be expanded--if people waitlist, then I'll increase the # of attendees.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Deerfield River offers pristine wilderness, a crystal clear river, and fun class I-III whitewater rapids. This intermediate whitewater rafting trip is perfect for families, friends, groups and youth organizations who are looking for a fun intermediate whitewater rafting trip. The trip is ten miles long. For most of the day, we paddle along through class I and II whitewater rapids, such as &amp;quot;Sideways Splash&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Freight Train&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Pinball&amp;quot;. Calmer stretches allow us to enjoy water fights and or a little swimming. The highlight of this adventure is an exciting run through the class III rapids of Zoar Gap! This trip is guided and includes a picnic lunch. Massachusetts most popular whitewater rafting trip!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Boston, MA: Miles: 100 | Travel Time: 2.5 Hours&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 2 West for about 100 miles, going through Greenfield, Shelburne, and finally Charlemont. As you go through Charlemont , look for a sign that says &amp;quot;Route 8A South&amp;quot; or a big blue sign that says &amp;quot;Berkshire East / Moxie Outdoor Adventures &amp;quot; with an arrow pointing left. Take that left, go 500 yards over the bridge and railroad tracks turn left at the T intersection. Go 3/10 of a mile, take your third right at the Moxie Outdoor Adventures sign (Berkshire East Moxie Outdoor Adventures entrance). Park in the lot at the bottom of the hill. We are located in the West lodge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way--the vote was pretty evenly split between 9/19 and 10/10 event!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254186834000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252698815000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>White Water Rafting</name><id>11349430</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253367900000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/11349430/</event_url></item>