<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Brookline Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.343372</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 424-6111</phone><name>Regal Fenway Stadium 13</name><city>Boston</city><id>668987</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Before the &lt;b&gt;7:10 pm&lt;/b&gt; screening of District 9, lets gather at Panera Bread. We can walk over to the movie theater at 6:50 pm to grab seats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, August 19th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 7:10 pm, 1 hr 53 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $11.00 ( plus service charge if bought from Fandango at &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/regalfenwaystadium13_aaovd/theaterpage?date=8/19/2009" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fandango.c...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About District 9:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/district9_114038/movieoverview?date=8/19/2009" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fandango.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Director&lt;/u&gt;: Neill Blomkamp &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Producer&lt;/u&gt;: Peter Jackson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Aliens become refugees in South Africa where they are kept isolated from any human contact. While being contained in the refuge being ignored of their welfare, their weapons become the sole interest of Multi-National United (MNU). But only one man , Wikus van der Merwe (Sharlto Copley), can activate these weapons. He becomes hunted for and only one place can give him refuge, District 9&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will grab the largest table he can find at the Panera Bread at 201 Brookline Ave in Boston, MA near the Fenway movie theater either in the front or back room, and decorate the table with red MEETUP table tents.  He'll probably get there by 5:40 pm. People can drop in when they wish. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign will be propped against his black messenger bag balanced on the corner of the table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sharlto Copley moves in front of the camera for 'District 9'&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;LA Times, 8/13/2009&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/news/la-et-performance13-2009aug13,0,6979174.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.latimes.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;He'd never acted in a feature before, much less played the lead in a big-budget science-fiction extravaganza produced by Peter Jackson. But for Sharlto Copley (SHARL-toe COP-lee), &amp;quot;District 9&amp;quot; was something of a relief.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I've been in the business side for a long time. I've owned companies. I've been a producer, director, writer; I've done quite a lot of stuff,&amp;quot; he says. &amp;quot;A lot of it was planning, strategizing, very stressful. Trying to control things that are ultimately out of your control. Acting didn't have anything to do with that. For me, it's about shutting my mind off, really, especially since all my dialogue was improvised.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 35-year-old Copley has made highly successful short films in his native South Africa, almost entirely behind the camera. When longtime friend Neill Blomkamp's deal to direct the film version of &amp;quot;Halo&amp;quot; for Jackson fell through, Blomkamp and Jackson looked for another project to do together. &amp;quot;Alive in Joburg,&amp;quot; a short Copley had produced with Blomkamp directing, came to mind: The totally revamped feature version became the space-aliens-as-unwanted-immigrants sci-fi adventure &amp;quot;District 9.&amp;quot; Copley hoped he'd have some behind-the-scenes role in the full production.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Neill was working on ideas for the script. He said, 'I want to shoot something to show Peter and maybe the investors what I'm thinking. Can you put another shoot together?' So, of course, I jumped at that,&amp;quot; Copley says by phone from Houston as he tours the country to promote the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blomkamp had created a character, a &amp;quot;bureaucrat for a large corporation in apartheid South Africa, who would occasionally go into District 9 and serve notices on the creatures. I jumped in front of the camera and we shot for about three or four hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Neill didn't tell me this was the main character of the film -- and certainly not that he realized as he was cutting together the footage, 'Maybe Sharl should be the guy.' It was all unbeknownst to me until a couple of months later, when Peter had already signed off on me,&amp;quot; he says, still amazed at how his life has changed so quickly, including his inner life.&lt;/i&gt; [ &lt;b&gt;MORE&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/news/la-et-performance13-2009aug13,0,6979174.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.latimes.co...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking at the Fenway&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, there is a parking lot just for the movie theater and the stores around it. No, I do not know how much it costs, but according to Povo Boston &amp;quot;Parking is available either in the lot next to Best Buy or in the Landmark Center garage. Remember to validate your parking ticket for two hours off your parking fee [at the Garage]&amp;quot; &lt;a href="http://boston.povo.com/Regal_Cinemas" target="_blank"&gt;http://boston.povo.co...&lt;/a&gt;. I think the garage is on Fullerton Street? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... And according to the Red Sox schedule at &lt;a href="http://www.mlb.com/schedule/index.jsp?c_id=bos" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mlb.com/sc...&lt;/a&gt; the Red Sox will not be in Fenway Park that night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailer:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/hdmovietrailers/district9-1116798515/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fandango.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257958229000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250171542000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>District 9 @ The Regal Fenway Stadium 13</name><id>11102910</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250722800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11102910/</event_url></item>