<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We were unable to hold an actual Pow Wow, this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its place, I'll post reviews of films that we would have discussed at the Pow Wow in order to help everyone make choices.  Those with high rating in bold.  Please feel free to add comments so that it will feel like we held a Virtual Pow Wow, and use this space to hook up with other members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;6:15 - (BRATTLE) - Computer Chess - IMDB: 6.5 - Will computers ever beat man in chess? A group of programmers and chess enthusiasts get together in 1981 to find out. The latest film by Andrew Bujalski (FUNNY HA HA; BEESWAX, IFFBoston 2009). "a dreamy, daffy tale about humongous computers playing chess against one another"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6:30 - Dirty Wars - IMDB: 7.0 - Investigative journalist Jeremy Scahill is pulled into an unexpected journey as he chases down the hidden truth behind America's expanding covert wars.  "This jaw-dropping, persuasively researched pic has the power to pry open government lockboxes."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;6:30 - Concussion - IMDB: 6.3 - A suburban lesbian housewife pushing 40 suffers a blow to the head that unleashes her latent sexuality, and sends her on an erotic journey that gives birth to a secret second life in this drama from first-time writer/director Stacie Passon. Abby (Robin Weigert) may have a loving family and all of the creature comforts in life, but even so, she can't fight a growing feeling of discontent. That all changes the day a speeding baseball smacks into Abby's skull, prompting her to acquire a pied-à-terre in Manhattan. Meanwhile, the more time she spends in the city, the stronger her libido begins to grow, leading her to seek work as a high-class escort while keeping her sordid new career a carefully guarded secret from her unsuspecting family.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;6:45 - Suitcase of Love and Shame - No Reviews - A forbidden love story played out in a decade that would soon spawn the sexual revolution. Part historical documentary and part experimental narrative the film reconstructs a mesmerizing and erotic narrative from 60 hours of reel-to-reel audiotape discovered in a suitcase. Recorded in the 1960's by a Mid-western woman and her lover they chronicle the details of their adulterous love affair.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:00 - Frances Ha - IMDB: 7.9/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RT: 100%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- A story that follows a New York woman (who doesn't really have an apartment), apprentices for a dance company (though she's not really a dancer), and throws herself headlong into her dreams, even as their possible reality dwindles. "Noah Baumbach, making his most compassionate movie since 2005's The Squid and the Whale, gives these lives the full French new wave/mid-period Woody Allen treatment, conferring charm and substance on even their most mundane interaction."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;8:00 - Best Kept Secret - No Reviews - An inspiring high school teacher must help her autistic students face life after graduation in one of the poorest cities in the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;9:00 - (BRATTLE) - Rewind This - IMDB: 7.3 - Home video changed the way the world consumed films. The cultural and historical impact of the VHS tape was enormous. REWIND THIS! is a documentary that traces the ripples of that impact by examining the myriad aspects of art,technology, and societal perceptions that were altered by the creation of videotape.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;9:15 - The Dirties - IMDB: 6.6 - Two best friends are filming a comedy about getting revenge on the bullies at their high school. One of them isn't joking. TY BURR "A grand-jury prizewinner at this year’s Slamdance, a festival that likes to show neighboring Sundance what edgy looks like. Matt Johnson’s queasy low-budget drama — about two bullied high school kids making a film about killing their tormentors — may have too much edge for a lot of people, but it delves into interesting and unsettling areas: the way storytelling fuels revenge fantasies, the blurry line between pretending and doing, the distortions of movie geekery. A scurrilous but inspired work, and one worth arguing with.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;9:30 - Oxyana - No Reviews - Oxyana is a state of mind, a nickname coined by the press to describe Oceana, West Virginia. Oceana is a rural coal mining town, which in recent years has become riddled with Oxycontin addiction. Oxyana is an unflinchingly close focus on the anguish and horrors of a community that the rest of the country would just as soon forget.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9:45 - The Hunt - IMDB: 8.3/&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RT: 91%&lt;/span&gt; - A teacher lives a lonely life, all the while struggling over his son's custody. His life slowly gets better as he finds love and receives good news from his son, but his new luck is about to be brutally shattered by an innocent little lie. "'The Hunt' is a masterful piece of film-making, powerful without being preachy, and an angry indictment of the shuttered world we've built ourselves."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please feel free to add a comment to meetup with other members, or to add information for any film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367207620000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366560139000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Evening Films at BIFF</name><id>115426342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367100900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/115426342/</event_url></item>