<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 135; Ashland, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01721</zip><lat>42.250042</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ashland Reservoir </name><city>Ashland</city><id>605341</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.472839</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello All,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It looks like Sunday is going to be the best day of the weekend, so Stella (yellow lab) and I are going to be hiking around the Ashland Reservoir and hoped we could get some people and dog friends to join us. If you haven't done it, it's about a 3 mile hike (just guessing) that follows the shoreline of the reservoir. It's moderately easy hiking though there are lots of exposed roots and some muddy areas to contend with. It's fine for the dogs to be off-leash and there are some choice places for the dogs to swim. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested, hit me up or just meet me at the reservoir's south end parking / boat launch area at 9 am on Sunday.  The best access is off of Rt 135 in Ashland. If you're headed westbound on Rt 135, pass the entrance for the Ashland State Park and take a left onto Olive St. Follow Olive for a couple of miles and take a left on Spring St. and that will take you directly to our meeting spot. Note: Spring goes through the middle of a sand / gravel quarry so don't be put off by that. &lt;br /&gt;My mobile is 508-308-1517. map of Ashland State Park&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/ashland.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210683825000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Why not!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210379309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Hike with the dogs</name><id>7909110</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210510800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/7909110/</event_url></item>