<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>On Sunday, Jan 9 from 2 to 4 PM we will have an advanced level meetup at the Cambridge Rindge and Latin High School (CRLS) in Cambridge. This game is intended to be approximately Yankee C level or equivalent. Players are required to know how to play a 6-2 and 5-1 formation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INSTRUCTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Because this game requires players to know formations, the RSVP procedure is a little different. If you'd like to play, please do the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Send an email to the event host using the following URL: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/message/?recipientId=4774008"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the email, confirm that you know how to play in a 5-1 or 6-2 offense, and mention your preferred position (if any).&lt;br /&gt;2. Players will be added to the list to fill up positions. Preference is given to Yankee C or above players (or equivalent), and people who have not been no-shows at previous meetups. There is a strict cap at 12 players to make sure everyone gets lots of playing time. Note that sending an email does not guarantee a spot to play; spots are only guaranteed if you are assigned a Yes RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost of the meetup will be $5. Please pay the organizer when you arrive before the meetup starts. The money goes to cover the cost of the court rental.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entrance to the gym is on Cambridge Street opposite Harvard Market. The nearest intersection to the entrance is Cambridge Street and Roberts Road. The nearest T stop is Harvard Square. The gym is about a ten minute walk from the T stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking near the school on Sundays is generally easy to find, as meters and residential parking rules are generally not enforced on Sundays (parking signs should say &amp;quot;EX SUNDAY&amp;quot; or similar).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Lee</member_name><member_id>4774008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294674505000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294019956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Advanced Indoor Volleyball</name><id>15890975</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294599600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/15890975/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/3/global_1997523.jpeg</photo_url></item>