<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bennett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372297</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.661.5000</phone><name>Regattabar </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>796303</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121820</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wed., July 29 @ 7:30 PM: Newpoli at Regattabar, One Bennett Street, Cambridge (Carmen Marsico and Angela Rossi - lead vocals, Bjorn Wennas - guitar, Roberto Cassan - accordion, Megumi Sasaki - violin, Geni Skendo - flutes, Brian O’Neill – percussion, Fabio Pirozzolo – percussion/vocals, with special guest Mike Rivard from Club d'Elf on bass)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newpol&lt;/b&gt;i is a group of exceptionally talented musicians, all alumni from Berklee College of Music and New England Conservatory, that performs Southern Italian Folk Music, mainly from the regions of Campania and Puglia, integrating a wide variety of styles such as Tarantella-Pizzica, Tammuriata, Villanella and the Neapolitan Canzone, encompassing music from the Middle Ages to the 19th century. Because Italian Folk music, with the exception of a small number of Neapolitan songs, has not received its deserved attention and recognition, neither in Italy nor abroad, Newpoli, guided by their passion for playing and researching these seldom played traditional styles, introduces to the audience, often for the first time, the joy and beauty of this music while recounting the ancient stories and rituals described in the lyrics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group has been enthusiastically received everywhere, as the audience, notwithstanding the language barrier, is mesmerized by the vitality, energy and spice of their music. They have performed throughout New England, at venues such as the Berklee Performance Center, Ryles Jazz Club, The Middle East, Dante Alighieri Society of Cambridge and First Night. They have been interviewed and featured twice, in 2006 and in 2008, by RAI International, the Italian International public television. They released their debut CD in March 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Formed in October of 2003, the group consists of two singers, Carmen Marsico and Angela Rossi, a Tamorra player (traditional Italian percussion), Fabio Pirozzolo, a percussionist, Brian O'Neill, an accordion player, Roberto Cassan, a classical guitarist, Bjorn Wennas, a double bass player, Kendall Eddy, a flute player, Geni Skendo, and a violinist, Megumi Sasaki.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's figure this out on the message board</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pasquale</member_name><member_id>9961972</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249264044000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247672223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Newpoli (Southern Italian Roots Music)</name><id>10882298</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248913800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/10882298/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/f/8/global_9681832.jpeg</photo_url></item>