<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>sliding scale</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to $10 at the door.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;*************************************&lt;br /&gt;Parking near Lir is really hard - you could get lucky or you could drive around for 30 or more minutes. There are parking garages by Back Bay station. Best bet is to take the T to Back Bay or Hynes Convention Center (which is the closest T stop).&lt;br /&gt;*************************************&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SoJust is 4! That's right, it's been FOUR years since our first event! Join us to celebrate &lt;b&gt;1400 members, 80 events and countless connections&lt;/b&gt; made since then! Our birthday parties are always our biggest events - we'll need all you SoJusters there to celebrate - and to eat up all the cupcakes on hand!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What may seem like just another liberal social group is really the start of a revolution. What can we create together?&lt;/i&gt; Join us if you are ready to go BEYOND ALLIES and build a CROSS-ISSUE PROGRESSIVE MOVEMENT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;As always we'll help you meet people&lt;/b&gt; - so no worries if you're new to SoJust, plus we'll have &amp;quot;looking for&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;ask me about&amp;quot; tags, a Catalyst Corner staffed by our amazing STARZ (regular attendees), our wildly popular Jobs Board and Action Stations to make it even more likely you'll find the right connections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is not a meeting - it's a fun networking social!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;No Program. No Speaker. Just Us. For Justice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;School Supply Drive&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the ways SoJust supports other organizations is by organizing a supply drive at our tri-annual Connecting for Justice events. At this event we're collecting school supplies for high school age youth who are in foster care at the MA Department of Children and Families (DCF). Bringing an item or two on &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/messages/boards/thread/3864120/post/37312508/?hash=37312508#37312508"&gt;this wish list&lt;/a&gt; to the event is one way that you can make a difference. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Arrive early! Dance Party starts at 8pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If I can't dance, I don't want to be part of your revolution.&amp;quot; &lt;/center&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns?&lt;/b&gt; Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us! &lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; Members are all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HEY ORGANIZERS!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers for the free lit table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Action Stations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can it be done within 2 minutes or 2 weeks of the event? &lt;br /&gt;Bring it so SoJusters can get connected to you and your work.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The venue is open to anyone over 18 and is physically accessible - elevator is at the back of the venue. Lir Irish Pub is across from the Hynes Convention Center, 2 blocks from that T stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Spread the word!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Share the &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=8770189934#!/event.php?eid=142843615744856&amp;amp;"&gt;Facebook event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join the SoJust &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=8770189934"&gt;Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Follow SoJust on Twitter:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/sojust"&gt;@SoJust&lt;/a&gt; and SoJust's Co-Founder &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/robbiesamuels"&gt;@RobbieSamuels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 1400 members and 4 years! of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find  the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>25</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286234433000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>73</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276742921000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SoJust is 4! Connecting for Justice (Open House)</name><id>13826386</id><headcount>123</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284674400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/13826386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/9/global_5202681.jpeg</photo_url></item>