<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 commercial street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.362200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Christopher Columbus Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>748388</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sorry about late posting.  Anyway this is what's going to happen.  We'll meet up at 11:30 at Christopher Columbus Park and walk to Galleria Umberto for lunch.  The Galleria is  open for lunch only 6 days a week and keeps serving until it runs out of food.  It features pizza, calzones, arancini and a number of other goodies.  It also features a line so wear comfortable shoes.  After our lunch we'll walk around the North End and I'll point out some of the more notable bakeries, etc.  We'll also walk by the narrowest house in Boston.  I plan to be finished between by about 2:00 PM. Afterward if you are so inclined you can do some shopping at Fanieul Hall or perhaps Haymarket. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to accomplish every thing within a reasonable amount of time the tour will leave Columbus Park at 11:35 AM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can park in the garages on nearby Broad St. but it's not cheap.  I recommend public tansportation.  The nearest T stop is the Aquarium Stop on the Blue line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Addendum:  Andy Maltzman, he of the well traveled walking set (bostoncitywalks.com),  has pointed out that the garage at International Place (IP) offers unlimited Saturday (and Sunday) parking for $9.    The IP Garage entrance is almost straight across the Greenway from the Rowes Wharf arch, just a few minutes walk from Christopher Columbus Park.  Note the Greenway is really the strip of land that exists between Purchase Street and Atlantic Ave. that used to be 93 before the Big Dig.  Additionally the subway stops of Government Center, Haymarket and State Street are not far either from the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Addendum Addendum:  &lt;b&gt;My cell is 617-840-9995&lt;/b&gt;.  If at the last minute you can't make it please call me.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There's a series of benches under some trellises in the park.  I'll be there</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244475176000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Baby Boomers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun</urlname><id>1347228</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Baby Boomers Meetup Group-Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243520944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North End Foodies Tour-Where to go and what to eat</name><id>10513410</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244302200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun/events/10513410/</event_url></item>