<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Wattaquadock Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.430644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.nashobawinery.com</phone><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>731361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.614016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please remember to post below if you need a ride. The event is Saturday, and we'd like everyone to have a way to get there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: We are planning to &lt;strong&gt;arrive at 11 a.m. at Nashoba.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't miss this popular annual event! On Saturday, September 22, we are taking a trip to the Nashoba Valley Orchard and Winery. Pick some apples, sample the wine, and get out of the city to enjoy the fall scenery with some excellent company! The new and familiar, alike, are encouraged to attend. &lt;a href="http://www.nashobawinery.com/"&gt;http://www.nashobawinery.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great trip for young ones, old ones, in between ones, and children, too! This event is terrifically kid-friendly, but keep in mind that any children found wandering the orchard unattended will be forced to milk the goats. (Just kidding- I am sure you will be able to find goats somewhere in town, though.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI, the best apples are available the second and third weeks of September: Cortland, Granny Smith, Red Delicious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP so we can get a head count and figure out car transportation. Please note below whether you can drive and how many passengers you can take, so that we can coordinate transportation. See you Saturday, Sept. 22!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilie</member_name><member_id>4710889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348337209000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347552886000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atheists Go Apple Picking at The Nashoba Valley Winery and Orchard</name><id>82231572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348326000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/82231572/</event_url></item>