<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>342 Longwood Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338568</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Longwood Galleria Conference Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>1034539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106693</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From the event description: "Join Dr. Nathaniel Jeanson (Ph.D., Harvard, Biology) for an in-depth look at how DNA comparisons, mutation rates, and modern cell biology challenge the validity of evolution. Question and answer to follow."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the third time in recent years that the Calvary Chapel in the City church group has invited Nathaniel Jeanson (Ph.D, Harvard) to lecture on the supposed weaknesses of contemporary evolutionary theory. In each of the past two sessions, the question and answer period was filled by scientifically-informed audience members (working biologists, engineers, science educators) standing to inquire about the obvious flaws in Jeanson's -- but Jeanson, throughout, was unruffled in the face of criticism. He's not there to deliver information, remember; he's there to deliver the spin. And he seems pretty far down the rabbit hole, so to speak... I'd reached out to him after his first presentation in 2010 -- just after he'd been granted his doctorate and weeks before he moved with his family to Texas to commence work with the anti-think tank, the Institute for Creation Research -- but his emails were evasive and he was non-responsive (if affably so) to any of the constructive criticism I was offering. (Why offer constructive feedback to a creationist, you wonder? Because I'd like to be able to repudiate creationism in its strongest form when it is peddled in public.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An interesting nota bene, from &lt;a href="http://www.icr.org/article/new-icr-research-associate-nathaniel" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.icr.org/article/new-icr-research-associate-nathaniel&lt;/a&gt;, answers the question, why did someone who is skeptical of the foundational concept in modern biology go to Harvard to get a degree in biology? Because a Harvard education "sounded like it would be useful for credentials and evangelism." H&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won't be able to go this year myself, but I encourage members to go down. Sit among members of the audience, rather than just in a group of our own BA folks. Have some conversations. Give some Christians a reason to pause and say, hey, this atheist I just met, was courteous, interesting, and informed. You never know when you might induce some helpful cognitive dissonance. And then, of course, stand up during the Q&amp;amp;A session, and really tell the truth to shame the devil. Jeanson's lecture last year was identical to the first one he presented, despite having had the basic errors in scientific information and logical reasoning pointed out to him. It would be interesting to see if he's retrenched, regrouped, and set out with a new PowerPoint presentation, or if he's recycling the same old misrepresentation and sleight of hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More about about Jeanson's past lectures -- debacles, really -- at the following links: &lt;br /&gt;

 - Link to a YouTube segment of the talk, at &lt;a href="http://thymocyte.blogspot.com/2009/08/nathaniel-jeanson-on-youtube.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://thymocyte.blogspot.com/2009/08/nathaniel-jeanson-on-youtube.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - BA member Steve Wertheim's report: &lt;a href="http://bostonatheists.blogspot.com/2009/08/report-on-nathaniel-jeansons.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://bostonatheists.blogspot.com/2009/08/report-on-nathaniel-jeansons.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Jeff Eyge's report on the lecture: &lt;a href="http://scienceblogs.com/pharyngula/2009/08/a_first-hand_report_of_nathani.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://scienceblogs.com/pharyngula/2009/08/a_first-hand_report_of_nathani.php&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - the Boston Skeptics' ongoing coverage: &lt;a href="http://bostonskeptics.com/tag/jeanson/" class="linkified"&gt;http://bostonskeptics.com/tag/jeanson/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - "Harvard Ph.D. Lecture Exposes Prejudices of Evolutionary Atheists", &lt;a href="http://www.icr.org/article/harvard-phd-lecture-exposes-prejudices/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.icr.org/article/harvard-phd-lecture-exposes-prejudices/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Rebecca Watson recap: &lt;a href="http://tech.groups.yahoo.com/group/SDARI/message/7018" class="linkified"&gt;http://tech.groups.yahoo.com/group/SDARI/message/7018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please, go -- make friends, spread good information, be civil, take photos, Tweet, make videos, and generally do what you can to lift the rock and let in some sunlight to disinfect the muddled mess of misinformation. This sort of dank confusion can only survive if it can stay hidden and safe in the dank refugia of incuriosity. (Not my most quotable line, but you get the idea.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335805406000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335568670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Evolution: Broken Science" (a creationist lecture)</name><id>62446942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335738600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/62446942/</event_url></item>