<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Westborough Spirituality Meetup member,    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How are you?    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a snow storm and I canceled the meetup. Now it is a new year, we can start fresh again.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IN the year of 2010, one of our member shared the Dr. Jill Taylor's sharing. It was very deep. I would like to play her speech on our meetup for 20 mins and we can discuss what her idea about we are One.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UyyjU8fzEYU" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been discussed about how to create the peace in the world though ourself. we also can create good energy for the world. As an old saying: A thousand miles begins with one step. Everyday we face a lot of people, with all of the relationships are the resource for us to create good energy. If we start sending out the peaceful energy to the world, this world will become much better.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be wonderful, if we combine the sharing of Dr. Taylor's science experience from having stroke. We understand that peace and energy is not too far away from us. It is how do we want to be. If we can transform our mindset, than everything around us could be very different. I am the one starting the peaceful energy and I am also the one stopping the vicious cycle. Even it is a tinny thing, but it may makes a huge different. It likes a butterfly effect.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to meet more friends with the same interest about seeking a spiritual life, please come and share your thoughts and experiences about how to practice spirituality in daily life.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the day and let’s create positive energy to the whole world. Hope see you all in our meetup.    &lt;br /&gt;It is also a first meetup this year. Hope we can start a good energy for this year.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It will be the 2nd building on your right hand side when you drive into condos.You can park any place with sign for guest/ visitor.  call me if you can not find it 6172237166</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan</member_name><member_id>4981726</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295876733000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spirituality-149</urlname><id>670379</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5999984741</group_lon><name>The Westborough Spirituality Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293736549000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Westborough Spiritual January  Meetup</name><id>15860882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295809200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/events/15860882/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/6/global_2055446.jpeg</photo_url></item>