<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>India Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.818152</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>India Point Park</name><city>Providence</city><id>1023970</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.392241</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As a way to explore providence, I'm going to put together a scavenger hunt to cover a bit of downtown and the east side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teams will be formed to scavenge the area based on clue sheets that will be distributed at the start.  Since this is a newcomers events, teams will be assigned at random just before the start.  The search area will kept to within a 1 square mile to reduce or eliminate the need for cars roaming the city.  Teams will be of 3-4 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The items to be &amp;quot;scavenged&amp;quot; will be a photo of the item described in the clue.   Every team will need to have at least one digital camera or cell phone with camera built in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your RSVP as a Yes or Maybe to the Scavenger Hunt that I'll be hosting this Sunday on the East Side of Providence.  I'm having a great time putting together the hunt and look forward to seeing everyone on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's how the hunt will work:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. I've tried to keep the hunt area small enough that it can be walked.  I expect that over the course of the hunt a team should cover 2-3 miles.  It is up to you to drive, but I hope it isn't necessary.  The hunt area encompasses about 1 square mile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. &lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt;:  The meeting location is going to be near Wickenden and East Street.  I recommend parking on East, Wickenden, Governor, Ives, Carpenter and George Cohan streets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. &lt;b&gt;Starting Location&lt;/b&gt;:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I'll be there by 3:40.  If you can, please arrive a little before 4pm so that teams can be assigned and the hunt can start as close to 4 as possible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. &lt;b&gt;What to Bring&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you have a digital camera, please bring it, and any cables that you need to connect it to a computer.  I need to be able to see the photos and verify that they are indeed of target items in the hunt.  To that end, I'll have a computer with to do that.  If you don't have a camera to bring, that's fine, Every team will have someone with a camera on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good Walking Shoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Money, if you want to partake of refreshments along the way, or at our end location.  Food will be available for order.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A sense of adventure and willingness to meet new people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. &lt;b&gt;Basic Rules&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Teams will be 4 to 5 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Each team will need a name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Each team will need one camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; All scavenged items must be photographed on a single device. (eg: teams must stay together)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Teams will be randomly chosen at the start area to encourage socialization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Scavenger Hunt ends at 6pm.  If you haven't found the Finish location by 6:15, please call me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Each item on the hunt will be worth a certain number of points, the team with the most points will win the adulation and applause of the other teams, and a free round on me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; If you become lost or need assistance, you will be able to call me during the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; There is no time bonus for finishing early, nor penalty for finishing late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; It may not be possible to get a photo of all items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Basic maps of the area will be provided that outline the search area and street grid.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Scavenger lists will be distributed once teams have been formed and had a moment to introduce themselves to each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find the bridge that no motorized vehicle can drive on.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249520105000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246640881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Ever Providence Scavenger Hunt</name><id>10796749</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249243200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/10796749/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>