<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This walk was selected because it will bring us to Boston's best Ethiopian restaurant! I missed it the first time and everyone said the food was great, so we are going back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will walk along this bike path from Forest Hills T station to the Back Bay station, bringing us pretty close to the restaurant.  After lunch we'llwalk back to our cars at Forest Hills.  Those who want to take the T back after lunch are welcome to do so as well. Parking is free on Sundays in the lot at the T station. Meet inside the Forest Hills station in front of the donut shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Addis Red Sea&lt;br /&gt;544 Tremont St.&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA. 02116&lt;br /&gt;617-426-8727 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.addisredsea.com/menu_index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.addisredse...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Southwest Corridor Park is a 4.7 mile, 52-acre, linear park stretching from the Back Bay to Forest Hills. It links the neighborhoods of South End, Back Bay, Roxbury and Jamaica Plain with a street-level, green open space for parkland and recreation. Approximately a quarter of the parkland is decked over the railroad tracks, providing more space for grass and plantings, and such recreational facilities as 11 tot lot areas, 2 spray pools, 7 basketball courts, 5 tennis courts, 2 street hockey rinks, 2 amphitheatres, and approximately six miles of biking, jogging and walking paths. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History&lt;br /&gt;In the 1950's and 60's, plans were developed for a 12-lane highway along the railroad right of way between Boston and Rte. 128, and on into Cambridge. The residents of the affected areas, including Jamaica Plain, Roxbury, South End, Back Bay, and Cambridge, began community protests and demonstrations against the destruction of their neighborhoods by the planned highway. After hundreds of heated meetings and protests, Governor Sargent scrapped the plans in 1969, and highway funds were used to develop mass transit, open space and recreational facilities. The new, relocated Orange Line and the adjacent Southwest Corridor Park were opened in May, 1987.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206974379000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200792740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Southwest Corridor Park &amp; Ethiopian</name><id>7154185</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206801000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7154185/</event_url></item>