<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>While we are not a Buddhist group per say, many are interested in Buddhism and its philosophies are at the core of our mindfulness practices. Here's an invitation from Maggie Miller, whose intention it is to bring together people from various groups and organizations interested in Buddhism. This Saturday they are hosting the first in what they hope to be a series of films at the First Parish Church. In her own words:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...a group of folks, from a number of different Buddhist and meditation groups, have been discussing ways of bringing together the Buddhist community in and around Southern and Mid-coast Maine. It is our hope to create a forum to get to know and learn about one another, to support practice, and build community. The inspiration for this arises from a similar coming together in Central Vermont. There, practitioners from over 10 different Buddhist groups, as well as individuals who do not belong to a particular group, but who practice in the Buddhist tradition, have been meeting from time to time over the past four years. They gather for potlucks, movies, community events, sharing, and to hear speakers, and sit together. It has been a rich and rewarding experience for them to connect and support each other in practice. We love the idea and want to create a similar opportunity for the Buddhist community here in Maine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Saturday's film title is: Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter... Spring. &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0374546/" target="_blank"&gt;Movie info...&lt;/a&gt; I've seen the movie and it's as close to a visual/moving meditation as I have seen in many years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is free and there is no need to RSVP, just show up and enjoy the show! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maggie Miller</member_name><member_id>5724466</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292489866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291660714000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhist Movie Night</name><id>15657736</id><headcount>135</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292113800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/15657736/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/2/3/global_20084851.jpeg</photo_url></item>