<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 14 John F Kennedy St  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138 </zip><lat>42.371902</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 500-3055 </phone><name>Russell House Tavern</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1343010</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.124110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Last month while walking through Harvard Square, I noticed Russell House Tavern, which occupies the same space as the mysteriously departed Z Square. Well, I went inside to check it out and was impressed with the classy and comfy decor as well as the cheery hostess and very helpful bartender.  Will you join us to check out one of the newest restaurants in the heart of the Square?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the brunch menu &lt;a href="http://www.russellhousecambridge.com/?page_id=85" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.russellhou...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in a great activity nearby, before or after brunch, consider the &lt;a href="http://www.culturalsurvival.org/bazaar" target="_blank"&gt;Cultural Survival Bazaar&lt;/a&gt;, which gives Indigenous artists, their representatives, and fair trade companies from around the world the chance to sell their work directly to the American public as well as entertainment.  It will be  held from 10am until 6pm at Harvard University The Laboratory at Harvard, Northwest Building 52 Oxford St. Cambridge, MA 02138&lt;br /&gt;((FREE PARKING at the Oxford Street Garage, 52 Oxford Street Cambridge, MA 02138))&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route. Less than five (5) minute walk from Harvard subway station on the Red Line or Bus #1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your driving route&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;Very limited parking at meters on Dunster and JFK Streets as well as Massachusetts Avenue. Check out &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Square Public Parking&lt;/a&gt; for garages and lots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEMBER GUIDELINES so our events run smoothly.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first reply, first seated basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with comment about your circumstances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's which are staffed based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me on my cell (617) 445-7549&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the bar downstairs. Ask for the Tonya/Meetup reservation.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291946632000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290649001000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Russell House Tavern Brunch</name><id>15551771</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291572000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/15551771/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/e/global_19856430.jpeg</photo_url></item>