<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Falmouth Heights Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02540</zip><lat>41.550920</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Martha's Vineyard</name><city>Falmouth</city><id>696603</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.600040</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Nothing like a day OR weekend on the Vineyard!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 8:45am at the Island Queen.   Call my cell if you can't find the group of cyclists at 617-894-8454.  Parking is available at the location where the ferry departs from.   See the link below..... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once we arrive on the island, we will allow sometime for several people to rent bicycles.  I will announce a time for us all to convene if some people want to explore Oak Bluffs for a short while while folks rent bikes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those staying over, I'm thinking I'll have a van taxi our bags to the hostel.  For those interested in that option, I'll need people to kick in some money for the taxi of our bags for the round trip to and from the hostel.   The rate is around $30 each way for the taxi unless we use the bus which requires two different buses.  The taxi may be the best way to go in terms of efficiency with time.  The $3 I charge for the ride just helps me cover the cost of the website for this group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helmets Required, bikes must be in good working order.  Have plenty of water on hand and snacks for energy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you post a MAYBE please be sure to check back several days before the ride to Change your RSVP to YES or NO so I have an accurate count of how many will be attending&lt;/b&gt;   Thank you!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll take the Island Queen to the Island&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.islandqueen.com/directions/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.islandquee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll likely do a 35 mile bike ride on a combination of bike paths and street.  Some of the island doesn't have bike paths as you get further from the main town.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;E-mail me if you want to stay at the hostel ASAP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I called on Sunday June 29th and there is space still for July 19th at the Martha's Vineyard Youth Hostel (there is no age limit to stay at the hostel :-).  $38 bucks a night includes complimentary breakfast.  To reserve a space at the hostel you need to give them a credit card but you can cancel for a full refund as long as it's 48 hours before the 19th (so by Thursday of that week). Separate Men's and Women's Dorm with sheets and towels available.   There is no curfew anymore like they used to have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Martha's Vineyard, the hostel is located smack in the center of the island, in West Tisbury. Edgartown-West Tisbury Road, &lt;br /&gt;Mail Address: Box 3158 West, Tisbury, Massachusetts 02575 &lt;br /&gt;Phone: 508-693-2665 &lt;br /&gt;FAX: 508-693-2699&lt;br /&gt;EMAIL-mvhostel@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usahostels.org/cape/himv/index.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usahostels...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Vineyard hostel is another great place where you get Spartan quarters in return for very low prices and a chance to meet and mingle with international guests, families, and other great travelers. You can make a meal in their spacious kitchen, and share a cab into town to have some beers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Fox, Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call my cell on the day of the ride 617-894-8454</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rob Fox</member_name><member_id>4368625</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216694617000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214626766000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Martha's Vineyard day trip or overnight option!</name><id>8232236</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216472400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/8232236/</event_url></item>