<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Galera, na festa de independência do Brasil em Allston, achei no chão o flyer para esse documentário.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Esse filme conta na participação de muitos músicos e cantores.  O filme explica como é realmente o Choro (&amp;quot;o jazz brasileiro&amp;quot;) que é o base do Samba e &amp;quot;a essência e alma da música brasileira&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/events/rio.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Página do filme no Regent Theatre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tem de ser em português com legendas inglesas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;O filme vai ser exibido 5 vezes entre os dias 20 e 22.  Confirme qual horario é melhor para você na enquete &lt;a href="http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/polls/94183/"&gt;aqui&lt;/a&gt; para que eu possa marcar a data em que a maior número de pessoas possa comparecer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Como chegar: &lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/directions.html"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regentthea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;De BiSaDo:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;THE SOUND OF RIO: BRASILEIRINHO&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mika Kaurismäki's follow up to his travelogue &amp;quot;Moro No Brasil&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Choro is Brazilian jazz, many people say. It could be true if Brazil's chorinho hadn't&lt;br /&gt;appeared before on the scene. After fading with the introduction of Bossa Nova in the '60s,&lt;br /&gt;the Brazilian music par excellence is getting a new lease of life.&lt;br /&gt;--Bruce Gilman - journalist, musician, and educator.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Regent Theatre in Arlington, Massachusetts is presenting an exclusive run of Mika Kaurismaki?s&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE SOUND OF RIO: BRASILEIRINHO from Thursday September 20 to Saturday September 22.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE SOUND OF RIO is a 90-minute swinging musical documentary film about Choro, the first&lt;br /&gt;genuinely Brazilian urban music that has evolved over the past 130 years into a fascinating form of&lt;br /&gt;modern tropical sound. It was back in the late 19th century in Rio de Janeiro when Brazilian musicians&lt;br /&gt;started to blend European melodies, Afro-Brazilian rhythms and the melancholic interpretation of the&lt;br /&gt;Brazilian Indians' music to create Choro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mostly instrumental, Choro was performed in dancing, beer and concert halls and is credited as being the first musical expression of the then-emerging urban middle class in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil's melting pot.&lt;br /&gt;Choro had a prominent place in the development of Brazil's cultural identity and remained a major popular music style until the 1920s, leading directly into Samba and later to Bossa Nova. As Villa-Lobos said, &amp;quot;Choro is the essence and soul of Brazilian music.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Included in the official selection of the Berlin International Film Festival, the film features performances by Yamandu Costa, Trio Madeira Brasil, Paulo Moura, Zeze Gonzaga and more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*THE SOUND OF RIO will screen Thursday, September 20, at 8pm, Friday, September 21 at 8pm and 10pm, and Saturday, September 22 at 8pm &amp;amp; 10pm at the historic Regent Theatre, &amp;quot;Arlington's Show Place of Entertainment,&amp;quot; located on 7 Medford St. (just off Mass. Ave.) in Arlington, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;General admission tickets are $7 in advance and $10 day of show. The Regent Theatre is MBTA and handicap accessible with free parking across the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please call or check web site as screening dates and/or times are subject to change.&lt;br /&gt;For information about the screening, please contact:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Regent Theatre&lt;br /&gt;PHONE: 781.646.4849&lt;br /&gt;URL: www.regenttheatre.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For information about the film, please contact:&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Stefan Karrer&lt;br /&gt;PHONE: 818.953.7809&lt;br /&gt;EMAIL: stefan.karrer@milanrecords.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bisado.com/home/news.php?id=1741&amp;amp;idMenu=21"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bisado.com/home/news.php?id=1741&amp;amp;idMenu=21" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bisado.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/events/rio.htm"&gt;Regent Theatre page on the film.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/directions.html"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regentthea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Most likely will be in Portuguese with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/d/event_2096541.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/d/highres_2096541.jpeg"&gt;Imagem maior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film will be shown 5 times between the 20th and the 22nd.  Confirm which time is best for you in the poll &lt;a href="http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/polls/94183/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; so I can schedule the date in which the greatest number of us can attend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190592379000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189756716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Filme documentário: The Sound of Rio: Brasileirinho</name><id>6357280</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190419200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/6357280/</event_url></item>