<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>249 State St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06473</zip><lat>41.376913</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-281-5411</phone><name>JROOS</name><city>North Haven</city><id>908742</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.882229</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come to JRoos for a night of good food fun and dancing with one of CT's top R&amp;amp;B bands, The Bernadettes.   JRoos has a casual atmosphere and a nice crowd.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For over a decade, The Bernadettes have been providing memorable musical entertainment at a variety of events and functions including weddings, corporate events, private parties, and fund raisers. Rhythm &amp;amp; Blues, arguably America's finest and most well known export, is the music The Bernadettes specialize in performing. The very familiar toe-tapping sounds of Motown, the infectious dance grooves of Memphis soul shouters such as Wilson Pickett, the smooth, sophisticated Philly soul music of Earth, Wind &amp;amp; Fire, the hard driving funk-rock of Sly and the Family Stone, the soothing grooves of R&amp;amp;B crooners like Marvin Gaye and Bill Withers, and, of course, the unforgettable music of the king of soul, Mr. James Brown - this is the music The Bernadettes perform. Yes, they'll mix it up with a few modern contemporary dance hits here and there, a classic rock number, or an oldies favorite, but the emphasis is on the classic &amp;quot;old school&amp;quot; R&amp;amp;B music that American baby boomers have grown up with and folks of all ages have enjoyed dancing to for several decades.  Check them out at  &lt;a href="http://jameskader.home.comcast.net/~jameskader/" target="_blank"&gt;their web site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve C</member_name><member_id>6197158</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241222875000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237735813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come join us for a night of  food,fun and dancing. The Bernadettes at JRoos.</name><id>10008457</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240704000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/10008457/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/3/global_7791699.jpeg</photo_url></item>