<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Ibbetson St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.385460</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Private Home</name><city>Somerville</city><id>7548122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111717</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/e/2/event_202435522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes we succumb to the Hollywood idea that being “in love” means finding some “right” other person and then making it work. But at its core, Love is a state of being, and one can feel that presence, or not. In this f*ree workshop, you will get an introduction of what it feels like to go past that magical, but temporary, condition we call “falling in love” to simply become aware of and allow love permeate your being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’ll learn specific tools that will support you in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coming back to a place of love again and again....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivating conscious communication skills vital to healthy relating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Becoming more intimate with yourself and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt; mini-workshop&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll have the opportunity to connect with others through a variety of exercises designed to open your heart and support you in sharing authentically with one another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and get a taste of what you’ve been craving in a totally safe, warm, loving and non-sexual environment.  Learn more about what the Human Awareness Institute has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please bring a pillow or cushion to sit on, a water bottle and your open heart!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My friend and colleague, Ben Farris, is facilitating this evening's event!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;span&gt;Each event begins promptly at the scheduled time. We ask that you arrive 15 minutes beforehand so that you’re settled when the event starts.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Note&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;There will be no admittance after the scheduled start time so as not to break the continuity of the Mini.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365819219000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>new-england-tantric-meetup</urlname><id>804252</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>New England Tantric Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364010415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Got Love? What's Holding You Back?</name><id>110631812</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365807600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/new-england-tantric-meetup/events/110631812/</event_url></item>