<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>189 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.519759</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 740-2337</phone><name>Tavern in the Square</name><city>Salem</city><id>996076</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895411</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Let’s go to Tavern in the Square for their award winning all you can eat Sunday brunch buffet. &lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.21.10 UPDATE: Between the 3 meetup groups we have over 25 people RSVP’d yes to go to brunch.  We will be calling in the reservation for all on Friday 4.23 at 1:00.  With a crowd this big we are not sure how they will be seating us or if we will be sitting at one big table or how close we will be to each other.  If this is a problem then this may not be the event for you and please change your RSVP or if your plans have changed and you won’t be able to attend please go in and change your RSVP, so we give the correct count to the restaurant, thank you for your help!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE: If you plan on attending this event please put your yes RSVP on the event page.  If you do not and the event fills up then you may not be able to attend.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little bit about Tavern in the Square: We are a neighborhood restaurant &amp;amp; bar focusing on great food &amp;amp; beverage, sports, entertainment, atmosphere and outstanding service. As with all our restaurants we pride ourselves on being an integral part of the neighborhood and community.  We have been there to check out their menu and the food is wicked good, and the buffet is “really big”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a list of the items that they will have on their buffet go to: &lt;a href="http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavsalem/content/home" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.taverninth...&lt;/a&gt; click on food and scroll down to the bottom of the page and check out all the items on the buffet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be scheduling this event on all 3 of our meetup sites, we will have to make reservations for all of us if you RSVP yes and your plans change please update your reservation as soon as you are able, seeing you may be taking up a spot that someone else could have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost for the buffet:&lt;br /&gt;Adults: $16.99&lt;br /&gt;Children: $8.99&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Meetup Table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272807189000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267321305000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go to Sunday Brunch.</name><id>12729346</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272209400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/12729346/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>