<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The following synopsis is from the MFA website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three Monkeys&lt;br /&gt;3:40 — 5:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, July 5, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;Remis Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three Monkeys by Nuri Bilge Ceylan (2008, 109 min.). From the director of Climates and Distant, Nuri Bilge Ceylan's Three Monkeys centers on a family's struggle to cover up the truth after a rising politician convinces his driver to take the blame for a hit and run. The film has all the makings of a noir-style psychological thriller--resentment, adultery, murder, and cynicism--but retains Ceylan's trademark striking cinematography, meditative shots, elliptical intrigue, and bleak tone. &amp;quot;No one working in cinema today can suggest an interior psychological state, solely through the camera's external observation of an unmoving character, as well as Ceylan can&amp;quot; (Peter Brunette, Hollywood Reporter). In Turkish with English subtitles. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From the Rotten Tomatoes site comes this perspective: &lt;br /&gt;Consensus: Exploring the effects of a family's dealings with an underhanded politician, this crime drama avoids showing the violent outcomes of its characters' misdeeds, resulting in a lingeringly potent film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a link to a more in-depth review:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2009/05/01/movies/01monk.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you would like to go to the restaurant afterwards for a discussion, please submit your RSVP.  We will go some place where we can get the food quickly since it will be a Sunday evening.  Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;Susan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be near the front row after the film with my MEETUP sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246061799000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Three Monkeys</name><id>10744387</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246822200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10744387/</event_url></item>