<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>344 Broadway </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.369938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>CAC Gallery at Cambridge Arts Council</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>11609482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On March 5, 2007, a car bomb exploded on al-Mutanabbi Street, the ancient street of booksellers, poets and writers, located at the literary and cultural heart of Baghdad, Iraq.  The attack killed 30 people and injured scores more. As part of an international response to this event, the Cambridge Arts Council presents “Al-Mutanabbi Street Starts Here,” a three-part exhibition of 261 artist books made by 260 international artists from 24 countries. This exhibition events aims to bear witness to the events on Al-Mutanabbi Street, and to collectively affirm that the right to a free exchange of ideas and culture in public space is never to be taken for granted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the course of six months and three exhibitions, the Cambridge Arts Council will present the entire collection of astoundingly powerful artistic creations along with a number of related events such as film screenings, poetry readings, curated conversations at the opening receptions, book-making workshops for children and adults, and in-depth panel discussions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit website for more information, event listings, images and video:  www.Al-MutanabbiStreetStartsHere-Boston.com and www.cambridgeartscouncil.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This coordinated artistic response to the al-Mutanabbi Street bombing originated with Beau Beausoleil, poet and bookseller in San Francisco, CA and co-coordinator on the artists' book project is Sarah Bodman. Each of the artists has created an edition of three books.  At the conclusion of the project, one set of the collection will be donated to the National Library in Baghdad, Iraq&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362089849000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360262591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Al-Mutanabbi Street Starts Here, exhibition 1</name><id>103526902</id><duration>1202400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360886400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/103526902/</event_url></item>