<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Stevens Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.691586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Weir Hill</name><city>North Andover</city><id>922750</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110088</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Weir Hill in Andover, MA is a TTOR property. Here's the blurb off the website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trace the western shoreline of a sparkling lake or enjoy a woodsy ascent to scenic views of the Merrimack Valley.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes Weir Hill a special place?&lt;br /&gt;We think it’s the striking vistas of both scenic Lake Cochichewick and of the broader landscape of the Merrimack Valley that will charge your imagination. Whether you prefer to wander the property’s eastern border along the lake shoreline or ascend to an overlook for a westward panorama, Weir Hill Reservation will replenish body and soul.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow the 0.75-mile Edgewood Farm Trail to reach the meandering shore of Lake Cochichewick, which dominates the east and south edges of this reservation. The two-mile-long lake and Weir Hill (&amp;quot;wire hill&amp;quot;) are the dominant natural features in the northeast part of town and easily its most scenic. In fact, Great Pond Road was laid out on the east shore to take advantage of the views across the lake and the hill rising just beyond. Cochichewick has long served as North Andover’s drinking water supply, so public access remains limited. Hikers of the Edgewood Farm and 0.4-mile Cochichewick trails can feel fortunate as they wander, enjoying terrific water-level views. Take caution if you trek this route in winter, though, as these trails get icy! BRING  YAKTRAX!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a quite different, but equally memorable experience, take the 0.71-mile Stevens Trail up the spine of Weir Hill to where a scenic overlook opens on the right. Hikers enjoy a broad panorama of the Merrimack Valley spreading below. On days of good visibility, you can see Mount Wachusett rising in the distance beyond Worcester, and northwest of Wachusett, New Hampshire's Mount Monadnock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Generations of agricultural use, a history of fire, and cutting and mowing regimes have created a patchwork landscape on Weir Hill that supports ten different types of plant communities, from a 60-acre oak-hickory forest to hillside seeps, intermittent streams, and wet meadows. Several threatened state-listed and watch-listed species can be found on Weir Hill, including the white bog orchid (Habenaria dilitata), violet bush clover (Lespedeza violacea), butternut trees (Juglans nigra).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails&lt;br /&gt;Four miles of trails, easy to moderate hiking, strenuous in places. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Main Entrance - Victoria's Black PT Cruiser w/purple flames (stop laughing!)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria</member_name><member_id>4404403</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>8</waitlist_count><updated>1264961203000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262143399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weir Hill, North Andover</name><id>12173410</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263052800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/12173410/</event_url></item>