<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Walk-In Registration</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Turning the Key: Marketing for Killer Deals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you satisfied with your current marketing strategies? Are the systems that you're currently using getting you the returns that you want? Would you like to try something different and improve your marketing systems in order to build your wealth faster?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For our July Turning the Key meeting, Than Merrill, star of A&amp;amp;E's &amp;quot;Flip This House&amp;quot;, has agreed to join us and speak about his own experiences with marketing. He'll be sharing with us the systems that he successfully uses for marketing &amp;quot;killer&amp;quot; real estate deals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These techniques have worked fantastically for Than; he's used the marketing systems that he'll be speaking about to build a multi-million dollar real estate business in three years, during which time he has purchased over 200 homes for prices substantially below market value.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the course of the evening, Than will be discussing many different topics, including:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* How to find 100 motivated seller leads-every month!&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;* How to find potential deals for 30-50% below market value-within a month!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* How to analyze a prospective deal in 10 minutes-learn how to separate the good            from the bad, fast! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on out to Turning the Key for an evening of education and networking, and let Than teach you how to make his techniques work for you! His experiences can help you change the marketing systems that you use, and have a positive impact for you and for your business! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/6/" target="_blank"&gt;Pre-Register for Turning the Key&lt;/a&gt; and save $5.00!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3372062</member_name><member_id>3372062</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183849536000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181261041000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turning the Key:  Marketing for Killer Deals</name><id>5866717</id><headcount>141</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183676400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/5866717/</event_url></item>