<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>989 Ellington Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06074</zip><lat>41.822426</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 289-7929</phone><name>Mill on the River</name><city>South Windsor</city><id>517746</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.588196</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hallo alle- Ein Glückliches Neujahr!! Dies ist eine Restaurantreise zuzüglich unserem üblichen erst-und-dritt Donnerstag Zeitplan. Es nimmt an einem Sonntag staat. Vielleicht werden einige Leute kommen, wer  für den  Meetups von Donnerstag nicht anschließen kann. Ich denke, dass viele von Ihnen dieses bekannte Restaurant genießen werden, das in einer schönen Einstellung ist. Es wird sein ein wirklich netter Ort, womit eurrem Deutsch-sprechenden Freunden zu hängen! Bitte RSVP für dieses Eregnis. Wir entweder werden einen Tischvorbehalt oder ein privates Zimmer oder Treffen im Loungegebiet haben, das von der Zahl abhängt, die erwidert. Einige Leute haben mir erzählt, dass sie die österreichische Speise lieben, und die Atmosphäre ist wirklich toll. Es ist in der AAA Zeitschrift diesen Monat überprüft. Sie haben alles von $7 Vorspeisen zu $35 Platten. Es gibt auch ein $22 prix fixe Abendessen mit Suppe oder Salat, Hauptgericht und Nachtisch. &lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We are meeting at 4:30 because it's Superbowl Sunday. About 14 people have told me that they are coming. Some of you may want to be home by evening.  There are  TV's in the bar area if you are an addict of the pre-game stuff!.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hallo alle-  Happy New Year!! This is a restaurant trip in addition to our usual first-and-third Thursday schedule. It is going to be on a Sunday.  Perhaps some people will come who cannot join us for our Thursday Meetups. I think that many of you will enjoy this well-known restaurant which is in a beautiful setting.  It will be a really nice place to hang out with your German-speaking friends!&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP for this event.  We will either have a table reservation or a private room or meet in the lounge area, depending on the number who reply.  Some people have told me that they love the Austrian food and the ambiance is really great.  It is reviewed in the AAA magazine this month.They have everything from $7 appetizers to $35 plates.  There is also a $22 prix fixe dinner with soup or salad, entree and dessert.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233697005000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Deutsch speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>german-425</urlname><id>438488</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford German Kaffeeklatsch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231727302000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday celebration and Restaurant trip!</name><id>9502367</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233523800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/german-425/events/9502367/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/b/b/global_3413819.jpeg</photo_url></item>