<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Quincy Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.228697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 849-1577</phone><name>Spazio Restaurant &amp; Bar</name><city>Braintree</city><id>824081</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.970417</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever felt like just spreading your hands and asking rhetorically, &amp;quot;What can I say?&amp;quot; Well, believe it or not, even your well-loved and ever creative Org Team sometimes encounters a situation that makes them feel the same way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Case in point: An Italian restaurant on the South Shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, Mike's thought was the same as yours: &lt;i&gt;And now for something completely different!&lt;/i&gt; (If you're too young to get the allusion...please don't tell Mike.) Yet the call of duty compels him to set fingertips to keyboard anew, and the call of companionship and cuisine draws him ever onward to another dining destination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fortunately, the things waiting for him at &lt;a href="http://www.restaurant.com/microsite.asp?rid=300533" target="_blank"&gt;Spazio Restaurant &amp;amp; Bar&lt;/a&gt; in Braintree include antipasti like &lt;i&gt;lightly fried calamari, mixed with sweet cherry peppers, served with a lemon aioli dipping sauce&lt;/i&gt; ($8.50) and &lt;i&gt;shaved lamb over a warm salad of baby greens, caramelized onion and goat cheese, with rosemary flat bread&lt;/i&gt; ($9.00) as well as main courses like &lt;i&gt;chicken stuffed with fennel sausage, sweet peppers and fresh sage, with garlic mashed potatoes and roasted acorn squash&lt;/i&gt; ($19.00) and &lt;i&gt;large shrimp and scallops, sauteed with squash and zucchini, in a light tomato cream sauce over bowtie pasta&lt;/i&gt; ($21.00).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sound interesting? Well, quite a few people have concurred over the years: Spazio opened on Quincy Avenue in Braintree in 1995 and has been a well regarded part of the South Shore's Italian dining scene ever since. SSDOMG will be heading there on Thursday, December 11, at 6:30 PM, and Angela and Mike hope that a good number of you will join us at a restaurant whose menu definitely does not stop at &amp;quot;red sauce&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spazio Restaurant &amp;amp; Bar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;200 Quincy Avenue, Braintree&lt;br /&gt;(781) 849-1577&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.restaurant.com/microsite.asp?rid=300533" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.restaurant...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, December 11 @ 6:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Mike &amp;amp; Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members and their Guests - FREE, Members and all other Guests - $2.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; $16.00 - $33.00, with most entrees between $18.00 and $21.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, December 10 @ 5:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Spazio is on &lt;b&gt;Quincy Avenue in Braintree&lt;/b&gt;, just a short distance from Weymouth Landing. The section of Quincy Ave. where Spazio is located is also part of &lt;b&gt;Route 53&lt;/b&gt;. Please note that we are giving directions from &lt;b&gt;Route 3&lt;/b&gt; because this will provide a prominent reference point for anyone who lives in the immediate area and would likely be the route of choice for people coming from a distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3, take Exit 17 (Union St).&lt;/b&gt; This is the Union Street Rotary. Exit the rotary by turning onto the Union Street, East Braintree exit, passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through one traffic light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next major intersection is Weymouth landing, where you will see a 7 Eleven convenience store on your left. At this point you can either bear right, heading into Weymouth Landing, or go straight, which brings you immediately to a traffic light. Go straight, then take a left at the light onto Quincy Avenue, keeping the 7 Eleven and Eastern Bank on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Immediately after you turn left there is another light at the entrance to the new Weymouth Landing MBTA station. Go straight through this light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next traffic light is at Gordon St. You will see a yacht club on your right. Go straight through this light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next traffic light is Bickford Rd. There is a Curry Hardware store on the far left corner. &lt;b&gt;Immediately after Curry Hardware is the strip mall where Spazio is located.&lt;/b&gt; Spazio is easily seen, but the mall also includes a closed West Coast Video store and a Curves franchise. If you find yourself passing Maria's restaurant on your left, you have overshot Spazio and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our table is reserved under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230482451000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228079717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spazio!</name><id>9252428</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229038200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9252428/</event_url></item>