<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Counterfeiters&lt;/b&gt; opens on March 7th, but I thought it would be a good idea to wait a couple of weeks until the crowds die down. There's no question  this will be playing for at least a couple of months at Kendall. Son of a gun- the actual screening time is 2 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The true story of Salomon Sorowitsch (Karl Markovics), counterfeiter extraordinaire and bohemian. After getting arrested in a German concentration camp in 1944, he agrees to help the Nazis in an organized counterfeit operation set up to help finance the war effort. It was the biggest counterfeit money scam of all times: over £130 million in British currency was printed, under conditions that couldn't have been more tragic or spectacular. During the last years of the war, as the German Reich saw that the end was near, the authorities decided to produce their own banknotes in the currencies of their major war enemies. At the Sachsenhausen concentration camp, two barracks were separated from the rest of the camp and transformed into a fully equipped counterfeiters workshop. &amp;quot;Operation Bernhard&amp;quot; was born. Kendall Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From an historical perspective, the story is interesting because it shows a different side of the war than what we're used to observing in motion pictures.  Reel Views&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stefan Ruzowitzky?s meshing of plot with debate is impressive. His film is compelling and clever. Time Out&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Counterfeiters is a testament to guile. [Director] Ruzowitzky scored the picture with tangos, and the tangos are meant to be Sally?s music -- seductive, insolent, triumphant. New Yorker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.timeout.com/film/reviews/84769/the-counterfeiters.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.timeout.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then we'll go to a local restuarant to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206471161000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><why>Based upon reviews (averaging 3 out of 4 stars for the most part) this seems like little more than a better- than -average WWII tale. Yet it takes home the Oscar. We should have an interesting discussion afterward to say the least!</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204073279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Counterfeiters</name><id>7414909</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206208800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7414909/</event_url></item>