<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.360001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 426-0111</phone><name>Beantown Pub</name><city>Boston</city><id>380287</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come and meet other Meetup members. Beantown Pub is located in the downtown of Boston, it is a great place to hang out and relax after work. It has pool tables, good food and drinks. For pool table, it's $1.75 per game...not charge by hours. Depends on how good you are, 1 game can be last long or short. This venue is big enough for you to mingle with each person freely. We will meet at the back where the pool tables are. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;If you are taking the subway from Green and Red lines, stop at Park ST. When you come up to street level of Park ST station, you should facing a church (renovation sign is up). At your right side is Burger King &amp;amp; Dunkin Donut, walk up to Tremont St...pass by the Suffolk Law school, you will see the Beantown Pub sign.  Sorry, I don't how to drive there, please use mapquest or yahoo to find the driving direction.  There are street parkings or parking lot around. I think the Boston Common underground is the cheapest ($10).   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have questions, please let me know. I will be there a bit early (5:30 pm) to see if I can hold the pool tables....they don't take reservations.  You are welcome to come earlier or later. Everyone is welcome. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan &lt;br /&gt;617-686-3430&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2140220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191539804000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190503536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour at Beantown Pub 9/28 6PM</name><id>6410357</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191016800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/6410357/</event_url></item>