<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1815 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.387146</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-354-7766</phone><name>Tavern in the Square - Porter</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>859456</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118996</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/e/0/event_93596032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hear ye, hear ye!&amp;nbsp; All ye beer drinkists and geekists, it's time once again to gather in on Porter Square, imbibe in tasty pub grub and suds, and expand our scientific and technological horizons.&amp;nbsp; Science by the Pint is back for the 2012 season :)&amp;nbsp; The first installation features Dr. Alan Aspuru-Guzik and colleagues, who will discuss their work on clean energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;For the uninitiated, Science by the Pint is an event sponsored by Science in the News, an organization of Harvard graduate students who are dedicated to bringing cutting edge scientific research to the public in a fun and informal format.&amp;nbsp; The event features a main speaker who talks for about 5-10 minutes about their research, then the team comes around to individual tables and spends one-on-one time answering questions over food and refreshments.&amp;nbsp; There are drawings for prizes, and lots of nerdy fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The event officially starts at 7:00, but the earlier you get there, the better chance you have of finding fellow nerds and a place to sit.&amp;nbsp; Plus you can get your food and drinks, and be ready once the action begins.&amp;nbsp; Doreen and I will have our nerdy Meetup pins, so look for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Tavern in the Square is located on Mass Ave, just a short walk from the Porter Square Red Line stop.&amp;nbsp; But for those who must drive, there is parking along side and in back of the building, entering just to the left of the main entrance, plus metered parking on Mass Ave (which stops collecting quarters at 6:00).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Park in the Porter Square Shopping Center at your own peril.&amp;nbsp; There be dragons there with tow trucks, who will be draggin' your car off to their lair someplace in the Bowels of Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/science-by-the-pint/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/science-by-the-pint/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavporter/"&gt;http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavporter/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us at the back across from the bar...we'll be wearing our Meetup pins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>24</waitlist_count><updated>1330209407000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329187856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science by the Pint!  Dr. Alan Aspuru-Guzik on Clean Energy</name><id>52257502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329867000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/52257502/</event_url></item>