<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Potential parking fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per car (CT resident)</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Squeezing in one more hike for the day! ;-) We'll meet up at the parking area at Black Rock State Park near the loop in the road beside Black Rock Pond. Then we'll a 2 - 3 mile hike (exact length depends on how much daylight we can get - i.e. heavy overcast will make a shorter hike). This event should be over by 5 PM. The effort for this hike is anticipated to be moderate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike is partially out and back and includes a loop in the middle. We'll start out on an unmaked trail to get to the Blue blazed trail (part of the Mattatuck trail system) and then take the red blazed trail to the northwest. We'll then pick up the blue trail again and follow that to the park boundary about .6 mile further. Then we'll hike back past the northern junction with the red trail to a scenic view. Then on past the southern junction with the red trail to where we first took up the blue trail. At this point we'll figure how much more daylight/time we have and if enough we'll hike the additional .47 mile out on the blue trail to the southern boundary of the park with Bidwell Hill Rd. (additional .94 mile total out and back). Then back to the parking area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a flashlight just in case clouds cut light levels near the end of the hike. I'll have a pack so I can carry them if need be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) is leading on this one so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tucked into the scenic rolling hills of the Western Highlands, 439-acre Black Rock offers a variety of outdoor activities (hiking, camping, swimming, fishing). Steep, wooded ledges covered with pine, hemlock and oak provide the setting for Black Rock Pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be a parking fee: $7 CT Resident, $10 non-resident&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the park (&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/parks/blackrock.htm"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt; ). A map for parking and trails (&lt;a href="http://dep.state.ct.us/stateparks/maps/blackrockgis.pdf"&gt;http://dep.state.ct.u...&lt;/a&gt; ).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 8 north: &lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 38&lt;br /&gt;* Turn left at the end of the exit ramp to first traffic light&lt;br /&gt;* Turn left at traffic light onto US Route 6 west&lt;br /&gt;* Park entrance is a 1/2 mile on the right on US Route 6. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 8 south: &lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 38&lt;br /&gt;* Go straight ahead at the end of the exit ramp to US Route 6 west&lt;br /&gt;* Park entrance is on the right on US Route 6.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1162849451000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162050221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Black Rock State Park in Watertown CT</name><id>5228711</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1162671300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5228711/</event_url></item>