<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;******ATTENTION*****&lt;br /&gt;****EVENT MOVED TO THURSDAY DUE TO WEATHER****&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I  thought it would be nice to have a Halloween get together for the group. You can dress yourself and/ or your dog up or not. I'll be bringing fresh cold New Hampshire water for the pups and fresh hot New Hampshire apple cider for the humans. I&amp;quot;ll be bringing homemade treats for the pups and some recipes for the humans. Hence, the treats. I thought it might be nice if anyone else makes homemade dog treats they could bring some along as well as the recipes to share. Just a thought, and again, if this doesn't work for you then just come by and play some ball and enjoy some cider. It should be fun. See you at the Park. &amp;quot;WOOF&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I changed the time on this meetup, I know its hard for alot of us to get to the park by 5 or so. So just come when you can. Darkness in the northern woods comes early these days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also.... after Benedictine Park, we are going to &lt;a href="http://www.t-bones.com/locations.php?loc=1" target="_blank"&gt;T-bones in Bedford&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.go2cjs.com/locations.php?loc=1" target="_blank"&gt;Cactus Jack's in Manchester&lt;/a&gt; (per Liz's most excellent suggestion) as they will donate $5 to the Animal Rescue league and give you a $5 gift certificate towards your next visit; a win-win donation! &lt;a href="http://www.t-bones.com/happenin.php" target="_blank"&gt;[ certificate rules ]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Don't hesitate to pipe in with your restaurant preference.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also be making our selections from the Pet Edge catalogue Liz gave us 2 weeks ago so we can make one larger order and save on shipping. So bring your catalog wish list, check book and mad money for dinner !!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the Picnic table towards the back of the park.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jennifer</member_name><member_id>4251176</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4894798</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225574721000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220914631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trick &amp; then a Treat Evening at The Park.</name><id>8717032</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225401300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/8717032/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/4/global_5449348.jpeg</photo_url></item>