<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Big Howdy Hello!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am joining some other folks to host a benefit cocktail party for my friend and community events producer  Aliza Shapiro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aliza recently found out that she has to have a medically necessary major surgery on February 18. As a self-employed community event producer (Truth Serum Productions) and full time performance artist, Aliza will not have any income during her surgery and recovery afterwards. The immediate need for this surgery is a surprise and she is unprepared for the financial strain that 4-6+ weeks of downtime will create. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through Truth Serum Productions events, her different venues like CineMental and via performing, Aliza has raised thousands of dollars for non-profits, special causes, and grassroots efforts and recently did a fund-raiser for the Massachusetts Transgender Political Coalition. Since 1994 Truth Serum Productions has hosted hundreds of artists from around the world and in doing so, has made Boston a better place for us all. We must come together to help support her though this surgery and recovery process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me at Utero-A-GoGo on Friday February 5, 2010 at 8pm. The party will be held at a private SOWA loft, recently featured in The New York Times. We’ll have celebrity bartenders (Josey Packard, recently featured on The Rachel Maddow Show and other other ladies of Lupec) mixing custom cocktails, delicious food and some entertainment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go here: &lt;a href="http://www.truthserum.org/uteroagogo1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.truthserum...&lt;/a&gt; and use PayPal to make a donation of $41 or more per person to attend the party. You can also use the links to use a credit card, or we can make arrangements for your donation at the event. Questions can be sent to me, or to the host committee at uteroagogo@gmail.com. When your donation goes through, your name will be added to the list to receive the address. If you can donate more, by all means, please do. Any amount you can donate will be appreciated and go far to supporting our friend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to spread the word to others you think would enjoy this opportunity and spend some time with other activists, artists, and musicians in an intimate setting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets show some community support and love to one of our own in need. I appreciate you taking the time to read this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks so much&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jo</member_name><member_id>3137718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boston Dyke March</member_name><member_id>3425442</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elisa</member_name><member_id>5219005</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>5396090</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>stephanie</member_name><member_id>5693742</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>spencer</member_name><member_id>5978741</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265764457000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends of the Boston Dyke March</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostondykemarch</urlname><id>997856</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Dyke March</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265389419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Utero-A-GoGo</name><id>12527959</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265590800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostondykemarch/events/12527959/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/6/global_7437302.jpeg</photo_url></item>