<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Endless Opportunities at Danvers Martial Arts &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello This is Anthony J Pasquale from Mindful Wealth! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a presentation on the Unfranchise Business System. Please feel free to invite members of your family or friends. Not only will you learn how to save money on everything you already purchase everyday, but you will also learn how to turn that savings into income.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MICROSOFT has recently partnered with Market America to create the Economy of the Future and Market America is changing the way people shop, the way people do business and the way people earn money on the internet.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have partnered with almost every major fortune 500 company and top names that you probably already shop at like walmart, target, ebay, etc...and they have also been featured nationally in haute living magazine, as well as our associates and partnerships all over the media. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If you wait for inspiration you'll be standing on the corner after the parade is a mile down the street.&amp;quot; -- Ben Nicholas  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been noticing (and I'm sure you have to), while many businesses and individuals might be struggling right now, that there is also a group of businesses and individuals flourishing. I've also noticed there are some common characteristics found in these businesses and individuals who seem to be doing well during some of these uncertain times.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are five characteristics that stand out:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) Help others be Successful in their dreams so they love what they do! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Help others create a path of wealth so they don't have to worry! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(3) Get them to help you help others so they feel the meaning in life! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(4) Have fun doing what you do best! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(5) Believe in something greater than yourself, step out of your own way and you will move quicker towards your destiny! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss this great event, come see how we are changing the way people live their lives! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Pasquale  &lt;br /&gt;AJP Enterprise  &lt;br /&gt;A Mindful Wealth Group &lt;br /&gt;United Martial Arts Center &lt;br /&gt;Osanna Seminars &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Live with Purpose and Passion Everyday&amp;quot; !  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.umachealth.com  &lt;br /&gt;www.danversmartialarts.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.couragewithin.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.couragewit...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ideal Business Center &lt;br /&gt;20 Locust Street, Suite 100  &lt;br /&gt;Danvers MA 01923  &lt;br /&gt;(978) 836-6501  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain &amp;quot;average&amp;quot;. These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will meet them at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254138428000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251902759000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Endless Opportunities and meet great people creating Mindful Wealth!</name><id>11268310</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253663100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/11268310/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/e/1/global_7343345.jpeg</photo_url></item>