<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two coastal hikes &amp;amp; a winter trip to Shipyard's Brewpub!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/7/4/event_8407796.jpeg" width="234" height="160" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rachel &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Carson&lt;/span&gt; Wildlife Refuge&lt;/strong&gt; has several units along the southern Maine coast. This section contains the refuge headquarters as well as a mile-long wildlife trail/boardwalk. This will be a short walk among pine woods, salt marsh, and river estuary with sightings of red fox and moose possible, as well as lot's of birds. Afterward, we'll drive a couple of miles to another special coastal area,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/f/4/event_91633812.jpeg" width="145" height="138" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parson&lt;/span&gt;'s Beach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Here there are dunes and sand beach to hike along for a couple of miles, and of course great ocean views. Parson's is a private stretch of prime sandy dune and beach that's been opened to the public by its owners. There's limited parking along Parson's Beach Rd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/9/0/event_91633712.jpeg" width="162" height="154" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;And by that time we'll be very hungry and thirsty, so we'll head over to &lt;strong&gt;Federal &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Jack&lt;/span&gt;'s&lt;/strong&gt; on the water in Kennebunkport for great views, Shipyard brews, margaritas, and an extensive menu. They are always friendly and welcome our large groups without a fuss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/1/8/event_91634872.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Figure&amp;nbsp;three hours of easy hiking followed by many hours of eating and drinking! If we still have some energy, there are some nice walks around the town of Kennebunkport, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool:&lt;/strong&gt; 11:15&amp;nbsp;AM Portsmouth Park &amp;amp; Ride 185 Grafton Ave. There are two parking lots. Meet in the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;overflow&lt;/span&gt; lot - the lot farthest from the main bus terminal building, farther up Grafton Ave. Meet&amp;nbsp;at the very back of the lot. I won't be there so use comments on the listing to let folks know you want to ride together. The Refuge is 40mins from Portsmouth.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;: The &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Rachel Carson Refuge&lt;/span&gt; is on Route 9 heading toward Kennebunkport, around the corner from&amp;nbsp;Wells Reserve. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parson's Beach&lt;/span&gt; Road is a right turn a little further down Route 9. (Don't take Hart Rd.) &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Federal Jack's&lt;/span&gt; is in downtown Kennebunkport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring Microspikes!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;(But come anyway if you don't have them.) &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;No Pets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.&amp;nbsp; Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving&amp;nbsp;home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329790169000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328549604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carson, Parson, and Jack!</name><id>51247052</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329584400000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/51247052/</event_url></item>