<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Twin Mountain</address_2><address_1>Off Rt 3</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03595</zip><lat>44.288383</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Galehead trailhead</name><city>Twin Mountain</city><id>353682</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.544020</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a moderate hike with no steep grades. This is a 5 mile trip from the Gale River Loop Rd off of Rt 3. &lt;br /&gt;The mountain is remote in winter because the dirt Gale River Road is closed. It's an approximate 1.6 mile walk from Trudeau Road on Rt-3. Follow the plowed and gated road (on-foot) to the road split. Stay left as the road splits and follow to the second split. At this fork, take your right and the trailhead is just .4 miles. This area sees allot of snowmobile travel so be careful if you're traveling at night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The wooded summit of Mt Galehead is just .5 miles from Galehead Hut via the Frost trail. This is the most direct route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the way up there are some views back towards the hut and the Twins. From the summit you can just make out Franconia Ridge through the trees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At about 3 miles, the trail bears away from the Gale River and begins a more earnest ascent to the Galehead Hut. The scenery is wooded with the occasional view out over the valley. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 4.6 miles you reach the saddle where the Galehead Hut (3,800 ft.) is located and the first really beautiful views. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.hike-nh.com/trips/gale_gar/galeHut.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From here much of the Pemigewasset wilderness is visible, especially in decent weather. Views of the Twins and lesser peaks are available, and the hut is an excellent place to rest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the hut the Twinway goes north towards South Twin and south towards Garfield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Galehead trailhead is located on the Gale River Loop (FR 92), just off NH Rt 3. &lt;br /&gt;opposite the intersection with Trudeau Road at Five Corners. The road is gated in winter. Hike 1.6 miles until you reach the parking area on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Winter mileage is 12 miles.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;Disclaimer and things you must know. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204638796000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201632852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter hike series: Mt Galehead   3/02/08</name><id>7221746</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204465500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7221746/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/4/global_3097044.jpeg</photo_url></item>