<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 141</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1346807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Please Note - to confirm your attendance at this event, you must register at the &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-contactless-payment-update/"&gt;MIT Enterprise Forum of Cambridge website&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've ever stood in line to buy a transit fare card in Boston, New York or other major city, you know the problems -- the people in front of you take too long; the machine's instructions are too complicated; some credit cards get rejected, and sooner or later the transit fare card will run out of money anyway.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now imagine you never have to stand in line at those machines again. You simply wave your smart phone at the gate, the gate opens and you proceed to the platform -- and the fare is automatically charged to your credit card or bank account.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's the vision of a group of leading innovators - in Near Field Communications, systems integration, chip development, and financial systems - speaking Monday evening, April 25th, at MIT. The topic is &lt;strong&gt;open contactless transit payment systems&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/rfid-contactless-payment-update/#register"&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George Kocur&lt;/strong&gt;, &amp;nbsp;A senior lecturer at MIT, George has been working for the past three years with London's transit system to develop the world's first Open Payment smartphone-based transit application. It's based on MIT research into Near Field Communications (NFC) and smartphone technologies sponsored by Nokia. &amp;nbsp;And now New York City's Metropolitan Transit Authority is planning to deploy these same Open Payment specifications. George may share some of the challenges to opening the payment market for public transit -- a very, very radical idea -- and a goal he's been working on with major transit operators and financial service providers. Those include, not just MasterCard, Visa and American Express, but also all the backend processors who may offer cities cost effective alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeff Emerson,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;A partner at Accenture's Advanced Systems and Technology practice, Jeff leads a major systems integration team committed to building open transit payment systems. As the CTO of Accenture's Transit business, Jeff establishes the technology vision for how Accenture's transportation software and related technology offerings will meet the needs of tomorrow's transit and payments market -- shifting focus to the passenger and placing customer choice and fare policy flexibility at the epicenter of innovation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wendy Humphrey&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp; As the business development executive for Bank of America's Integrated Channels organization, Wendy is focused on realizing the benefits of digitizing currency transactions using contactless payment to lower processing costs and accelerate dollar volumes. As such, she identifies, investigates and monitors opportunities to deepen and expand strategic business relationships that advance integrated channel capabilities for the Bank of America's integrated Consumer Banking eChannels and Customer Solutions organization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Charlie Walton&lt;/strong&gt;, As chief operating officer of INSIDE Secure, a provider of contactless chips, here in the United States, Charles leads the launch of new contactless and NFC products in the payments, transit and access/ID verticals. As the founder and CEO of Caradas, he was involved in authentication and smart card system development and integration programs with Visa, MasterCard, Fleet Bank, and Target. In addition, he served as COO of Diversinet driving mobile security initiatives, along with smart card and security experience with Securify (SVP, Security Services), CertCo (COO), and Spyrus (Director of Electronic Commerce). He was also the co-founder of the CyberTrust business at GTE and instrumental in capturing key first contract wins with MasterCard, American Express and in Japan through the CyberTrust Japan joint venture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Louis Bianchin&lt;/strong&gt;, A seasoned veteran of the RFID market, Louis is driving the deployment of smartcards and NFC smartphone enabling technologies for Watchdata Technologies USA, a world leader in innovative smart card, data security, authentication and chip operating system technologies. Louis is a Certified Smart Card Industry Professional (CSCIP) and a LEAP (Leadership, Education, &amp;amp; Advancement Program) member with the Smart Card Association. He is actively involved as well in the Healthcare and Payment Councils at SCA. Louis has been a Lecturer at Boston University, Harvard University and University of Quebec in Montreal and is a member of the MIT Enterprise Forum RFID SIG Program Committee.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Cronk</member_name><member_id>465168</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Louis Bianchin</member_name><member_id>9866665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303827521000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294682951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NFC Smartphones for Tap 'n Go Transit Payments</name><id>15994716</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303768800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/15994716/</event_url></item>