<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Update: Hi Everybody! I just spoke with a ranger at Dunn Park. Today's event is a go yet with wind gusts expected up to 30MPH today, we are going to have to skip doing the outdoor fire today. He tells me we can still bring marshmallows to cook at the indoor fireplace though. We may be the bulk of attendees today so it will be like having our own little party. See you all soon. We can still bring our goodies if we'd like to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Come join the fun with me at Dunn Park. This is a scheduled event with a ranger leading a short hike and enjoying snacks by the huge indoor fireplace following the hike. This is a great event for beginner hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;We can also make this a longer hike and enjoy cooking outside if we wish to. This event is child and dog(on leash) friendly. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I cannot copy and paste this event so please click below for further information...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/events/1-1dunn.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/events/1-1dunn.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Note that pre-registration by December 30th is requested(Yet not required) for this event. Thank you! The telephone number is posted so please check out the information and call ahead if you able to. Please also RSVP here and mention if you'll be bringing something to enjoy outside at the cooking fireplace as well. If you want to bring something but not sure yet what...just maybe say "bringing something for the fire." Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Please also note: I've been on these trails many times in the winter months and they always seem to be icy especially around the lake so I recommend using some kind of traction, ie: micro-spikes, crampons, etc...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/dunn.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/dunn.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dunn State Park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fishing at Dunn Pond &lt;br /&gt;

 Dunn State Park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;289 Pearl St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gardner 01440 &lt;br /&gt;

 978 632-7897&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 130-acre park features a 20 acre pond, walking trails, swimming, fishing, picnicking, public programs, and play equipment. Private canoes and non-motorized boats are allowed on the pond. In the winter the trails are open for cross country skiing, ice skating is allowed on the pond and often there is a fire blazing in the visitors centers fireplace. All activities offered by the park are accessible to people with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking Fees &lt;br /&gt;

 Parking fees are in effect at Dunn State Park from Memorial weekend through Labor Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail Map &lt;br /&gt;

 Download printable version (pdf)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park Directions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The park is located in north central Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the East/Northeast/Southeast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-495 to exit 29, Rt. 2 west. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 23.5 miles on Rt. 2 west to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 At the bottom of the exit ramp, merge onto Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2.7 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left on to Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Park entrance is on left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take 1-90 west (MA PIKE) to exit 10, I-290 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 18.75 miles on I-190 north and merge onto Rt. 2 west. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 12 miles on Rt. 2 west to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 At the bottom of the exit ramp, merge onto Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2.7 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left onto Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Park entrance is on left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the West&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Rt. 2 east to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 At the bottom of the exit ramp, take a left on to Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2.8 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a left on to Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Park entrance is on left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Southwest/Northwest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-91 to Exit 27, Rt. 2 east. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 29 miles on Rt. 2 east to exit 24, Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 At the bottom of the exit ramp take a left on to Rt. 140 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2.8 miles on Rt. 140 north and take a right on to Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 1 mile on Rt. 101 west, Pearl St. &lt;br /&gt;

 Park entrance is on left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are no parking fees in effect right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357626016000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356298859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Day Hike/Snacks by the Indoor Fireplace at Dunn Park</name><id>96358682</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357059600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/96358682/</event_url></item>