<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Meeting time:&amp;nbsp; As far as I can tell,&amp;nbsp;the movie is scheduled to&amp;nbsp;start at 7:30 p.m. so please plan to meet at 7:00&amp;nbsp;p.m. in the outer lobby of the AMC Framingham. I plan to get in line for tickets about 20 minutes before so we can get snacks and then get seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discount tickets: I will have discount coupons available so we can get tickets for $8.00 each. (Retail price is $10.50.) I will collect $8 in cash from each person and then I'll get in line to buy tickets for all. Exact change is helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, those who want to are welcome to go out to a local restaurant to chat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Film description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the Great Depression, Jacob, a penniless and recently-orphaned veterinary school student, parlays his expertise with animals into a job with a second-rate traveling circus. He falls in love with Marlena, one of the show's star performers, but their romance is complicated by Marlena's husband, the charismatic but unbalanced circus boss. &lt;br /&gt;Director: Francis Lawrence &lt;br /&gt;Cast: Robert Pattinson, Reese Witherspoon, James Frain, Christoph Waltz &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG-13 &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Romantic Drama &lt;br /&gt;Runtime: 2 hr.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the outer lobby, off to the right as you come in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>6039490</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304095215000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>I hear the book is great!</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303651615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framingham Movie Meetup: Water for Elephants - Thursday, April 28, 2011</name><id>17413682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304031600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/17413682/</event_url></item>