<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>154-158 Prospect St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.369123</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-8661 </phone><name>Koreana</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1090255</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101136</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diner time by arriving promptly.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip and tax.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a yes after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO in less than twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you have RSVPd for NO-Show it will count as if you have NO-SHOWED.....   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone, from you , who could or has been on the wait list, to the organizer as well as the restaurant's wait staff based on our reservation.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-four hours from the event and you are not able to attend or you are running late, you must contact the organizer.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than twenty-four hours RSVP change from YES to NO is an expected courtesy.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation , please  RSVP NO with a comment requesting to place on the wait list.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and venue by completing the surveys after the events.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizer(s) will arrive at least fifteen minutes before the event to confirm seating as well as welcome you.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just to let you know parking is free on Sunday in Cambridge and the restaurant offers free parking spaces near their establishment call them for more information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best place to park is on Broadway street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are taking the MBTA - take the Red Line to Central Square  go to Mass Ave and Prospect Street. Once on Prospect Street walk down pass Whole Foods Market on your left and one more block Koreana will be on your right hand side before the next set of lights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Korena visit their web site at:&lt;br /&gt;www.koreanaboston.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside the resturant.
Reservations will be under Jo-Ann Keith..</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allan</member_name><member_id>4472329</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208293472000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><why>Good converstaion, and the people at this meetup what can  I say great group, fun etc.
This place offers food for everyone.</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205200299000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at Koreana</name><id>7507310</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208120400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7507310/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/2/global_3453010.jpeg</photo_url></item>