<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.733029</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bow Tie Cinema City</name><city>Hartford</city><id>684699</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.661139</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the last night that Bow Tie Cinema City will be at their Brainard Road location.  Starting on Friday 23 July they move to the Palace 17 &amp;amp; Odyssey Theatre (another Meetup is already planning to go, we may tag onto them for &amp;quot;The Kids Are Alright&amp;quot; on opening night) so this is the last chance to see movies here.  Even though we have another meetup scheduled for this evening, there should be enough time to get from there to here for a 7:30pm showing.  And for those who cannot attend the earlier movie, join the other indie fans in Hartford for one final viewing at this obscurely-located cinema.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE:  Tonight when we went to see &amp;quot;Coco &amp;amp; Igor,&amp;quot; the cinema had posters up and they handed out flyers stating that BOTH the final movies at the Brainard Road location will be FREE.  So come to either one, and we might go to The Chowder Pot after for a farewell round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the movies is &amp;quot;The Queen&amp;quot; starring Helen Mirren and Michael Sheen.   &lt;a href="http://www.thequeen-movie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thequeen-m...&lt;/a&gt;   This movie gives a behind-the-scenes view of life in Buckingham Palace, centering around the death of Princess Diana and how the royals reacted, or felt they were required to react.  At Monday's movie one of the indie fans said it was &amp;quot;very British, very reserved&amp;quot; but quite interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other choice is Roberto Benigni's &amp;quot;Life is Beautiful (La vita e bella)&amp;quot; if you'd rather:  &lt;i&gt;The film is a Chaplinesque fable about the power of imagination set against the stark reality of World War II Europe. The film combines satire, physical comedy, social commentary and a touch of the surreal into a uniquely moving story of love. At the center of the fable is Guido, an enchanting individual with childlike innocence and grand dreams of owning his own book shop. It's 1939, and he has come to the Tuscan town of Arrezzo with his poet friend Ferruccio. With unabashed humor and joy, the two seek fortune and romance, ignoring the growing anti-Semitism and Fascist government that surrounds them. Guido falls in love with Dora, a beautiful young school teacher, and a fairy tale romance ensues.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both movies won multiple awards when released.  Come see one and say farewell to the Brainard Road location.  Free popcorn and soda pop, too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;{Someone asked how to find me - I'm a short brunette and I usually knit before the movie.  I'll probably see &amp;quot;The Queen&amp;quot; and we can gather in the lobby following the films - I'll be knitting!}&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280434260000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279045264000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cinema City's Last Night - Free Movies!</name><id>14090934</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279840500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/14090934/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>