<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>America thinks Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin were the first pioneers to the moon, Alexei Fedorchenko’s mocumentary and debut film proves them wrong. &lt;b&gt;FIRST ON THE MOON&lt;/b&gt; reveals a Soviet cosmonaut, Ivan Kharlamov, who traveled there and back in 1938. He pilots his secretive space craft back to Chile, from where he undertook an arduous journey across the Pacific, through China and Mongolia finally finishing in Mother Russia. First on the Moon is a wonderful expression of the utopian spirit--the sense of limitless possibilities of human ingenuity and imagination--of the Space Race that raged during the 1950s and ‘60s before the American’s accomplishments shadowed the Soviet experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2005) dir. Alexei Fedorchencko,1h15m, in Russian with English subtitles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Sunday from Russia kicks off with this film at the Coolidge, part of their ongoing series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll gather across the street at Panera Bread starting at noon for conversation and coffee.  This is meant to be a fun film event, so we'll enjoy meeting up before the film rather than have a formal sit-down discussion after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those wishing to see both &lt;b&gt;First on the Moon&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;USSR's The Ascent&lt;/b&gt; at 4:00 pm at the MFA, there will be plenty of time in-between films to get there.  If the weather cooperates, Tom may lead an expedition from the Coolidge to the MFA, speaking russian the entire way, of course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can't see this film on Nyetflix, so come out on Sunday and join us,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me, Comrades, at Panera Bread across the street  holding a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222190295000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220289327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FIRST ON THE MOON </name><id>8663381</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222016400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8663381/</event_url></item>