<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Valley Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03215</zip><lat>43.947884</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waterville Valley Ski Area</name><city>Waterville Valley</city><id>1962461</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.501991</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Wedeln Summer hiking series kicks off with a hike to the summit of Mt. Tecumseh, home of Waterville Valley ski area.&amp;nbsp; This will be the first of three hikes this summer under the theme of "You've Skied (or Boarded) it, now Hike it!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will depart from the parking lot of the ski area, ascending the Mt. Tecumseh trail. The trail is about 2.5 miles to the summit with a climb of about 2,200 feet. In addition there is an optional .5 mile long spur trail to the top of the High Country lift that should provide great views. We will travel at an easy to moderate pace, reaching the summit in 1.5-2 hours. Waterville Valley is located off of exit 28 of I-93 in New Hampshire on highway 49. Once you take the exit, turn right and drive through Campton. The ski area access road is about 10 miles from I-93 and should take about 2 hours to drive to from Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please dress appropriately for hiking (Backpack, Sturdy shoes/Hiking boots, at least 2 liters of water, high energy snacks/lunch for the summit, and if possible no cotton) I will have a map and a basic first aid kit with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, there is a parking lot on the side of 49 that has access to the Mad River for a post hike dip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Severe weather will cancel this hike, I will update as we get closer to hiking day.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in a Gold/Silver Volvo XC70.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George Fraley</member_name><member_id>10925592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309098279000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306888893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt. Tecumseh (Waterville Vallley)</name><id>20447091</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309093200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/20447091/</event_url></item>