<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Boston Entrepreneurs Network is a premier networking group where professionals and entrepreneurs meet in mutual support of business to network, socialize, learn, and promote a thriving community of entrepreneurs.    Wine and snacks provided!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule: &lt;br /&gt;6pm-6:30pm -- Open Networking over wine and snacks&lt;br /&gt;6:30-6:45pm -- Meeting Called to Order and Individual Introductions to group!&lt;br /&gt;6:45-7pm -- Referrals announced, tesimonials, and welcome to new members.&lt;br /&gt;7pm-7:30pm -- 3 10-minute open discussions on topics selected by members from prior meeting.&lt;br /&gt;7:30-7:40pm -- Presentation by group member on topic of interest to membership!&lt;br /&gt;7:40-7:45pm - Announcements, selection of topics for next meeting and presenter.&lt;br /&gt;7:45-8pm -- More Networking! (and wine!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: The Boston Entrepreneurs Group will meet every other week on Wednesday from 6-8pm.  We had a great meeting at the last meeting where we discussed what the members want to get out of the Boston Entrepreneurs Networking Group.  The group decided that we wanted to following outcomes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Referrals&lt;br /&gt;2) Open Discussion on Topics relevant to running a business&lt;br /&gt;3) Education/Presentations on topics of interest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The way the group seeks to achieve these outcomes:&lt;br /&gt;1) Regular attendance (when possible)&lt;br /&gt;2) Dedication to coming with either a referral, a friend, or having met one-on-one with another group member during the week to build trust.&lt;br /&gt;3) Create a fun and supportive environment!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all next time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Marston</member_name><member_id>2731493</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1152914548000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1151535984000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Entrepreneur JULY Meetup</name><id>5000366</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1152741600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/5000366/</event_url></item>