<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>These are movies I didn't see this summer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Site (2009) Directed by Michael Mann. Screenplay by Michael Mann, Ronan Bennett and Ann Biderman, based on the book by Bryan Burrough. Cast: Johnny Depp, Christian Bale, Marion Cotillard, Billy Crudup. Back in the Great Depression when soup kitchens, tent cities and hoboes were part of life, Indiana farm boy John Dillinger charmed the public by choosing the much-hated banks as the target of his robberies. Johnny Depp gets the charm no problem but he doesn't stop there, creating an ambiguous hero who both ruthless and charismatic. The woman in his life is tough-talking Marion Cotillard, winner of the Best Actress Academy Award for La Vie En Rose; while the FBI honcho bent on taking Dillinger out is played by an edgy Christian Bale (The Dark Knight). Don't miss one of the last chances to see Public Enemies on the big screen, where director Michael Mannís visual wizardry will blow you away. &amp;quot;Public Enemies comes at you like Dillinger did: all of a sudden. It's movie dynamite.&amp;quot; Peter Travers, Rolling Stone 133 min.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the lobby, with glasses, a smile, and maybe, still a ponytail.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252712382000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251772633000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Public Enemies</name><id>11253725</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252539000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11253725/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>