<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ACROSS STREET from 261 Union St. (Crepes Tea House), Ground Floor; Park &amp; enter on the opposite side of the st. from Tea House</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.099113</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>A to Z Moving Company</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>698661</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.617401</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will have guests from New York City on hand. You're invited!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t try to make friendships &amp;hellip; we make powerful bonds between men, whether they like each other or not. &amp;nbsp;A &amp;lsquo;regular guy&amp;rsquo; can step into this space and be feel empowered to tell the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;unvarnished truth&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;about his life.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re not here to put on a show for each other.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re not here to set ourselves up in opposition to a perceived &amp;lsquo;other&amp;rsquo; in the world. We&amp;rsquo;re not here to offer salvation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re here to cut through the bullshit&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;that we&amp;rsquo;ve been taught are the fundamentals of being a man. We&amp;rsquo;re here to step through the fear of showing up authentically, warts and all, in our lives and loves. We&amp;rsquo;re here to find and explore our self-made purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you struggle with commitment,&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with discipline, with emotional honesty, with feelings of powerlessness or inadequacy, with anger, frustration, depression &amp;ndash; this is a kind of bonding that will help you break old patterns and find YOUR PLACE in a community.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are outwardly successful&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and looking to become more integrated with other parts of &amp;nbsp;your life &amp;ndash; this is a place to come and explore, refine and express the other parts of yourself that may be hiding out in the shadows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you have never felt safe or at ease in a group of men&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;- this is a place to figure out why and to change that. Your success depends on your efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are a change agent, a man working with others for the good of society&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;- this kind of bonding is essential to your efforts to create sustainable solutions in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the flag hung inside the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305123544000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>We will have the cast from a new play by James Scruggs on hand to experience a men's circle with us, one night ahead of their reading in Northampton. This is bound to be an evening of exploration and discovery.</why><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304565039000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BONUS Open Men's Group this Month Tuesday May 10</name><id>17551288</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305066600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/17551288/</event_url></item>