<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone invites its members and the specter of Helena Ruth Wooster&lt;br /&gt;To join us for a cup of coffee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Restaurant was once the Wooster Estate of the late William HH Wooster.&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Wooster once lived there with his wife and six children.&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Wooster was considered to be a Captain of Industry.&lt;br /&gt;He was involved with the Seymour Manufacturing Company, Trust and Water Company.&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Wooster, his family members, and especially his daughter, &lt;br /&gt;Ruth, are believed to have their spectral energies still within the Wooster Estate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.carouselgardens.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.carouselga...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.carouselgardens.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to the Web Site, some of the happenings involve:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.carouselgardens.com/paranormal.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.carouselga...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.carouselgardens.com/paranormal.html&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wooster ghostly cat is still prowling and meowing around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ghostly glasses are falling to the ground and making noises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coats are being tugged when no one is there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A place on the table is left for Ruth.  Maybe we should do that?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Chef was giving a waitress a hard time.  A Spoon fell on his head.&lt;br /&gt;The waitress thanks Ruth for her support.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cosmicsociety.com/carouselmeeting.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cosmicsoci...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.cosmicsociety.com/carouselmeeting.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.100megsfree4.com/farshores/phaunt2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.100megsfre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.100megsfree4.com/farshores/phaunt2.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://books.google.com/books?id=IhOaKHzVKgYC&amp;amp;pg=PA6&amp;amp;lpg=PA6&amp;amp;dq=carousel+gardens+ruth&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;ots=_ZreucZXtC&amp;amp;sig=ddn6oO4Z-Ijhg12W0hkk-P93fis#PPA6,M1" target="_blank"&gt;http://books.google.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;books.google.com/books?id=IhOaKHzVKgYC&amp;amp;pg=PA6&amp;amp;lpg=PA6&amp;amp;dq=carousel+gardens+ruth&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;ots=_ZreucZXtC&amp;amp;sig=ddn6oO4Z-Ijhg12W0hkk-P93fis#PPA6,M1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open when no one is there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your camera to this coffee and maybe spectral energy Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe we can get photos of at least orbs, if not even more energy forms.&lt;br /&gt;The Carousel Gardens Restaurant (CGR) websites has photos of orbs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe the Ghost Investigators will share their stories of the investigations that&lt;br /&gt;They have done in this restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybes will be allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a joint Coffee Talk &amp;amp; Unknown Zone &lt;br /&gt;Meet Up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members might want to come here on their&lt;br /&gt;Own for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fridays for Karaoke&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Wednesdays of the month for the Cosmic Societys&lt;br /&gt;Ghost Hunter Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Psychic Fairs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We might add more information as we get closer to the event date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;January 26,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tony Diana has agreed to give a lecture at this Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;That is unless some urgent case does not come up.&lt;br /&gt;He might be able to work with Carousel Gardens&lt;br /&gt;In case he needs some presentation equipment for the room.&lt;br /&gt;At this time it is unknown if Tony will be bringing any guests with him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All other members who attend this meet up are encouraged to&lt;br /&gt;Add to the discussion of the Meet Up during the Q &amp;amp; A &lt;br /&gt;and after the lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday, January 26, I went there in person to &lt;br /&gt;Confirm the reservation and leave a deposit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is just off Rt 67.   Coming from West Haven / New Haven, I really&lt;br /&gt;Did not see the sign.  I had to go beyond Rt. 8 and turn around&lt;br /&gt;in a McDonalds (after getting a coffee)  and&lt;br /&gt;Then I saw the huge CGR sign.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is on North Street, but I could not&lt;br /&gt;Find a North Street sign any where at that intersection.&lt;br /&gt;I got it, the specter energy keeps taking the street sign?&lt;br /&gt;Actually, more than likely local kids took it down and the&lt;br /&gt;State is slow in putting one back up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best way to describe where it is...&lt;br /&gt;On Rt 67, when you get into Seymour, look for an intersection&lt;br /&gt;That has a Gulf Gas Station, Village View Pizza Restaurant, &lt;br /&gt;Exxon Gas Station and Citgo Gas Station.&lt;br /&gt;CGR is up a hill right behind the Gulf Gas Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I shall cancel and reschedule this Meet Up if there is any&lt;br /&gt;Adverse weather that might affect the driving conditions.&lt;br /&gt;Rt 67 is full of dangerous curves during normal &lt;br /&gt;Driving Conditions.  &lt;br /&gt;Rt 34 to 115 to 67 was a little less risky than Rt 67.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, Feb. 19&lt;br /&gt;Ghost Investigator Tony Diana and his sister, Psychic&lt;br /&gt;Medium Angelina Diana have confirmed that they&lt;br /&gt;Are both attending this Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;Angelina might be doing randon psychic readings&lt;br /&gt;At this Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to know more about Angelina, then&lt;br /&gt;Her Meet UP link is below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://psychics.meetup.com/273/"&gt;http://psychics.meetu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;psychics.meetup.com/273/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B.&lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;Greater New Haven Unknown Zone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Assistant Organizer of Coffee Talk&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have reserved a room in my name at the restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205438766000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Who wants to have a hot drink and brunch in a haunted restaurant?</why><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197827288000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee in a Ghostly Seymour Restaurant</name><id>6921853</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205085600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6921853/</event_url></item>