<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Curzon Mill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.822050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-7223</phone><name>Maudslay State Park</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>848934</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.926670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bike &amp;amp; Hike Newburyport, MA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;an adventure for Cyclists, Hikers, Nature Lovers &amp;amp; Birders&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Featuring:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Moseley State Park&lt;br /&gt;Historic Newburyport &lt;br /&gt;Parker River National Wildlife Refuge&lt;br /&gt;Sandy Point State Reservation&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our adventure begins with a ride through the grounds of the former Moseley estate.  See the ruins of a 19th century mansion and gardens and in-season, the state’s largest mountain laurel display.  From here we will pedal through historic downtown Newburyport on route to Parker River National Wildlife Refuge ultimately ending on the tip of the island at Sandy Point State Reservation.  Along the way we will do some exploring off our bikes by foot.  Lunch will be on the beach.  We will return to are starting point by retracing our route with a stop for ice-cream along the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate Mileage:&lt;/b&gt; about 22 miles roundtrip?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Terrain:&lt;/b&gt; overall flat with a combination of surfaces – asphalt, dirt/gravel road &amp;amp; uneven trails with rocks &amp;amp; roots.  &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Mountain Bike is MANDATORY&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moseley State Park&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The former Moseley family estate on the Merrimack River, now state park features 19th century gardens and plantings, rolling meadows, towering pines, and one of the largest naturally-occurring stands of mountain laurel in Massachusetts. Most spectacular are the ornamental trees and masses of azaleas and rhododendrons that bloom in May and June.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Park Website – print a trail map here&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/maud.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parker River National Wildlife Refuge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Established in 1942 to provide feeding, resting, and nesting habitat for migratory birds. The refuge occupies 4,662 acres on the southern two-thirds of Plum Island, a barrier island on the Northeast coast of Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/no...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sandy Point State Reservation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sandy Point is at the very southern tip of Plum Island, a classic Atlantic Ocean barrier island. The 77-acre park is among the state's most beautiful and popular coastal beaches. It is also an important nesting area for the piping plover, a threatened species, and the least tern, a species of special concern in Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/sndp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Starting Point:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Moseley State Park&lt;br /&gt;Curzon Mill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;Newburyport, MA&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Important:  The park has two different entrances.  Please be careful which one you head to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maudslay State Park is located in north-eastern Massachusetts, on the North Shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North and South: Take Rte. 95, exit 57 to Rte. 113 east. Follow 113 east for half a mile and turn left on Noble St. At stop sign turn left onto Ferry Rd., bear left at fork and follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From West: Take I-495 exit 55 to Rte. 110 east. Continue 1 mile to Merrill St., turn right at second light. Continue on Merrill St./Spofford St. for 1.5 miles. Turn right before stop sign onto Ferry Rd., follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Equipment:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Helmets are mandatory for the event.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;You must have a Mountain Bik&lt;/u&gt;e to participate in this adventure.  Please be sure to bring a spare tube and pump.&lt;br /&gt;Bicycle Chain - it will be a long walk back to the car!&lt;br /&gt;Sneakers for Nature Walks if you will be wearing clip on bike shoes.&lt;br /&gt;Sunglasses &amp;amp; Bug Repellant&lt;br /&gt;Bring a picnic lunch, water and snacks.  Water may be refilled during a Rest Stop at The Refuge Headquarters and Visitor Center before crossing the bridge onto Plum Island.&lt;br /&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON. &lt;br /&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fees:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Parking Fee at Maudslay State Park is $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;The Entrance Fee for Parker River National Wildlife Refuge is $2.00 pp for walk-ins.&lt;br /&gt;No fee to enter Sandy Point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Current Weather Forecast for Saturday&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;70’s, partly cloudy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: I will check the forecast on Friday.  This event is subject to cancellation if the weather changes for the worst.  Please be sure to supply your contact info so that I may notify you.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Departure Time:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive at 8:45 am to unload your bike and gear up.  &lt;u&gt;Wheels roll promptly at 9:00 am.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273430416000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272508610000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike &amp; Hike Newburyport, MA </name><id>13325966</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272717900000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13325966/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/4/global_14701716.jpeg</photo_url></item>