<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Look for High St and Glencliff home for the elderly</address_2><address_1>Sanitorium Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03238</zip><lat>43.992449</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Glencliff Trail</name><city>Glencliff</city><id>551566</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.886938</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be hiking Mt. Moosilaukee via the Glencliff Trail and Moosilauke Carriage Road to the summit of Mt. Moosilauke.  The total distance covered is 7.8 miles and should take approximately 7:00 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail runs from High St. (formerly Sanatorium Rd.) to the Moosilauke Carriage Rd. in a sag just north of Moosilauke’s South Peak. It is part of the AT. There is only one steep section, and the footing is generally good. The trailhead parking area is on the right a short distance past the trail sign; from here, one may follow an old farm road past a gate.  The upper part is above the treeline and greatly exposed to the elements, so it can be dangerous in bad weather. The lower part, up to a barricade, receives heavy snowmobile use in winter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am considering this a winter hike and foot traction is required.  No cotton clothing is allowed.  Please know your abilities and limits prior to signing up.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All participants are required to read and agree to the waiver and liability waiver posted on this site.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>DIANNE AND I WILL BE IN A BLACK FOUR DOOR ECHO</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240334081000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239717833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT MOOSILAUKE</name><id>10182158</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240059600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10182158/</event_url></item>