<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1057 Kingstown Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02879</zip><lat>41.451012</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Kingstown Public Library</name><city>United States</city><id>1529044</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.495087</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are currently working on a series of steps aimed at developing Trade Rules and Trading Plans. Our &amp;quot;agenda&amp;quot; is an informal one that primarily consists of the following:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Members and guests sign in.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Informal discussion while respondents arrive. This may be centered around almost any related topic such as a review of some given stock chart, various indicators and their usefulness, or perhaps a trade someone has either made or might be considering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Presentation and interactive discussion. Questions are always encouraged during the presentation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adjournment  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are NOT an investment club where members contribute to a pool and mutually select investment issues. &lt;br /&gt;We ARE individual traders, each with their own style and approach (some of us trade for a living) who get together to share ideas and strategies. &lt;br /&gt;Anyone is welcome to join us, and yes - even the most uninformed novices. Our members are a good group of people and more than willing to mentor anyone so inclined as to put up with us. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We discuss issues from fundamental and technical analysis to books on trading, from candlestick patterns to various &amp;quot;trader friendly&amp;quot; web sites, and from price indicators to trading strategies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why not join us for a meeting or two? It doesn't cost anything, it may be just what you're looking for, and who knows... maybe you'll even learn something useful right away!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one manning the laptop &amp; projector.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Dreczko</member_name><member_id>4521820</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206184862000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>We cover a wide range of material from the very basics on up. Our goal is to become better traders through information sharing, discussing issues from different perspectives, and mentoring one another.</why><group><who>IBD Enthusiasts and Traders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ibd-739</urlname><id>559772</id><group_lat>41.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202329031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trade Rules &amp; Trading Plans (cont'd)</name><id>7277928</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205964000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ibd-739/events/7277928/</event_url></item>