<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>409 The Hill</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.078239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.427.2583</phone><name>Blue Mermaid</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>812382</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.759410</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let’s play Pop Quiz Team Trivia, the game where useless knowledge pays!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pub trivia has been a big hit all over the nation for several years now and there is no indication that it’s going to let up. Are you an expert in some arcane knowledge? Do you know who or what the tallest, oldest, fastest, longest, smallest, widest is? Then you just may be a ringer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our DJ Phil will ask questions in such areas as Literature, Science (shout SCIENCE!), Sports, Geography, Music, Entertainment, TV, Movies, History, and more. In teams of up to 5 members we select our answers and make our bids. It’s the bidding that makes the game so interesting; in each round we can bid 1, 3, 5, or 7 points for our answer, but we can only bid each score once. Manage your bidding well and beat other teams even when you don’t know many of the answers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our anchor team (sometimes known as the Corner Crüe) has been playing since February 2008 and are now five-time defending monthly champions! Prizes are shared among team members who return for another game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not only are there prizes for winning, Phil usually has T-shirts, ball caps, or other swag to give away during the evening. Even the lowest point team wins as the team in last place in each round gets a prize (and yes, we’ve taken home a few of those).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, join us for a game of Pop Quiz Team Trivia; you just might have fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Try to arrive before 6:30 p.m. to secure a table and enjoy happy hour. Teams are up to groups of six or fewer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then come up with a team name; make it something you like as teams earn monthly points as well as weekly game points.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Caribbean-inspired fare available as well as a wide selection of beer, wine, and mixed drinks. Game sponsor beverages are happy hour priced all night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: The Blue Mermaid is part of “The Hill,” a cluster of historic homes located at High Street off Hanover Street behind the Hilton Garden Inn across from the Parking Garage and close to all the shopping and activities of downtown Portsmouth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from I-95: Take exit 7 toward downtown Portsmouth. Travel approximately 1 mile on Market Street. Take a right onto Russell Street (at the corner of the Sheraton Hotel) at the first stop sign you will face “The Hill” and a large parking lot. Enter the parking lot and proceed to the far left hand corner. The Blue Mermaid is the blue building with yellow lettering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info, including current parking status, go to &lt;a href="http://www.bluemermaid.com/" target="_blank"&gt;bluemermaid.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316475578000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288893404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pop Quiz Team Trivia at the Blue Mermaid</name><id>nkrtpypmbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316471400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/33239142/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/e/c/global_2393356.jpeg</photo_url></item>