<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>215 Great Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01464</zip><lat>42.578570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-425-4311</phone><name>The Bull Run</name><city>Shirley</city><id>380565</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.642235</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saturday, January 26, 2008 at 6:00 PM   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: Cocktail Hour begins @ 6pm  &lt;br /&gt;The Show starts @ 8pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: $25.00 per person,includes dinner and the show. There is a cash bar.  &lt;br /&gt;Seating's are '8' to a table although they may allow us to put tables together? I'm &lt;br /&gt;not sure of this... &lt;br /&gt;Call: 978-302-6400 to purchase your ticket or by  &lt;br /&gt;credit card through The Bull Run Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: If you RSVP 'yes' Please add to your RSVP if you have purchased your  &lt;br /&gt;ticket. I set the time to meetup for 6pm. This may change depending on  &lt;br /&gt;attendance.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All details: www.bullrunrestaurant.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cafe Murder  &lt;br /&gt;by Nathan Hartswick &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us in this hilarious murder mystery comedy as Rosemary Saint-John, a loud, annoying hypochondriac, celebrates her birthday with her four kooky sisters. When she disappears and is presumed murdered, the only objective witnesses in the restaurant are you, the audience members, who must cast your vote.  &lt;br /&gt;Was it one of Rosemary's sisters - the hippie, the valley girl, the trucker or the soccer mom? Was it the self-taught detective? The passionate French chef? The polite and proper maitre'd? The sarcastic waiter?  &lt;br /&gt;No one is above suspicion in this delightful dinner theater murder mystery!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TICKETS ARE AVAILABLE BY CALLING: 978-302-6400, OR BY CREDIT CARD AT THE BULL RUN RESTAURANT  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone interested?  &lt;br /&gt;_Jo &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Talk About This Event &lt;br /&gt;Post the first comment and get a discussion going! &lt;br /&gt;Your comment has been posted! Check back soon to read updates. Post another comment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will get there just before 6pm. From the front entrance, there is a bar and cozy fireplace. I will be right by the fireplace keeping warm : )  For those who may not know me I will have a meetup sign. You can also ask for the 'Meetup Group.'</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201561469000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>This will be a fun way to spend a cold winter evening. 
WOW, dinner and a show for $25.00 a value!</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199386462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CAFE MURDER @ The Bull Run in Shirley </name><id>7022591</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201388400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7022591/</event_url></item>