<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>257 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 629 8717</phone><name>Diesel Cafe</name><city>Somerville</city><id>705077</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;How about some lighter summer reading with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Reverse Commute by,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Sheila Blanchette&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author will try to join us for the discussion!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sophie Ryan, a middle-aged woman on the verge of a nervous breakdown, is stuck in a dead-end job barely paying her bills. Adding to her problems, she and her husband, Ray, live in an old New Hampshire farmhouse with endless, humorous calamities. One night when Ray is out of town, Sophie has a vivid, passionate dream that inspires her to hatch a plan to change her life and fulfill her dreams of escaping the farmhouse and her job. Meanwhile, in the same suburban office where Sophie works, is a twenty something young girl also stuck in a cubicle, bored with her job and frustrated with life after college. One snowy night, she barely makes the train home and finds the last available seat across from a strikingly handsome, mysterious young man. We follow Sophie and Ray and the young couple, keeping up with their dramas while at the same time trying to make the leap into their newly imagined, idealistic lives. Like a fast moving train, the story carries us along through twists and turns, obstacles and speed bumps to the surprising conclusion.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paras Hezar</member_name><member_id>12400154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368065623000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363964349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers ~ The Reverse Commute</name><id>110518312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368054000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/110518312/</event_url></item>