<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>NOTE this is a TWO DAY festival, but Meetup does not allow multiple-day events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;===============&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Information about the BCMFest 2009 line-up, schedule and other information will be updated via the BCMFest Web site, bcmfest.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With its pan-Celtic music, community focus, low-key approach, multi-generational lineup and universal sense of fun, the BCMFest is a sterling example of how to make a tradition live and grow.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;~Dirty Linen April/May 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Performers include: Annalivia; Matt Heaton &amp;amp; Flynn Cohen; Session Americana; Gloucester Hornpipe and Clog Society; Katie McNally &amp;amp; Jonathan Fagan; Blue Moose and the Unbuttoned Zippers; Fireside; Long Time Courting; the Folk Arts Quartet; Seoige; Amanda Cavanaugh &amp;amp; Friends; Dan Gurney with Martin Langer and Matt Heaton; The Bridgebuilders; Matching Orange; Michael O'Leary &amp;amp; Friends; Mairin Ui Cheide; Highland Dance Boston; Emma Beaton &amp;amp; Nic Gareiss; Janine Sirignano &amp;amp; Sean Smith; Royal Scottish Country Dance Society; Four at the Crossroads; Eric Merrill; Kristin Andreassen; Emerald Rae; Christine Morrison Dancers; Kimberley Fraser; Liz Simmons; Hannah Read; Shannon Heaton; Susie Petrov; Calum Pasqua.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Events: Boston Urban Ceilidh; Kick-Off Concert at Club Passim; &amp;quot;BCMFest Performer Make-Over&amp;quot;; &amp;quot;BCMFest Dance Spotlight&amp;quot; Finale Concert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Complete list of festival performers and events will be available at www.bcmfest.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, January 9 ~ Kick-off concert at Club Passim, 7 p.m.,&lt;br /&gt;Long Time Courting; Dan Gurney with Martin Langer and Matt Heaton; Blue Moose and the Unbuttoned Zippers.&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $25/$23 for Club Passim members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, January 9 ~ Boston Urban Ceilidh, Springstep, Medford, 7:15 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Laura Cortese and friends.&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $15, $10 with student ID&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Present ticket stubs from the Kick-Off Concert at the BCMFest Boston Urban Ceilidh and get in free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 10 ~ BCMFest Dayfest, performances from 10:45 a.m. through the afternoon at Club Passim and First Parish of Cambridge.&lt;br /&gt;Admission: morning and afternoon only, $15, $13 for Club Passim members; combination (Dayfest plus Finale Concert, $25, $23 for Passim members)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, January 10 ~ Finale Concert, &amp;quot;BCMFest Dance Spotlight,&amp;quot; 8 p.m..&lt;br /&gt;First Parish of Cambridge. Produced by Emerald Rae, featuring appearances by Annalivia, Eric Merrill, Kristin Andreassen, Emerald Rae, Christine Morrison Dancers, Kimberley Fraser, Liz Simmons, Hannah Read, Matt Heaton, Shannon Heaton, Susie Petrov, Calum Pasqua and many others. Admission: $15, $13 for Club Passim members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$25 for combination Dayfest plus Finale Concert, $23 for Club Passim members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets may be ordered through Club Passim, &lt;a href="http://www.clubpassim.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.clubpassim...&lt;/a&gt;, or 617-492-7679.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask for me</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231719260000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230592712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BCMFest</name><id>9404158</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231545600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/9404158/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/3/global_6768803.jpeg</photo_url></item>