<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In this meeting of the Boston Dreamers, we will learn a new approach to understanding the worlds of dreaming by using Theosophy. The Theosophical Society is a spiritual research tradition that was founded in 1875 by Helena Blavatsky and friends, and further developed in the 20th century by such famous names as Annie Besant, C. W. Leadbeater, and Rudolf Steiner. Many of our modern concepts of spiritual evolution, such as chakras and auras and the astral plane, were adapted from Eastern traditions by Theosophical students.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carl Schroeder will give a talk on the research he is doing into new applications of Theosophy for the categorizing and mapping of dreams. What are the differences between dreams on the astral and mental planes? How can we look for our spiritual guides? Where do the heavenly beings reside? Particular attention will be given to the planes of existence, and how dreams in different energy bodies (out-of-body experiences) support different types of contact with the higher realms of our spiritual evolution. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carl is currently writing a book on the topic with the help of his own lucid dream friends, so questions will be welcomed. You’re encouraged to think back on some of the most important and unusual dreams you've ever had, and bring highlights for sharing and comparing with the examples of major dream types. For an outline of his theories, see &lt;a href="http://www.SoulStirring.org/cosmicdocent/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SoulStirri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carl Schroeder is an engineer by trade and a mystic at heart. He runs the annual Mystical Art and Talent Show in Cambridge every October, for details on participating see &lt;a href="http://www.SoulStirring.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SoulStirri...&lt;/a&gt; - Carl has studied his dreams for over twenty years, and written several websites from the mystical perspective of life including film reviews at &lt;a href="http://www.MysticalMovieGuide.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.MysticalMo...&lt;/a&gt; and essays and art at &lt;a href="http://www.AstralResearch.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.AstralRese...&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, July 14, 2009 &lt;br /&gt;7 pm - 9:00 pm (Two hours)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is a sliding scale - $10-$20. Anyone who cannot afford to pay should contact the group organizer Deerheart, to arrange alternatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 25 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. Blessings, Deerheart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by car: Very limited parking at chapel, otherwise nearby streets such as Broadway and Mass Ave. There is a free small parking lot on Kirkland Street side of chapel, up to 8 cars. Coming from either direction on Massachusetts Ave into Harvard Square, turn onto Cambridge Street, then onto Quincy Street and around the corner onto the parking lot on Kirkland Street. The chapel is right on the corner of Quincy Street and Kirkland Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by T: The Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel is a lovely Gothic-revival stone chapel located at 50 Quincy Street in Cambridge, Mass. Please note that the official and historical name as may be found on maps and church directories is The Cambridge Society of the Church of the New Jerusalem (Swedenborgian). We are located at the corner of Quincy and Kirkland Streets, across from Harvard's monumental Memorial Hall/Sander's Theatre, which is behind Harvard Yard in Harvard Square. Access is an easy 5 minute walk from the Harvard Station MBTA stop on the Red Line and buses - just walk through Harvard Yard and ask anyone for Memorial Hall if you don't readily see the large fancy tower, then walk around the Hall to the chapel. (We're not part of Harvard in case you were wondering, but we're close neighbors in good standing, and we host field service from the students of the nearby Divinity School).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information and directions for the Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, check out their website. &lt;a href="http://www.SwedenborgChape.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Swedenborg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250035890000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244777807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mapping Your Dreams With Theosophy</name><id>10635494</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247612400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/10635494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/e/global_9103086.jpeg</photo_url></item>