<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Colovos Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.137072</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gregg Hall - Environmental Technology Building</name><city>Durham</city><id>1200877</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.936242</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a hiker, adventure racer, hunter, or outdoor lover? Do you carry a map and compass? Do you know how to use them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Up North Orienteers will hold an outdoor map and compass skills workshop on Sunday, May 5, 2013 to teach you these skills, and give you an opportunity to practice them in the woods. The event will be held rain or shine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Classes will be held outdoors at 10:30 am, 11:15 am, and 12 noon to teach the following skills: &lt;br /&gt;

reading a map for scale, declination, climb, and features &lt;br /&gt;

understanding the parts of your compass and how to use them &lt;br /&gt;

using your compass to navigate &lt;br /&gt;

ways to determine distance traveled &lt;br /&gt;

using your map and compass to determine where you are &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

After your class, you can practice the same skills on one or more orienteering courses in the woods ranging from 2 to 6 miles. All participants must check out by 2:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost is only $5.00 for the map and compass workshop and the practice courses in the woods. You will be asked to register and sign a waiver form. Note that there are no restroom facilities at the site. Bring your own compass, or you can borrow one on site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check UpNoOr.org for updates or additional information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to the workshop: From NH Route 4, exit at Route 155A (UNH - Whittemore Center). Turn towards Durham and travel 1.2 miles on that road to the UNH Campus. Go straight through the traffic circle and at the first traffic light take a right onto College Road and travel 0.3 miles. Turn right onto South Drive, go under the RR overpass, and make an immediate right onto Waterworks Road. Take your first left into the parking at the Gregg Hall lot. If that lot is full, go back to Waterworks Road, turn left onto Colovos Road, and right into the parking for Chase and Ritzman Labs. Do not park your car in anything that isn't a legal parking space since UNH has stiff parking fines. Registration will be outdoors in front of Gregg Hall.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Faye</member_name><member_id>3391935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367793031000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366737388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Map and Compass Workshop</name><id>115786172</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>16200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367762400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/115786172/</event_url></item>