<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>44 Pickman Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.508164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-280-0750</phone><name>Richard Tosti-Home</name><city>Bedford</city><id>350414</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.289515</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a Yes Dance-I ask you to be respectful and say yes to anyone who asks you to dance once- please understand this is our number one value- if you are able to say yes then this is a great event for you to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Format: &lt;br /&gt;Location is in a warm, loving and relaxing environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $12.00 plus wine or food assignment&lt;br /&gt;DJ - Dancing will be available &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An evening of Italian Romance: Feel the Passion!&lt;br /&gt;The Temple will be transformed into an Italian romantic setting with romantic music, romantic surroundings and fabulous delicious Italian food.&lt;br /&gt;If your last name begins with the following letter please bring the following. &lt;br /&gt;Serving size for 6: &lt;br /&gt;Please label your dish, name and what it is. My favorite traditional  meal on Christmas Eve is Home made Raviolis, which I make from scratch. I'd like to share  them with  you.&lt;br /&gt;Example:  Fabulous Home made Ravioli's- Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;Suggestions: Only to give us order and not have an abundance of one food. If your last name begins with the following letters, please bring one of the items or somthing similar:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A-C    tossed green salad / antipasto / vegetable tray with dip (make sure to include dressing)&lt;br /&gt;D-G    Italian entrée – only suggestions - meatballs / sausage, peppers &amp;amp; onions / ziti with sauce / baked stuffed shells / linguini with sauce and of course cheese/lasagna,/ chicken with broccoli &amp;amp; ziti / vegetable lasagna / calzones / pizza / baked macaroni and cheese. &lt;br /&gt;H        Red or white grapes&lt;br /&gt;I-Q     wine or beer&lt;br /&gt;R-S    Italian bread and butter – with 1 bottle soda&lt;br /&gt;T-V    1 bottle soda with a dessert (only suggestions – Italian cookies, brownies, pie or cake)&lt;br /&gt;W-Z   1 gallon of water with a dessert (only suggestions – Italian cookies, brownies, pie or cake)&lt;br /&gt;NO CHIPS AND ALL THAT OTHER STUFF . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable dance  party. Of course if you are unable to bring anything, then your entry fee will be $20.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer and Host Home &lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host- Richard Tosti &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. &amp;quot;Time of party: 7:30PM -11:30pm&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;2. &amp;quot; Dress code- &amp;quot;business casual&amp;quot; - &lt;br /&gt;no jeans/sneakers &lt;br /&gt;3. &amp;quot;You can enjoy the music and dance if you like&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;4. Initial temperature will be 62 in summer for the first hour. Body heat will warm up the room to a comfortable 68-70 degrees in one hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purpose is to Socialize with similar people of our age who are searching for a lifetime partner. &lt;br /&gt;40-65 age group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I began these parties in my home in July 2006-twice a month &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our common Values: Common denominator &lt;br /&gt;Have fun meeting old and new friends &lt;br /&gt;Circulate, talk to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;If someone is alone go up to them and say hi! &lt;br /&gt;Nonsmokers &lt;br /&gt;Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are coming because you got this email, this is your invitation. Please invite other friends, Particularly men. My personal goal is to have an equal amount of men and women &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are very close on equal numbers of men and women. The last dance we had 75 women and 60 men. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group was formed on the principle of synergy. Working together to invite quality people. We must take responsibility for inviting people. Again, my personal goal is to have an equal ratio of men and women, hope you will help. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can sign up on &lt;a href="http://dance.meetup.com/393/"&gt;http://dance.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You do not need to email me personally. &lt;br /&gt;140 guests only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the time, the location, what you should bring. Let's have fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions &lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth &lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;Burlington,MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128 North &lt;br /&gt;Exit 32 B Middlesex Tpk (Burlington/Arlington) &lt;br /&gt;Fork right-Middlesex Tpk Burlington-on the left is Burlington Dodge/Barnes/Noble &lt;br /&gt;Right on to Burlington Mall Rd-on left is Longs Jewelers &lt;br /&gt;Take left after Kohls-Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;Burlington MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two Parking lots on the right side of building. Enter through the side entrance . &lt;br /&gt;3rd parking lot two houses up at Church-we have permission &lt;br /&gt;4th parking lot across the street-McGinnis Ave-Mt Hope Church&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Sept. 13th, Sat.-7:30pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339201545000</updated><rating><average>4.40999984741</average><count>22</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>136</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219582431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Private Singles Party 40-65</name><id>8608958</id><headcount>153</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221348600000</time><rsvp_limit>140</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/8608958/</event_url></item>