<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I had heard a lot of good things about Fat Boy Bill's and last night found out they were all true - it is a great place to catch some live music. Which is a good thing, because in a couple of weeks, Bill's is going to host a truly great group - Jason James and the Baystate Houserockers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason and the Houserockers played at the Blues and Brews Festival at the Nashoba Valley Ski Area back in the summer, and they were phenomenal. So I am excited to get the chance to see them at a small venue like Bill's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With sixteen years working the clubs, guitarist Jason James is by no means new to the New England blues scene. A soft-spoken young man offstage, but once he steps up to the mic, it's easy to see why he is called Worcester's undisputed king of guitar showmanship. His casual 50's look and signature pompadour is his everyday mode of dress, but this is no Elvis wannabe. Influenced by idols Johnny Cash, Sleepy LaBeef, Cub Coda, Jerry Lee Lewis, George Thorogood, and Bo Diddley, guitarist Jason James rips into original and classic Chicago, Texas and Delta blues, rock and roll, and country with a distinctive rockabilly and roots edge. His deep voice echoes Thorogood and fingers fly across the fret board as he slides across stage, slinging his guitar left, right, and behind his head. . . . Jason James &amp;amp; the Bay State Houserockers brings down the house with one helluva show. Not to be missed!&amp;quot; &lt;b&gt;Lisa Marie, The Blues Audience&lt;/b&gt;, September 2004&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Note*&lt;/b&gt; - I am posting this as a joint event with the Mass Blues, Brews and BBQ group, so if you are in both groups and plan on attending, please only RSVP yes with one group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233110564000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231112078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jason James and the Bay State Houserockers</name><id>9443824</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232242200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/9443824/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/7/3/global_6830931.jpeg</photo_url></item>