<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Charles Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.358238</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sloan Merrill Gallery</name><city>Boston</city><id>12855952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070541</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Queridos e Queridas  Portuguese Language Speakers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Portuguese Festival 2013 has begun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The festival consists a series of Portuguese cultural events co-hosted by the Boston Consulate General of Portugal. (&lt;a href="http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org"&gt;http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is the exhibit opening and reception for Portuguese American artist, Jose L Santos.  This is event is a free and public event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event starts at 7, let's meet 15 before at 6:45pm at the entrance lobby, so we can meet and greet before the event starts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are late, I can not guarantee that you will be able to recognize members of the group for this will be a roaming, mix and mingle event. So please do your best to be on-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will also be a co-Meetup event with the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/"&gt;Boston Culture Club&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am looking forward to enjoying this event with the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**********************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;Public Transportation and Parking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;I strongly recommend public transportation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;* The nearest Subway, T stop is the Red Line, Charles/MGH stop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;There are also buses that stop nearby, please visit the ﻿﻿﻿&lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/trip_planner"&gt;www.mbta.com/rider_tools/trip_planner&lt;/a&gt; to plan your trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;For parking, there may be some street parking available. The Boston Common has an underground garage that is walking distance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more details about the festival and artist....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org/#!painting-exhibition/c409"&gt;http://www.bostonportuguesefestival.org/#!painting-exhibition/c409&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/135443009977303/?ref=2"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/135443009977303/?ref=2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;﻿&lt;a href="http://www.joselsantos.com"&gt;www.joselsantos.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Jose L Santos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I am a first generation Portuguese American. In 1952, my parents, both the eldest children in their families, immigrated to the United States from the farming town of Evora, Alcobaça, Portugal. They left behind the life they knew, a life working the land, to pursue another that they were told and believed was better, here in the United States. With little formal education and limited knowledge of the English language, they came to adapt to and like their New England environment, and never returned to Portugal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;My identity as a Portuguese American has had a tremendous impact on my values and perspective as an artist. Through my painting, I try to capture my unique culture identity by portraying the deep pride of its people as well as its still-vibrant age-old traditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

My work is as much about the labor that goes into each piece as it is about the end result. I try to keep my artistic language simple and direct, so it speaks to the common person, who to me represents the many people who make up my community. My work allows me to visually express what I understand and observe in my family, friends, community and place. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

My paintings and drawings have led me on a continuous exploration that has taken me in many directions. Through these explorations I have come to know people and places a little more intimately. By perceiving and contemplating, and then using the results to create and express, I feel like I have a closer connection to these people and places.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

While much of my work is introspective and highly personal, I also enjoy capturing the subtleties of nature outside of my studio. There is much to be gained from taking the time to observe one’s surroundings and creating from these experiences. Wherever I am, that’s where I belong.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This exhibit showcases a body of work that has been created in the last few years. One strand that runs common to all the pieces in this show is that they are all realistic. Hopefully, by viewing them, everyone can share a common experience."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;José L. Santos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at the entrance lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367850649000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366038803000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joe L Santos Art Opening Exhibition and Reception / Boston Portuguese Festival</name><id>114441612</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367621100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/114441612/</event_url></item>