<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Garden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.376698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Church in Cambridge, Congregational</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9471012</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122955</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Author and ex-FBI asset, Susan Lindauer "Extreme Prejudice"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, October 2, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;CORRECTION!! The venue is:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;"First Church in Cambridge, Congregational" and the address is:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;11 Garden Street&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;That is also at the corner of Mason Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;It is across from the end of the Cambridge Common right next to the&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : 12.727272033691406px"&gt;Commander Hotel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHO CAN AMERICANS TRUST?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Terrifying Story of the Patriot Act and the Cover Ups of 9/11 and Iraq&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if the government decided to invent a great lie to sell a disastrous war and a questionable anti-terrorism policy? What would happen to the Assets who know the truth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Former CIA Asset, Susan Lindauer, provides an extraordinary first-hand account from behind the intelligence curtain that shatters the government’s lies about 9/11 and Iraq, and casts a harsh spotlight on the workings of the Patriot Act as the ideal weapon to bludgeon whistle blowers and dissidents. A terrifying true story of “black budget” betrayals and the Patriot Act, with its arsenal of secret evidence, indefinite detention and threats of forcible drugging, EXTREME PREJUDICE reveals one Asset’s desperate struggle to survive the brutal cover ups of 9/11 and Iraq.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EXTREME PREJUDICE delivers a high tension expose of the real facts surrounding the CIA’s advance warnings of 9/11 and Iraq’s contributions to the 9/11 investigation. It reveals the existence of a comprehensive peace framework, which would have accomplished all U.S. objectives in Baghdad without a single casualty. A true life spy thriller that goes inside the Iraqi Embassy and prison on a Texas military base, EXTREME PREJUDICE reveals the depths of deception by leaders in Washington and London to promote a questionable image of their terrorism policy, and the shocking brutality to suppress the truth of their failures from the American people and the world community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Above all, EXTREME PREJUDICE offers a critical examination of the Patriot Act’s assault on defendant rights in the Courts, when liberty and freedom to dissent from government policy are the highest stakes. EXTREME PREJUDICE is a personal narrative accessible to all audiences, not an academic book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Susan Lindauer provides us with an overdue exposure of the depths to which governments are prepared to descend to prevent disclosure of their dishonesty and malfeasance, her knowledge having been gained through bitter personal experience.” –Robert Black, Q.C., Scottish architect of the Lockerbie Trial at Camp Zeist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Unfolds like a suspense thriller from deep within the struggle for global sanity, at the hands of those perpetrating dark secrecy. Pay attention.” –Janice Matthews, Director, 911Truth.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All truth passes through three stages. First, it is ridiculed. Second, it is violently opposed. Third, it is accepted as being self-evident.” Arthur Schopenhauer (1788 – 1860)&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351215413000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348617204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>10/2 6:30pm Author / ex-CIA asset, Susan Lindauer "Extreme Prejudice"</name><id>84087712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349217000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/84087712/</event_url></item>