<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;PAYMENT POLICY:&lt;br /&gt;$30 if pre-paid&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER AND PAY HERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://moxievision.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://moxievision.ev...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dating but not sure what you want? Sort of sure, but want more clarity? In a relationship and not sure if it meets your expectations? Discover your vision for relationships, romantic or friendship, with this workshop, led by Certified Life Coach Julie Melillo. You’ll create a “Relationship Vision” complete with all the things that you need to be happy.Bring a notebook or journal and a pen and come ready to brainstorm! Exercises, questions and tools will help you create your vision.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Discover what you really want in relationships!&lt;br /&gt;*Create a “Relationship Vision”&lt;br /&gt;*Naturally attract the right people&lt;br /&gt;*Know what you will and won’t accept&lt;br /&gt;*Take action more easily by understanding and trusting yourself&lt;br /&gt;*Learn how to visualize&lt;br /&gt;*Choose your ultimate goal for relationships -- and find out how to achieve it more easily using visualization&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About your Workshop Leader:&lt;br /&gt;Coach, writer, artist, speaker Julie Melillo is a Certified Life Coach who coaches entrepreneurs, CEOs, financial traders, attorneys and artists in Manhattan. She is a member of the NYC International Coach Federation chapter and recently appeared on Life Coach TV. Julie brings her passion for personal development to her clients withher five-step goal-reaching success process andpersonality type strength expertise.&lt;br /&gt;Once payment is received, two days before the teleclass, you will receive the calling conference/bridge number and PIN to access this teleclass.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249081414000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialnetworking</urlname><id>251346</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246975438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discover Your Vision For Your Relationships - Teleclass - 8pm Eastern Time</name><id>10820948</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248393600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialnetworking/events/10820948/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/5/global_5337269.jpeg</photo_url></item>