<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Fear and Loathing is back on - &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/11785888/"&gt;Terry Gilliam's &amp;quot;Fear and Loathing …&lt;/a&gt; on Monday. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be getting there between 7 and 7:15 and will have a blue LED sign that says Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Matt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The late Hunter S. Thompson's drug-ridden novel, Johnny Depp's eccentricity, and Terry Gilliam's absurdist style is a perfect match in the movie adaptation of &lt;b&gt;Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas&lt;/b&gt; which takes much of it's visuals from the crazy illustrations found in the book itself. Hunter S. Thompson himself even makes a brief appearance as himself...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Brattle Film site&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091221.html#b"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Repertory Series&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tilting At Windmills: The Films Of Terry Gilliam&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Fear And Loathing In Las Vegas&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;at 5:00, 7:30, 10:00 PM   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(1998) dir Terry Gilliam , w/ Johnny Depp, Benicio del Toro [118 min] &lt;br /&gt;Leave it to Gilliam to film one of the world’s most un-filmable novels. The late, great Hunter S. Thompson’s legendary gonzo account of sex, drugs, and, well, more drugs in the desert is, on its own, a bizarre, psychedelic road trip into insanity. Married with Gilliam’s truly inspired vision, it becomes a warped evocation of America on acid. Welcome to Bat Country&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Terry Gilliam Film Festival&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/091221.html#b"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Tilting At Windmills: The Films Of Terry Gilliam&lt;/u&gt;: Despite the fact that his career includes as many infamously unfinished films as completed masterpieces, the visionary director Terry Gilliam continues to prevail as a vital voice in contemporary film. Surely one of the most determined filmmakers ever, Gilliam cobbles together budgets from multitudes of international sources and consistently draws from a pool of amazing actors for his idiosyncratic projects. In celebration of his newest feature, the phantasmagoric Imaginarium Of Doctor Parnassus – which had it’s own series of disasters including the untimely death of its star – the Brattle has put together a tribute to Gilliam that includes all of his best-known films&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Terry Gilliam's website&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.terrygilliam.com/bio.html"&gt;http://www.terrygilli...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[Terry Gilliam's] next project, [after 12 Monkeys], Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas (1998), an adaptation of Hunter S. Thompson's 1971 novel, was the ultimate &amp;quot;trip&amp;quot; movie. Detailing Thompson's drug-addled journey to the gambling capital of the world, it starred Johnny Depp as the author's alter ego, Raoul Duke. The movie was the perfect vehicle for Gilliam to create an alternate universe fueled by the mind-bending substances in which the lead characters freely and plentifully indulge. With melting faces, a lounge full of human-sized lizards, bats flying in the desert, and a demon with breasts on its back, the movie didn't need and didn't really have a plot. Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas was the definition of a love-it-or-hate-it movie&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the book, according to Wikipedia&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fear_and_Loathing_in_Las_Vegas"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas: A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream is a novel by Hunter S. Thompson, illustrated by Ralph Steadman. The book is a roman à clef, rooted in autobiographical incidents. The story follows its protagonist, Raoul Duke, and his attorney, Dr. Gonzo, as they descend on Las Vegas to chase the American Dream through a drug-induced haze. The novel first appeared as a two-part series in Rolling Stone magazine in 1971, was printed as a book in 1972, and was later adapted into a film of the same name in 1998 starring Johnny Depp and Benicio del Toro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] The novel lacks a clear narrative and frequently delves into the surreal, never quite distinguishing between what is real and what is only imagined by the characters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The basic synopsis revolves around journalist Raoul Duke and his attorney, Dr. Gonzo, as they arrive in 1970s Las Vegas to report on the Mint 400 motorcycle race. However, they soon abandon their work and begin experimenting with a variety of recreational drugs, such as LSD, cocaine, alcohol, mescaline, and cannabis. This leads to a series of bizarre hallucinogenic trips, during which they destroy hotel rooms, wreck cars, and have visions of anthropomorphic desert animals, all the while ruminating on the decline of American culture&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The theatre entrance is on the left side of the building - look for our sidewalk poster case&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Take the MBTA Red Line to the Harvard Square stop. Use the Brattle Street exit through the bus way. When you reach the top of the stairs you will see Brattle Street ahead to the right. The Brattle Theatre is the second building on the left side of the street, next to Wainwright Bank and Eastern Mountain Sports&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt</member_name><member_id>6567601</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261615453000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257284182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Terry Gilliam's "Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas" @ Brattle Theater</name><id>11785888</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261441800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11785888/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/b/5/global_11632277.jpeg</photo_url></item>