<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389535</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center of Arts at the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1046137</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106069</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/6/e/c/event_217402252.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calling all foodies, artisan craft food devotees, craft brew fans, localvores, brew hobbyists, ethnic food lovers, and the curious minded! Join us for the&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;2nd Annual Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Session 1: Hyper-Local Home Brew Showcase &amp;amp; Brewfest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, June 14, 2013, 6:30 – 9:30pm (tickets released in April)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Session 2: Hyper-Local Brewfest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, June 15, 2013 3:00 – 6:00pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Session 3: Hyper-Local Brewfest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, June 15, 2013 7:00 – 10:00pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Tickets:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://hyperlocalbrew.eventbrite.com"&gt;hyperlocalbrew.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Why join us at Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest is an annual event presented by Sustainable Business Network of Massachusetts (SBN) to highlight and promote local brewers, vintners, artisan beverage makers, home brewers, and food vendors, and is a major annual fundraiser for SBN’s Boston Local Food Programs. The goal of SBN’s Boston Local Food Program is to transform the local food system by raising awareness about the abundance of wonderful locally grown and produced products in Massachusetts and New England and by encouraging individual consumers, food and beverage producers, and vendors to Think Local First.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s more, Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest is a unique event that not only showcases local beverage producers, but also showcases local brews incorporating local ingredients! Examples in the past have included brews made with TAZA Chocolate, local hops, apples, cranberries, grapes and even local oysters! While having unlimited 2oz tastings from local brewers, you can also sample and purchase delicious and ethnic local food from local food vendors like Valicenti Organico, TAZA chocolate, and more. A recap on Hyper-Local 2012 can be found &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/5HzsO"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New this year – Hyper-Local Home-Brew Showcase!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 New this year for the Friday evening session, SBN will launch our first Hyper-Local Home-Brew Showcase, highlighting home-brews and home-brewing with local ingredients. It is a chance for aspiring brewers to experiment and try what is available in the New England region for making their products. Attendees will have an opportunity to learn more about farm brewing, interact with other aspiring brewers, hear from experts, as well as taste a selection of the brews that will be showcased during the Saturday Sessions! More details about the Hyper-Local Home-Brew Showcase are forthcoming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Involvement is Important!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This year your support will not only benefit SBN, a 501-c3 organization whose mission is to help develop economies that are local, green, and fair, but $1.00 from all ticket sales will benefit the Arts at the Armory as well! Join us to support local business. Eat Local. Drink Local. Be Local.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location- Center for Arts at the Armory &lt;br /&gt;

 Center for Arts at the Armory is conveniently located at 191 Highland Avenue, between Davis and Union Squares in Somerville, Massachusetts. We encourage you to take public transportation and enjoy your unlimited tasting night at Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If driving, please make sure to be safe and plan for a designated driver. Limited parking is available at the rear of the building on Highland Avenue. Additional parking is available for free at: 112 Central St, Somerville, MA 02143 and 75 Belmont St, Somerville, MA 02143 (after 6 pm). For more information on how to get to the venue, check out our directions &lt;a href="http://bostonlocalfood.com/our-events/hyper-local-craft-brewfest/"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights of Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest, June, 2012&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Somerville Beat "The T-shirts said it all: Eat local. Drink local. Be local. Local was the word of the night at the Hyper-Local Craft Brew Tasting on Saturday [June 16, 2012] at the Armory on Highland Ave."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sweetly Serendipity "This festival was tons of fun, and so yummy – the best kind of festival!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wine Dine with Us "The event [...] showcased thirty local breweries, wineries and food vendors. The event was a blast!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ampersand &amp;amp; Modern Vintage "This tasting was truly one of the more memorable in the area mixing established microbreweries like Cambridge Brewing Company, Sam Adams, and Narragansett, up-and-comers like Somerville’s own Slumbrew, and the “so happy we’ve just been introduced” to breweries like Nightshift Brewing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1371357579000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>beer buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CraftBeerCrew</urlname><id>1469154</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Craft Beer Crew</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364160564000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest at Somerville Armory (Ticketed event)</name><id>110845992</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>100800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1371247200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CraftBeerCrew/events/110845992/</event_url></item>