<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Warren Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02914</zip><lat>41.817637</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comedy Connection</name><city>East Providence</city><id>972416</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.383156</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This evening I spoke to the person at the box office for the Comedy Connection. They are recommending that we have  as many people there as possible, at the door,  at 7:30 p.m, and I am going to recommend that we all try to be there at that time. This is a 1/2 hour before the start of the show, and they said that they will set aside seating for what we need. They have also said that they will wait until around 7:45 p.m. until they start chargeing us, and if we have 20 or more people there at that time we will get a $3.00 discount. I plan to arrive at around 7:15 , and will wait in the parking area until 7:30. If you do arrive after that time tell them you are with Tim and the Providence Biking and recreational group, and you will get your discount if we are eligible for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;` If there are people who decide not to attend, please try not to be a no show and just change your RSVP, so that others may attend. I will set up a waiting list so others can take your place.The two venues also seem to be going out of their way for us`.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both the Comedy Connection and Club 133 have said they will do their best to accomodate us. The performer for the Comedy Connection  As I have written before is April Macie along with guest Jason Marcus. If you click on the link below you can find information about her as well as a video. Club 133 as I wrote before is located right next door, and the band is stoneleaf, which I do not really know all that much about. We can still keep this part of the evening open for suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone has any suggestions, pleast post them, and I will also leave a contact no# tomorrow in case it is needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ricomedyconnection.com"&gt;http://www.ricomedyconnection.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>11253417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350256739000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347666038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy night!</name><id>82453342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350084600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/82453342/</event_url></item>