<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of State and Pleasant Streets</address_2><address_1>26 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Richdale Food Store</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1126642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Yup it&amp;rsquo;s summer time in Newburyport and what is one of the best ways to join in on the summer time fun?&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Checking out the sites and sounds of Yankee Homecoming!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s go check out everything that is happening down town Newburyport, we will be walking around maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll get a bite to eat or maybe grab a cooler off of a great ice cream!&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; So bring your walking shoes and your thirst for some summer time fun and join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Things to know about this meetup:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;We may not be able to all stick together at this event, if you are not comfortable with that then this event may not be for you, please remember that when you are RSVPing for this event.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;If we sit at a restaurant depending on how many of us there are we may not be able to sit together and or we may have to wait.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Please be patient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;May be tough please allow enough time to park and meet us. You now HAVE to pay for parking in a few of these lots.&amp;nbsp; You may also park in legal spots on the street. If you park in a nearby neighborhood, please be respectful of residents and all parking laws - do not block fire hydrants or driveways. Police will ticket or tow all cars which are parked in illegal spaces.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay at this event.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;, we thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;We look forward to spending a great summer evening with our friends!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be outside of Richdale</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312720272000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312254772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk around town</name><id>27909731</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312585200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/27909731/</event_url></item>