<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Bennett Cir</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01821</zip><lat>42.546307</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>978 362 3741</phone><name>Jeff's House</name><city>Billerica</city><id>486449</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.241776</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Heroes in Time and Space is a light-mood episodic HERO system (&lt;b&gt;not Champions&lt;/b&gt;) game of &amp;quot;street level&amp;quot; pulp fiction heroes.  Players build their characters  in isolation, with no knowledge of the other player characters, who can come from any place in time and space.  Then, they are all thrown together to solve a situation.  Much of the fun comes from seeing how wildly different characters cope with each other and the environment in which they find themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No knowledge of the HERO system is necessary, though HERO veterans are as welcome as newcomers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To make it easier on all of us, the first few games will be run using the HERO Sidekick system, which is a streamlined version of HERO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The game is scheduled for 6 hours, though we can run over if we need to and everyone wants to.  I'm planning the first 90 min or so to be dedicated to character creation and basic rules explanations however I'd rather not have to do all the character design work then and there.  So &lt;b&gt;if you can email me your character conception before the game so we can pre-generate your character it would help.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A character conception can be as simple as &amp;quot;MacGuyver from the TV show&amp;quot;, though I may ask you for clarifications as to exactly what it means to you.   Email me directly at jeffpk@gmail.com so we don't spoil the surprise for the other players ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can handle up to 8 players, though if others would like to come, I have quite a library of RPG and other game material people can use to run pick-up games, or bring their own.  I've had over 20 people in the living room in the past.  I have snack stuff here but it would help if everyone could bring one munchie (A bottle of soda, a bag of chips or whatever.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's my house.  Shouldn't be that hard to spot me.  ;)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jeffpk</member_name><member_id>6148678</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202749349000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Have a heroic character from movies or books you've always wanted to play?  Here's your chance!  HiTaS is a light hearted, cross genre game where characters from anywhere  in time and space meet to solve a crisis.</why><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200938468000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Heros in Time and Space</name><id>7164178</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202576400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/7164178/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/7/global_942311.jpeg</photo_url></item>