<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street, 2nd Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1065386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183899</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This will be the last Nourishing Oasis for the summer. (They will resume in Sept.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At moments of clarity and alignment our spirit shines through. These are our peak experiences, when we feel whole, alive, connected, and free. There is an implicit sense of safety and of being fully ourselves. There is a noticeable absence of fear, shame or obligation. There is no need to contort ourselves in order to obtain or keep the love and acceptance of others. We are filled up from within with unconditional love and the complete rightness and worthiness of our Being. There is nothing we have to do to earn it. It simply is. We simply are whole, loved and connected to something greater than our ego identity. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this place of connection, ease, clarity and abundance we tap into our Life Purpose. We re-member our unique gifts and calling - what we are here to contribute - which is also what brings us the most joy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through guided meditation, reflection, sharing, expressive drawing and movement, you will tap into your alignment with Spirit and sense of personal Purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please join us for this unique evening of renewed connection with yourSelf, supportive community, and the true compass of your life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Open to all: singles, friends and couples. Beginners welcome! No prior Tantra or artistic experience needed. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(No gender balance necessary. It is irrelevant for this workshop.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brynn Bishop&lt;/strong&gt; is a Love and Empowerment Coach with over 25 years experience in the fields of body-mind integration and conscious relating. Her passion is guiding people on the path of intimacy, freedom and fulfillment. Her workshops have been touted as “welcoming, enlightening, transformative, empowering, heart-opening and deeply nourishing.” Brynn is known for her wisdom, compassionate presence and mastery at having all aspects of the person feel safe and accepted. She has been called “Midwife for the Embodied Soul.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339892704000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332346171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nourishing Oasis: Tapping Into Purpose</name><id>57263752</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339803000000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/57263752/</event_url></item>