<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What: LOWELL FOLK FESTIVAL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: July 27, 2008 12:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Click the link below to find out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Description: What: LOWELL FOLK FESTIVAL &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: July 27, 2008 12:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Description: The Lowell Folk Festival has been a yearly event for more than 20 years. It is the largest FREE Folk Festival in the country and  encompasses  6 music stages prominently placed across the city offering varied settings &amp;amp; styles of performances. The festival has grown and is huge! &lt;br /&gt;Learn more @ : &lt;br /&gt;www.lowellfolkfestival.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATED 7/23/08:&lt;/b&gt; We will meetup just outside the JOHN ST GARAGE across from Boardinghouse Park at noon. It will be very congested.. I will have a meetup sign. Other groups are expected to join us.  WE WAIT 10 MINUTES for &amp;quot;YES!&amp;quot; RSVPs... we do not wait for &amp;quot;maybes.&amp;quot;  If you know you will be late? I will send you my cell# to get in touch with me ( in a separate email message) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GO TO: &lt;a href="http://lowellfolkfestival.org/festival-map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://lowellfolkfest...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for a map of our meetup location (and also the festival) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****The Lowell Folk Festival includes 6 stages of entertainmnet, ethnice foods arts &amp;amp; crafts of all kinds all over the city! It's HUGE!  therefore we mau break off into small groups... &lt;br /&gt;***** A lot of walking is involved... make sure you wear comfy shoes... Also, you may wish to bring a blanket? or chair as there usually is no seating at any of the venues.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: FREE&lt;br /&gt;**Performances &amp;amp; activities within the festival are FREE. Food, beverages, and sale merchandise are not.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Included in the details of the event</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217347813000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214845280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lowell Folk Festival</name><id>8246587</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217174400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/8246587/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/f/6/global_4637110.jpeg</photo_url></item>