<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>229 Main Street</address_2><address_1>Alumni Recital Hall (Redfern Arts Center)</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03435</zip><lat>42.930000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Keene State College</name><city>Keene</city><id>441720</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.279999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Friday, April 10, at 7:00 pm: David Ray Griffin, the foremost researcher and spokesperson for 9-11 Truth will be speaking at Keene State College, in  Keene, New Hampshire. [details to follow]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The title of his talk will be  &amp;quot;9/11: Time for a Second Look.&amp;quot; He will be pointing out that many people---including politicians and journalists---formed their ideas about 9/11 and the 9/11 truth movement early on, when there seemed little reason to doubt the Bush administration's honesty and when the 9/11 truth movement could be caricatured, without too much exaggeration, as a bunch of kids on the Internet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But now we have abundant evidence of the Bush-Cheney's administration's willingness to break the law and to tell lies that would lead to millions of deaths. And the 9/11 truth movement is now led intellectually by scientists and other professionals, as shown by the emergence of various organizations, including Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth, Firefighters for 9/11 Truth, Lawyers for 9/11 Truth, Medical Professionals for 9/11 Truth, Pilots for 9/11 Truth, Political Leaders for 9/11 Truth, Religious Leaders for 9/11 Truth, Scholars for 9/11 Truth and Justice (which includes a lot of scientists), Veterans for 9/11 Truth, and the Scientific Panel to Investigate 9/11. The movement also includes several former intelligence officers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to these professionals, the evidence that the official story is false is now overwhelming. The only problem is to get people to look at the evidence. Once they are willing to do this, they quickly see that the official story simply cannot be true.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, the replacement of the Bush administration with the Obama administration is important in three respects. First, potential whistleblowers may become less afraid to come forward. Second, the media may become more willing to expose the dozens of contradictions and other problems in the official myth. And third, there is at least the chance for a real investigation. The petition for both Religious Leaders for 9/11 Truth and Political Leaders for 9/11 Truth, for example, ends by asking President Obama to authorize a new, truly independent, investigation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Monadnock 911 Truth Alliance. ZZZ - donations will be accepted to help cover expenses. Further information when available. For more information contact ABC&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239577634000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237992620000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>David Ray Griffin - Keene - 9/11: Time for a Second Look</name><id>10032414</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239404400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/10032414/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/8/global_6998040.jpeg</photo_url></item>