<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 Atlantic Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.362568</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Boston Sail Loft</name><city>Boston</city><id>11422422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050980</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Courageous Sailing has been committed to providing quality sailing to people of all ages for 25 years, including high school students. Since the Spring of 2011, Courageous has been proud to partner with Boston Public Schools in order to provide a positive outlet for teenagers through the sailing teams we coach. What better way for teenagers to learn communication, responsibility for their actions, and hard work, if not through sailing? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Help support the Boston Public Schools High School Sailing Team and all of the great high school sailors participating each year by joining us on Thursday, February 7, at the Boston Sail Loft! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 As usual, we'll be providing appetizers and some great raffle prizes, including an up-cycled tote bag from Hoist Away Bags. Save time, buy your raffle tickets now, and pick them up when you arrive: 5 for $10 or 15 for $20. Remember--all proceeds will go directly to supporting the BPS team and helping Courageous provide coaching, gear, and fleet improvements!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>BillS</member_name><member_id>2822960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360333737000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359424040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cocktails for Courageous: Support Boston Public's High School Sailing Teams!</name><id>101889692</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360281600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/101889692/</event_url></item>