<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &amp;quot;Cashing In On Discounted Notes and Pre-Foreclosures!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;with Donna Bauer, The NoteBuyer®&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting - Thursday, April 16th  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can you do using Donna Bauer's proven strategies?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Purchase notes and mortgages for 40 to 70 cents on the dollar! &lt;br /&gt;* Find excellent sources of good (performing) and bad (defaulted) paper! &lt;br /&gt;* Work with distressed homeowners and create win-win solutions! &lt;br /&gt;* Acquire properties in pre-foreclosure below wholesale! &lt;br /&gt;* Do deals without using your own money or credit! &lt;br /&gt;* Purchase notes and real estate in your IRA!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Bauer is nationally recognized as the leading authority on discounted notes and the pre-foreclosure market. She founded The NoteBuyer, Inc. in 1990 to provide a wide range of educational and support services to real estate investors. Her personal investing career spans 25 years and includes thousands of note purchases and property transactions. Donna has also managed large-scale commercial developments, including a downtown highrise, office park, and 500-unit apartment complex. She frequently appears on television and radio as a distinguished expert on note buying, pre-foreclosures, IRA investing, and general real estate issues.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting - Thursday, April 16th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of Boston AREIA (visit &lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/memberships.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonarei...&lt;/a&gt;) are free&lt;br /&gt;Visitors pay $25.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - Power Hour - Open to All - Special Networking event - BE THERE EARLY OR MISS OUT!&lt;br /&gt;6:00 - Orientation - Members and Visitors - get more out of your visit and your membership &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western Hotel, 380 Winter St, Waltham, Ma&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240090685000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>97</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237502082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association April Meetup</name><id>9991589</id><headcount>97</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239917400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/9991589/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>