<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341400</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Brugger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>317494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121030</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We will be combining the November and December meetups as our usual 4th Sunday of the month falls around both Thanksgiving and Christmas.  The meetup will be held on Sunday, Dec. 2 @ 4pm at Brugger's Bagels in Coolidge Corner.  We will be discussing the book: &amp;quot;In God We Trust: All Others Pay Cash&amp;quot; by Jean Shepherd.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description from Booksense.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Before Garrison Keillor and Spalding Gray there was Jean Shepherd: a master monologist and writer who spun the materials of his all-American childhood into immensely resonant -- and utterly hilarious -- works of comic art. These two reissues represent the peak of his achievement, a compound of irony, affection, and perfect detail that speaks across generations.&lt;br /&gt;In God We Trust disproves the adage &amp;quot;You can't go home again&amp;quot; as Shepherd bends the ear of his hometown-buddy-turned-bartender, Flick, with tales of his quest for a Red Ryder BB gun, a terrifying encounter with a school bully, the unlikely Indiana roots of Pop Art, and a struggle to land a fish to rival The Old Man and the Sea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wanda Hickey's Night of Golden Memories is a universal (and achingly funny) orchestration of Midwestern puberty rites, from the gut-wrenching playground antics of one Delbert Bumpus, to the supernal glow surrounding unapproachable high school beauty Daphne Bigelow, to the memorable disaster that was Shepherd's (and everyone else's) junior prom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A comic genius who bridges the gap between James Thurber and David Sedaris, Shepherd may have accomplished for Holden, Indiana, what Mark Twain did for Hannibal, Missouri. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sabina</member_name><member_id>1638720</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196802684000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190691876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November/December Meetup</name><id>6422443</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196629200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/6422443/</event_url></item>