<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join the best Fashion Industry Meetup in the world with members who are experienced, or beginners, in every aspect of the fashion industry. We help each other in our goal to rebuild the fashion industry in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP for March 19th meetup. We are emphasizing all our designers, beginners and advanced, especially clothing designers. You are the core of our meetup group. There will be some with established businesses to show and talk. Our new venue is at ZWeave, Inc., thanks to David Buck, it’s CEO and a member of the Boston Fashion Industry Meetup. You will also hear about the world of fashion and technology, and a new software for designers, ZDesign. The address is 107 South St. 6th floor. (Yes, there is an elevator) The entrance is around the corner. Parking is always difficult anywhere in Boston. So we advise you park at an MBTA station and take the Red Line to South Station. The venue is across the street from South Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;January's and Feruary's meetups were the best yet, each with 40 members attending. We have had great panel discussions on various aspects of selling and marketing - and aspects of production, pattern design, fabric resources and fabric trimming. There are people from every aspect of the fashion industry to network with:, Designers (clothing, jewelry, fabric), photographers, sellers and marketers, models, makeup artists, event planers, etc.  Enjoy light refreshments as you converse, connect, and network with fellow fashion entrepreneurs.  We encourage you to bring examples of your work, a positive attitude, enthusiasm, and the willingness to have fun. You may bring food to share as well. There is a $2 fee at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Fashion Industry Meetup organizers&lt;br /&gt;Shirley, Ron, Jamall, Anne, Prithi &amp;amp; Constance,&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will greet you. Make sure you RSVP Yes so that we know you are coming.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley Willett</member_name><member_id>1480973</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jamall Oluokun</member_name><member_id>6487580</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Prithi Pais</member_name><member_id>7208428</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Constance</member_name><member_id>7401817</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne Norman</member_name><member_id>8862626</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238855493000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235088409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Fashion Industry March Meetup</name><id>9779417</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237500000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/9779417/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/9/global_5522201.jpeg</photo_url></item>