<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>71 Beach Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chinatown Gate</name><city>Boston</city><id>1057599</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059863</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Step through the Chinatown gate and experience the rich cultural and architectural history, from 1875 to present day, on this walking tour of Chinatown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This thriving, self-sufficient community combines the irrepressible spirit of the East with a Boston flavor. A myriad of 19th century immigrants lived in this area situated along the flats along the South Bay and it eventually became home to the largest Chinese community in Boston. A unique mix of residences and family operated businesses, the intimate streets are lined with Chinese restaurants and specialty shops. Recently, Vietnamese, Laotians, and Cambodians have further expanded the ethnic diversity of the neighborhood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This guided tour traces Chinatown's rich cultural and architectural history, from 1875 to present day, and a vibrant convergence of old and new. The narrow streets and collection of 19th century buildings create an intimate atmosphere and unique look at Boston history for this 90-minute walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour will start promptly at 2pm.  Meet near the Chinatown Gate, a short walk from either South Station on the Red Line or Chinatown Station on the Orange Line.  Look for me (amy!) wearing a Meetup logo button.  Tour is $15 per person (or $5 for card-carrying Boston By Foot members - see &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;website for details on becoming a member&lt;/a&gt;).  Bring cash to purchase your tour ticket from the docent when you arrive. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me (amy!) wearing a Meetup logo button</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296074125000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271875948000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston By Foot tour - Chinatown</name><id>13250076</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272217500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13250076/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/d/global_2274701.jpeg</photo_url></item>