<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>275 West Natick Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02886</zip><lat>41.729004</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Warwick Bike Path</name><city>Warwick</city><id>7569992</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.484400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;How to find me ... I'll be wearing a salmon-color tank top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet/park at the overpass near 275 West Natick Road in Warwick, you'll see a sign for the bike path. If you don't have GPS, look for the billboard type sign for the "Extended Stay America" which can be seen from Route 2, opposite side of the Warwick Mall. North Star Rentals is immediately west of Extended Stay America, and the bike path parking area is immediately west of North Star Rentals. There's a lot of parking on both sides of West Natick Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an easy ride as the path is flat. Please arrive at 1:00pm so that we can be on the bike path at 1:15pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The West Natick Road crossing is the beginning of the Warwick section of the Washington Secondary Bike Path. Round-trip from Warwick to Coventry is about 17 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FYI, The Washington Secondary Bike Path begins in Cranston and ends in Coventry and is about 28 mis R/T. I'm building up to it! ;-) The West Natick Road crossing is about 5.5 miles from Cranston. For those who would like to ride the entire path it's very convenient to park at the train tracks far right side of the Sanford Brown building formerly Gibbs College (85 Garfield Ave., Cranston); there's plenty of parking. The bike path is adjacent to the train tracks. If you're coming from Cranston on the bike path, West Natick Road is the crossing before the rusty, steel bridge in Warwick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday looks like it's going to be a nice day, the forecast is partly cloudy, 79-F, with 20% chance of rain. Rain will cancel the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to bring water, bug spray, sunscreen, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/3/f/0/event_126997872.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/1/c/event_126996892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jillian</member_name><member_id>10764233</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339447152000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338949719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Warwick to Coventry Bike Ride (Washington Secondary Bike Path) 17 miles R/T.</name><id>67941772</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339347600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/67941772/</event_url></item>