<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>574 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01826</zip><lat>42.685254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-452-8800</phone><name>American Legion</name><city>Dracut</city><id>1200222</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.277431</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>sorry to postpone, but the longer I wait the more people I get, and the more fun it will be (plus I had a scheduling conflict)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;have you often thought...&amp;quot;wish I had more time to speak with people, on a more personal level&amp;quot; in the meetup scene, or otherwise...here's a way of breaking out of your shell and meeting people face-to-face in a comfortable atmosphere.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had soooo much fun with this, I'm going to try it on my own.  I got involved after attending a speed dating party and what a great concept it is.  Meet 6-12 people in one night, on a personal level, in the space of 1 to 1.5 hours, and have fun at the same time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;there is one age group 47-60, filled up for women, and the others filling up, but I need more men especially, and more women and men, in the over 60 age group.  Don't be shy, this is low stress, fun time dating :) I have ads out there, so not only will you meet people in your meetup one on one, you'll meet others from other meetups and some who are not in meetup at all.  On the whole I've got a great crowd of both men and women, and I'm looking forward to this, and hope you are, also.  If your check is cashed, you made it into the group, if I run out of room in your age group, I will send the check back.  Please be sure to provide a telephone number and email, for contact information, when you send your check in.  If you cannot make this new date, please email me, and I will send your check back.  There are no refunds after June14th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;suzie's speedy dates?  looking for ideas/name for my new adventure.  I use to work for a well-known &amp;quot;speed dating&amp;quot; company, and was pretty successful at it.  I had a one year &amp;quot;non-compete&amp;quot; clause after I left, which is now expired.  They charge $35 for their parties, which are now pretty much defunk, because of the economic climate.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The night will be split into 3 separate age groups...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:00-6:00 for 60+ year olds&lt;br /&gt;6:00-7:30 for 47-60 &lt;br /&gt;7:30-9:00 for 35-47 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is $10 per person, and I'm holding it at the American Legion in Dracut, 574 Broadway, Dracut, MA on June 24th.  I have 3 meetup groups now, and with a total of over 1,600 members, and as an assistant organizer on a couple more, I'll be &amp;quot;putting it out there&amp;quot; to a couple more groups.  I will also advertise in a local paper. To reserve your seat, please send a check to me at:&lt;br /&gt;PO BOX 793, Pelham, NH 03076 and indicate your sex (in case I can't tell by your name:) your age and the age you'd like to be in.  Please leave your phone number and email as well, for any emergency cancellations.  All info provided will be completely confidential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concept is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;women are seated and men go from table to table, and spend 6-7 minutes each, speaking to their &amp;quot;dates&amp;quot;.  After those dates, you will mark down which women/men you'd like to be in contact with again.  You can of course mark down as many as you like.  If that person picks you as well, you will be sent an email, with that persons contact info.  No last names are used, and ONLY your email is shared, if you wish, or certainly you can try and get a number that night fellas, if you're brave ;)  I found it is a pretty nice way of meeting new people, without going to a dating website and &amp;quot;emailing&amp;quot;  and conversing with someone, you can't see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;you do not need to respond &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; to this event.  I can keep your response confidential, if you'd like to be a surprise :) Please email me for availability as the day gets closer.  &lt;br /&gt;I will update this meetup, if an age group fills up or for any important changes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a lot of fun, and if you have any questions about it, feel free to email me.  And yes, you can join 2 age groups if you like, if there is room, but of course the price will be $20 :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to do this again, I had soooo much fun with this, and met so many nice people myself.  Sometimes at the meetups I'm so involved with introductions and partying, I really don't get to meet a lot of the members, on a more personal level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The American Legion has been totally renovated and is a really nice bar (cash bar of course).  Get there a little early and have a &amp;quot;warm-up&amp;quot; drink...I'll provide some munchies.  you can certainly bring some if you like :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to &amp;quot;meetup&amp;quot; with you there...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW, if I'm using anyone's picture from my previous speed dating events, and you object, please let me know and I'll remove it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>park in the back, and enter through front door...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277486976000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271162852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Suzie's Speed Dates :)</name><id>13168377</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277416800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/13168377/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/f/a/global_14355578.jpeg</photo_url></item>