<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce continues to teach us about the amazing Enneagram of Personality.  This week the focus will be on relationships.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a description of the workshop from Herb: &amp;quot;Learn all the ins and outs of relating well to each Enneagram type and how the types combine, which tend to be more compatible. Learn and practice techniques that work well with each type. Open both to beginners and people who know the Enneagram.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00.   A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served.  We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it.  Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit of 30 has been set.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** Details from Herb Pearce’s website *****     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About the Enneagram **&lt;br /&gt;The star-shaped Enneagram (Greek for &amp;quot;nine&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;drawing&amp;quot;) groups human emotions and behavior—positive and negative –into nine personality types. According to the Enneagram theory, personality develops as a result of a unique combination of genetics, cultural influence, family and childhood experience, and spiritual growth inclination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About Herb Pearce **&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce, M. Ed is a Arlington-based, individual, couples and family therapist, with over 29 years experience. A leading expert in the Enneagram, he has led over 2,000 Enneagram experiences in the last 18 years with talks, public workshops, counseling, and teambuilding trainings in corporations and organizations. Herb's trainings, talks and workshops provide a wealth of understanding and clarity regarding personality differences and his presentation style is direct, but gentle and humorous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238197464000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236575971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enneagram Relationship Dynamics with Herb Pearce</name><id>9913231</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237590000000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/9913231/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/8/global_7203288.jpeg</photo_url></item>