<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.352823</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 478-3100 </phone><name>Institute of Contemporary Art</name><city>Boston</city><id>731894</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043059</lon></venue><fee><label>Group donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while checking out iconic Obama imagery?  Are you looking for like-minded progressives to gallery walk with in Boston? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in?  Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions AND seeing the new Shepard Fairey exhibit?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Join SoJust at the ICA for Iconic Art for Justice!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Check out this video:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=awKJQ-HfEHc" target="_blank"&gt;Shepard Fairey, Creator of Iconic Obama Image, Speaks About His Art&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker.  Just show up and take in the art.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP&lt;/span&gt; yes, maybe or no&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;i&gt;newcomers always welcome&lt;/i&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Meet us at 6pm in the lobby and take advantage of FREE Target Thursdays at the ICA.  After the tour we'll regroup at &lt;a href="http://www.icaboston.org/visit/water-cafe/" target="_blank"&gt;Wolfgang Puck's Water Cafe&lt;/a&gt; in the ICA lobby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions and parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.icaboston.org/visit/directions-and-parking/" target="_blank"&gt;www.icaboston.org/visit/directions-and-parking/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the Red Line to South Station and transfer to the Silver Line Waterfront (towards the airport). The ICA is short walk from World Trade Center station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit left onto Congress Street. Walk one block to the corner of B Street and turn right, crossing Congress Street. Follow B Street for one block. At the corner of B Street and Seaport Boulevard cross the street and turn left. At the next corner, turn right onto Northern Avenue. The ICA is on the right. You will pass the entrance to Anthony’s Pier 4 and two parking lots before coming to the driveway leading to the ICA entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;. Learn about our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/pages/Annual_Membership_Fee_details/"&gt;Suggested Annual Membership Fee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235851499000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233892473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Iconic Art for Justice</name><id>9685040</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235084400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/9685040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/a/global_7202394.jpeg</photo_url></item>