<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>606 Walnut Tree Hill Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06484</zip><lat>41.330600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 929-8425</phone><name>Jones Family Farms</name><city>Shelton</city><id>664466</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.168526</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>PLEASE GO TO THERE WEBSITE AND SIGN UP FOR THE HIKE  &amp;quot;BRING LUNCH AND WE WILL HAVE A PICNIC AND THEN DO SOME WINE TASTING.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jonesfamilyfarms.com/events/winery" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jonesfamil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Farmer's Heritage Hike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a hike through time on our historic Homestead Farm to explore 150 years of New England’s farming stories at Jones Family Farms. Search for signs of the farm’s evolution from a sheep operation, to a dairy farm, lumber mill, and current use as a harvest-your own farm and winery. Learn how Shelton has changed over the past several centuries, and how this 6th generation farm has changed with it. Enjoy scenic views, rambling stone walls, and a wide variety of plant and animal life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Spring 2010 public hikes are recommended for ages 12 and up with families welcome.&lt;br /&gt;• Sturdy footwear (i.e., boots, hiking/walking shoes) is required for these hikes over moderately difficult terrain on farm roads, fields and hills.&lt;br /&gt;• A water bottle is recommended.&lt;br /&gt;• Rain or shine, severe weather cancels. (Muddy walking areas are possible).&lt;br /&gt;• Cost: $5 per person (*The Farmer’s Heritage Hike will be offered at no charge as part of the CT Forest and Park Association Trails Day). This can be paid in person the day of the hike.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Saturday, June 5, 2010 - 10:00am - 12:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Sign up for Farmer's Heritage Hike&lt;br /&gt;Email: *&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;An e-mail address is required for users who are not registered at this site. If you are a registered user at this site, please login to sign up for this Event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275870955000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269858982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vineyard Hike and Followed by Lunch and Wine Tasting At "Jones Family Farms"</name><id>13022483</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275746400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/13022483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/1/global_4236481.jpeg</photo_url></item>