<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to everyone who came yesterday to our Valentine's Day/Super Bowl party!  We had the highest attendance on record so far, and enjoyed seeing our friends that are new owners attending for the first time -- Ida, Jaqlyn &amp;amp; Rosie, Amy,  Audrey &amp;amp; Dexter,  David,  Abbey &amp;amp; Cosmo, and Judy &amp;amp; Tess! Also, welcome to Jamie, Taylor and Austin who just adopted their new pup, Brady and who came to visit the Meet with him!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Maltese Meet for the coming month will take place on Sunday, March 5.  We will meet again from 1pm to 4pm at Especially for Pets in Sudbury. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seeing that we are coming up to St. Patrick's day, this time I'm encouraging everyone, including the dogs, to wear something green!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special note:  for those of you that have been searching high and low for some easy-to-use stairs for your dog to climb up to your bed, Especially for Pets in Sudbury and Wayland has them!  They come in 3, 4, 5 and 6 step versions.   We are trying them out and they seem quite good!  Also, a real plus is that they're made of very light material, easy to move. You have the phone number for Espec. for Pets in Sudbury and the number for Wayland's store is (508) 647-6923.  If the right size isn't there, they can order it. Measure the distance from floor to bed top, and then ask for the height of each type of staircase from Especially for Pets so that you can get the right size.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maltese best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1141754460000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1139166080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Maltese March Meetup</name><id>4848051</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1141581600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/4848051/</event_url></item>