<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>at the door</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for an excuse to clean out your t-shirt drawer(s)? Want to show off your best potluck dish? This is the event for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP at &lt;a&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt; (newcomers welcomed!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T-SHIRT SWAP  &lt;br /&gt; Bring 3 or more lightly used t-shirts. Leave with the same number! All sizes welcomed - remember this is a group of like-minded progressives, so bring interesting radical t-shirts and not just your &amp;ldquo;Walk&amp;rdquo; shirts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Children welcomed! We'll set up a separate table for childrens' t-shirts. Please indicate in your RSVP that you plan to bring childrens' t-shirts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;POTLUCK  &lt;br /&gt; Vegan, vegetarian and carnist dishes welcomed. Please list all ingredients on a card so SoJusters with allergy/dietary concerns can safely enjoy themselves. There is a kitchen with a microwave - there is no oven/stove. Be creative! We love variety and don't mean a variety of chips &amp;amp; salsa. Beverages welcomed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE  &lt;br /&gt; 6:00-7:00pm Browse t-shirts and eat!  &lt;br /&gt; 7:00-8:00pm T-shirt swap&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING&lt;/strong&gt; - if you're driving you may need to circle quit a bit to find a parking spot or park in a garage (The one by Harvard Kennedy School is the least expensive).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With almost 1700 members and 4 1/2 years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston (90+ events!), Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302873862000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300409893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck &amp; T-shirt Swap for Justice</name><id>16962004</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302818400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/16962004/</event_url></item>