<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>925 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351435</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Agganis Arena</name><city>Boston</city><id>759423</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;/b&gt; My niece is in the hospital, so I am going to have to pass on leading a group to this on Saturday. I'm probably going to be heading there tomorrow morning. Feel free to organize in the &amp;quot;Talk About This Event&amp;quot; section on the bottom of the write-up. Someone can volunteer to carry a red MEETUP sign, which you can print out on a color printer. Go to MORE -&amp;gt; FILES and an image should be there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-T.J. Maher&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anybody want to explore this on the last day of the event, say at 9:00 am? It's free! Let's see what robots the junior high and high schoolers these days can build for this year's FIRST (For Inspiration and Recognition of Science and Technology) competition, where teams build robots to compete with each other. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;u&gt;Saturday, March 27th&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonfirst.org/event-information-agenda.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:00 AM -- Pits and Machine Shop open&lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 9:30 AM -- Opening ceremonies&lt;br /&gt;9:30 AM - 12:15 PM -- Seeding matches&lt;br /&gt;12:15 - 12:30 PM -- Alliance selections&lt;br /&gt;12:30 - 1:30 PM -- Lunch&lt;br /&gt;1:30 - 4:30 PM -- Final rounds&lt;br /&gt;4:45 - 5:45 PM -- Awards ceremony&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM -- Pits close; crates packed &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year's game these high-schooler's robots should play is called &lt;b&gt;Breakaway&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Breakaway is a game played on the field above. Each match consists of a 15 second autonomous period and a 2 minute teleoperated period. Two alliances, one red and one blue, composed of three FIRST Robotics Competition (FRC) teams each, compete in each match. The object of the game is to attain a higher score than your opponent by shooting soccer balls into a goal, climbing on the Alliance Tower or Platform, or by lifting and suspending an alliance robot off the playing surface.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Each scored ball is worth 1 point, each robot on the Alliance Tower or Platform is worth 2 points, and each robot suspended from another robot is worth 3 points&amp;quot;. [ &lt;b&gt;Diagram of the playing field&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://bostonfirst.org/event-information-description.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt; ] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The teams &lt;a href="https://my.usfirst.org/myarea/index.lasso?page=teamlist&amp;amp;menu=false&amp;amp;event=MA&amp;amp;event_type=FRC" target="_blank"&gt;https://my.usfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt; are from all over New England, and even Canada, Great Britian and Brazil. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The competition is at Agganis Arena at Boston University, 925 Commonwealth Avenue, Boston, MA and T.J. Maher has no clue where to meet. The opening ceremony is at 9:00 am. Maybe we should group up by 8:45 am?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About FIRST:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonfirst.org/about.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;FIRST (For Inspiration and Recognition of Science and Technology) is a one-of-a-kind program for middle and high school students founded by inventor Dean Kamen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Designed to encourage students to pursue science and engineering, FIRST, works with mentors within business, education and government to make science as cool as sports&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Mission&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our mission is to inspire young people to be science and technology leaders, by engaging them in exciting mentor-based programs that build science, engineering and technology skills, that inspire innovation, and that foster well-rounded life capabilities including self-confidence, communication, and leadership.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dean Kamen [founder] is an inventor, entrepreneur, and tireless advocate  for science and technology. His passion and determination to help young people discover the excitement and rewards of science and technology are the cornerstones of FIRST (For Inspiration and Recognition of Science and Technology). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;FIRST was founded in 1989 to inspire young people's interest and participation in science and technology. Based in Manchester, NH, the 501 (c) (3) not-for-profit public charity designs accessible, innovative programs that motivate young people to pursue education and career opportunities in science, technology, engineering, and math, while building self-confidence, knowledge, and life skills&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Previous FIRSTs&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.usfirst.org/aboutus/content.aspx?id=880" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonfirst.org/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Parking: Garage parking is available on-site for a max daily rate of $10.  Metered street parking also exists&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Red Line: Take the Red Line to Park Street, Once at Park Street transfer to the Westbound Green Line &amp;quot;B&amp;quot; train, Take the &amp;quot;B&amp;quot; train to either the St. Paul Street or Pleasant Street stop; both are approximately one block from the Arena&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Directions and Parking in Adobe Acrobat form: &lt;a href="http://bostonfirst.org/pdf/2007%20Boston%20FIRST%20Directions%20and%20Parking.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonfirst.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269868526000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267067356000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FIRST - For Inspiration and Recognition of Science and Technology @ Boston U</name><id>12702063</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269694800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12702063/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>