<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Total Cost</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us for a delicious jazz brunch at Chester's at Mill Wharf, overlooking Scituate Harbor.   They offer a buffet brunch with all the breakfast options as well as seafood, chicken, roast beef, etc.  The band has been there for years, keeping people entertained throughout the brunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time/Date:  11:15 AM Sunday, May 18th, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Chester's Mill Wharf, 146 Front St, Scituate, MA 02066&lt;br /&gt;Web: www.millwharf.com&lt;br /&gt;Minimum/Maximum: Attendance is limited to 20 people.  One Guest is allowed per Member.&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place:  11:15 AM for 11:30am reservation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: Jazz-brunch is $22.95, which includes the meal, tax, tip, and juice.&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees:  $ 2.00 pp&lt;br /&gt;Other Costs: alcoholic beverages, coffee, etc. to be paid at end of meal&lt;br /&gt;Please Note:  &lt;br /&gt;Total Cost of Brunch and Fees is $25.00 which will be collected at check-in.  Anything additional will be collected at the end of the meal when the bill arrives.  VIP/Annual Members and Organizers pay $23.00.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, May 16th @ Noon ~ The Restaurant has asked us to finalize our reservation by Friday night.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organized by:  Angela and Susan&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather:  Event takes place rain or shine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please Note: The restaurant has requested we all be present before being seated.  We have built-in some time for folks who are running late (or may be lost).  This will also allow us to check everyone in and collect the fees before we are seated.  If you are going to be more than 15 minutes late please note it in your RSVP Comments.  Although we would rather have you join us if you are going to be late, if you will not be joining us before Noon then please RSVP No for this event.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 3:  Take exit 13 - Rt. 53 North.  Travel one mile to Junction of Rt. 123.  Get onto Rt. 123 East.  After crossing Route 3A, bear right onto Driftway.  Continue to Front Street and Scituate Harbor.  Mill Wharf Restaurant is located behind the Welsh Company Gift Shops after CVS and before TK O'Malley's.&lt;br /&gt;Lost?:  Call restaurant at 781-545-3999.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The RSVP list was printed @ 12:30pm on Friday, May 16th.  At that time, there were 17 Yes RSVPs.  We are calling the restaurant to advise them that we will have 18 in our party, therefore, there is room for another person.  Anyone who can no longer attend should change their RSVP to No but should know they will be considered a No-Show.  Angela has limited internet access this w/e so please email Susan with any questions or post your question on the &amp;quot;Talk About It&amp;quot; section on the Event Page which will allow any member of the Organizer Team to view and answer your question.  Thank you!  See you Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting in the Lobby (or outside the front door if it's nice out) and then we will go to our table together.  The restaurant has requested we all be present before being seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312746937000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><why>This is an extremely delicious brunch with a wide variety of options with a beautiful view overlooking Scituate Harbor.  It is sure to be a fun, relaxing, laidback and filling event.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207357718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Favorite Brunch: Jazz Brunch at Mill Wharf</name><id>7676142</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211123700000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7676142/</event_url></item>