<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>For some folks, a New Year means &amp;quot;Thank goodness! A fresh new start.&amp;quot;  For others, a continuation of &amp;quot;Hooray! More great experiences and successes.&amp;quot;   For many of us, it's usually a combination of relief and anticipation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So, how do we make sure that in 2009, our stories are &amp;quot;Two Thumbs Up!!&amp;quot;...all about attracting more joy, more lovingness, more of what we want ?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First step...Stop clinging to stories and beliefs that no longer serve you, especially the ones that have stopped you from your happiness and successes in 2008.  Does this mean burying the &amp;quot;troubling thoughts and shame and guilt&amp;quot; and fake being happy and saying positive affirmations 24/7?  We know that this will only attract more unhappiness and failure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clarissa Rodriguez, BostonLOA member,&lt;/b&gt; will guide us to learn &lt;b&gt;Byron Katie's simple yet powerful process of inquiry related to The Work&lt;/b&gt; to help separate you from your stressful stories and beliefs. She will share how her business and personal life has transformed &amp;quot;quantum leaps&amp;quot; this past year combining using The Work and Law Of Attraction principles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Work is about using a series of simple, specific questions that helps you explore and unravel assumptions, projections and interpretations associated with your stressful &amp;quot;story&amp;quot;.   &lt;b&gt;The power lies in your willingness to go within and answer each question honestly. You learn to check with your inner truth and bring forth clarity and lasting insight.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&amp;quot;Once the four questions are alive inside you, your mind becomes clear, &lt;br /&gt;and therefore the world you project becomes clear. &lt;br /&gt;This is more radical than anyone can possibly imagine.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;- Byron Katie&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Imagine being FREE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– from the stressful reactions that follow from negative thinking,&lt;br /&gt;– to respond rather than react, to step out of assumptions and work with the facts, feeling centered and present, and using each situation as a gift for self-discovery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Imagine Who You Would Be and How Attractive You Would Be in 2009 Without Your (Stressful) Story!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;============&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Clarissa Rodriguez&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides being an enthusiastic student and &amp;quot;practice-ioner&amp;quot; of Law Of Attraction  and The Works, Clarissa is also a successful serial entrepreneur.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: crodriguez8@usa.net&lt;br /&gt;www.clearroadassociates.com&lt;br /&gt;www.seventeenss.com&lt;br /&gt;www.realityfilmscorp.com&lt;br /&gt;www.ideabusinessbuilders.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235948456000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>75</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228871331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction January Meetup</name><id>9311158</id><headcount>76</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231286400000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/9311158/</event_url></item>