<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-1667</phone><name>Harvest Co-Op Market/Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>428348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Chick lit rules!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next pick is The Secret Life of Bees by Sue Monk Kidd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from &lt;a href="http://www.suemonkkidd.com/SecretLifeOfBees/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.suemonkkid...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Living on a peach farm in South Carolina with her harsh, unyielding father, Lily Owens has shaped her entire life around one devastating, blurred memory?the afternoon her mother was killed, when Lily was four. Since then, her only real companion has been the fierce-hearted, and sometimes just fierce, black woman Rosaleen, who acts as her &amp;quot;stand-in mother.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Rosaleen insults three of the deepest racists in town, Lily knows it's time to spring them both free. They take off in the only direction Lily can think of, toward a town called Tiburon, South Carolina?a name she found on the back of a picture amid the few possessions left by her mother.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There they are taken in by an eccentric trio of black beekeeping sisters named May, June, and August. Lily thinks of them as the calendar sisters and enters their mesmerizing secret world of bees and honey, and of the Black Madonna who presides over this household of strong, wise women. Maternal loss and betrayal, guilt and forgiveness entwine in a story that leads Lily to the single thing her heart longs for most.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;The Secret Life of Bees has a rare wisdom about life?about mothers and daughters and the women in our lives who become our true mothers. A remarkable story about the divine power of women and the transforming power of love, this is a stunning debut whose rich, assured, irresistible voice gathers us up and doesn't let go, not for a moment. It is the kind of novel that women share with each other and that mothers will hand down to their daughters for years to come.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have high hopes for getting outside this summer, and if we do, we'll be heading across from the John Harvard Statue in Harvard yard.  However, after checking the weather report, it looks like rain, so will likely be sticking to the couches of the Cafe tonight.  Will post a final location tomorrow afternoon, but, despite my high hopes, I think we'll be back inside...check your email tomorrow afternoon and will send my cell number out for final details.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be trying to hoard the couches in back</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216249477000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213638956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge readers: The Secret Life of Bees</name><id>8153009</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216076400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/8153009/</event_url></item>