<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone, Can you believe it's almost a year!! I guess time flies even when you're NOT having fun ;) with my daughter's "Angel Date" coming up soon, I'd like to invite all who know me, and/or were so supportive to me (in my time of serious "black hole" being ;) to my home on Friday, September 16th, for a candlelight vigil, and maybe even a bonfire, if the town allows it (I have giant marshmallow sticks and marshmallows lol). Her actual date is the 17th, but I have another family committment on that date. For those of you that are family, we will say a special prayer for my cousin Carolanne, who at the young age of 45, just passed away on Sept. 12th due to a brain aneurism. And we'll give an opportunity to anyone else who would like to remember a loved one, on that evening. If you'd like to come, please bring a candle, although I will pick some up. If it's windy, it would be nice to have candles in glass, so they won't blow out. I'm thinking 7pm, and if you'd like, to come at 6pm and bring something to share, we can have a bite to eat, beforehand. Please email me at stisbert@yahoo.com if you are bringing any goodies, so I won't duplicate. If you email me through meetup, I will get the message later, than sooner. And please bring a lawn chair, bug spray? and your own brand of drink ;) If anyone has a Hanson CD, we can play a few songs from her favorite band. A little OOOM BOP never hurts ;) Let's make it a joyous occasion, and with all the candles, Lauren will be looking down upon us, at the beautiful light signifying happiness and joy, for she surely has her wings by now, in the Pearly Gates of Heaven. hugs to all, susan&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send directions to those who say they are coming...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316215024000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316009235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate Lauren's "Angel date"</name><id>33511322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316210400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/33511322/</event_url></item>