<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste. 470</address_2><address_1>98 Derby St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.180230</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-740-9430</phone><name>REI</name><city>Hingham </city><id>730383</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.908089</lon></venue><fee><label>Cost</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>pp-tbd</description><amount>75.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join members and Guests of the SSFMG as we participate in REI's &amp;quot;Introduction to Road Cycling&amp;quot; (aka Biking 101) event!  This is a great introduction to Biking for beginners as well as those that have biked and would like to learn more basics to build their foundation.  Our members have been requesting this type of class for a while now and we have finally been able to offer it to our members.  This is a 6-hour class w/ a prompt 10am departure from REI and 4pm return to REI.  Please bring a picnic lunch.  The day will consist of instruction as well as biking.  We will spend about half of the time biking, possibly more, depending on how fast everyone catches on.  All equipment is provided (including bikes) and we will have transportation to and from the REI store and our biking location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some things you will learn include but are not limited to:&lt;br /&gt;- Road riding etiquette and risk&lt;br /&gt;- How to bike and avoid injury&lt;br /&gt;- Basic Bike Maintenance skills&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the official description for Introduction to Road Cycling for REI's Outdoor School.  &lt;i&gt;This outing is for riders just starting out or those looking for a refresher course.  We'll cover basic riding techniques, road riding etiquette and risks, and basic bike maintenance skills.  Novara road bikes are provided at no extra cost.  See REI.com/outdoorschool for details on what to wear.  Recommended for ages 14 and older; under 18 must be accompanied by a parent or responsible adult.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost of this class is as follows.&lt;br /&gt;REI Members: $55&lt;br /&gt;Non-Members: $75&lt;br /&gt;Discount - Will be received upon check-in at the event: Annual Members $5, Group Members $3, Guests $1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biking 101&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, September 20th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;9:45am-4pm&lt;br /&gt;REI&lt;br /&gt;98 Derby Street&lt;br /&gt;Derby Shoppes&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-740-9430&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;To Register&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;1. RSVP to put yourself on the Wait List.  &lt;br /&gt;2. Call REI to sign-up for the class (pay and register).  &lt;i&gt;Please state you are with the &lt;u&gt;Meetup&lt;/u&gt; Group so you will be properly registered.&lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;3. Once you have received your email confirmation note it in your RSVP Comments.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. The Event Organizers will check-in w/ REI periodically to confirm who has registered and will then move all those who have paid/registered to the Yes RSVPs.  &lt;br /&gt;B. If you are no longer able to attend please change your RSVP to a No so we can allow another member to join us.  (You MUST register w/ REI in order for us to consider you a Yes RSVP.)&lt;br /&gt;*Please Note: Everyone starts on the WL and will then be moved to the Yes RSVP once they have registered for the class w/ REI.  The Organizer Team Members overseeing this event will take care of this as they will check-in w/ REI regularly to get updates on who has registered.  Please check back here for updated details towards the end of August.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: $55 (REI Members), $75 (Non-REI-Members) - The SSFMG will giving you and your Guest a 'cash back' discount upon check-in at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cancellation Policy w/ REI&lt;/b&gt;: Full refund at least 48 hours in advance.  However, if we have less than the minimum number of Yes RSVPs due to cancellations the event may be cancelled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee&lt;/b&gt;: None, there is no Event Fee for this class.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/b&gt;: Angela - Please contact w/ questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max&lt;/b&gt;: We need at least 5 members in order for this to happen.  We currently have 8 spots held for us.  Any spots not taken by us will be released after Monday, September 14th.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests&lt;/b&gt;: One per member.  This class is open to the public so they can register on their own as well but if they register with us they get $1 back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ages&lt;/b&gt;: 21+ - Adults Only&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/b&gt;: Please finalize your RSVP by 4pm on Thursday, September 17th.  Any changes after this time from a Yes to No RSVP will be marked as a No-Show.  Any Yes RSVPs at this time who do not attend the event will be marked as a No-Show.  For more information on our Group's No-Show policy please refer to the Membership Information on our About page by clicking on the following link.  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/b&gt;: Heavy rains will cancel.  We will notify everyone by 5pm on Friday if this event is cancelled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Located in the Derby Street Shoppes off Exit 15 on Route 3.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  &lt;br /&gt;- This is for adults 21+ only.&lt;br /&gt;- You must register and pay w/ REI before we can move you to the YES RSVPs.&lt;br /&gt;- This event runs from 9:45am-4pm with a 10am departure time from the store. &lt;br /&gt;- Please bring a lunch, water, and sunblock.&lt;br /&gt;- Any Yes RSVPs after the RSVP Deadline who do not attend will be marked as a No-Show and will NOT receive any refunds from REI or the SSFMG.&lt;br /&gt;- Please contact GO Angela or AO Chandra with any questions, especially in regards to cost.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the front door.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253744493000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250364043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biking 101</name><id>11118990</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253454300000</time><rsvp_limit>3</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/11118990/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/8/global_3818056.jpeg</photo_url></item>