<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever wondered if there are really other planes of existence besides the physical world in which we live? Many people have heard stories or had experiences of these realms, only to be invalidated by a culture which does not believe in things it cannot see. The spiritual world is a vast expanse of consciousness and energetic vibration which is much higher than that of the physical world. One’s spiritual senses must be cultivated and activated through prayer and meditation in order to relate to the higher worlds. Come and begin to reclaim your spiritual senses and experience these realities for yourself. &lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;About the presenter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare is a mystic; ordained priest; Master Teacher of Christian mysticism; and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 15 Centers of Light in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she co-directs the effort to develop the Sophia Peace Center. She is the author of &lt;u&gt;Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path To Enlightenment&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347703000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250129199000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Higher Worlds</name><id>11100204</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250897400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/11100204/</event_url></item>