<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>499 Mountain Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01473</zip><lat>42.503555</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wachusett Mountain Ski Area</name><city>Princeton</city><id>1564621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.885429</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For anyone looking for a great mid-week opportunity to get outside for some solid exercise closer to home on a weekly basis - this is your chance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rising above the surrounding forest to a height of 2006 feet, Mount Wachusett stands as a unique landmark within the central New England landscape. From the summit, a clear day reveals views of Mt. Monadnock in New Hampshire, the Berkshires to the west, and the Boston skyline to the east. The 3,000-acre Wachusett Mountain State Reservation surrounds the summit and offers a wealth of natural and recreational resources. The Reservation's natural resources include forests, alpine meadows, ponds, streams, fields, and even a perched bog. Recreational opportunities abound at the reservation including hiking, nature study, hawk watching, picnicking, and skiing. The Reservation offers 17 miles of hiking and walking trails, including 3.9 miles of the Midstate Trail, which runs from Ashburnham to the Rhode Island border. Mountain Road stretches to the John Hitchcock Visitor's Center at the summit, a short distance from the Wachusett Mountain Ski Area, which is the largest in eastern Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Trail Map can be found here: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/wachusett.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/wachusett.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we plan to do:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this new weekly series we will hike a variety of trails, ranging from 4-6 miles, on average. We will take different routes to the summit, passing through various terrain, including fire roads and rocky trails - both flat and steep. Expect hikes to last between 1.5 to 2 hours. We will adjust the hiking routes and times based on who shows up and what the group woul like to do. Special requests can be made ahead of time. Dogs are allowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These hikes are intended for intermediate and above hikers looking to get some exercise/training for their weekend hikes further north. The pace will be faster than average, but geared towards the group's abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Wachusett Ski Area parking lot. While the lodge may be closed, there will be access to a bathroom, if needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email me with any questions or route suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will update these hikes with suggested routes as they get closer.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Audra</member_name><member_id>5480374</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346893905000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346326935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wachusett Wednesday's - Weekly Series</name><id>qbbbddyqmbhb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346882400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/80056362/</event_url></item>