<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cyber Security -&lt;/strong&gt; Risks and rewards for new venture launch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfnov11.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you launching a new business in cyber security and looking for insights on successful strategy, fund raising and trends to grow your business. Perhaps you need to better understand cyber security risks in order to protect and grow your business? Whether you are starting a business or you&amp;rsquo;re an entrepreneur in cyber security, you need to have effective strategies, an understanding of growing trends and financing methods to succeed in the internet marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assessing the risks and opportunities is critical to any business so you can best deploy appropriate strategies for raising business capital, avoid missing profitable opportunities, prevent a serious business disruption, or halt theft of critical intellectual property due to Cyber Crime. What strategies are effective in starting-growing a business in cyber security and how can you successfully capitalize on this? What are the risks to start-ups from cyber threats that can prevent a successful launch? How do you keep security costs low and effectiveness high? What are the new technologies and growth areas on the horizon? Does your business need to gain a better picture of growing cyber threat trends or the needs of potential customers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the next EntreTech Forum, cyber security industry insiders we will investigate two directions for the audience; cyber security threats and business insights to help raise money and build successful business and growth strategies. We will open up the floor for an interactive discussion with our panelists and audience. We welcome startups in all fields to join us. The forum&amp;rsquo;s panel will draw from leaders in industry, academic and government fields. The panel&amp;rsquo;s goal is to help startups and businesses in cyber security better understand, utilize and leverage the panelist&amp;rsquo;s experience in launching businesses, identifying major changes in technology and protecting businesses. Please join us for what will be an informative and interactive discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panel:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terry B. Anderton&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Trunity, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richard Pietravalle&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Principal, MITRE Corporation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Peter Ross&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Management Consultant, &lt;br /&gt;

Managing Director at Mass Tech Partners and Board Member at the Green Data Center Alliance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frederic Bowne &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Founder and Managing Principle of Perpetuation, LLC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meeting Location:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Emerging Enterprise Center at &lt;br /&gt;

Foley Hoag the Bay Colony Corporate Center &lt;br /&gt;

1000 Winter Street, Suite 4000 (North Entrance) &lt;br /&gt;

Waltham, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meeting Time: 6:30 - 9:30 p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting Cost:$25 public, $10 students and active military:&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321404244000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314976765000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cyber Security -  Risks and rewards for new venture launch</name><id>qnlkbcyppbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321399800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32005522/</event_url></item>