<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of State and Pleasant Streets</address_2><address_1>26 State Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Richdale Food Store</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1126642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://chambermaster.blob.core.windows.net/images/events/1189/2426/EventPhotoFull_EventPhotoFull_springfest_weblogo.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5.25 UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;The weather for tomorrow is suppose to be partly sunny (at least that is what 1 report says).  As I was driving through downtown I noticed they are setting up the vendor food tents, and the Chamber site says that this event will happen rain OR shine!  So bring your umbrella or rain jacket and meet us in town for some fun!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Come celebrate the season in downtown Newburyport!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Come and enjoy great live music, art, fine crafts, and food from Newburyport's best restaurants. On this date Jam Static&lt;a href="http://www.reverbnation.com/jamstatic"&gt;http://www.reverbnation.com/jamstatic&lt;/a&gt; will be playing, let's go cheer them on while enjoying the sites and sounds around town.  The festival is from 10-5pm, and the band is playing 1-4pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; The town will be crowded, allow enough time for when you get stuck in traffic!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; Where ever you are able to find a spot, in any of the parking lots or on street, but remember that you have to pay the meter if you are in a lot. There are 5 lots surrounding downtown: 1 on each side of the Fire House/Not Your Average Joe's (East lot/West lot), when you are coming down Water Street There is the one behind all the stores next to Green St behind the Unitarian Church (big white one on Pleasant Street), this is the lot that is near Inn Street. 1 is off of Prince Place which is the street before the library 1 after the Library on State Street (which is the smaller lot, maybe 15-20 spots) IF you park on the street there is a 2 HOUR minimum and you will get ticketed if you do not move your car!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seating:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;There are a few benchs where the band is playing not sure if we will be able to sit as the area usually fills up!  So bring a chair if you want to sit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This event will be scheduled on my 2 sites (A Circle of Friends and Connections and friends), there may be more people coming then you see.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, give me a call:  978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember if you have not paid your dues this year, this event would be a good opportunity to do so.  Thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be outside waiting on the corner. (This is just a meeting spot), if you are running late then you can meet us where the band is playing.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369606205000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368764692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Springfest Newburyport</name><id>119833872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369585800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/119833872/</event_url></item>