<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>906 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.202822</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 848-1151</phone><name>Sintra Restaurant</name><city>Braintree</city><id>1182910</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.005078</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Our ever-popular letter series continues!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our &amp;quot;S&amp;quot; poll produced two winners that stand head and shoulders above the competition; one of which we've been to twice before, and one which is new to the group. Faced with that, the Org Team agrees that the one to go to is... &lt;b&gt;both&lt;/b&gt; of them! But please understand if we give pride of place to novelty and run Scarlet Oak alittle later in the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this month, the &amp;quot;S&amp;quot; spotlight shines solely on Sintra!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And we can say without reservation that it is worthy of a star turn, folks. Sintra has been included in discussions of the South Shore's top-tier restaurants for years and the Org Team's recent experience indicates that it is still up there. Both Mike and Angela were very pleased with our attentive and personable server, as well as the preparation and presentation of our entrees. And dessert? Angela, a connoisseur of creme brulee, breathlessly declared Sintra's version to be the best she'd ever had.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good enough for ya? We hope so, because we'd hate to have our members miss the chance to get to know Sintra when we go there on Tuesday, February 23rd at 6:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sintra Restaurant&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;906 Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA&lt;br /&gt;(781) 848-1151&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.sintrarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Sintra Restaurant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Angela and Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Yes. One per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact an Event Organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Sintra's prices are somewhat high-end for the South Shore (though you &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; spend more elsewhere, believe us), but quite reasonable for what they offer. Pasta dishes are available as half orders for $10.00 - $12.00, or as full orders for $19.00 - $23.00. Entrees listed online range from $21.00 (Baked Chatham Haddock) to $29.00 (Grilled New York Sirloin).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility:&lt;/b&gt; This is handicap-accessible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Monday, February 22nd @ 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/b&gt; We will only cancel if there is a snowstorm the day of the event. TBD - Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on &amp;quot;weather&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sintra is located on &lt;b&gt;Washington Street&lt;/b&gt; in &lt;b&gt;South Braintree Square&lt;/b&gt;; quite close to Exit 17 off Route 3 and an easy drive for most of our members. We are providing directions from Route 3 in order to guide members who may be coming from a distance and also because the Union Street Rotary is a well known local reference point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3:&lt;/b&gt; Take &lt;b&gt;Exit 17 (Union St)&lt;/b&gt;. This is the Union St. Rotary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the &lt;b&gt;Union St/South Braintree/Braintree&lt;/b&gt; exit from the rotary. This will bring you immediately to the traffic light at Ivory St. (The entrance to The Marketplace at Braintree, where Borders and Big K are located, will be on your right.) Go &lt;b&gt;straight&lt;/b&gt; through this light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next light is the intersection of Union St. And Washington St. Turn &lt;b&gt;left&lt;/b&gt; onto &lt;b&gt;Washington&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go &lt;b&gt;straight through&lt;/b&gt; the &lt;b&gt;next two lights&lt;/b&gt; (Central Ave. and JFK Memorial Dr.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will shortly pass St Francis of Assisi Church on your left, then immediately see a &lt;b&gt;CVS on your left&lt;/b&gt;. The CVS is on the near corner of Holbrook Ave. Turn &lt;b&gt;left&lt;/b&gt; onto &lt;b&gt;Holbrook Ave.&lt;/b&gt;, then immediately turn &lt;b&gt;right&lt;/b&gt; into the &lt;b&gt;parking lot behind Sintra&lt;/b&gt;, which is shared with Giovanna's Salon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sintra has a rear entrance that opens onto this parking area, or you can walk around to the front and enter from Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under 'Angela' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'. We have the upstairs room!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267911452000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265396188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scintillating Sintra!</name><id>12529010</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266967800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/12529010/</event_url></item>