<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>; see directions below</address_2><address_1>182 Memorial Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358536</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Building 6, Room 120</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>408704</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In this midsummer night we will be treated to two presentations on technical analysis. The first is from David Weis and the second is from Chuck Dukas. Chuck Dukas is well-known to long-time Boston area technicians through his leadership of the Market Technicians Association.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spotting Market Moves with Price and Volume by Chuck Dukas, President of TRENDadvisor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a student of the markets the past three decades a quest of Mr. Dukas is to discern market moves and trends by price volume relationships.  Early in his technical analysis career Mr Dukas found volume to be a  challenge for him to peg to price.  He lacked the common thread of analysis that today is his normal analysis routine.  In his presentation Mr Dukas will:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Display simple yet very powerful analysis techniques to spot and uncover turning points for any financial instrument.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clearly identify patterns where price and volume contraction has abated and a new market move is about to unfold.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Show lucid signs of when the trend is about to end where traders are unwilling to pay higher prices for the financial instrument.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Show how supply / demand relationships play an import role to expansion / contraction based on price and volume.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talk about how his algorithm is accommodated by most all trading software programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; Mr. Dukas is a published author and President of TRENDadvisor.com, a Web site generating positive performance for investors and traders. His newly released acuTREND Trading System Software is receiving high praises and reviews from the trading community.  Chuck Dukas was recently named to: The Best And The Brightest Of Technical Analysis by Stocks &amp;amp; Commodities Magazine. He was the former Chairperson of the New England chapter of the (MTA) Market Technicians Association and regular guest speaker at major Universities and Colleges on the East Coast, he has also written numerous articles for Technical Analysis of Stocks and Commodities and Stocks, Futures and Options Magazine and frequently appears on media shows.  He may be reached at (704) 385-7000 or by email at: chuck@trendadvisor.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chuck's website is: &lt;a href="http://trendadvisor.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://trendadvisor.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Logical Reading of Bar Charts by David Weis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the past decade David Weis has taught many students the art of chart reading. These students became profitable traders after three to six months.  His methods are based on the writings of Richard D. Wyckoff and incorporate Mr. Weis's observations about price/volume behavior - the outgrowth of trading for 38 years. In his presentation Mr Weis will:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Show a market unfolding one bar at a time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combine the size of the daily range, the position of the close, the volume, and the interaction between the open and the range to tell a story about the trend and the turning points.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Show that this method can be applied to charts of any time period.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stress the application to the current market situation.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; David Weis is a market analyst with over thirty-six years experience. Mr. Weis served as the director of Technical Research for ContiCommodities, Inc during the mid-1980s. Although most of his work has been tied to the futures markets, he worked for several years in a fixed income group where he assisted cash bond traders with timing recommendations. Mr. Weis has conducted seminars and workshops on technical trading throughout North America, Europe and the Far East. He is the recognized authority on the trading methods of Richard Wyckoff. He is the former editor of the Elliott Wave Commodity Letter published by Robert Prechter and former editor/publisher of Technical Forces, a monthly market letter centered around price/volume analysis. In addition, he has written numerous articles on technical analysis and is the author of Trading With the Elliott Wave Principle: A Practical Guide and the co-author of Charting the Stock Market: The Wyckoff Method. Mr. Weis is currently consulting with institutional clients, stock traders and futures traders. He is an active trader and has developed unique short-term trading techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking and Walking Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the MIT map to the building: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/bin/map?locate=room_6-120;zoom=level3;selection=6;selectlayer=Buildings;selectfield=facility;centerx=711467;centery=495621" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We suggest you park as you do for Building E51 and walk to Building 6 - the building highlighted in red. Walk down Amherst Street, cross Ames Street, walk down the sidewalk until you get to Building 6, then walk in through the big doors in the center of the building. Room 120 is straight ahead.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216854381000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>24</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>139</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211309975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Technical Night - Lessons From Two Practitioners</name><id>7976258</id><headcount>155</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216681200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/7976258/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>