<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Old River Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.692941</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-975-3600</phone><name>Wyndham Hotel </name><city>Andover</city><id>809493</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.204044</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Beautiful &amp;amp; Functional Office Spaces&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether your office is in the basement of your home or in an office suite of a business center, Karen Mansur from Living Peace, Professional Organizing and Denyne Sanville from Denyne Designs are going to teach you how to make the space not only beautiful but functional so that you can work effectively and efficiently.  We will take you through the steps of creating an office space that is a reflection of your individual taste and style where you will be motivated and inspired to be your best each day. Sharing the tips and tools of the trade, we will offer advice from furniture placement, office ergonomics and choosing appropriate containers to selecting the right colors for the walls - and the file folders too! Don't miss this informative &amp;quot;Lunch and Learn&amp;quot; seminar where you'll walk away motivated to create the office of your dreams.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Karen Mansur&lt;/b&gt;, Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, Living Peace(r) From direct sales to retail management, her wide range of marketing skills offer the unique ability to fulfill our ever-changing needs in business development and public relations.  Combining these skills with her compassion for people and her love of organizing, she is a natural fit with the team.  Karen will often be the first point of contact for our clients and business partners, but will also provide support in garnering more speaking opportunities, seminars and workshops.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Karen lives in Newbury with her husband Christopher and their two children, Jacob and Chelsea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Denyne Sanville, Owner, Denyne Designs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is an expert at creating interior spaces for her clients that inspire and nurture the soul. She uses a holistic approach and gets to know the whole person while applying her unique gift with colors, patterns and forms, a very original and creative disposition and a trained designer's expertise.&lt;br /&gt;The most satisfying part of her job as a professional working woman and mother is to work collaboratively with her clients and inspire them to discover and design their dream homes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Denyne Lives in Dunstable with her husband Dan, their two boys Kyle and Shaun, and her dog Miss Georgia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen Campaiola</member_name><member_id>6037081</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279386041000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Daring Women!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup</urlname><id>1412014</id><group_lat>42.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Dare To Be Phenomenal's Success Minded Women's Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276774676000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DARE Networking Luncheon</name><id>rwlgnynkbsb</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279121400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup/events/13828461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/4/0/global_12349600.jpeg</photo_url></item>