<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Terminal Street #100</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.382763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Organics</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>12898752</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060211</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what goes on behind the scenes of a local food business? Join us at Boston Organics’ warehouse in Charlestown for a tour of their facilities and a conversation about our food system with Boston Organics and Bootstrap Compost. You’ll learn how these local businesses are working to connect farmers and consumers in the Boston area and close the loop in our food chain. Organic snacks will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Organics has been an active and involved player in the local agricultural infrastructure in New England since they first started in 2002. It is an independently owned organic food home-delivery service that sources only organic fruits, vegetables, and specialty products like coffee, chocolate and snacks. Customers order individual boxes each week, which are delivered to their doorsteps. The company was founded in 2002 by Jeff Barry and just celebrated its 10-year anniversary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap Compost is Greater Boston’s only year-round kitchen scrap pickup service. The company uses bikes, trains, hand trucks, and the occasional vehicle to collect and transport compostable material from houses, apartments, dorms, co-ops, and condos. Founded by Andy Brooks, the company is growing leaps and bounds - over 20% a year. Bootstrap just recently moved into the Charlestown industrial complex, next to Boston Organics, to help keep up with high demand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/event_227760032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/6/event_227760502.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>6980975</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366941967000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366605819000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Behind the Scenes at Boston Organics and Bootstrap Compost</name><id>115528172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366930800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/115528172/</event_url></item>