<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The next book we will read is &amp;quot;Founding Faith: Providence, Politics, and the Birth of Religious Freedom in America&amp;quot; by Steven Waldman. An unabridged audiorecording is also available. Copies of the printed book and the recording are available in public libraries and online. We will meet on Saturday, November 21, 2:30PM until 5:00PM at USNH, 700 Hartford Turnpike in Hamden. We will have a pot luck dinner until 3:30 PM and will then discuss the book. Please bring a dish to share.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Founding-Faith-Providence-Politics-Religious/dp/1400064376" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Review&lt;br /&gt;“Steven Waldman, a veteran journalist and co-founder of Beliefnet.com, a religious web site, surveys the convictions and legacy of the founders clearly and fairly, with a light touch but a careful eye.”&lt;br /&gt;—New York Times Book Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Waldman ends by encouraging us to be like the founders. We should understand their principles, learn from their experience, then have at it ourselves. 'We must pick up the argument that they began and do as they instructed – use our reason to determine our views.' A good place to start is this entertaining, provocative book.”&lt;br /&gt;—New York Times Book Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Steven Waldman's enlightening new book, Founding Faith, is wise and engaging on many levels, but Waldman has done a particular service in detailing Madison's role in creating a culture of religious freedom that has served America so well for so long….Founding Faith is an excellent book about an important subject: the inescapable—but manageable—intersection of religious belief and public life. With a grasp of history and an understanding of the exigencies of the moment, Waldman finds a middle ground between those who think of the Founders as apostles in powdered wigs and those who assert, equally inaccurately, that the Founders believed religion had no place in politics.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;–Newsweek&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Well-wrought, well-written and well-reasoned—a welcome infusion of calm good sense into a perennially controversial and relevant subject.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;–Kirkus Reviews&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Founding Faith takes up two central questions about religion in early America. First, what did such Founding Fathers as Benjamin Franklin, John Adams, George Washington, Thomas Jefferson and James Madison usually believe? And second, how did it come about that the First Amendment to the Constitution guarantees that 'Congress shall make no laws respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof'? The answers to these questions carry implications for our lives today, since at stake is the flash-point principle of the separation of church and state.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;–Washington Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“There is a fierce custody battle going on out there for ownership of the Founding Fathers. Founding Faith strikes me as a major contribution to that debate, a sensible and sophisticated argument that the Founders’ religious convictions defy our current categories.”&lt;br /&gt;–Joseph Ellis, author of American Creation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Steven Waldman does a great job describing the nuances of the Founders’ beliefs and the balances they struck, thus rescuing them from those on both sides who would oversimplify their ideas.”&lt;br /&gt;–Walter Isaacson, president of the Aspen Institute and author of Benjamin Franklin: An American Life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“This is a history every American should know, and Waldman masterfully tells it.”&lt;br /&gt;–Jim Wallis, author of The Great Awakening&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Steven Waldman recovers the founders’ true beliefs with an insightful and truly original argument. It will change the way you think about the separation of church and state.”&lt;br /&gt;–George Stephanopoulos, chief Washington correspondent, ABC News, and anchor of This Week&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Steve Waldman makes the strong case that the culture wars have distorted how and why we have religious freedom in America. Americans can be inspired by this story–the extraordinary birth story of freedom of religion.”&lt;br /&gt;–William J. Bennett, author of America: The Last Best Hope&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“An unusually well-balanced book on an unusually controversial subject. Not every reader will agree with Waldman that, of the Founding Fathers, James Madison’s conclusions about religion and society were best. But all should be grateful for the way Waldman replaces myths with facts, clarifies the complexity in making the Founders speak to present-day problems, and allows the Founders who differed with Madison a full and sympathetic hearing. An exceptionally fair, well-researched, and insightful book.”&lt;br /&gt;–Mark A. Noll, University of Notre Dame, author of America’s God&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Author&lt;br /&gt;Steven Waldman is co-founder, CEO, and editor in chief of Beliefnet.com, the largest faith and spirituality website. Previously, Waldman was the national editor of U.S. News &amp;amp; World Report and a national correspondent for Newsweek. His writings have also appeared in The Atlantic, The Washington Post, The New York Times, Slate, The Washington Monthly, National Review, and elsewhere. He appears frequently on television and radio to discuss religion and politics. He is also the author of The Bill, a book about the creation of AmeriCorps. Waldman lives in New York with his wife, the writer Amy Cunningham, and their children, Joseph and Gordon.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sholem</member_name><member_id>445389</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259767488000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254673074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion and Pot Luck</name><id>11543337</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258831800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/11543337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/global_5196186.jpeg</photo_url></item>