<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Airport Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.275730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Better Living Center</name><city>Worcester</city><id>4699292</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.855408</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are pleased to announce the upcoming screening of the film &lt;em&gt;Forks Over Knives.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; If you have already seen it, this is your chance to view it again and bring a friend.&amp;nbsp; We will also host a 100% vegetarian potluck.&amp;nbsp; If you decide to bring a dish, kindly include a recipe so we can give out copies.&amp;nbsp; But bringing food is not required.&amp;nbsp; Come and enjoy a great evening of healthy, delicious food and a movie! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; Saturday, Jan. 14, 5:30 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Where:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Better Living Center, 2 Airport Drive, Worcester, MA &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Free &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Info:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; (508) 243-1289 &lt;strong&gt;This event is a community service of the Seventh-day Adventist Church.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Forks Over Knives&lt;/em&gt; examines the profound claim that most, if not all, of the degenerative diseases that afflict &lt;br /&gt;

Americans can be controlled, or even reversed, by rejecting animal-based and processed foods. The major storyline &lt;br /&gt;

traces the personal journeys of Dr. T. Colin Campbell, a nutritional scientist from Cornell University, and Dr. Caldwell &lt;br /&gt;

Esselstyn, Jr., a former top surgeon at the world renowned Cleveland Clinic. Inspired by remarkable discoveries in &lt;br /&gt;

their young careers, these men conducted several groundbreaking studies and their separate research led them to the &lt;br /&gt;

same startling conclusion; degenerative diseases like heart disease, Type 2 Diabetes, and even several forms of cancer, &lt;br /&gt;

could almost always be prevented &amp;ndash; and in many cases reversed &amp;ndash; by adopting a whole foods, plant-based diet. &lt;br /&gt;

In addition, cameras follow real-life patients who have chronic conditions from heart disease to Diabetes. Doctors &lt;br /&gt;

teach these patients how to adopt a whole food, plant-based diet as the primary approach to treat these ailments&amp;mdash;while &lt;br /&gt;

the challenges and triumphs of their journeys are revealed. &lt;br /&gt;

Further information about this film can be found online at &lt;a href="http://www.forksoverknives.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.ForksOverKnives.com&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326585386000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326377286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Screening of the film Forks Over Knives and Potluck</name><id>47801582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326580200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/47801582/</event_url></item>