<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>ADDRESS EMAILED 1 WEEK IN ADVANCE</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04049</zip><lat>43.728172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rebecca's House</name><city>Limington</city><id>1040139</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.704552</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll host a creative dinner party, then go see the Limington Fireworks! For a small town, it has one of the best displays around!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So how is this all going to work?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Review the list of menu items below. &lt;br /&gt;2. Choose an item you would like to provide.&lt;br /&gt;3. When you RSVP yes, please leave a comment on what you can bring/make. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;*Make sure you review other people's &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to see what items are already taken. If you would like to bring something other than an item listed below, please do, and post what you will be bringing as a comment as well.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once we are finished with the dinner party, we will carpool 2 miles down the road to watch the &lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;fireworks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. We will have a place set aside ahead of time with the perfect view!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE RSVP YES ONLY IF YOU CAN ATTEND!&lt;/b&gt; If you RSVP yes and are bringing an item, please provide plenty of notice if you need to cancel. I recommend a minimum of 1 weeks notice for cancellations due to the holiday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner Menu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;1. Pina Coladas&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Old-style recipe for this popular drink. The coconut cream needs to have the right consistancy, some find the alternative, coconut milk to be too thin, however you can add condensed milk to coconut milk to bring up it's thickness. Add pineapple juice if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scale ingredients to servings&lt;br /&gt;60 oz light rum&lt;br /&gt;60 tbsp coconut cream&lt;br /&gt;60 tbspcrushed pineapples&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put all ingredients into an electric blender with 2 cups of crushed ice. Blend at a high speed for a short length of time. Strain into a collins glass and serve with a straw.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;2. Sherbet Punch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    *   Two 2 liter bottles of ginger ale, well chilled&lt;br /&gt;    * 1/2 gallon container of sherbet (any flavor)&lt;br /&gt;    * 2 quarts of pineapple juice, well chilled&lt;br /&gt;    * Punch bowl&lt;br /&gt;    * Serving ladle&lt;br /&gt;    * Cups&lt;br /&gt;All ingredients can be mixed together upon arriving at the party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Red Wine Steak Kabobs&lt;br /&gt;* 2 large beef bouillon cube (equivalent to make 2 cups)&lt;br /&gt;* 4 cups water&lt;br /&gt;* 3 cups Cabernet Sauvignon wine&lt;br /&gt;* 4 tablespoons minced shallots&lt;br /&gt;* 12 tablespoons butter&lt;br /&gt;* 3 lbs. boneless beef top sirloin steak, cut into 1 1/2-inch cubes&lt;br /&gt;* 2 medium yellow onion, cut into 1 1/2-inch triangles&lt;br /&gt;# Add beef bouillon cube, wine, and shallots to a large skillet and cook over high heat until mixture boils and reduces to half, about 15 minutes. Remove from heat and swirl in butter 1 tablespoon at a time. Cool to room temperature. Pour half of the sauce into a small bowl, cover, and refrigerate until ready to serve. Pour remaining sauce into a large bowl and add steak and onions turning to coat. Cover bowl and marinate in the refrigerator for 1 hour. Remove steak and onions from marinade and thread alternately on to metal skewers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;# Preheat grill according to manufacturer's instructions for medium heat. Grill kabobs for about 10 - 15 minutes, turning occasionally during cooking process, until steak is desired doneness. (A 10-minute cooking time should result in medium-rare steak over medium-hot, ashen coals.) Meanwhile, warm up reserved sauce in the microwave or in a saucepan until just warm. Remove kabobs from grill and arrange on individual plates or a large platter. Drizzle sauce over kabobs and serve immediately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;4. Bacon and Horseradish Sliders&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ingredients:&lt;br /&gt;3 lb. ground beef&lt;br /&gt;4 tsp. fresh minced garlic&lt;br /&gt;1/2 C. minced onion&lt;br /&gt;2 tsp. salt&lt;br /&gt;1 tsp. freshly ground black pepper&lt;br /&gt;12 slices crisp-cooked bacon, halved&lt;br /&gt;24 mini hamburger rolls (or cut-out rolls), split&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Horseradish Sauce:&lt;br /&gt;4 tbsp. sour cream&lt;br /&gt;6 tbsp. prepared horseradish&lt;br /&gt;1/4 teaspoon fresh ground black pepper&lt;br /&gt;1/2 tsp. salt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instructions: 1. To make your slider patties, combine the beef, garlic, onion, salt, and pepper. Mix with your hands.&lt;br /&gt;2. Divide into 24 equally-sized balls, and shape into patties. Cover, refrigerate, and let patties chill for at least an hour, or even overnight.&lt;br /&gt;3. To make your mayonnaise, whisk together the mayo, sour cream, horseradish, pepper, and salt. Refrigerate at least an hour, and up to 3 days.&lt;br /&gt;4. Grill you mini burgers about two minutes per side for medium doneness, 3 minutes a side for well done.&lt;br /&gt;5. Serve these little burgers on your buns, topped with a piece of bacon and some of your horseradish sauce. Talk about a fun fourth of July snack! &lt;br /&gt;*The recipe calls for teeny hamburger buns, which can be hard to find. Me? Well, I cheat. I buy regular hamburger buns and cut little circles from them with a teeny biscuit cutter (or small round cookie cutter). Yes, you tend to waste a bit of bun this way, but... the effect is worth it. Don't use plain white bread, because you won't get the same soft top crust! High quality hamburger buns are best, but you can use the el cheapo kind. If you're on the lookout for make-ahead 4th of July appetizer recipes, this can be made ahead, too. Simple make up the burgers ahead of time, mix the horseradish ahead of time, and use pre-cooked bacon. Done and done.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;5. Salad of your choosing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Vegetables of your choosing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. Cookies!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*2 dozen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;8. A dessert of your choosing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10. Home-made potato chips&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ingredients&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * 16 russet (baking) potatoes, peeled and sliced diagonally 1/8 inch thick&lt;br /&gt;    * 2 stick of butter, melted&lt;br /&gt;    * Coarse salt to taste&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instructions: Pat the potatoes dry between paper towels and arrange them in one layer in 2 buttered cookie sheets pans. Brush the potatoes with the butter, bake them in a preheated 500°F oven for 15 to 20 minutes, or until the edges are golden brown. Sprinkle them with the salt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9. Watermelon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10. Your favorite summer appetizer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;11. Your favorite summer food to share!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Luke and I will supply some additional items to eat........ to be determined!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280013135000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275528755000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creative Dinner Party then Fireworks!</name><id>13679230</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278190800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/13679230/</event_url></item>