<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;I'm learning from this not to schedule movies more than 2 weeks out. Doubt is out (of the theaters). So let's go see &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809785152/info" target="_blank"&gt;The Curious Case of Benjamin Button&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&amp;quot;I was born under unusual circumstances.&amp;quot; And so begins &amp;quot;The Curious Case of Benjamin Button,&amp;quot; adapted from the 1920s story by F. Scott Fitzgerald about a man who is born in his eighties and ages backwards: a man, like any of us, who is unable to stop time. We follow his story, set in New Orleans from the end of World War I in 1918, into the 21st century, following his journey that is as unusual as any man's life can be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I realize the change of movie may affect your decision to attend, so please make sure your RSVP is up-to-date. You can respond until 5:30 Tuesday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet right inside the theater doors at 7:30. The movie starts at 8:00. If you're late, lost, or have a last-minute RSVP, please call my cell (508-308-4897).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;I don't &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809966791/info" target="_blank"&gt;Doubt&lt;/a&gt; this one will be awesome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;It's 1964, St. Nicholas in the Bronx. A vibrant, charismatic priest, Father Flynn, is trying to upend the school's strict customs, which have long been fiercely guarded by Sister Aloysius Beauvier, the iron-gloved Principal who believes in the power of fear and discipline. The winds of political change are sweeping through the country, and, indeed, the school has just accepted its first black student, Donald Miller. But when Sister James, a hopeful innocent, shares with Sister Aloysius her suspicion that Father Flynn is paying too much personal attention to Donald, Sister Aloysius is galvanized to begin a crusade to both unearth the truth and expunge Flynn from the school. Now, without a shred of proof or evidence except her moral certainty, Sister Aloysius locks into a battle of wills with Father Flynn, a battle that threatens to tear apart the Church and school with devastating consequences.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This one's nominated for a Golden Globe, so it's sure to be a stirring drama.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the meetup with exact time a few days before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted tickets for FMM members and their guests is $8.50. (Just be sure to include guests in your RSVP.) Small popcorn and small soda vouchers are available for $3.00 each. Please be sure to include guests in your RSVP, so I know how many to expect. Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at Doubt!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232762638000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231033255000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Curious Case of Benjamin Button, was Doubt</name><id>9437216</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232497800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/9437216/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>