<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;9/13 UPDATE: The word is in SurfSide5 has shut their kitchen down for the season. (YES the bar is open).  So if you were planning on getting dinner there then you are free to bring in whatever you want to eat.  IF you want to grab something from any of the beach eats, or something from home, your choice no problem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;The meetup time is 6:30 if you aren't able to show up then, then come when you can and find us either inside or on the deck.  See you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9.9.12 UPDATE: There is a $5.00 cover charge which starts at 8:00. I am not able to put in a reservation for tables on the deck.  Also we may not be sitting near each other and/or who knows how many tables will be open when we get there.  Please be patient as you wait for tables to be open.  You may be sitting with people that you don't know...... but that could be a good thing, who knows you may make a new friend or two??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's go Back to Salisbury Beach and check out Don't Call Me Shirley at SurfSide5 Beach Bar &amp;amp; Grille it is their debut!!!  Let's go cheer them on and blow the neighbors away.  SurfSide 5 features a huge 8,000 sq.ft. deck located directly over the ocean, SurfSide5 is the place to catch the surf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.  This phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues?  Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can pay your dues at this event. I Thank you for paying your dues!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to dancing the night away with you at Salisbury Beach!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in and find us either inside or on the deck.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347737518000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346091310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don't Call Me Shirley Debuting in a NEW location!</name><id>79590592</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347661800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/79590592/</event_url></item>