<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets do a great workout the day before Thanksgiving! &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; This one is sure to get our legs burning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taken from The November Project website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in lower Allston, &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?q=harvard+stadium&amp;amp;ll=42.366693,-71.127098&amp;amp;spn=0.009005,0.019226&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=harvard+stadium&amp;amp;hnear=harvard+stadium&amp;amp;cid=0,0,5734807670269610128&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;iwloc=A" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Stadium&lt;/a&gt; is one of the favorite workout spots of the November Project tribe. Its capacity crowd of over 30,000 people can be seated on thirty-one sets of concrete-block seats in each section of the stadium. There are 37 sections in this horseshoe shaped building, which brings the total of 1147 concrete seats that we tackle every week. Sections are separated by regular size stairs that we use to go move between the sections. To put it short and simple we run up the big seats and come down the small steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Workouts: &lt;br /&gt;

- Full tour – 37 sections in the shortest period of time. &lt;br /&gt;

- Tour of 50 – starting at section 37 to section 13 and back for a total of 50 sections in the shortest period of time. &lt;br /&gt;

- 35 minutes – covering as many sections as possible in 35 minutes &lt;br /&gt;

- Century – 100 sections in the shortest time possible&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information see:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://november-project.com/stadium/" class="linkified"&gt;http://november-project.com/stadium/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, while I am listing this as a meet up, once there, The November Project is actually running this--we are all participants; I am NOT an organizer at the event.  I am posting this for us to organize who is interested, maybe determine car pooling options.  The event happens rain or shine, according to the group's website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In terms of parking: I have been to the Stadium before and there is on street parking on that road; if the gates are open (which I don't know) then there is also parking on at the actual site.  (A fellow runner is planning on participating on Nov 7; if she does, she will provide me with more info and I will update this listing.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>where everybody gathers--I have not done this before either; the workout starts at 6:30am; be sure to arrive early</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica</member_name><member_id>10925522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353571077000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352216151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Run Harvard Stadium with The November Project</name><id>90207902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353497400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/90207902/</event_url></item>