<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>548 Main St. (Rte 20)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01518</zip><lat>42.116207</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 347- 0888</phone><name>Corner Stone Creations</name><city>Fiskdale</city><id>508227</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.113411</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FREE Paranormal Investigation Class/ Haunted Dinner&lt;br /&gt;When&lt;br /&gt;    Saturday, February 27, 2010 2:00 PM 20100227T190000Z &lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    If you are new to paranormal investigations or just want to brush up on your skills, please join us for a Paranormal Investigation 101 class, followed by an investigation of a historic building with a reputation for being paranormally active. Afterward, we*ll head to a nearby pub for dinner and discussion of the investigation. IMPORTANT: When you register, please say whether or not you will be going to dinner, so that I have an accurate count for the dinner reservations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This is a joint meetup, for Footprints Paranormal and Central MA Wiccan meetups, and spaces are limited, so I encourage you to register soon. If you want to attend and don*t have an opportunity to do so this time, please let me know, so that I can plan another class later in the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Class will cover the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Introduction (current theories on what is a ghost, types of hauntings,&lt;br /&gt;    etc.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Do*s and don*ts for investigations&lt;br /&gt;    * How to prepare for and conduct an investigation (note: we will not be covering how to do a formal investigation of a client*s private residence--it is beyond the scope of this class)&lt;br /&gt;    * Protection (how to ground yourself and keep yourself safe during an&lt;br /&gt;    investigation)&lt;br /&gt;    * Equipment basics (includes practice with basic equipment)&lt;br /&gt;    * Q and A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Investigation:&lt;br /&gt;    We'll be investigating the second floor of a large historic building in Sturbridge. The location does not have electricity or heat, so dress warmly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    What to bring:&lt;br /&gt;    Flashlight (mandatory)&lt;br /&gt;    Notepad for recording information during the investigation Any equipment you already own (for example, voice recorder, camera)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Time:&lt;br /&gt;    Class 2-5pm&lt;br /&gt;    Investigation 5-6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Class location:&lt;br /&gt;    Cornerstone Creations&lt;br /&gt;    548 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;    Fiskdale, MA 01518 (a part of Sturbridge)&lt;br /&gt;    (508) 347-0888&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Parking:&lt;br /&gt;    Parking is available at the Copper Stallion parking lot, a few doors down the street, or at Sturbridge Marketplace, across the street from Cornerstone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Dinner will be at the Whistling Swan, which is right near Pete's and where the haunted investigation is going to be, you can check out their website at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;a href="http://www.thewhistli.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thewhistli...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This place is also haunted, with recent ghostly activity reported recently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Though the class is limited due to space, if you are interested in joining us for dinner, please&lt;br /&gt;    email Tala at: talawolf7@webtv.net by Thursday, Feb 25th for reservations.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267750360000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pagans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pagan-1307</urlname><id>1221723</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pagan Learning Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265851848000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Paranormal Investigation Class/ Haunted Dinner</name><id>12575935</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267297200000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pagan-1307/events/12575935/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/9/5/global_7092405.jpeg</photo_url></item>