<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Clinton St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360661</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.424.ROCK (7625)</phone><name>Hard Rock Cafe</name><city>Boston</city><id>746069</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054817</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for Sugar and Spice- A Valentine's themed evening of sexy fun not to be missed! Featuring salsa dancing lessons, live salsa band, body painting by a renowned artist, best lips contest, tacky pick-up lines contest, red carpet entrance, delicious appetizers, silent auction and raffle. This event will be held at the trendy Hard Rock Cafe, Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceeds from the evening will benefit Project Smile, the non profit organization run by your Meet Up organizer Catherine, that helps children involved in traumatic situations. Project Smile donates stuffed animals, coloring books/crayons, small toys and books for police officers, fire fighters and paramedics to give to children involved in traumatic events. Project Smile also donates items to the Department of Children and Families for children entering foster care. Since 2003, Project Smile has donated over 23,000 items and works with 143 police and fire departments in New England to help thousands of children annually. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are only $25 and can be purchased at www.projectsmile.org/events.htm or at the door, if available. For a limited time, advanced tix are only $20- get yours online today!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside event. If need, please call 774 232 0000</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235090621000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232404119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sugar and Spice</name><id>9558293</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234481400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/9558293/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/6/a/global_7001738.jpeg</photo_url></item>