<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>People often perform a majority of their good deeds at Christmas.... however, good deeds are needed year round! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Did you know that it's the little things that can brighten a person's day?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For our first ever &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day of Good Deeds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, we'll start simple:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. We'll meetup and make some cards &amp;amp; notes with positive thoughts or words of inspiration. Here are some examples of what we'd put on the cards &amp;amp; notes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Where the willingness is great, the difficulties cannot be great.&lt;br /&gt;- Niccolo Machiavelli&lt;br /&gt;We can do whatever we wish to do provided our wish is strong enough. What do you want most to do? That's what I have to keep asking myself, in the face of difficulties.&lt;br /&gt;- Katherine Mansfield&lt;br /&gt;We should not let our fears hold us back from pursuing our hopes.&lt;br /&gt;- John F. Kennedy&lt;br /&gt;Man can live about forty days without food, about three days without water, about eight minutes without air ... but only for one second without hope.&lt;br /&gt;- Hal Lindsey&lt;br /&gt;Knowledge of what is possible is the beginning of happiness.&lt;br /&gt;- George Santayana&lt;br /&gt;Happiness comes more from loving than being loved; and often when our affection seems wounded it is only our vanity bleeding. To love, and to be hurt often, and to love again-this is the brave and happy life.&lt;br /&gt;- J. E. Buckrose&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Once we've made the cards, we become RAK Bandits! (Random Acts of Kindness Bandits). This is where we deliver our cute notes and cards, by mailing them anonymously to someone who needs some positive thoughts, or place them on cars for a random person to find.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;So what do YOU need to do to help us make this happen?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign up to bring one of the items below, plus bring a dish, snack, or drink to share with the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Envelopes&lt;br /&gt;2. Blank Cards&lt;br /&gt;3. Cards with beautiful pictures, but blank on the inside.&lt;br /&gt;4. Decorating Pens&lt;br /&gt;5. Stickers&lt;br /&gt;6. Glue&lt;br /&gt;7. Scissors&lt;br /&gt;8. Card paper (like for scrapbooking) to cut, decorate, and attach to the cards as embellishments.&lt;br /&gt;9. Any scrapbooking or card making supplies you may have.&lt;br /&gt;10. Blank Paper&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the following website for ideas for&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt; future Day of Good Deeds!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.randomactsofkindness.org/images/stories/RAOK_Logo.png" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295357239000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290890477000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Day of Good Deeds #1!</name><id>klkxpypcbtb</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295121600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/15568779/</event_url></item>