<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>195 Newport Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02170</zip><lat>42.269165</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>La Paloma</name><city>Quincy</city><id>4498372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.023865</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us for a Mexican meal at one of Quincy's best!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, Novermber 10th @ 12pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;La Paloma Mexican restaurant offers an extensive menu ranging from simple Enchiladas to complex Paella. At La Paloma we believe in presenting dishes that are flavorful, not merely spicy. The combination of our superior food and courteous staff makes for a memorable meal. Our “homey” atmosphere is perfect for couples, groups and families. We have a full liquor license and make the best Margaritas north of the Rio Grande.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At La Paloma, you'll find that a great waitstaff and great food are combined to create an exceptional experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lunch menu: $8.99-$11.99&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner menu (available during lunch): $4.99-$17.99&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Please meet inside the front door. We may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: [Current] Annual Members - FREE, Members - $2 each; $6 to become an Annual Member&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: One per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: November 9th, 8pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our Group's No-Show Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;No-Show Policy on Membership Information Page:&lt;/em&gt; (Please click on the following link to be taken directly to the page.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cash Only Policy&lt;/em&gt;: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Based on the weather forecast we should be OK.  There may be a passing shower but we will meet rain or shine.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather").&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages tab for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From South and 128:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Southeast Expressway to Furnace Brook Parkway. Follow Furnace Brook Parkway to the 5th traffic light (counting the blinking light at Furnace Brook School). There is a Super Petroleum station on the left and MBTA tracks ahead. This is Newport Avenue. Turn left, continue on Newport Avenue past Wendy's. Newport Center is next door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;From the South Shore:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 3 to Exit 19 (Quincy Adams T Station). Follow Burgin Parkway for approximately two miles. It then becomes Newport Avenue. Continue on Newport Avenue for approximately one mile. We are located on your left past Wendy's at 195 Newport Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Boston &amp;amp; Points North:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Southeast Expressway to Neponset Circle (Exit 12 - 3A Quincy-Plymouth), over the bridge and off at first exit. At traffic light turn right onto Newport Avenue. Continue on Newport about 1 ½ miles. We are located in the Newport Center, just past Super Stop &amp;amp; Shop.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://www.lapalomarestaurant.com/index.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debbi  </member_name><member_id>22304061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352591559000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351119922000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ole'! Mexican Lunch</name><id>88431452</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352566800000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/88431452/</event_url></item>