<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 E Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.535690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Augusta Curtis Cultural Center</name><city>Meriden</city><id>260056</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.797250</lon></venue><fee><label>Admission fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>each at the door</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>** UPDATE **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I noticed the times originally given in this Event were wrong, so I've changed the Event.  Doors open 5pm, movies start 5:30.  Last time this festival was held in this venue I'm pretty sure it sold out and people were being turned-away.  Though this year they've roughly doubled the seating I think, maybe more.  In any case, I (Jason) plan on being there before 5 to ensure I get in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** UPDATE **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the film lineup has been posted. to see it, &lt;a href="http://www.nhuff.com/lineup.html" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i'll start off by saying this: the New Haven Underground Film Festival is not in New Haven, and to my knowledge never has been (not sure about '04). maybe one day it will be (one can hope!). that said, if you like film, especially small-budget independent film, this festival has in the past showcased some real gems, and no doubt will again this year. from the &lt;a href="http://www.nhuff.com/" target="_blank"&gt;festival's website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The New Haven Underground Film Festival was founded in 2004 by filmmakers who have been through the glorious highs and crushing lows of the international film festival circuit. From these shared experiences came the calling to create a real alternative to the political madness, market-driven pitfalls, and cultural elitism that defines many film festivals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our goal is to celebrate both entertainment value and artistic integrity, without commercial pressure or fear of censorship. By exposing the movie-going public to unique and entertaining work, created outside or despite the Hollywood system, we are working to foster an outlook that promotes devoted audience support for great filmmaking, regardless of its origin or its budget.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the festival runs from 5pm to 12:30am, with the awards ceremony immediately afterward. &lt;a href="http://video.google.com/videoplay?docid=2315193969942366379" target="_blank"&gt;here's one of the original and entertaining films from last year&lt;/a&gt; (done all with legos).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;questions? can't guarantee I'll have answers, but feel free to call me (Ben): 203-554-5144&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179177013000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176055413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sat. 5/12 - the New Haven Underground Film Festival</name><id>5649860</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179003600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5649860/</event_url></item>