<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 may street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.257946</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Photo Studios</name><city>Worcester</city><id>2095731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.825211</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/400711133323607/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/400711133323607/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's summer, Perfect time to add some Swim Wear shot's to your portfolios. Will have 10 models available by invite only, men and women. Limit 20 photographers, so preregister today! &lt;br /&gt;

Paypal payment@worcesterphotostudios.com, call 800-210-9531, e-mail Chris@worcesterphotostudios.com or stop by to register.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $60 for photographers; Hair, Makeup artists and designers are free! Models by invite only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring: Photographers can bring their own lights or use ours. There will be space for indoor and outdoor shooting. Props are encouraged. Designers should bring suits and accessories they would like to show off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code of conduct:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alcohol and drugs are strictly prohibited at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are attending one of our events, please take a moment to review this. If you are under 18 years of age, you MUST have a parent or legal guardian come with you. You may not have an older sibling, or other relative (unless they are your legal guardian) sign you into the GMS. Your parent or guardian must fill out the Model Release with you and have a valid ID.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inappropriate behavior will result in a verbal warning by a WPS staff member. If such behavior continues, you will be asked to leave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These rules are put in place for everyone's safety and comfort. Any questions about Code Of Conduct or studio rules can be directed to info@worcesterphotostudios.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345458696000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344866300000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Swimwear Shoot</name><id>77529012</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345392000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/77529012/</event_url></item>