<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>32 Vassar Street</address_2><address_1>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 155</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1119883</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;UNIVERSITY – INDUSTRY COLLABORATION&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MIT Enterprise Forum invites you to join us and hear from four outstanding technologists and business leaders in the Auto ID and Sensing field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date and Time:  Monday, June 14th at 6:00 PM at the MIT Stata Center room 32-1555.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;PANELISTS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Steve Miles, Research Scientist, MIT Senseable City Laboratory; Research Affiliate, MIT Auto-ID Laboratory &lt;br /&gt;• Prof. Charles Kochakian, Merrimack College RFID Training Center&lt;br /&gt;• Prof. Ramaswamy Nagarajan, UMass Lowell Nanotechnology Center&lt;br /&gt;• Moderator:  Michael Ohanian, former President of Intermec Technologies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This program offers the attendees an important opportunity to engage in the vital debates and discussions surrounding the future of RFID/Auto ID education.  The panel discussion will provide an insight into the tremendous progress being made in providing the education and training of students and professionals in the field of Automatic Identification Technology. We are seeing a greater number of schools providing the education and hands-on training as RFID and Auto ID technologies moves into the mainstream of how business is conducted by global industries.  Each of our panelists will provide a unique perspective of what is happening at their respective institution.  How are universities and industries collaborating to provide the technologists of tomorrow?  What benefits are being provided through University/Industry collaboration?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many other questions will be addressed by the panelists including:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Are US universities leading Europe and Asia in RFID/Auto ID education/research?  If not, what’s missing?&lt;br /&gt;• A historical perspective &lt;br /&gt;• How will the education process drive adoption forward at an increased rate?&lt;br /&gt;• Providing a venue and forum for hardware/software providers, system integrators, VAR’s, channel partners and end users.&lt;br /&gt;• How are schools providing curriculum and hands-on training?&lt;br /&gt;• Is STEM the answer to encouraging our youth?&lt;br /&gt;• What do institutions of higher education need to provide to business owner/managers?&lt;br /&gt;• How can you and/or your company support these activities?&lt;br /&gt;• The convergence of RFID and Naontechnology?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the PANELISTS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Ohanian&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Ohanian is a Consultant to the Automatic Identification Technology Industry with specialization in bar code, wireless and RFID technology. Serves on the Board of Directors/Advisors of Several High Tech AIDC companies. Ohanian is a member of the AIDC 100 organization and is a recognized authority in RFID technology.  He is committed to the advancement of RFID technology in the global marketplace. He has consulted for numerous companies and universities who are planning to enter the RFID arena.  Currently he is assisting Merrimack College in establishing a hands-on RFID training center. &lt;br /&gt;He has over forty years experience in the electronics industry and has held senior management positions at Raytheon Company, Litton Industries, Lockheed Martin, and Intermec Technologies.  Ohanian served as President of Intermec Technologies from 1995 – 2000.  Intermec Technologies is a global supplier of bar code and RFID data collection products/services and system solutions for the industrial, retail and government markets. He has a BSEE in Electrical Engineering from Merrimack College and serves on the Board of Trustees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charles Kochakian is an Adjunct Professor in the Dept. of Electrical Engineering at Merrimack College&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While at Merrimack Charles Kochakian has created and taught a course entitled Disruptive Technologies with AutoID-Sensor (AID-S) technology being its primary focus. Prior to joining the EE Dept. he organized a lecture series and workshop on RFID for MC and participated as one of the presenters.&lt;br /&gt;He has had a leading role in establishing the RFID Training Center and Laboratory, a facility used for training of students and professionals as well as for testing and performance evaluation of AID-S  systems. And has planned and participated in tailored on-campus training sessions for NXP. &lt;br /&gt;He has supervised student projects which have included a proof of concept demonstration of a UHF RFID secured access control system for Massport;  a feasibility study of an Auto ID system for monitoring and control of waste hauling truck traffic for the Town of North Andover; a pilot project of a RFID system to be used in the MC library and a senior project to design and build a small compact reader having both near field and far field capability. At present he is exploring the feasibility of using MEMS and nanotechnology for the next generation of passive and active AID-S tags.  Collaborating with the University of Mass-Lowell (UML) to explore the utilization of nanotechnology in manufacturing printed HF and UHF antenna for RFID tags/sensors. &lt;br /&gt;Charles received his BSEE from Merrimack College and a MS in Aeronautics and Astronautics from MIT.  After a 43 year engineering career at MIT and Draper Lab and 15 years of part-time teaching of electronics at Merrimack College he retired.  Besides his aforementioned faculty position he is President of CRK Engineering Consultants, a life member of IEEE, a senior member of AIAA and Professional Engineer.  Over the past 8 years he has addressed educating today’s electrical engineering /computer science/business students about RFID  technology specifically and AID-S in its broader venue to prepare them for the emerging disruptive technology that it is likely to be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prof. Ramaswamy Nagarajan, UMass Lowell Nanotechnology Center&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ramaswamy Nagarajan is an Assistant Professor in the Plastics Engineering department at UMass Lowell. His interdisciplinary research group at UML is involved in the development of advanced functional materials (electronic, photo-responsive polymers and nanoparticle based electrically conductive inks). In collaboration with the Center for high rate nanomanufacturing (CHN) and Nanomanufacturing centers of excellence (NCOE) at UML, Dr. Nagarajan’s group has developed novel wireless sensors for remote structural health surveillance. Dr. Nagarajan’s research interests include biocatalysis, flexible electronics and organic photovoltaics. Over the past decade he has also developed novel ‘greener’ routes to the synthesis of conjugated polymers and biomimetic catalysts. Dr. Nagarajan has extensive experience in molecularly integrated hybrid nanomaterials  (incorporating electro-active/ photo-responsive polymers into bio-based materials). &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Nagarajan has B.S degrees in Chemistry and Rubber Technology, Masters and Ph.D in Polymer Science. Dr. Nagarajan’s industrial experience includes roll-to-roll manufacture of flexible electronic products. Dr. Nagarajan’s unique combination of experience in science and engineering has enabled him to advance UML’s research and educational efforts in the area of flexible electronics and sustainability.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come and address your questions to our distinguished panelists.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For registration, please visit &lt;a href="https://alum.mit.edu/smarTrans/public/Register.dyn?eventID=38587&amp;amp;groupID=298" target="_blank"&gt;https://alum.mit.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Miles</member_name><member_id>10116261</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277809867000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258687418000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>University – Industry Collaboration</name><id>11917264</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276552800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/11917264/</event_url></item>