<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;(This is a cross post. Please only RSVP to one meetup group/Facebook group.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Four Falls Spring 2009&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1. Crystal Cascade&lt;br /&gt; 2. Glenn Ellis Falls&lt;br /&gt; 3. Jackson Falls&lt;br /&gt; 4. Diana’s Bath&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With peak runoffs from snow and ice melt Spring is arguably the best time for waterfall hikes!&lt;br /&gt;I hope you will agree with me in that I have put together a fun outing that will take us to four very unique falls in the same day. Although considered easy hikes you will want to be in good health and able to walk a minimum of one mile. Please come prepared with appropriate clothing and shoes (extra socks are always smart), water and food and any medications you require.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please meet at the entrance to the Pinkham Notch Visitor Center store at 11:30am. When you pull into the parking lot enter the building to the left up a slight incline. I will be there with my backpack. Photos of me are on the site. There are benches and a mini restaurant inside. This is also where you can buy your parking pass, join AMC and purchase gear you forgot, snacks, water and some pretty cool books. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave for Crystal Cascade at noon sharp. Please keep in mind all times are approximate and if history shows us anything it’s that schedules will change based on what the group present would like to do. as a side note, While you are prepping for your perfect shot please do keep an eye out for your fellow photogs and try to be aware of what they are shooting too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noon - The first of our four falls hike will be Crystal Cascade which is a short hike just .4 miles on the Tuckerman Ravine Trail behind the Pinkham Notch Visitor Center AMC welcome center. This waterfall drops a total of 100 feet in two uneven steps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:30p - From there we will take a short drive south to Glenn Ellis Falls. Considered the jewel of this valley. It has a designated parking lot, a trail leading under Route 16, some (possibly slippery) steep stone stairs, and a great view of a powerful waterfall 64 feet tall. There is a short waterfall just upstream from the main falls, and another just downstream, each being about 10' in height. In addition, immediately above the crest of the main drop is a hidden 10' plunge into a tight cleft in the rock. This is only visible if you do a rock scramble to the brink. Please be smart about rocks – many slippery rocks don’t even look wet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3p - Our third stop will be Jackson falls which is located right on 16A. The stream has acres of rock to spread out over. This is a long slanted, fractured bank of granite that just so happens to have a river running upon it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:30p - Between Jackson Falls and Diana’s bath we will stop at the Red Parka pub which is on our way to our final stop for a late lunch early dinner. Or a pint or two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6p - Our final Falls stop of the day is Diana’s bath. This is one of my favorite places to shoot. A short walk into the National Forest opens up to a series of drops and dips along a granitic streambed. The falls slide over wide and convoluted ledges of colorful Conway Granite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Suggestion:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; All of the places we visit as well as the other hiking locations throughout the national forest range have a $3 parking fee. I strongly suggest buying a day pass at the Pinkham Notch Visitor Center (Our first stop). Personally, I purchased a year family pass for $25. This gives you two all year parking passes. If you and another person “split” the family pass it’s only $12.50 each for the entire year to park at any location! It’s also nice to have two in the situation you want to park cars at either end of a hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Links&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pinkham Notch Visitor Center (Across the street from Wildcat Mountain)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/lodging/lodges/pnvc/index.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/lodging/lodges/pnvc/before-you-go.cfm#dir" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Appalachian Mountain Club: &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;. AMC has huts and places to stay on the cheap. Check out their site if you want to stay up country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Great Glenn Trails: &lt;a href="http://www.greatglentrails.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.greatglent...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crystal Cascades: &lt;a href="http://www.northeastwaterfalls.com/waterfall.php?num=87&amp;amp;p=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northeastw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Glen Ellis Falls: &lt;a href="http://www.northeastwaterfalls.com/waterfall.php?num=144&amp;amp;p=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northeastw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jackson Falls: &lt;a href="http://www.northeastwaterfalls.com/waterfall.php?num=184&amp;amp;p=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northeastw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diana’s Bath: &lt;a href="http://www.northeastwaterfalls.com/waterfall.php?num=288&amp;amp;p=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northeastw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you have time try a stop at Sabbaday Falls: &lt;a href="http://www.northeastwaterfalls.com/waterfall.php?num=418&amp;amp;p=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northeastw...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; * All times are suggestive. Locations may change. If there is a 50% or greater chance of precipitation forecasted for the day of the hike at this link  &lt;a href="http://www.weather.com/weather/weekend/03846?from=36hr_topnav_undeclared" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.weather.co...&lt;/a&gt;  the trip will be canceled with no “rain” date scheduled. Always check the Meetup site for status. The organizer(s) takes no responsibility for your attendance or safety. Your participation is done so on your own accord and you assume all risks.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the entrance to the AMC store. See my photo on the site.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240999027000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237825430000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Four Falls Spring 2009</name><id>10016173</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240673400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/10016173/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/4/global_7806708.jpeg</photo_url></item>