<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>770 Boston Post Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06437</zip><lat>41.288795</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comfort Keepers</name><city>Guilford</city><id>1845621</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.675476</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We all have a book inside of us. A great story idea you've thought about for years or perhaps sharing information on a subject you are an expert in. You do not have to be a literary icon to get a book published. There are many ways to finally write and create your book, which has proven to be a leading tool in promoting your business, credibility and expertise! Come join AWBL on May 18, for a special panel of published authors will share their success secrets with you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;SANDI KAHN-SHELTON&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, is well known to the CT shoreline as a journalist and fiction book author. She has been a newspaper reporter with the New Haven Register for many years, and has recently released her fourth novel, one of which, she is now working on securing movie rights for. Sandi also teaches writing workshops on the CT shoreline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;LISA LELAS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, is a magazine editor and newspaper/national magazine columnist, as well as a professional speaker on the subject of Organizing ones Time, Space &amp;amp; Goals. She has written 2 non fiction books through a main stream NY publisher, published an audio book, and most recently self published a children's picture book on the subject of organizing. Her first book, 'Simple Steps: 10 Weeks To Getting Control of Your Life' landed on many bestseller lists, based on a self-help program she developed, which was featured several times on The Oprah Winfrey Show, Today Show, etc. &lt;em&gt;Lisa is also on the leadership board of AWBL.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DODIE MALARDO,&lt;/strong&gt; is the author of the popular romance novel, "Penelope's Cruise".  Dodie turned her life experience into a novel which she has used as a starting point for her own charity, To Give Is Divine, Ltd. whose mission is to develop and implement creative, innovative fundraising campaigns and donate a significant portion of those proceeds to Americancharities, initially focusing on food banks, homeless shelters andchildren at risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa </member_name><member_id>9510638</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337802252000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Association-of-Women-Business-leaders</urlname><id>1543671</id><group_lat>41.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>AWBL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335472704000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FROM PEN TO PUBLICATION: Secrets to writing and publishing your book!</name><id>62282332</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337344200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Association-of-Women-Business-leaders/events/62282332/</event_url></item>