<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 JFK St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.369562</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>JFK Bridge Park area</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>958963</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122681</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If you are like me, you've been ITCHING to take your bike out, almost to the point where it could be considered a medical condition...  Here's your shot!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be leading a bike ride making a loop to Walden Pond from the Harvard Square area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE ROUTE: We will start near Harvard Square at the park next to the JFK bridge (Harvard Square side).  From there, we will take the Charles River bike path out of Cambridge until Watertown, and I'm still deciding on the best route to Walden pond from there, but it will take us past the Cambridge Reservoir.  At Walden Pond, we will take our shoes off and relax for a bit, hopefully catching some sun!  After we've chilled for a while, we will head northeast toward Lexington until we connect with the Minuteman Bikeway and head back.  Our destination from there will be Davis Square where we can catch a bite to eat to end the day.  PLEASE LET ME KNOW IF YOU HAVE ANY GREAT RECOMMENDATIONS ON THE ROUTE!  I will try to post a map closer to the date, and I will update the text with the final plan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE PACE: Ideally, I'd shoot for a 15 mph pace, but I think we'll going 10-12 mph on the paths since it will be packed, though I plan to hit at least 15, higher if we can handle it, once we get out in the open. In all honesty, I have no idea how long it will take.  I would plan at least 4 hours - we will hang out at Walden Pond based on consensus.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: Feel free to ride whatever kind of bike you want as long as you can keep up.  I'll be riding a fixed gear bike.  Bring any water and food as needed. Flat repair tools are always smart.  A helmet is recommended!  Also, there is a recommended $5 donation that goes to Rob to cover past and future meetup.com fees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to contact me with any concerns or questions!  I hope to see a big group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NASTY WEATHER WILL CANCEL THIS EVENT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joys,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Guy with the bike ;)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246800883000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242330241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>30 miles - Walden Pond Adventure! Cambridge to Concord</name><id>10412912</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243177200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/10412912/</event_url></item>