<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>852 Daniel Webster Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.096977</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Liberty Springs trail head</name><city>Lincoln </city><id>1908081</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.679886</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather looks fantastic Monday (about time), and I thought I would take a small group up Mt Liberty via the Liberty spring trail, with the option to possibly run over to Mt Flume.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike will be 8 miles with about 3k gain if we just hit Liberty, if we head over to Flume that will add 2 more miles and another thousand (is that right? sounds like more than I remember) feet of gain. Book time for just Liberty is about 5 hours, but we will move at the pace of the slowest hiker, so please do not sign up if you have to be back in town for dinner plans or something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail head for Liberty Springs is on RT 3 just past the Flume visitor center in Franconia notch NH (the address is actually the Flume visitor center).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should be reasonably fit to come on this trip, I mean we are talking about going up hill for 4 miles straight, think about that. Being a beginner hike I have no speed requirements, I don't expect you to have any idea how fast you are able to hike, if you have experience please keep in mind the group might not be a fast paces one, depending on who signs up (I like to take in the sights and just enjoy nature sometimes anyway). No prior hiking experience is necessary, but a good sense of humor is key! There is likely to be a lot of mud and a lot of bugs (yay spring!), waterproof boots are always good, but if you don't have them be sure to have another pair of shoes to change into when you get back to the car. You will want a couple liters of water, a map and compass are always good ideas. You will want to bring warm layers, just because it's nice at the trail head doesn't mean it isn't amazingly cold as soon as you get above the trees (which this hike just does at the very end, but you will want to be able to enjoy the view, it's truly outstanding). I'm sure I'm forgetting details, if you have any questions please feel free to ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My cell is 857 998-9005, if it looks like you are going to be a little late, please let me know as soon as possible, because I probably won't have reception at the trail head.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a silver 2 door Honda civic and have curly brown hair (see picture)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pete</member_name><member_id>4010848</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306945479000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306506241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last minute beginner/intermediate Memorial day hike - Mt Liberty</name><id>19948661</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306762200000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/19948661/</event_url></item>