<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come be a part of the beginning of something new. I am designing a cooperative, story driven multi-player online game, and I am offering the members of this group a chance to help shape it. The goal for the event is just to open up discussion on the subjects covered in the game, but there will be plenty of time for writing of all sorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will post ahead of time a primer for everyone detailing the level of technology, the major power blocks, and a few of the major plot points that will be covered in the game. Come with a few ideas of your own to through into the mix and your opinions on what you think the shape of the world should be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone who shows up will receive mention in the credits of the game. Those who wish their content be included in the game can also be listed as a writer in the credits. When we start hiring in the January/February time frame, anyone who participated early will be offered first shot at the writing positions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any writer's works generated during the event belong to the writer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner will be provided at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I live by Alewife station with plenty of parking in the area. WiFi and power outlets will be available for those who need them.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347160583000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SF Writers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-SFandF-Writers</urlname><id>137807</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Science Fiction &amp; Fantasy Writers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345751843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Help create a story driven MMO</name><id>79063872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347123600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-SFandF-Writers/events/79063872/</event_url></item>