<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Depot Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03087</zip><lat>42.842327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Windham Rail Trail - Windham Depot Entrance</name><city>Windham</city><id>575567</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.298195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let's hike or snowshoe the Windham Rail Trail towards Derry. The trail is fairly level so you are welcome to bring your corss country skis just incase there is enough snow. The intent of this outing is to travel at a moderate pace, enjoy the views, and chat with each other along the way.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will adjust the mileage to the ability of the group. The more ambitious walkers are welcome to go as fast and far as they want and then catch up with the rest of us on their way back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After we finish, let's go to the general store at the corner for hot chocolate, a snack, or lunch. They make great homemade soups, chill, sandwiches, salads, and homemade cookies ...&lt;/span&gt; Yummm! They do not take credit cards, so remember to bring cash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please dress in layers, bring your spikes in case it is slippery, and bring plenty of water. As always, everyone that participates does so at their own risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is cross-posted to other meetups, so please RSVP "YES" on one site only, so that we avoid duplications. No need to RSVP "No" if you cannot attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain cancels this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barb/Peanut cell phone: (603)540-7467&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet in the parking lot near the Depot.  I will wear a meetup pin.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb / Peanut</member_name><member_id>7901156</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357864553000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357628286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MID DAY - MID WEEK at the Windham Rail Trail</name><id>98523482</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357835400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/98523482/</event_url></item>