<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1339 Whirlwind Hill</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.436666</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-265-5526</phone><name>Gouveia Vineyards</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>1189908</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.765769</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I've been to Gouveia before and it's a great winery. Their wines were good, but even better is the space that they have outside for lounging, snacking, drinking wine and enjoying the view. Let's go for the tour at 4pm and then we can do the tasting for $8.00. You can bring food but no outside beverages are allowed. I'll bring some cheese and some italian bread I think. Bring something to share if you don't mind. List it in your RSVP details or the comments. Dogs are allowed but you can't bring them inside the tasting building. So you'll have to have a babysitting plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winery website:&lt;a href="http://www.gouveiavineyards.com/"&gt;http://www.gouveiavineyards.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going North on I-91&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Exit 14, Woodhouse Avenue. Turn left onto Woodhouse Avenue. Turn right onto South Airline Road. Turn right onto East Center Street. Turn right onto Whirlwind Hill Road. The winery is approximately half a mile on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going South on I-91&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Exit 14, East Center Street. Turn left onto East Center Street. Turn right onto Whirlwind Hill Road. The winery is approximately half a mile on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or text me if you can't find us 716-307-6590</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jocelyn</member_name><member_id>8761972</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344809153000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Smiling Happy Faces</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford</urlname><id>1498492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Eat, Laugh, and Be Merry in West Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342289061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Afternoon at a Winery - Gouveia in Wallingford Sunday Aug 12</name><id>73336642</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344798000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford/events/73336642/</event_url></item>