<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Look for the building with the mushroom looking dome on top. http://tinyurl.com/yl3gstp</address_2><address_1>21 Ames Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Green Building (Building 54)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1215370</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088074</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I will teach you all about using jQuery to enhance your apps and make them easy to use and more engaging and fun. I will keep it simple, so you will walk away with the tools and skills on how to add jQuery to your site. Forget all the other JavaScript frameworks - jQuery is the only one you need!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your laptops!&lt;/b&gt;  After the talk, we'll do some jQuery exercises together and you'll be writing jQuery by the end of the evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A brief outline of what we'll cover&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; What is jQuery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Demo of some neat stuff that jQuery can do&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Where to get it, and how to add to your website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Syntax&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Progressive Enhancement ( what it is, why it's important )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Ajax&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Plugins &lt;br /&gt; - What they are (with examples)&lt;br /&gt; -  How to use them&lt;br /&gt; -  How they make jQuery more powerful&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Practical uses for jQuery ( how you can use it, and how I use it everyday )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Documentation and Where to find help online&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; jQuery Exercises - We'll write some code together&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm excited about this last part and will make sure we have plenty of time for it. You will see how easy it is when we write some jQuery together. I'll give out a bunch of exercises and we can do them together. I find it's the best way to learn a new language. Some examples of what we'll go over:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Creating professional looking touches in minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Selecting and manipulating DOM elements&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Adding custom functionality to links and buttons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Integrating jQuery UI&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Plugins ( how to find, some examples.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Progressive Enhancement &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; AJAX &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've been curious about jQuery then this is for you. I will teach you all the basics and work with you on real life practical examples so you can use it on your next project. You won't want to miss this event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About me (Andrew Drane)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am Senior Web Developer at BetterLesson, a startup company in Cambridge. We have a web platform where teachers can build and share their curriculum. I work with both front and back end development, and write the majority of jQuery and Javascript.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before that, I was a freelance web development consultant for 4 years, building sites of all types from online wine retail, recipes and finding interesting ingredients, to online biographies.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Don't use the 21 Ames Street address. Check out http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=54 for a map of this building's location on MIT campus</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Murphy</member_name><member_id>4790321</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Drane</member_name><member_id>8266401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272327309000</updated><rating><average>4.61000013351</average><count>18</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>113</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261946266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enhance your apps with jQuery</name><id>12154308</id><headcount>114</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270681200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/12154308/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/1/global_12396689.jpeg</photo_url></item>