<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1033 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351951</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.787.4242 </phone><name>Brown Sugar</name><city>Boston</city><id>906361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121927</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I, Mark Shar, will be presenting "The Inextricable Need for and Value of Purpose: Why Your Success and Happiness and Self-Esteem Require that You &lt;em&gt;Begin&lt;/em&gt; Everything with the &lt;em&gt;End&lt;/em&gt; in Mind"...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is purpose? Why is it important? How is it connected to self-esteem? How can it drive you to success and the achievement of happiness, both for the smallest to the largest aspects of life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;One cannot escape one's nature, which means one cannot escape the fact that as a living entity you require purpose to survive. Human beings get to choose the purpose and meaning of their lives. And the necessity of purpose, or purposeful living, is rooted in our biology, tied to our nature as living entities. It is inescapable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Consider that purpose integrates; purpose gives direction and meaning.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I will be discussing in summary what Ayn Rand and Nathaniel Branden each have to say about the subject. I will be adding my own thoughts along the way, especially as relates to crafting statements of purpose (sometimes called life purposes or mission statements). I will also discuss the connection between Purpose and "The Sanction of the Victim".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at Noon on Sunday, March 25, 2012 at the Brown Sugar Cafe on Commonwealth Ave in Boston for as brief a presentation as I can make -- followed by a lively discussion and great camaraderie. All &lt;em&gt;purposeful&lt;/em&gt; criticisms, questions, witticisms, confusions, exasperations, metaphors, epanalepses, cheers, jeers, hyperboles, etc. are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for our familiar faces... look for the table with the "Meetup Group" sign or ask a waiter/waitress</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Shar</member_name><member_id>9291676</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332700853000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326262062000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Inextricable Need for and Value of Purpose ...</name><id>47618852</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332691200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/47618852/</event_url></item>