<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Sylvia Scarlett&lt;/b&gt; 1935 USA  94 minutes- starring Katharine Hepburn and Cary Grant, directed by  &lt;br /&gt; George Cukor &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An overlooked 1930's Hollywood comedy, somewhat ahead of its time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Since this is a weeknight event, when you RSVP, please indicate if you will be joining us for our post-film discussion . This will be very helpful in making an accurate reservation for the restaurant.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Universally rejected by the public upon its initial release, &lt;b&gt;Sylvia Scarlett's&lt;/b&gt; reputation has undergone a reversal over the years, and it is now recognized as an unusual film of exceptional quality. Certainly, the reasons why the public shunned it are clear. Not only were both stars playing somewhat against type, they were playing characters that sometimes challenged the audience to approve of them. In addition, the movie shifts tones and genres wildly, in a manner that is more acceptable to modern audiences, but would have been off-putting in 1935.  All-Movie Guide  4 Stars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's an odd film that treads into certain uncomfortable gray areas. To start, Hepburn in the title role plays most of the movie in drag, but the rest of the movie is just as nutty. When Sylvia's father, Henry , is caught embezzling, the pair of them flee Paris for London, Henry smuggling a batch of silk. Sylvia cuts off her hair and dresses as a boy to lure away suspicion. On the ship over, they meet Jimmy 'Monk' Monkley (Cary Grant), a con man who fingers Henry so that he can slip through customs. Afterward, the trio team up for a life of crime. Combustible Celluloid&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately what the director George Cukor and Hepburn thought was a masterpiece was totally misunderstood by the public at the time. At its preview it was given a contemptuous reception: booing, screaming and people leaving en masse after about twenty minutes. However, this is now considered to be a classic, mostly because it deals with the subject of cross-dressing, and also because it has a strong heroine. It's certainly not traditional mainstream studio stuff, and this is one of its attractions now, as it was its biggest problem in the 1930s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cukor said afterwards that his only regret was the addition of a conventional beginning and ending to try and accomodate the audience. Certainly, with out that the film would be much better, but even as it is it's worth seeing both for good performances by Hepburn and Grant, and its refusal to adhere to traditional Hollywood expectations. Edinburgh UniversityFilm Society&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film itself should be a lot of fun and I anticipate a good discussion at the restaurant. And by the way, the films at The Boston Public Library are free &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign before and after the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245805956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sylvia Scarlett with Hepburn and Grant</name><id>10721172</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247781600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10721172/</event_url></item>