<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Camping and hiking from Sat., 5/27/06 thru Mon., 5/29/06 at Devil's Tombstone campground in the Catskill Mountains in NY. Devil's Tombstone and is about a half hour from Woodstock, and has some incredible hiking. There are a number of great hikes that could be had in a group as a whole or breaking into smaller groups. The actual hikes are TBD. The leader and expert on this event is Erin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving time is about 2.5 hrs. from the Hartford area to the camp location. For those going together we'll meet at a location TBD in the Hartford area. if you would like to come for just a day, or leave later in the day, Erin will send you directions. But please note, if you are lost, there is no cell reception in this area, so Erin cannot receive calls. The link has a phone number to the campground that can help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Devil’s Tombstone is a very small &amp;amp; quiet campground, and very basic (i.e. no electricity). There’s running water, but only on the water taps, and bathrooms do not have flush toilets. The good news: you are given free access passes to north-south lake (a 10min. drive down the road and where Kaaterskill Falls is) to enter the park &amp;amp; campground. There are fully functional bathrooms with hot showers, electricity, and whatnot….. so if you need to be sparkling clean, no need to worry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pay attention to the Message Board as details will be hashed out there (like trying to leave earlier that 7:30 AM to have more time for daylight hiking and fun!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camping Fee:&lt;br /&gt;$12.00 (Erin has more details on this)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Extra Details:&lt;br /&gt;Lots of warm clothes &amp;amp; blankets/sleeping bags. it gets super cold at night, so be prepared. the days are just regular weather as it is here. Each person must bring enough food for the two nights of camping and three days of hiking/activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of Erin's favorite suggested hikes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kaaterskill Falls&lt;br /&gt;Highlights: highest two tiered waterfall in New York &lt;br /&gt;Near: Haines Falls, NY &lt;br /&gt;Distance: 1 mile round trip &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain: 300 ft &lt;br /&gt;Hike Time: 1 hours &lt;br /&gt;Difficulty: Very Easy &lt;br /&gt;Trail Condition: Well maintained trail &lt;br /&gt;HikeType: Out and Back&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Tremper&lt;br /&gt;Highlights: fire tower, easy trail, mountain views &lt;br /&gt;Near: Woodstock, NY &lt;br /&gt;Distance: 6 miles round trip (slow moving) &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain: 1900 ft &lt;br /&gt;Hike Time: 3.5 hours &lt;br /&gt;Difficulty: Moderate &lt;br /&gt;Trail Condition: Well maintained trail &lt;br /&gt;HikeType: Out and Back &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.dec.state.ny.us/website/do/camping/campgrounds/devilstombstone.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dec.state.ny.us/website/do/camping/campgrounds/devilstombstone.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dec.state....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540179000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1144418191000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping &amp; Hiking in the Catskill Mts. NY Memorial Day Weekend</name><id>4895442</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1148729400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4895442/</event_url></item>