<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 1/2 Mt. Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.369850</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-349-0071</phone><name>Daedalus</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>622819</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So now that I've figured out that this is truly what Sundays are for (besides Football), it's time for another &lt;b&gt;SUNDAY FUNDAY!&lt;/b&gt; We had a great group and good times at the last one, let's do it again. (Maybe not as many jokes this time though, guys, not even one peep)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I pushed this one back a little because the weather is going to be so amazing, that this will definitely be perfect outdoor night beer drinking time. FYI during the day it is supposed to be &lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt; and the&lt;i&gt; low&lt;/i&gt; for the night is &lt;b&gt;58&lt;/b&gt;. Not too shabby (plus for any pansies there are also heaters on the roof.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Okay so this location (&lt;a href="http://www.daedalusharvardsquare.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Daedalus&lt;/a&gt;) may not be as beer-full as Sunset but I figure we need to vary our scene just a bit. And dang man, they got beer, who are we to judge if it's only 12 taps. But seriously, the view and the space is awesome. Plus, next week we'll go to Publick House for all that feel 'options deprived'.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't be fooled by the website, they are not that fancy.  I'm going to try and make reservations Sunday morning for that evening so please try to rsvp before Sun Morn.  Their kitchen is open until 10:30 pm and they have a late night menu until 1am.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So catch some rays during the day and grab some beers with us in the evening, shall be fun!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the Hostess for the Meetup group &amp; I'm sure we'll be loud.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241388187000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240502491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Funday @ Daedalus Rooftop Patio</name><id>10251580</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240783200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/10251580/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/d/global_8300749.jpeg</photo_url></item>