<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Beach St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>My Thai Vegan Cafe</name><city>Boston</city><id>949551</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062557</lon></venue><fee><label>Group Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover expenses</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Need a break from the stress of work, the economy, and everyday life? Looking for something to do that is fun, cheap and progressive?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for &lt;b&gt;Games for Justice at My Thai Vegan Cafe*&lt;/b&gt;! Arrive by yourself or bring a friend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scrabble, Boggle, Apples to Apples, Scattegories - what's your favorite board game? Bring it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look no further if you're seeking like-minded folks to game with, want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while you Boggle, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. If you want to build a strong cross-issue social justice movement, SoJust is for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Haven't been to My Thai? The food is delicious!  Check out the &lt;a href="http://www.bostonveg.org/restaurants/MyThaiCafeMenu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;My Thai menu&lt;/a&gt; filled with yummy vegan options. &lt;i&gt;Menu prices are reasonable, but they've requested an $8 minimum per person, so come hungry!&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*My Thai is located in Chinatown&lt;/b&gt;, 3 Beach Street, 2nd floor, at the corner of Washington St. Sorry, but this venue is not wheelchair accessible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MBTA:&lt;/b&gt; Chinatown stop/Orange Line, Boylston St. stop/Green Line&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us if you want to &lt;i&gt;cross-promote your events and campaigns&lt;/i&gt; while enjoying great cocktails, are &lt;i&gt;new to the area&lt;/i&gt; and looking for groups to get involved in, or you've been looking for &lt;i&gt;like-minded progressives&lt;/i&gt; to hang with in Boston.  &lt;b&gt;Newcomers always welcomed!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hey organizers!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word &lt;b&gt;bring flyers&lt;/b&gt; - there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the website - just click '&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/"&gt;Messages&lt;/a&gt;'.  The &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/calendar"&gt;SoJust Calendar&lt;/a&gt; is packed with social justice-related events held throughout Greater Boston.  Help us keep it filled - tell us about events you hear about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Head up to the 2nd Floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271726709000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269310329000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Games for Justice</name><id>12963606</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271282400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/12963606/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/1/a/global_13867562.jpeg</photo_url></item>