<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our friends at GreenFleece Farm are hosting an open house (Saturday morning) &amp;amp; workshop (Saturday and Sunday) on natural building, straw bale and earthen plaster construction on Sat 8/27 &amp;amp; Sun 8/28 and 
&lt;em&gt;members of the permaculture community are invited to join!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details from GreenFleece:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://t0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTcfa6lfIgzEghro6PaFYgBHWUOv-PTQXvufW_orgCHYOLFDc_b3w" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Saturday AM Open House:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 8:30 on Sat morning Bryan Felice will present an excellentslideshow presentation overview of natural construction techniques.He has some exciting &amp;ldquo;hot off the press&amp;rdquo; research on buildingperformance from DevaRacusin, who has been involved in constructing these systems foralmost 2 decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;We will then give a brief overview of the design process for theaddition at GF Farm as well as the basics of passive solar design. At that time we will describe other workshops &amp;amp; opportunities that we hope to offer for observation or participation this fall: Cob Construction, Radiant Heat floor installation, Solar Hot Water design, Rocket Stove design, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Workshop:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://www.mnn.com/sites/default/files/user-1457/building_bales.sec_.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Sat afternoon will focus on the basics of straw bale insulation. Sunday will focus on earth plaster &amp;ndash; recipes, techniques, tips for cold climates. We will have Bryan Felice on Sat &amp;amp; both Bryan &amp;amp; Deva Racusin providing instruction on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Since it is an enormous amount to cover, Bryan, Deva &amp;amp; crew will beavailable on-site the following week for anyone interested in spending a day or half a day doing hands-on work under supervision. That week will focus on the fine detailing with straw &amp;amp; plaster. This is quite an opportunity to work with some very experienced folks in the field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;To register for workshops you can RSVP here but you must also contact Deb Ganster at GreenFleece (djganster@yahoo.com) to confirm and arrange payment, etc. There is a $45 charge for the weekend workshop participation (Saturday afternoon &amp;amp; Sunday). To attend as &amp;ldquo;open house&amp;rdquo; participant Sat morning &amp;amp; observe the process, registration is not necessary. For directions, contact Deb. To add work supervision the following week, contact Deb also. Questions for Bryan: bryan@undustrial.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deborah Ganster</member_name><member_id>11393481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314974825000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313525375000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Natural Building, Straw Bale &amp; Earth Plaster (2-day Workshop)</name><id>29734441</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314448200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/29734441/</event_url></item>