<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>168 Elm Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03055</zip><lat>42.837467</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chapanga's Griddle &amp; Grill</name><city>Milford</city><id>3531242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.665253</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Slakas are at Chapa&lt;a href="http://www.theslakas.com"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/0/0/event_161158112.jpeg" width="411" height="247" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;ngas in Milford tonight! (NOT their usual Haluwa hangout!)  One of our favorite bands (I even got to sing with Chris at Karaoke several times!) they rock the house for music and dancing, especially at Chapangas!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Slakas are A 5 piece Nashua-based classic/modern rock, high energy cover band that has been playing local venues &amp;amp; events in the southern NH area for about 6 years. With Dave Thorp’s endless energy on the drums, Jason White’s ripping lead guitar riffs, Deb Lussier’s vocals&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/6/0/event_161157952.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;, Rick Letourneau’s bass keeping the low end rhythm and Chris Lussier multi tasking on rhythm guitar, harmonica, vocals &amp;amp; keyboard, the Slakas will get your feet moving and up on the dance floor!  Covering a variety of artists such as Led Zeppelin, Heart, Boston, Journey, Bad Co., Foreigner, Pink, Alice In Chains, Areosmith, Gretchen Wilson even Lady Gaga, The Slakas are sure to please any musical taste!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://Chapangas.com"&gt;Chapangas&lt;/a&gt; has great food and drink too!  Their &lt;a href="http://www.chapangas.com/menu.php"&gt;menu&lt;/a&gt; has a little bit of everything and great appetizers too! (esPECially the chicken tenders in multi flavors! ;-P)  Betty and I dine there a lot or just stop in for drinks, at great pri&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/7/4/event_161159252.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;ces!  I can get a big Shocktop or Blue Moon for the price of a regular Bud elsewhere.  Betty can even get a diabetes-friendly Margarita that tastes great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chapangas is just past the Milford Oval, if coming from Nashua.  Right before Sal's Pizza, the District Courthouse, the Jade Dragon, Family Dollar, Golds Gym, Tractor Supply and AFTER Advance Auto Parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seating CAN be limited there, if they setup in the front.  Hope they take my advice and setup in the big back room! :-)  We saw another band play back there and it was great! The band starts at 9, we're eating at 7:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom D'A c603-521-8392&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom D'A</member_name><member_id>5016514</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348281522000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348254109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Music, dancing and food with Slakas @Chapangas in Milford NH 2nite!</name><id>83476092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348270200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/83476092/</event_url></item>