<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Rockingham Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03087</zip><lat>42.812271</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 898-4422</phone><name>Jonathan's at Park Place Lanes</name><city>Windham</city><id>1163913</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.248814</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is from dj Donny's email:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We are running a Karaoke contest at Jonathon's....   It is part of a national competition that is open only to bowling centers which host karaoke.  Jonathon's is the only center in New Hampshire that is participating, and there are none in Massachusetts or Maine....    This is going to be big.  Up for grabs at our level is a trip to Las Vegas for the finals.  That's right, it's GUARANTEED that one person from Jonathon's will be sent to Las Vegas in June for the National Finals with their air fare and hotel completely paid.  Once in Vegas, the representive will perfom on a huge stage with a full light and sound systems on front of thousands of people!  At the national level, third place will pay $1000, 2nd place will pay $2000 and 1st place will pay $5000!       But wait, there's more....   The winner at the national level will also get to stay for a couple of extra days and be the open act for a National headlining band in Las Vegas!   Last years winner opened for Lea Ann Rimes.......  This is VERY COOL!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The competion started last Tuesday and we will qualify one person at each karaoke (Tuesday and Friday nights) for the local finals which will be held at Jonathon's on Saturday, May 22nd.  So, please, come on down and enter the competition or watch some great singers.  Or, just come on down to sing, drink and have fun, we're still having as much fun as humanly possible and you do NOT have to be a part of the competition to come and sing and have fun........  And if you have friends that are singers, GET THEM DOWN THERE! IT COULD BE THERE BIG BREAK!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;note: Rockingham Rd. is Route 28.&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 93, exit 3, take Rt. 111 eastward. At the intersection with rt. 28, make a right onto rt. 28.  Jonathan's is on the left, not far down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have posted this event with several meetup groups.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the MEETUP sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>NeilL</member_name><member_id>3034835</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269562993000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268813974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Karaoke Contest</name><id>12899321</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269389700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/12899321/</event_url></item>