<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Chapel St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308662</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St. Patrick's Day Parade Route</name><city>New Haven</city><id>883209</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.932617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&amp;quot;Join the City Parks and Town Green   &lt;br /&gt;to turn the St. Paddy's Day Parade green!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;City Parks and Town Green are looking for volunteers   &lt;br /&gt;to march in the parade and recycle along the way.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Volunteers AKA &amp;quot;Green Men and Women&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;will march in the parade with blue recycle bins,   &lt;br /&gt;collecting cans and bottles from the crowd,   &lt;br /&gt;and dumping them into a recycling truck.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The goal is to collect 3,700 lbs of recyclables this year,   &lt;br /&gt;which is 10% of the total garbage yield from last year's parade.   &lt;br /&gt;Last year the team collected 700 lbs and this   &lt;br /&gt;year we're hoping to supplement that with   &lt;br /&gt;two parade floats staffed with our &amp;quot;Green Team&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event promises to be fun! There will be costumes (green of course)   &lt;br /&gt;and good cheer for all volunteers.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;from Dev:  I was thrilled to see the Parade for the first time last year.  Part of the ‘fun’ is that it’s the only day that people can drink publicly in the streets while the parade goes by.  At its best, it’s a community event with some extra ‘spirit.’ At its worse... It kind of turns chapel street into a mound of garbage by the end of it.  And by garbage… I mean mainly cans and bottles that can/should be recycled (but are not).  I gathered what cans I could last year and took them to the one recycling place I could find (two blocks up from where the we (the collective) was watching the parade) – but it was clear something dramatic needed to change to send the message that people should recycle the cans/bottles that they drink from at the Parade even though there aren’t many public places where they could do so.  I think the ‘green parade’ idea is great because we can still enjoy the parade (hell… we’ll be IN it!) and we can immediately make a difference in the amount of recyclable cans/bottles collected (as opposed to being left as garbage).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See the article MetroMix did on the green efforts: &lt;a href="http://connecticut.metromix.com/events/article/st-patricks-day-goes/1014546/content" target="_blank"&gt;http://connecticut.me...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;From the organizer, Win Davis: &amp;quot;Thank you all for your assistance with recycling at the parade!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please meet at City Hall, 10:30am 2nd floor in one of the conference rooms on the right side of the big hall to get dressed and briefed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please wear comfortable &amp;amp; warm shoes as we will be doing some walking. We're making everybody a green team cape made of green fabric, purchasing green face paint and hair spray (face paint and hair spray is optional) and asking everybody to wear green and black clothing to compliment the cape. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be able to provide non-latex rubber gloves for all participants (likely two pairs each) as well as bins to march with, so our major concern is for people to stay warm and wear comfortable shoes.  We will be marching along side one of the City's recycle trucks and collecting recyclables from the crowd.  Our job is to keep the crowd on the sidewalk and collect as many cans, bottles, water bottles and other recyclables as possible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have two floats in the parade, a float in the first Division and a float in the 7th division, so we need volunteers to split up into two groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Sunday, March 15th&lt;br /&gt;Times: &lt;br /&gt;9-10am parking  (Parking for marchers is offered at corner of Orange and Grove Street) there is a shuttle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:30-11:30a Meet at City Hall to get costumed and organized.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:30am - walk back to the corner of Grove and Orange to take the shuttle bus up to the staging area of the parade to meet up with the float in Division 1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12-12:30pm - short break&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1pm - parade begins and we should begin marching.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call or email with further questions but when we're in City Hall, I expect to have a briefing of all volunteers to get everybody ready to go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For any questions, please call my mobile phone anytime (from dev: I'll put Win's number in my RSVP so it's not posted forever)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Win&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;I’ll be the contact for this event on our end – my phone number is in my RSVP. The ‘green parade’ event itself will be sponsored by the City Parks and Town Green organizations.   Thanks!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237302593000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235146766000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Help New Haven GO GREEN while being in the St. Patrick's Day Parade!</name><id>9783735</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237129200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/9783735/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/c/c/global_7385580.jpeg</photo_url></item>