<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Local photographer Teya Rutherford is moving out of state and invites you to “strip” her studio: learn her secrets about lighting, posing, processing and business and walk away with some great door prizes – equipment valued between $100 and $500.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This two-day workshop contains information essential to improving your craft and both saving and making you money in your full or part-time portrait business. Learn grassroots and online marketing secrets and how to make each of your clients look beautiful with hands-on tutorials in lighting, posing and Photoshop liquify.&lt;br /&gt;The $499 workshop fee* includes two full days of programming, personal portrait portfolio critique and goody bag of actions, business forms, policies and marketing materials.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further information and payment link visit &lt;a href="http://teyaphoto.com/workshop/workshop.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://teyaphoto.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*special discounts available&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Teya:&lt;br /&gt;With degrees in education and law (J.D.), Teya Rutherford has transformed herself into one of the top portrait photographers in Massachusetts. She has been recognized with awards from the Professional Photographers of Massachusetts and Wedding and Portrait Photographers International and is the photographer of choice for both families and high school seniors who want to look like models. She relishes the opportunity to use her talent for teaching and her legal, business and photographic knowledge to educate and inform the local photographic community and has done so through past events in conjunction with the Worcester Photography Center, such as the Trash the Dress shoot, the fund-raising lighting workshop and the talk on protecting online images.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Teya Rutherford&lt;br /&gt;Photography by Teya&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://teyaphoto.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://teyaphoto.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(617) 480-6153&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241148207000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236011927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>“Strip My Studio” workshop on April 25th and 26th</name><id>9860160</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240664400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9860160/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/0/global_7522736.jpeg</photo_url></item>