<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>999 Boston Post Rd E</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.351414</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 460-9618</phone><name>Stephen Anthony's Resaurant</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>1518127</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;After a long search I have found a breakfast resaurant that while located on the fringes of Greater Boston, also offers seating for large groups and superb food. Their specialty is their home made sausage, served as a semi-flattened patty and in 3 flavors, ofcorurse they serve all our breakfast favorites in a friendly atmosphere. Check out their menu here: &lt;a href="http://www.stephenanthonys.com/images/breakfast_menu_08-09.pdf"&gt;MENU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The restaurant is easy to get to too! Just get on rt 20 west and it's on the left hand side just after you cross into Marlborough from Sudbury. To get to rt 20 you can take any of the major or minor north/south routes. From rt 95 it takes about 25 min to get there, if you are coming via 495, take exit 24A and head east on rt 20, the restaurant will be 5 miles up on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those looking to ride out there together should meet me at the Hess in Newton at 8AM, KSU at 8:15. We will take Rt 30 West and then head north to rt 20.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After lunch (weather pending) we will go for a ride - details TBA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all members regarless of whether you have paid dues or not, a good opportunity to meetup for the first time and see if you are cut out for touring with Twisted Touring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain date: Sunday 3/20&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300659178000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297688196000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opening Day Breakfast</name><id>16558393</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300539600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/16558393/</event_url></item>