<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please watch the NH Ruby site for more information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wiki.nhruby.org/index.php/Upcoming_meetings" target="_blank"&gt;http://wiki.nhruby.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NH Ruby and Rails User Group will hold its June 2008 meeting at the usual spot, RMC Research in Portsmouth. This month we have the honor of having Brian DeLacey return to give another interesting talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's a Rubyist to do when great environments come along but don't&lt;br /&gt;(yet) support Ruby? Google App Engine, for instance, only supports Python. Well, of course - Learn Python! It's easy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting will give a quickstart intro to Python for the Rubyist. &lt;br /&gt;We'll then take a look at &amp;quot;Hello World&amp;quot; running on Google's App Engine. &lt;br /&gt;You may leave wondering whether Django is Python's jazz improvisation of Rails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To keep things environmentally friendly, we'll do the demos on a newly built, energy efficient PC running Ubuntu and using a just a few watts of power with Intel's new Atom processor. We'll also spend a little time talking about how simple, fun, and inexpensive it was to build this powerful little Atomizer. You may find &amp;quot;atomic power&amp;quot; is a great way to experiment with Ruby and learn Python.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Tuesday, June 17, 2008. 7-9 PM.&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: RMC Research Offices, 1000 Market Street, Portsmouth, NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a map and driving directions, see our wiki site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wiki.nhruby.org/index.php/Upcoming_meetings" target="_blank"&gt;http://wiki.nhruby.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there?</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213916684000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Many great ruby things</why><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhruby</urlname><id>885450</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The NH Ruby and Rails Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211328432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast NH Ruby and Rails June Meeting</name><id>7978906</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213743600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhruby/events/7978906/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/f/global_4005199.jpeg</photo_url></item>