<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/a/event_168002682.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Awesome cast, action adventure rife with political incorrectness....awesome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Showtime is 6:20PM.  I will be at the theater by 5:30 and we should head in for seats around 6:50.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, I arrive at the theater an hour before the show to start gathering people, and we head in for seats about 30 minutes before the show, so we can sit together.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; This also allows us to take turns getting snacks, etc., before the previews start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;There has been a lot of buzz about this movie, so it is probably a good idea to buy your tickets ahead of time.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note, if for some reason this movie sells out, they will probably make us line up in the lobby.  If not, look for us at the tables by the escalator.  If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after.$$$$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; December 25, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; The Weinstein Company &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt;Quentin Tarantino &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt;Quentin Tarantino &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt;Leonardo DiCaprio, Jamie Foxx, Christoph Waltz, Samuel L. Jackson, Gerald McRaney, Dennis Christopher, Laura Cayouette, M.C. Gainey, Don Johnson, Kerry Washington, Anthony LaPaglia, RZA, Tom Wopat, James Remar, James Russo, Todd Allen, Jonah Hill &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Western &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://unchainedmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Unchainedmovie.com&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/unchainedmovie" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/unchainedmovie" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Set in the South two years before the Civil War, "Django Unchained" stars Academy Award®-winner Jamie Foxx as Django, a slave whose brutal history with his former owners lands him face-to-face with German-born bounty hunter Dr. King Schultz (Academy Award®-winner Christoph Waltz). Schultz is on the trail of the murderous Brittle brothers, and only Django can lead him to his bounty. The unorthodox Schultz acquires Django with a promise to free him upon the capture of the Brittles – dead or alive. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Success leads Schultz to free Django, though the two men choose not to go their separate ways. Instead, Schultz seeks out the South’s most wanted criminals with Django by his side. Honing vital hunting skills, Django remains focused on one goal: finding and rescuing Broomhilda (Kerry Washington), the wife he lost to the slave trade long ago. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Django and Schultz’s search ultimately leads them to Calvin Candie (Academy Award®-nominee Leonardo DiCaprio), the proprietor of “Candyland,” an infamous plantation where slaves are groomed by trainer Ace Woody to battle each other for sport. Exploring the compound under false pretenses, Django and Schultz arouse the suspicion of Stephen (Academy Award®-nominee Samuel L. Jackson), Candie's trusted house slave. Their moves are marked, and a treacherous organization closes in on them. If Django and Schultz are to escape with Broomhilda, they must choose between independence and solidarity, between sacrifice and survival...&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356883410000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349966197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Django Unchained (6:20PM Show)</name><id>86522272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356820200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/86522272/</event_url></item>