<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TIME UPDATED:  Turns out they have THREE showings on Sunday.  I picked the latest because someone said earlier does not work.  And I've cross-posted to a cooking meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a foodie as well as a movie geek, I thought this would be an interesting movie to sample.  From their summary:  &amp;quot;This documentary captures the never-before-filmed Meilleurs Ouvriers de France, France's highest honor in the art of patisserie. &amp;quot;   (Netherlands, USA, UK, France, 84 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website for the film:  &lt;a href="http://kingsofpastry.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://kingsofpastry....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;People often ask why we would make a film about a French pastry competition –especially after making films on Dylan (Don’t Look Back) and politics (The War Room). But as soon as we met chef Jacquy Pfeiffer it became clear that the Meilleurs Ouvriers de France competition was not going to be your average Top Chef cook off. These reality TV shows seemed like mere wind sprints compared to the marathon three-day M.O.F. contest which Jacquy was preparing to enter. But winning is not all that this epic contest represents. Becoming a M.O.F. (Best Craftsman in France) is a lifelong dream for French artisans that can only come true by seeking excellence. As Jacquy would say, “The M.O.F is not about doing the ‘best that you can do’ but the ‘best that can be done.” This degree of perfection in the pastry profession, like most Olympic contests, is achieved through passion, sacrifice, and extraordinary skill — and as we found out, for Jacquy and the other fifteen finalists, a lot of luck.&amp;quot;   [MORE ON THE WEBSITE]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289177948000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285000220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Kings of Pastry" @ Real Art Ways</name><id>14832543</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289173500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/14832543/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>