<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>At January 2008's meetup, each of us identified a specific area in our Wheel of Life to set a clear   &amp;quot;Be-Do-Have&amp;quot; intention to manifest in 2008.  We agree that it would be great to actively support each other in manifesting our intentions by checking-in every few months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our March meetup, we plan to have this check-in. So, please &lt;b&gt;bring your &amp;quot;Be-Do-Have&amp;quot; intention&lt;/b&gt; and share how you're doing.**  Let's celebrate our progress together.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In small breakout groups, we will also lovingly support each other with more &amp;quot;inspired&amp;quot; ideas and suggestions to implement the &amp;quot;DO&amp;quot; aspects of our Be-Do-Have intentions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stefan Pagacik, BostonLOA member,&lt;/b&gt; will also share with us the simple yet powerful suggestions from The Strangest Secret that would move our &amp;quot;Be-Do-Have&amp;quot; intentions powerfully, on a daily basis, closer to manifestation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The strategies from the Strangest Secret, inspired by Earl Nightingale himself, became the basis of the very successful Nightingale-Conant corporation.  &amp;quot;Many thousands of people have attributed The Strangest Secret with turning their lives around and helping them make their fortunes in the world.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you commit to using The Strangest Secret strategies with Law Of Attraction principles for 30 days, where do you think you would be in fulfilling your heart's desires?  Join us at our March meetup to find out!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you very much, Stefan, for your gift of time and facilitation at our March meetup!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We dedicate this meetup to everyone who have dreams and look towards fulfilling them in 2008!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Note: For folks who did not participate in the &amp;quot;Be-Do-Have&amp;quot; activities in January and plan to join us in March, go to &amp;quot;Files&amp;quot; ( on left side bar of BostonLOA meetup site ) and open the file &amp;quot;BostonLOA Meetup_BeDoHave0108&amp;quot; document to access a summary and activity worksheet. &lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/files/"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please complete page 3 of worksheet as best as you can and bring it.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; If you have questions, email ChewHoong at bostonloameetup@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;or bring them to the March meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Stefan Pagacik &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;www.SPinnovatenow.com&lt;br /&gt;to contact Stefan: stefan@spinnovatenow.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides being an enthusiastic student and &amp;quot;practice-ioner&amp;quot; of Law Of Attraction, Stefan is also a successful consultant bridging several industries including media and entertainment, software/IT, private equity and technology.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most recently, Stefan has formed Greenpoint, a global venture growth consultancy helping early-stage technology companies and eco-focused projects and/or companies realize market and financial milestones leading to exit via sale, merger or IPO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stefan currently resides in Plymouth, MA.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204848584000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202260003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction March Meeting</name><id>7272178</id><headcount>36</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204675200000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/7272178/</event_url></item>