<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Hunt Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.836670</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amesbury Sports Park</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1486796</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.945374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yallaboard.com/deals/57"&gt;http://www.yallaboard.com/deals/57&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yallaboard.com/deals/57"&gt;Legendary Adventure Expo Party &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Friday | March 18th | 6:00pm-11:00pm | Amesbury Sports Park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have brought together champions of Adventure &amp;amp; Partying from communities like Social Boston Sports &amp;amp; Snowriders, to adventure powerhouses like Eastern Mountian Sports, Amesbury Sports Park, and Northern Outdoors thrown in free adventures from snowtubing, to off-road segway rides to playing with sled dogs, and added great eats, New England's finest drinks, beirut &amp;amp; cornhole games and live musical performances by Speed the Harvest and WXGR 101.5FM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and SnowRiders is bringing their freestyle Ski &amp;amp; Snowboard Rail Jam Competition with a $500 prize...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select an option above to get your:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Tickets for entry to the event $29 ($95 value) including free tubing, interactive adventure expo, and party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Bus tickets for our legendary guests who need a ride from Boston to Amesbury Sports Park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Here's a preview of your ridiculous night for a ridiculously low price of $29, save 70%!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2011 Adventure Expo Party&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sample Unique Adventures (Specific activities may vary at the mercy of Mother Nature)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Snow tubing up to 45mph - by Amesbury Sports Park&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Freestyle Ski &amp;amp; Snowboard Rail Jam Competition with a $500 grand prize - by SnowRiders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Extreme Challenge Course Race&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Intro to New England's best adventures:  &lt;br /&gt;o Ride off-road Segways,  &lt;br /&gt;o Play with husky sled dogs,  &lt;br /&gt;o Take a whitewater raft down the slope,  &lt;br /&gt;o Shoot at the paintball range,  &lt;br /&gt;o Hot Air Ballooning &amp;amp; Paragliding 101,  &lt;br /&gt;o Intro to snowshoeing and cross-country skiing and many more... By our amazing partner adventure companies including&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eastern Mounatin Sports Schools | Northern Outdoors |Muddy Paw Sled Dog Kennel | Parafly Paragliding | High 5 Ballooning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Party&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Beirut, Cornhole, &amp;amp; Games - by Social Boston Sports&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Live Music &amp;amp; Dancing - by Speed the Harvest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Live DJ Broadcast - by WXGR 101.5F&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* BBQ, Booze, Bonfire - by Amesbury Sports Park, Pabst Blue Ribbon, Cabin Fever Whiskey, Kennebec Brewery, Red Bull, and more...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prizes and Giveaways  &lt;br /&gt;Chance to win trips, gear, and swag from New England's top adventure operators &amp;amp; outfitters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Need a place to stay?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For our legendary guests from out of town, we have arranged a discount at a nearby hotel. Check out the Fairfield Inn by Marriott Amesbury and if you book by phone - (978) 388-3400 - say you are visiting the Adventure Expo &amp;amp; Party at Amesbury Sports Park with group code of "Adventure Expo"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks again to our Sponsors:  &lt;br /&gt;Amesbury Sports Park  &lt;br /&gt;PBR  &lt;br /&gt;WXGR  &lt;br /&gt;Speed The Harvest  &lt;br /&gt;Social Boston Sports  &lt;br /&gt;EMS Schools  &lt;br /&gt;Northern Outdoors  &lt;br /&gt;SnowRiders  &lt;br /&gt;Touchstone Research  &lt;br /&gt;Cabin Fever Whiskey&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roni</member_name><member_id>10600890</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300490435000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's gonna be one giant party with so many different things to do. Definitely a great experience for those that like an adventure! 

Plus, who wouldn't want to go snowtubing, ride a segway, learn about how to ride in a hot air balloon, etc?!</why><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>South-Shore-Rock-Climbers</urlname><id>1496386</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>South Shore Rock Climbers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299822717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 2011 Adventure Party hosted by YallAbroad</name><id>16882028</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300485600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Rock-Climbers/events/16882028/</event_url></item>