<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard Street, Brookline, MA 02446</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1765151</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122467</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Alloy Orchestra returns to the Coolidge for their first show since the sold out 2010 screening of The Complete Metropolis. This time they present Alfred Hitchcock's final silent film, Blackmail.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Alice White (Anny Ondra), girlfriend of Scotland Yard detective Frank Webber (John Longden), murders an artist in self-defense but fears being discovered. In the muddle of trying to cover her tracks, she mistakenly leaves her gloves at the crime scene. Frank is assigned to the case and immediately recognizes the gloves as belonging to Alice. He attempts to conceal her involvement, but local petty thief Tracey (Donald Calthrop) saw Alice leave the artist's apartment the night of the murder and begins to blackmail the couple. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Master of suspense Alfred Hitchcock began the production as a silent film. Halfway through filming, however, the producer wanted to cash-in on the success of "talkies", and so had Hitchcock begin shooting two versions - one silent, one sound. The "talkie" version is now more ubiquitous, but the British Film Institute retains a print of the rarely-seen silent version. This silent print has been touring with the Alloy in the U.S., but it will be returned to the BFI shortly after the Coolidge screening. Don't miss this rare opportunity to see this superior, critically acclaimed silent version of Hitchcock's classic tale of murder and blackmail on our giant silver screen, accompanied by Alloy's spectacular original score, performed live. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This screening will be preceded by the newest Alloy composition for German Dada artist Hans Richter's classic short, Filmstudie (1926). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Alloy Orchestra is a three man musical ensemble, writing and performing live accompaniment to classic silent films. Working with an outrageous assemblage of peculiar objects, they thrash and grind soulful music from unlikely sources. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Performing at prestigious film festivals and cultural centers in the US and abroad (The Telluride Film Festival, The Louvre, Lincoln Center, The Academy of Motion Pictures, the National Gallery of Art and others), Alloy has helped revive some of the great masterpieces of the silent era. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An unusual combination of found percussion and state-of-the-art electronics gives the Orchestra the ability to create any sound imaginable. Utilizing their famous "rack of junk" and electronic synthesizers, the group generates beautiful music in a spectacular variety of styles. They can conjure up a French symphony or a simple German bar band of the 20's. The group can make the audience think it is being attacked by tigers, contacted by radio signals from Mars or swept up in the Russian Revolution. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Alloy collaborates with some of the worlds best archives and collectors (such as the George Eastman House, The British Film Institute, Paramount pictures, Film Preservation Associates and The Douris Corporation) to present audiences with the very best available prints of some of history's greatest film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meetup Notes&lt;/strong&gt;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please PLEASE be sure to buy your ticket in advance!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Sounds of Silents always sells out and this will be one you definitely won't want to miss.  I'll be at Panera from about 5.30 until 6.15 and then in line.  After the film I'll wait in the lobby for 10 minutes so that people can gather to go out for a post-movie discussion they wish. It being a school night, I'll likely call it a night after the film though I'll be open to arm-twisting!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See below...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caroline </member_name><member_id>10711981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347971309000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345683914000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blackmail (Sounds of Silents with the Alloy Orchestra)</name><id>78951492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347922800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/78951492/</event_url></item>