<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02081</zip><lat>42.162697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Norfolk County Agricultural High School</name><city>Walpole</city><id>3161151</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.238655</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;PCS PETWALK 2011, SUNDAY SEPTEMBER 18, 2011, 10AM &amp;ndash; 3PM (rain or shine!) NORFOLK COUNTY AGRICULTURAL HIGH SCHOOL... Tie on your walking shoes and join fellow animal lovers for the 13th Annual PCS PetWalk at the Norfolk County Agricultural High School in Walpole. Enjoy a day of fun and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to bring the dog! This annual event is held to raise money for homeless animals cared for by the Purr-fect Cat Shelter. Ask friends, family and coworkers to sponsor you and collect donations to be turned in the day of the walk. Participants turning in sponsor money by 1pm will be eligible for a chance to win a $100 shopping spree at Especially for Pets! Participants meeting certain pledge levels will be eligible for prizes. The PetWalk is an approximate 3-mile wooded walk along the trails of the &amp;ldquo;Aggie&amp;rdquo; campus. A shorter paved route is also available for those who choose not to walk the wooded path or, collect donations and let the PCS Walk Team walk for you. Canine companions are welcome to join the fun and will receive a doggie bandanna and a goody bag from PetWalk Sponsor Especially for Pets (while supplies last). After your walk, head over to the field area for fun, music, refreshments and lots of great booths!... Center field events and activities for Everyone: Animal rescue organizations, animal related businesses and services, Demonstrations, Pet Samples, Raffles, Photo Contest, Live Music by &amp;ldquo;Double Trouble&amp;rdquo; - Ruth Debrot and Fred Lungo Refreshments also available (donations gratefully accepted!)... For the Kids: Face painting, Games, Pet Portrait Contest... For the Dogs: The Purr-fect Pooch Contest and MORE!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316469222000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314137899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Purrrfect Cat Shelter Pet Walk!</name><id>30624691</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316354400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/30624691/</event_url></item>