<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Portsmouth, NH</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.041771</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Portsmouth</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>247492</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.788208</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Holiday Tree Lighting, Seafood Chowda at the River House and a Candlelight Stroll at Strawberry Banke       &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 4, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Christmas Fair in Portsmouth goes on all day, but the tree lighting is at 5pm, we can warm up with chowder at the River House near the event, then walk over to Strawberry Banke for a wonderful trip into the past and a wonderful feeling for the holidays.  If you only want to do the Candlelight Stroll, meet us there at 6:30pm on the dot so we can get a group discount (Last year it was $6 off per ticket.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Strawberry Banke, stroll through life in a simpler time as 350 years of American history, winter traditions, and holiday celebrations unfolds around you in New Hampshire's oldest waterfront neighborhood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Historic houses from four centuries decorated in period regalia&lt;br /&gt;•Hundreds of candles lighting the lanes and landscape&lt;br /&gt;•Gingerbread house contest and display (please contact leadinterpreters@strawberybanke.org This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it for contest information&lt;br /&gt;•Live music and holiday entertainment for all ages&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring the whole family for a wholesome stroll through the sights, sounds, and smells of New England's favorite holiday season. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: Adults $20.00, Children (5-17) $10.00, Families (2 adults and your children ages 17 and under) $50.00. Children 4 and under are FREE. Tickets are non-refundable. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Candlelight Stroll is a signature event of Portsmouth and is noted as &amp;quot;One of the top ten things not to miss in New England&amp;quot; - Boston Globe in Portsmouth, in one of &amp;quot;A Christmas - America's Prettiest Towns&amp;quot; - Forbes Traveler. For complete details of the Vintage Christmas events please visit the Vintage Christmas website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Parking Information:&lt;br /&gt;There is only handicapped parking available at the Museum for Candlelight Stroll. All other visitors should utilize the free Vintage Christmas Trolley and public parking areas. Please click here for a map for the free Vintage Christmas Trolley. Please click here for a map with additional parking information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather Information: Candlelight Stroll will be held regardless of weather conditions. Tickets are nonrefundable and non-transferable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Candlelight Stroll is supported in part by a grant from the New Hamsphire State Council on the Arts and the National Endowment for the Arts, Lincoln Financial Group, Liberty Mutual Insurance Group, and the Sheraton Portsmouth Harborside Hotel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  14 Hancock Street&lt;br /&gt;Portsmouth NH, 03801&lt;br /&gt;Call 603.433.1100 for more information &lt;br /&gt;Site Design by Graphic Details &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a red cape and standing in front of the old church on the Square across from the tree at 4:30pm</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen</member_name><member_id>3330386</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291568800000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>North shore Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Newburyport-Singles-30s-40s-and-50s</urlname><id>1554197</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>Newburyport Singles 30's 40's and 50's</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288209276000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Spirit in Portsmouth: the Tree and the Candlelight Stroll</name><id>15250237</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291498200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Newburyport-Singles-30s-40s-and-50s/events/15250237/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/7/global_19121319.jpeg</photo_url></item>