<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For June we have two books once again. They are: The Emperor of Ocean Park &amp;amp; Freakonomics. You may read whichever one you choose. (Please note, you do not have to read both books)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Emperor of Ocean Park&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A complex, smart mystery filled with intrigue, drama, and more than a little danger awaits in Stephen L. Carter's engaging debut novel, The Emperor of Ocean Park. After the funeral of his powerful father (a federal judge whose nomination to the U.S. Supreme Court became a public scandal), Talcott Garland, an African American law professor at an Ivy League university, is left to unravel the meaning of a cryptic note and carry out &amp;quot;the arrangements&amp;quot; his father left behind. Armed with fortitude and familial devotion--though paranoid of his wife's fidelity--Talcott soon finds himself in an investigation that entangles him with a number of questionable Washington, D.C., denizens, including attorneys and government officials, law professors, the FBI, shady underworld figures, chess masters, and friends and family. All the while Talcott tries not to hurt his attorney wife's chance for a judicial nomination--and their fragile marriage--but the closer he comes to unraveling his father's dark secrets, the more dangerous things become. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Freakonomics&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Which is more dangerous, a gun or a swimming pool? What do schoolteachers and sumo wrestlers have in common? Why do drug dealers still live with their moms? How much do parents really matter? How did the legalization of abortion affect the rate of violent crime? These may not sound like typical questions for an econo-mist to ask. But Steven D. Levitt is not a typical economist. He is a much-heralded scholar who studies the riddles of everyday life from cheating and crime to sports and child-rearing and whose conclusions turn conventional wisdom on its head. Freakonomics is a groundbreaking collaboration between Levitt and Stephen J. Dubner, an award-winning author and journalist. They usually begin with a mountain of data and a simple question. Some of these questions concern life-and-death issues; others have an admittedly freakish quality. Through forceful storytelling and wry insight, Levitt and Dubner show that economics is, at root, the study of incentives how people get what they want, or need, especially when other people want or need the same thing. In this, they explore the hidden side of . . .well, everything. The inner workings of a crack gang. The truth about real-estate agents. The myths of campaign finance. The telltale marks of a cheating schoolteacher. The secrets of the Klu Klux Klan. What unites all these stories is a belief that the modern world, despite a great deal of complexity and downright deceit, is not impenetrable, is not unknowable, and if the right questions are asked is even more intriguing than we think. All it takes is a new way of looking. Freakonomics establishes this unconventional premise: If morality represents how we would like the world to work, then economics represents how it actually does work. It is true that readers of this book will be armed with enough riddles and stories to last a thousand cocktail parties. But it can provide more than that. It will literally redefine the way we view the modern world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservation for Musa</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>8272134</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247948582000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242905400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June's Book Club Meeting </name><id>10461475</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246053600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/10461475/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/b/a/global_8733514.jpeg</photo_url></item>